Huh?!
Ah shit, I fell asleep.
Wait, where am I even?
Have you awoken, Miss Arakawa?
What the hell?!
Who's there?
I am a heavenly voice.
I'm here to guide you.
You used up your energy in the real world
and reincarnated into another.
Another world?
Y'mean I died?!
Yes, from overwork and no sleep.
Karoshi, huh...
And now you have a mission:
to save this world's food supply.
It's time to put all of
your farming wisdom to the test.
Head 40: Arakawa Tensei
That Time Arakawa Hiromu Reincarnated in Another World and, Using Her Knowledge of Farming,
Became Unrivaled and Turned into a Real-Ass Noble
Head 40: Arakawa Tensei
That Time Arakawa Hiromu Reincarnated in Another World and, Using Her Knowledge of Farming,
Became Unrivaled and Turned into a Real-Ass Noble
Head 40: Arakawa Tensei
That Time Arakawa Hiromu Reincarnated in Another World and, Using Her Knowledge of Farming,
Became Unrivaled and Turned into a Real-Ass Noble
Head 40: Arakawa Tensei
That Time Arakawa Hiromu Reincarnated in Another World and, Using Her Knowledge of Farming,
Became Unrivaled and Turned into a Real-Ass Noble
Head 40: Arakawa Tensei
That Time Arakawa Hiromu Reincarnated in Another World and, Using Her Knowledge of Farming,
Became Unrivaled and Turned into a Real-Ass Noble
Head 40: Arakawa Tensei
That Time Arakawa Hiromu Reincarnated in Another World and, Using Her Knowledge of Farming,
Became Unrivaled and Turned into a Real-Ass Noble
Head 40: Arakawa Tensei
That Time Arakawa Hiromu Reincarnated in Another World and, Using Her Knowledge of Farming,
Became Unrivaled and Turned into a Real-Ass Noble
Head 40: Arakawa Tensei
That Time Arakawa Hiromu Reincarnated in Another World and, Using Her Knowledge of Farming,
Became Unrivaled and Turned into a Real-Ass Noble
Head 40: Arakawa Tensei
That Time Arakawa Hiromu Reincarnated in Another World and, Using Her Knowledge of Farming,
Became Unrivaled and Turned into a Real-Ass Noble
Head 40: Arakawa Tensei
That Time Arakawa Hiromu Reincarnated in Another World and, Using Her Knowledge of Farming,
Became Unrivaled and Turned into a Real-Ass Noble
Head 40: Arakawa Tensei
That Time Arakawa Hiromu Reincarnated in Another World and, Using Her Knowledge of Farming,
Became Unrivaled and Turned into a Real-Ass Noble
Welcome, reincarnate Arakawa.
We have high hopes for you.
Th-Thank you!
Our kingdom has long faced cold weathers,
resulting in poor wheat crops,
and thus, high bread prices.
We've heard many complaints from our people,
and there's concerns about potential riots.
Oh, reincarnate,
surely you have the solution to our problem.
Err, maybe?
What ever should we grow?
Easy: potatoes!
Let us grow a large bounty of potatoes
and make it the staple of this kingdom!
They're easy to grow in cold climates,
and since I happen to come from a potato farm...
Err, Arakawa, if I may.
Yes?
These "potatoes" you speak of...
What are they?
Eh?
Oh crap! Have potatoes not reached
this kingdom yet?
In the real world, potatoes came from
the Andes Mountains in South America,
Andes Mountains, South America
and were spread across Europe by Spanish voyagers
in the late 1500s
Andes Mountains, South America
Across Europe
during the Age of Exploration.
Seems like this other world is still in a time
before potatoes came in from abroad.
At least, I think...
Umm... O-Oh! Do you have any writing tools?
This is a potato!
Ring any bells?
Nope, no clue.
Heavenly voice, I'm sorry!
I failed you!
Please relax, Arakawa.
Another dud reincarnate.
Let's have her executed publicly.
No hesitation?!
By the way, you draw quite well.
Y-Yes! I'm a manga... I mean, a painter!
Interesting! May I ask you
to draw my portrait?
Done!
S-So quick! Let me see...
(Portrait illustrated by Arakawa Hiromu)
My word! This is me?!
I look so dashing!
Hey, draw me too!
I shall! Everyone here gets a portrait!
Shit, shit, shit, shit...
I gotta come up with a good crop soon
or they'll execute me!
W-Wait, is that what I think it is?
Then, Arakawa spotted something big—
a potato flower!
Arakawa traced the origin of this flower
and discovered a potato field
yet to be cultivated!
She used her potato farming wisdom
to introduce selective breeding
and successfully established potatoes
throughout the kingdom!
Whew, that was easier than I thought.
Splendid work, Arakawa.
You've completed your mission.
As a reward, I will grant you one wish.
F'real? Ooh, the choices, the choi—
There's trouble!
The potatoes energized the people
into overthrowing the monarchy!
Storming through a wheat field, just like anybody else
Potatoes are crazy powerful!
One big slip, and my life flashes before my eyes
Have you decided on a wish?
But even through my wounds my body still shines!
Oh, uh, take me home!
I want to go back to my old life! Please?
Then this is where we say goodbye.
So on nights so painful I can't help but have a cow
Once you go back,
stay well rested, okay?
I'll shake off the vines entangling me and look forward
Huh? I'm back?
Or... was that all a dream?
Just pushing yourself forward makes every task a breeze
Oh, hello, Ishii!
Hello! Is it okay if I come by
to pick up your manuscript?
Not that I can prove it!
Oh, sure. I was just finishing it—
ORANGES
Wh-What's the matter?!
Sorry, no can do.
My manuscript burned to ashes.
ORANGES
Huh?! How?
I'm gonna get some rest.
I've worked too hard lately.
B-But your manuscript!
The heavenly voice told me
to get good rest.
What heavenly voice?!
Arakawa, answer me!
ARA
KAWA
And so, Arakawa saved the other world
and got a good night's sleep.
Noble Farmer 3rd Season...
Fin!