Noble
FARMER
Tokachi, Hokkaido.
A region with 250,000 hectares of farmland,
spanning 1.08 million hectares overall.
A key figure in this land's farming history
is pioneer Yoda Benzo.
My cultivation
Began only with some pigs
And a cooking pot
Head 25
Pioneering Tokachi
Yay, we're learning about the pioneers!
Growing up in Tokachi, I had a lot of
opportunities to learn about its farming history.
Please enjoy this short clip!
Yoda Benzo and the Banseisha
Narrated by Koyasu Takehito
In 1882, the Banseisha was formed
with the intent of pioneering Hokkaido.
The next year, 1883, they set foot
in what's presently known as Obihiro.
But their settling was fraught with strife.
At the end of May,
their crops faced frost damage.
In November, a large bear came
and ate the Ainu hunters.
One spring, they lost 20 cows
to cold and hunger,
and 4 pigs to a fire.
Another year, they were faced with an uber-large bear
and a flood of unprecented proportions.
It's just one thing after the other!
One of their mothers once spoke...
If you think you can settle there,
you must be bonkers!
But her sons would not give up.
You're still going?!
One summer, they were attacked
by a locust swarm
which devoured everything.
Soon, Obihiro was no more than a wasteland.
Yikes, that's bad!
Next fall, they returned.
And the year after.
Stop it! Benzo's already dead inside!
Despite their many hardships,
the party cleared a forest in Obihiro
Marusei butter
Bansei condensed milk
and produced butter
and condensed milk.
Yoda Benzo and the Banseisha
Produced by: HSK
FIN
Man, sounds like Tokachi
was a rough spot to settle!
We wouldn't have the agriculture
in Tokachi today
were it not for their extraordinary endurance.
We didn't have it nearly as hard,
but Arakawa Farms has done cultivatation
to expand its fields!
Please enjoy this short clip!
Cultivating Arakawa Farms
Narrated by Koyasu Takehito
Another one?!
Cultivating Arakawa Farms
Narrated by Koyasu Takehito
Hey, let's clear out the mountains
to make more fields.
Okay!
"How hard could it be?
We have machines nowadays!"
...So Arakawa thought going in.
They cut trees, pulled out their roots,
picked up rocks
and leftover roots...
TRASH
Picked up more,
and more,
TRASH
and more.
Thinking it was good enough,
she got on a tractor to level the field...
and it got caught on a tree root.
But I picked up so much!
Even after they started growing crops,
they kept seeing tree roots for around 3 years.
Nature is terrifying...
Even in the mechanical era,
cultivating land is a difficult task.
Arakawa had a newfound respect
for her ancestors
who pioneered the land under
severe circumstances.
Cultivating Arakawa Farms
Produced by: HSK
FIN
Oh yeah, didn't my great-grandpa
pioneer here? What was he like?
From what I've been told,
Tanaka Shozo
Politician who worked
hard to resolve the
Ashio Copper Mine
pollution case
he fought the Ashio Copper Mine pollution case
alongside Tanaka Shozo.
When he was up against the police,
he'd pick them up and toss them
into the rice fields, one after the other.
Dang, what a fighter.
Then he skedaddled to Hokkaido
after an arrest warrant.
He's a criminal?!
And this great-grandfather's name
was Yosaku.
Like the lumberjack?!
These days may have lost their wonder
But they're certainly still fruitful
You can't take things for granted
The Earth's still spinning as we speak
Maybe our lives have gotten depressing
But we're growing up with love and care
There's only so many people out there
So keep showing me your love