Noble
FARMER
These are my parents, whom you're familiar with.
When asked how they know one another...
We were childhood friends, y'see.
She lived three houses down from me.
Our family's home has a river flowing through it,
but it goes through Okan's home as well.
As she often says...
A ride down the river in a wash tub
will bring me straight back home!
I can't say a wash tub would work in real life,
but what about in fiction?
New Show
WASH TUB REVOLUTION
Don't tell me you're late, Hanako.
Want a lift?
In the Tub Night and Day
CV: Tamura Mutsumi
Only Daughter, Makes Wash Tubs
CV: Honda Mariko
Oh, put a sock in it, Taro!
I'll never get in your wash tub, I swear!
Can we do a shojo manga around this?
Pass.
Head 36
A Vow Between Farmers
So your parents knew each other as kids!
I love those kinds of love stories!
Thinking about my own parents'
childhood romance does not excite me.
Oh yeah. How do people go about meeting farmers?
As far as I know, usually "farm-marriage hunting."
Like marriage hunting but...?
Say, women who want to marry dairy farmers,
*Personal opinions.
Please be aware that not all dairy farm helpers are necessarily marriage hunters.
you can start by finding a job
as a dairy farm helper.
This'll help you find many different dairy farmers.
From the health of their cows
and the state of their barns,
to their employees' treatment
and the size of their farm,
you can get a decent idea
of the farmer's character on the job.
Then, after a long inside observation,
when you've found the single farmer
of your dreams, shoot your shot!
Ooh! What kind of shot do I take?
Good question...
Figure it out yourself.
You're leaving the most damning part to me?!
Can we do a shojo manga
around this?
Hanako, you're late!
Want a ride?
T-Taro! Give it up.
I'm NOT getting
in your wash tub.
T-Taro! Give it up.
I'm NOT getting
in your wash tub.
Pass.
Wash Tub Revolution! *Meaningless title
Noble
FARMER
Get 100 pulls for free!
Download Noble Farmer today!
Noble
FARMER
Now that we've talked about scoring farmers,
let me tell you about things you see
in farmer weddings!
I bet they're super unique, aren't they?
Farmer Wedding Things!
There's three weddings this month?!
All this gift money will put us in the red!
All the weddings in the off-season!
I'll go ahead. I have to get dressed!
I'll be there once I'm done working!
The farm don't rest on wedding day!
Marrying the eldest son
of a farm family? As if.
You're signing yourself up for hell!
The groom is a fine gentleman
who makes a gazillion yen a year. A literal noble farmer!
He doesn't make his wife do farm work either.
Why didn't you introduce him to us?!
A stir from the guests
in the women's camp!
I need a wife...
I wanna find one here and now!
A stir from the guests
in the men's camp!
I like our asparagus better.
Vegetable farmer
Cattle farmer
This meat could be more aged...
Farmer food critics!
Union President! It's good to see you!
Oh, you sell the machinery, yes?
My tractor's started breaking down.
Who even are these guys...?
So many guests from the agricultural industry!
Here I... go!
Flower farmer
A bouquet toss with a gorgeous bouquet!
Here I... go!
Vegetable farmer
A bouquet toss with a veggie bouquet!
Enjoy!
Dressing as a wedding gift!
I'm supposed to bring this home with me?!
POTATOES
Produce as a souvenir!
Congratulations on your matrimony!
Why are you dressed like that?!
The visitors are big buff agri-muscleheads!!
That concludes Farmer Wedding Things!
These things can't be real things!!
Storming through a wheat field, just like anybody else
One big slip, and my life flashes before my eyes
But even through my wounds my body still shines!
So on nights so painful I can't help but have a cow
I'll shake off the vines entangling me and look forward
Just pushing yourself forward makes every task a breeze
Not that I can prove it!