Noble
FARMER
This is a call I had one day with my elder sister
while she was on the farm.
Approx.
Ezo
Arakawa
So now we have four cats here.
Everyone here's been working hard
to take care of them.
Glad to hear it!
We have to play with them, like,
every single day, y'know.
Arakawa
Such a pain.
I'm not convinced.
Later on, during the fall harvest...
Oh!
Wow, that's a lotta pumpkins.
Hard at work polishing pumpkins!
I never want to look at
or touch a pumpkin ever again...
Aww, they're growing very well!
Keep it up! At least there's some blessing
within all those pumpkins.
Blessing? All they do is climb
on my lap and get in my way...
Haha, cats sure are clingy.
Little gremlins interrupting work!
Don't ever call my kitties gremlins again!
Jeez, moody much?
Head 31
Viva Dogs and Cats
Then I started getting bombarded
with pictures and videos of the cats every day!
Like getting food pictures, but cuter, huh?
Hey, as much as they're a treat for the soul,
they can be a headache sometimes too.
This one's about some different cats.
Arakawa Farms had an office
in a log cabin,
which, outside our knowledge,
the cats had turned into a restroom,
making the cabin into a stink house.
Should we put up a wire fence
to keep the cats out?
Hmm... Oh, I have an idea!
Gardening fences and creepers
I installed gardening fences
and added creepers to bring it all together!
Whoa! Looks great!
This'll keep the cats
and their poop out!
Alright then...
Let's see whether they can fit in or not.
Cut it out!
As you see, living with cats means
taking control of their choice of bathroom.
Right, they'll poop just about anywhere.
Oh! Speaking of poop,
I have a good dog story!
Using poop as a transition?
I hope you'll have fun with my doggy!
Dogs from the city that normally
walk outside on a leash
run like crazy when set free
in a wide open area.
They're having a blast.
I'm so hap—
Cesspit
The end.
That's crazy...
Noble
FARMER
State your name!
Noble Farmer!
You too!
Aw, I was hoping for more
snuggly fun times with dogs and cats!
Well, I don't know about snuggly fun times,
but I do have one of Densuke.
When he was brought on to the farm
for the first time, I had to teach him his territory.
No crossing this line. Got it?
Nope, out.
I did this over and over again
until he understood he couldn't cross.
Since he's smart, he figured it out pretty quickly.
So Densuke here hates cats,
and chases every one he sees vigorously.
*Rearing and entry of pet animals in a sanitation control zone is prohibited
under the Standards of Rearing Hygiene Management of
the Ministry of Agriculture, Forestry and Fisheries of Japan.
The cat seemed to catch on
that Densuke couldn't enter the cow barn,
and the two would stare each other down
from both sides of the line.
Talk about willpower...
Mameta, on the other hand,
didn't care about cats, so he'd waltz into the barn
and get kicked out by the cows,
which convinced him to stay away.
So stupid!
And when Oyajidono
called for my little brother...
Hey, Densuke!
Wait, I mean, Eldest Son!
He'd mix the two up.
Those dogs are dominating the family!
Storming through a wheat field, just like anybody else
One big slip, and my life flashes before my eyes
But even through my wounds my body still shines!
So on nights so painful I can't help but have a cow
I'll shake off the vines entangling me and look forward
Just pushing yourself forward makes every task a breeze
Not that I can prove it!