Noble
FARMER
Here you are!
Pancakes with premium butter!
Woo! Nothing tops off pancakes better
than a square of butter like this.
Butter is certainly a delight,
though growing up on a dairy farm
makes it a rough topic to think back on.
I can see that. Butter shortages and things like that
must be hard for dairy farmers.
When cows get frail from heat waves,
they produce less raw milk,
which means making less butter as a result.
Yo, where's the butter?!
Milk them cows and make us butter!
I tried, but nothing's coming out!
Well squeeze harder!
I can't! It won't change anything!
Get me that manuscript already!
Blank
I'm out of material!
Then milk what you've got!
Blank
I can't! It won't change anything!
And that's how demands for butter
and manuscripts are similar!
Blank
Thank you for milking it all this time.
Head 33
Butter
Wasn't there a surplus of butter
because of COVID?
It played a part, certainly,
but even before COVID, butter has gone
back and forth between shortages and surpluses.
On that note, can excess butter be used
in agriculture? Like, as fertilizer or something.
You can fertilize fields with vegetables,
but not butter, since it has fat and salt in it.
What causes surpluses
of raw milk and butter anyways?
Oh, simple: cows are living animals!
For starters, there's less demand for raw milk
in early spring and during the New Year.
Drinking milk demand (Milk processed)
Raw milk production
Now, as much as we'd love to flick a switch
and shut off production,
cows need to be milked everyday
or they get sick.
Thus, we can't control how much milk we get.
Early spring and the New Year?
They're comfortable times for cows,
allowing for increased milk production,
More milk under cool climate
Less milk under heat
but it just doesn't mesh with
the activity of humans.
Happy New Year
All sorts of factors come into play
in both seasons,
Happy New Year
Less demand during vacation season
More demand due to heat but less milk
Less demand during New Year/spring break
such as the lack of school lunches due to holidays,
and decreased consumption of milk during the New Year.
Oh, so you put the surplus of raw milk
from those seasons to use...
Yes, by making lots of dairy products
like butter.
But once the supply of milk
exceeds the capacity of the factories,
Factory
the rest has nowhere else to go.
And all the butter produced
expires after only about six months.
Warehouses can only hold so much,
so they have to dispose of anything close to expiring.
I'll drink some milk and cheer you on!
Let's move on from the heavy
dairy farming talk
and learn how to make butter at home!
Yippee! Sunshine and flowers!
First, you'll need some non-homogenized milk!
Non-homogenised milk is that which has
not been broken down using a homogenizer.
Since its milk fat globules are big,
they'll stick together easily, making for easier butter.
Fill up an empty plastic bottle
about halfway with this milk then put a lid on it.
Now all that's left is to
give it a good shake!
Wow, really?
How long do I shake it for?
'Bout an hour.
Seriously?!
1 Hour Later
Water
Butter
I shook it for an hour
for this?!
Oh, and if you use heavy cream with over 40% milk fat,
your butter will only take about 10 minutes.
Then why didn't you tell me to use heavy cream?!
Ah, there's also a much quicker way
to make butter from that non-homogenized milk.
I'll take it! Just tell me!
It'll make faster if you shake it in ice water.
You think you know now just
how difficult it is to acquire food?
Go on and give this a try for yourself!
Storming through a wheat field, just like anybody else
One big slip, and my life flashes before my eyes
But even through my wounds my body still shines!
So on nights so painful I can't help but have a cow
I'll shake off the vines entangling me and look forward
Just pushing yourself forward makes every task a breeze
Not that I can prove it!