Cha-cha-cha-cha, cha-cha-cha-cha, Tea Dog
Come along with me (Oh yeah!)
My little ray of sunshine (Let's go!)
Run to me with a great big smile (All the way)
When we're together (Oh yeah!)
I feel so magical (Alright!)
And so much warmer (Doo-doo-doo-doo)
You little scamp, Tea Dog
My perky little Tea Dog
TEA DOGS
I L-O-V-E you, Tea Dog!
Heartwarming
Tales
Have You Hid From
the Rain Lately?
“Have You Hid From the Rain Lately?”
This is Chai
from the curry shop Calcutta.
Today, he’s off in another town
on an errand for his owner.
It’s getting pretty late though.
CALCUTTA
He rushes to hide from the rain.
He really wanted to get home...
Ugh, I’m all soaked...
Do you have a home, little guy?
Yeah, I feel you.
I don’t get it.
Why does it feel so hard to go back?
You understand what I’m saying?
Where are you going?
My home’s after this right.
What about you?
I can’t do this...
It’s too late to go back.
You really should bring an umbrella
when you go out on a rainy day.
Mom?
You’re going to catch a cold!
We’re having your favorite:
stewed hamburg steak.
Wait for me, Mom.
Then, Chai remembered...
CALCUTTA
it’s actually pretty lovely
to have someone waiting for you.
Rainfall may cloud your soul
But rain makes you happier
When the sun returns
Cha-cha-cha, cha-cha-cha
Tea Dogs, cha-cha-cha
Take a rice cake, stick a bean on it
Give it two lil eyes
Give it big leaves, paws, and a butt
Then its leaf tail, and you're all done