Cha-cha-cha-cha, cha-cha-cha-cha, Tea Dog
Come along with me (Oh yeah!)
My little ray of sunshine (Let's go!)
Run to me with a great big smile (All the way)
When we're together (Oh yeah!)
I feel so magical (Alright!)
And so much warmer (Doo-doo-doo-doo)
You little scamp, Tea Dog
My perky little Tea Dog
TEA DOGS
I L-O-V-E you, Tea Dog!
Heartwarming
Tales
As I’m sure you know,
life isn’t all sunshine and rainbows.
Indeed, you too sometimes get
sad or tired, right?
Are There Any Tea Dogs
Where You Live?
“Are There Any Tea Dogs
Where You Live?”
Mana, you need to understand.
Dad can’t help it, he has work.
Mana, get back here!
Mana loves her dad,
but he’s always too busy
to be home.
Even today, on her birthday.
Hey!
Wait!
Come back!
Oh!
Mana, where were you?
Mom, this puppy’s name is Ryoku.
Can we keep him?
In our apartment, hmm...
Her mother was suddenly met
with a wave of nostalgia,
as if she'd seen this before.
I see.
We’ll ask Daddy about it
when he comes home, okay?
Okay!
Hey, Mom!
Mom, Dad’s home!
Big bro!
Dad’s home even earlier than usual.
These tea dogs, soothing
the hearts of tired humans...
are certain to be found
where you live.
There’s not one far from you!
Sudden sadness or sudden tears
There’s someone nearby
Waiting for you to notice
Cha-cha-cha, cha-cha-cha
Tea Dogs, cha-cha-cha
Take a rice cake, stick a bean on it
Give it two lil eyes
Give it big leaves, paws, and a butt
Then its leaf tail, and you're all done