Cha-cha-cha-cha, cha-cha-cha-cha, Tea Dog
Come along with me (Oh yeah!)
My little ray of sunshine (Let's go!)
Run to me with a great big smile (All the way)
When we're together (Oh yeah!)
I feel so magical (Alright!)
And so much warmer (Doo-doo-doo-doo)
You little scamp, Tea Dog
My perky little Tea Dog
TEA DOGS
I L-O-V-E you, Tea Dog!
Heartwarming
Tales
Report Card
SORA CHANO
Hey, big bro!
What’s wrong, Sora?
Spring break starts tomorrow,
but Sora’s mom scolded him,
and now he’s down in the dumps.
Nah-nah!
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Hi, Dad!
Hmm...
That smells like Grandma’s tea.
Just do your best next time.
Alright! Let’s go visit
your grandmother.
Grandma!
Be it nostalgic fragrances
Or nostalgic places
If they’re on your mind
Go after them
Have You Gone Home
to the Country Lately?
“Have You Gone Home
to the Country Lately?”
Cha-cha-cha, cha-cha-cha
Tea Dogs, cha-cha-cha
Take a rice cake, stick a bean on it
Give it two lil eyes
Give it big leaves, paws, and a butt
Then its leaf tail, and you're all done