Cha-cha-cha-cha, cha-cha-cha-cha, Tea Dog
Come along with me (Oh yeah!)
My little ray of sunshine (Let's go!)
Run to me with a great big smile (All the way)
When we're together (Oh yeah!)
I feel so magical (Alright!)
And so much warmer (Doo-doo-doo-doo)
You little scamp, Tea Dog
My perky little Tea Dog
TEA DOGS
I L-O-V-E you, Tea Dog!
Heartwarming
Tales
Are There Any Tea Dogs
Right by Your Side?
“Are There Any Tea Dogs
Right by Your Side?”
!@# MOVERS
All of a sudden,
it’s time to say goodbye.
!@# MOVERS
Dad finally came to a resolve:
he’s going to go home to the country
to help on his parents’ tea field.
I’m going to miss this place.
Me too.
Are you sure about this?
Yeah. My father’s getting pretty old,
and I really want to spend more time
with the kids.
While they’re happy to be spending
more time with their dad,
Mana and Sora don’t want to leave
this town either.
Neither does Ryoku.
Ryoku, do you want to stay here too?
Of course not!
You like being with me, don’t you?
Mana, Sora, it’s time to go!
Ryoku...
Ryoku!
You can’t normally see them,
but Tea Dogs are everywhere.
Whenever you’re tired or sad,
Ryoku is a carefree, peaceful green tea dog
take a look around you.
Then... just watch.
Cool and naïve, Long is an oolong tea dog
Perseverant Earl is a righteous black tea dog
Pampered Chai is a shy black tea dog
Cha-cha-cha-cha, cha-cha-cha-cha, Tea Dogs
Run with me (Oh yeah!)
Further and further (Let's go!)
Let's play and have fun together (Forever and ever)
Even if I feel down (Oh yeah!)
So long as I have you (Alright!)
I'll be smiling before I even know it (Doo-doo-doo-doo)
Wow! This room is so big!
My friend, Tea Dog
Thank you, Tea Dog
I L-O-V-E you, Tea Dog!
When you feel tired
And empty inside
Or lonely
And on the verge of tears
There’s one right next to you
I’m sure of it
Cha-cha-cha, cha-cha-cha
Tea Dogs, cha-cha-cha
Take a rice cake, stick a bean on it
Give it two lil eyes
Give it big leaves, paws, and a butt
Then its leaf tail, and you're all done