Cha-cha-cha-cha, cha-cha-cha-cha, Tea Dog
Come along with me (Oh yeah!)
My little ray of sunshine (Let's go!)
Run to me with a great big smile (All the way)
When we're together (Oh yeah!)
I feel so magical (Alright!)
And so much warmer (Doo-doo-doo-doo)
You little scamp, Tea Dog
My perky little Tea Dog
TEA DOGS
I L-O-V-E you, Tea Dog!
Heartwarming
Tales
Have You Felt
Emotional Lately?
“Have You Felt Emotional Lately?”
LONG-LONG EATS RAMEN & FRIED RICE
It may seem like every day
is the same day on loop,
but it changes slowly and gradually.
Long is watching this baby
as always.
It may seem like every day
is the same day on loop,
LONG-LONG EATS RAMEN & FRIED RICE
but that’s not the case at all.
It changes very slowly
and very gradually.
I wonder when babies
stop needing all this attention.
But I guess their neediness
is what makes them so cute.
You said it.
I hope this one stands up soon.
LONG-LONG EATS RAMEN & FRIED RICE
OPEN
CLOSED
Man. Nothing ever changes.
Yes, Long?
Oh my!
Honey!
Look! Our little one
is standing up!
Perhaps what this couple
nearly forgot
was to appreciate these
small, emotional moments in life.
Yesterday, today
Tomorrow and thereafter
Even if they feel the same
There’s always something in store
Cha-cha-cha, cha-cha-cha
Tea Dogs, cha-cha-cha
Take a rice cake, stick a bean on it
Give it two lil eyes
Give it big leaves, paws, and a butt
Then its leaf tail, and you're all done