Cha-cha-cha-cha, cha-cha-cha-cha, Tea Dog
Come along with me (Oh yeah!)
My little ray of sunshine (Let's go!)
Run to me with a great big smile (All the way)
When we're together (Oh yeah!)
I feel so magical (Alright!)
And so much warmer (Doo-doo-doo-doo)
You little scamp, Tea Dog
My perky little Tea Dog
TEA DOGS
I L-O-V-E you, Tea Dog!
Heartwarming
Tales
Have You Looked Up
at the Sky Lately?
“Have You Looked Up
at the Sky Lately?”
Mom is feeling worn out.
Some days are like that, right?
These days happen
for no real reason.
Ryoku is worried about Mom.
Oh?
Ryoku has an idea!
Alright!
Right! Don’t just sigh.
Take a deep breath and refresh yourself!
Don’t you agree, Ryoku?
Don’t get so worn out
Just look up at the sky
And take a deep breath
There we go
Doesn’t that feel much better?
Cha-cha-cha, cha-cha-cha
Tea Dogs, cha-cha-cha
Take a rice cake, stick a bean on it
Give it two lil eyes
Give it big leaves, paws, and a butt
Then its leaf tail, and you're all done