Cha-cha-cha-cha, cha-cha-cha-cha, Tea Dog
Come along with me (Oh yeah!)
My little ray of sunshine (Let's go!)
Run to me with a great big smile (All the way)
When we're together (Oh yeah!)
I feel so magical (Alright!)
And so much warmer (Doo-doo-doo-doo)
You little scamp, Tea Dog
My perky little Tea Dog
TEA DOGS
I L-O-V-E you, Tea Dog!
Heartwarming
Tales
Have You Written
Any Letters Lately?
“Have You Written
Any Letters Lately?”
COFFEE
Some people write letters on end
but never send them.
Like this man, the owner of
café Casablanca.
Instead of mailing his letters,
he leaves them next to his coffee can.
It’s not that he doesn’t want to.
These letters just take courage to send.
In his time of need, someone
brings along a gentle fragrance.
One day, as the owner was
preparing to open the café...
Dad?
Welcome home.
The many letters left unsent
Carry heavy feelings left untold
But the words that matter most
Are “I miss you”
Cha-cha-cha, cha-cha-cha
Tea Dogs, cha-cha-cha
Take a rice cake, stick a bean on it
Give it two lil eyes
Give it big leaves, paws, and a butt
Then its leaf tail, and you're all done