Cha-cha-cha-cha, cha-cha-cha-cha, Tea Dog
Come along with me (Oh yeah!)
My little ray of sunshine (Let's go!)
Run to me with a great big smile (All the way)
When we're together (Oh yeah!)
I feel so magical (Alright!)
And so much warmer (Doo-doo-doo-doo)
You little scamp, Tea Dog
My perky little Tea Dog
TEA DOGS
I L-O-V-E you, Tea Dog!
Heartwarming
Tales
Have You Made Any
Wonderful Memories
Lately?
“Have You Made Any
Wonderful Memories Lately?”
Mana’s best friend Ken
and Hana are moving away.
It’s time to go!
Mana, I’ll come to play, okay?
Wait for me!
We promised we’d be
together forever...
She loved Ken, and now he’s gone.
Mana’s so sad, she doesn’t know
what to do.
Let’s dig this up some day, okay?
Okay!
Oh right!
Some things never get old,
like things that warm your heart
every time you take them out.
No matter how far apart you get
Or how much time passes
You’ll always be together
In your memories
Cha-cha-cha, cha-cha-cha
Tea Dogs, cha-cha-cha
Take a rice cake, stick a bean on it
Give it two lil eyes
Give it big leaves, paws, and a butt
Then its leaf tail, and you're all done