Coming up on Punirunes...
The show is squishing!
Punirunes.
They're squishsterious creatures
you might find just nearby.
They all love to be squished.
When the Squishsterious Antenna glows,
a new puni-pal might come to hang out!
Meeting Up with Unirune♪
"Meeting Up with Unirune♪"
Everyone is having fun together
as always.
Strange. Tomorune's not with them today.
Where could Tomorune have gone?
Tomorune has gone
to the Squishsterious Forest in Puniland.
Tomorune has resolved to see Unirune
after wanting to talk to it for a long time.
Could Unirune be through here?
Tomorune is looking its hardest
for Unirune.
Meanwhile...
Airune and friends are doing
their own search for Tomorune.
Tomorune searches to no prevail,
but it won't give up.
Tomorune still hasn't come back yet?
Oh, Airune...
Airune is very worried
over Tomorune.
Tomorune has looked all over,
but Unirune is nowhere to be seen.
Tomorune has gotten lost
because of the strange power
protecting the forest.
Tomorune has melted
from loneliness!
Unirune is a legendary Punirune
with squishsterious powers.
But its powers cannot turn
Tomorune back to normal.
A melted Punirune needs
the squish of a human.
"I'm sorry," Tomorune says to Unirune.
"For what I said that day..."
"I shouldn't have said
we were puni-pals no more."
"I wanted to apologize
this whole time."
"I'm so sorry..."
"No, I am!"
"I promise I'll save you!"
I wonder what happened
to Tomorune.
Come to think of it, I haven't seen
Yuniko in a while either.
Isn't that the Puni-Pal Link glow?
Huh?
Wait, what?! Airune?
Oh, my. Unirune used its powers
to summon Airune and its friends.
Unirune asks them to help it out.
O-Oh my!
They're all wrapping around Tomorune
and squishing it together!
Tomorune turned back to normal
thanks to all of its friends' squishes.
It looks like Unirune used up
too much of its powers.
I'm glad your friendship was patched up,
Tomorune and Unirune!
Punirunes Album
Punirunes Album.
This is an expedition attraction
in Squishy Park.
The Punirunes Exploration Squad heads off
to adventure, treasure maps in hand!
No matter what the treasure is,
they must set out to uncover it.
Even if a boulder
chases them down,
or they go down a river,
or they nearly fall from a cliff,
they will make it to the very end.
You've got this,
Punirunes Exploration Squad!
After many troubles,
they finally reach the goal!
And then...
Whoo! Pow, pow!
Their treasure was a fireworks
show just for them!
Their hard work paid off.
And this exploration made the Punirunes'
bonds grow even deeper.
Punirunes Album
What memories do you think
they'll make next time?
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Airune and its friends
are all gone.
I wonder if they got to meet Unirune.
Who is Unirune anyways?
Next Time
I know it's puni-pals with Tomorune.
Huh?! Something real bad is happening
to Unirune and the forest?
Oh no! They're all gonna go from puni-squishy
to kachi-frozen!
Next Time
Tomorune and Unirune♪
Next time: "Tomorune and Unirune♪"
"Puni" in next time!