Coming up on Punirunes...
The show is squishing!
Punirunes.
They're squishsterious creatures
you might find just nearby.
They all love to be squished.
When the Squishsterious Antenna glows,
a new puni-pal might come to hang out!
Once Upon a Punirunes♪
"Once Upon a Punirunes♪"
Day in and day out, Airune the bully,
Ururune the troublemaker,
and Coolrune the slob
have Tomorune at their behest.
There is a party in Puniland today.
But they won't let Tomorune come with.
With a strange sound comes...
Loverune the fairy
has appeared!
"Take this pumpkin carriage
to the party."
"But the magic will wear off at midnight."
Prince Enerune has arrived
at the party.
"May I have this dance,"
"you in the headband?"
Oh no! It's almost midnight!
The magic is going to vanish!
Loverune the goddess
has appeared!
"Did you drop...
"this golden headband,
"this silver headband,
"or this star headband?"
"Please answer honestly."
Tomorune wants to tell the truth,
but cannot remember which one it dropped.
"Or perhaps did you drop
this puni burger?"
"You are a liar.
And liars get nothing."
Princess Loverune
has fallen for Prince Enerune.
But her feelings are not requited.
"Who stole the prince's affection?"
"Mirror, mirror, on the wall,
who is the fairest of them all?"
Tomorune got lost
walking home.
Loverune the witch
has appeared.
"Would you like a scrumptious
appuni pie?"
This appuni pie is enchanted
to make you fall asleep.
Tomorune seems wary about it.
Then how about a puni burger?
The puni burger is enchanted
to make you sleep too!
T-Tomorune, you're under a sleeping spell!
"You ate the puni burger,
so you have to fall asleep!"
"Phew..."
Tomorune has fallen asleep
thanks to the spell.
Around that time,
Prince Enerune entered the forest.
"This star headband...
it's the one that Punirune was wearing!"
It's a perfect fit!
Tomorune fell asleep for real!
Loverune the goddess
has appeared.
Err, goddess Loverune,
why are you using fairy Loverune's magic?
"Did you drop this..."
I don't think Coolrune
can handle any more than this.
It's in shambles now.
Ururune the troublemaker
springs into action.
But this troublemaker's
about  to break into tears.
Its friends try to cheer it on...
but troublemaker Ururune
could not hold back.
Tomorune has awoken!
"May I have another dance?"
"You may!"
Wow! That was great!
So emotional!
You looked so handsome, Enerune!
And you shone like a star, Ururune!
You all did amazing!
So everything we just saw
was a puni-play the Punirunes put on
for their human friends.
It was very thought-provoking.
The Punirunes couldn't get enough.
Their curtain call went on for five more rounds.
Punirunes Album
Punirunes Album!
The Punirunes found some paint
in a warehouse.
There's so many different colors.
Everyone looks so excited!
Ururune comes up with a stellar idea.
The idea? To get a blank white canvas
and draw their hearts out together!
Paying no mind to the mess,
they paint a little there,
and roll a little here.
They're putting their soul into art.
What could they be drawing?
Oh my! It's a giant Airune!
The artist behind this masterpiece,
Punee Runz,
will be spoken of for generations to come.
Just kidding.
The Punirunes are very proud
of the piece they've put together.
Punirunes Album
What memories do you think
they'll make next?
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
"Come on down to the
Punirunes Festival!"
"Our performers include...
Loverune!"
Next Time
"Puni-Pal 5 feat. Tomorune!"
"Surprise: Puniland's big superstar
will be performing too!"
Next Time
Next time: "The Festival with Utarune♪"
The Festival with Utarune♪
"Puni" in next time!