Coming up on Punirunes...
The show is squishing!
Punirunes.
They're squishsterious creatures
you might find just nearby.
They all love to be squished.
When the Squishsterious Antenna glows,
a new puni-pal might come to hang out!
I Love ❤
Squish Contact♪
"I Love ❤ Squish Contact♪"
Peek.
Peek!
So squishy...
Double the squish!
Darn it!
I'll give you lots of squishies
when I'm done with my homework!
Airune looks lonely.
The pair decide to go out and play
Puniland
so they don't distract Yuka.
This is Puniland's
Squishsterious Pond.
Squishsterious Pond
Airune found a beautiful Squishflower.
Aw, what a pretty flower!
It's so squishy!
You can squish-skate on this pond.
Tomorune performs
a puni-ple axel!
Well done.
Airune still seems lonely.
It must really want to play with Yuka.
All done! Go, me!
Here come the squishies!
Wait... They're not even here?!
Man...
I really wanted to squish them.
Huh?
Wait... what? Huh?!
I'm gonna fall!!
What the?
This pond is plumpy like gelatin!
What is this place?
Huh?
Is that Yuniko?
Am I seeing things?
Airune, Tomorune!
Weird. Did you two get bigger?
Huh? What do you mean "no"?
Are you saying...
I shrunk?!
"Welcome to Puniland"?
What?
Whaaat?!
Yuka has somehow found herself
in the land of the Punirunes!
This is nuts!
A hug for you, Airune!
And a hug for you, Tomorune!
And a hug...
for both of you at the same time!
Squish contact!
Gosh, you're so squishy!
I only ever get to squish you with my finger,
but now that you're so big...
I can do this...
...and this!
And this too!
This is so much fun!
Maybe I'll fall asleep here tonight
instead of my bed!
I'm just kidding.
I gotta get my fill of Puniland while it lasts!
Wow! Even the twigs and leaves
here are squishy!
Huh? What is it?
Aww!
So many Babyrunes!
They're so tiny!
But even bigger than usual!
So precious...
Oh? Coming!
Here I...
go!
Squish'n Jump?
Sounds fun!
How do you play?
I see! You have to jump to the top!
Here I come... Yeah!
Awesome!
I made it—
Wait, what?!
That was wild!
There's even more fun things to do?
Let's go!
Squishy Market
So this is Squishy Market!
Oh?
Isn't that your favorite Puni Burger?
You want me to have it?
Thank you!
I'll give it a taste!
Oh my!
That squishy, chewy feel...
The squishy puni patty
sandwiched between two squishy buns...
It's like a squishy puni paradise in my mouth!
Nay, a punidise!
Huh? You want me to try
appuni pie too?
Thank you!
Now to see how your favorite tastes!
So squishy and sweet!
The taste of the squishy pie
and the squishier appuni...
They're the puni-perfect match!
I feel like my cheeks are gonna
squish right off!
Huh?
Huh? I'm growing?
Wait, what? What's happening?
Airune and Tomorune try to keep her
from growing by pushing her down.
I'm gigantic!
Now I can't play with you two here anymore...
What is it?
Aww!
What a pretty flower!
It's so cute and squishy!
They got Yuka to smile again
with the Squishflower. How lovely!
I love you two so, so, so much!
Squish contact time!
Squish contact makes everyone happy!
Huh?
Wait, what?
I'm back?
Was that...
a dream?
I want to make squish contact
with you guys at full size again.
The Puni Channel!
And squish.
Puniland: Part 2
Today, I'll be introducing
Puniland: Part 2.
This is the Squishsterious Pond.
It's like a plumpy gelatin.
Looks like a lot of fun
to squish-skate on!
And this is a popular park
in Puniland.
Naturally, the slide is squishy as well.
Here I... go!
To our squishy final stop!
I'm gigantic!
Time for the question!
What does Airune give Yuka
to make her smile?
Here's the answer...
Here's the answer!
That's right: a flower.
A Squishflower,
with squishy petals and leaves!
What a pretty flower!
And it brought a smile to Yuka's face.
That's all for today!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Loverune, do you know
what an "anniversary" is?
It's a day you memorize
so you don't forget a special memory!
Next Time
Celebrating anniversaries
sounds beautiful!
What's gotten into you, Loverune?
You're getting really hyper,
and I don't know why!
Next Time
Celebrating
an Anniversary♪
Next time: "Celebrating an Anniversary♪"
"Puni" in next time!