Coming up on Punirunes...
The show is squishing!
Punirunes.
They're squishsterious creatures
you might find just nearby.
They all love to be squished.
When the Squishsterious Antenna glows,
a new puni-pal might come to hang out!
A Tropical Trip on the South Seas♪
"A Tropical Trip on the South Seas♪"
Oh? What could this place be?
What bliss...
Yuka's family is by the seas,
where it's summer all year long!
This is just amazing...
And you can thank your mom
for winning this trip
from the winter sale raffle
at the mall!
A vacation worth take-ation-ing!
Let this southern island
soothe your sol!
Let's go-cean!
Whoo! Even your puns
are themed for the summer!
Squishing you two while
gazing out at the sea...
is like the peak of squishing!
I should get started on lunch.
Oh?
Good idea! I'm starting to get hungry!
I'll go make something yummy!
I'll help!
We're making southern cuisine!
Hm?
Oh? Looks like Airune and Tomorune
brought things to play at the beach.
Nice! Split the watermelon!
...Or split the pumpkin?
It's too tough to break...
Yeah! Can't go to a southern island
without going for a swim!
I don't think that's how you use a swim ring!
Look at you go!
Wow! Fantastic!
But...
you're still using that wrong.
Hey, Yuka!
Hi, Aoi! Hi, Enerune!
Is Komugi being good?
Yeah! See for yourself.
Hi, Komugi!
So it's still daytime out there?
Yeah! I'll show you.
The ocean is so beautiful!
See?
It really is!
There must be so many rare fish out there!
Look out for the cirrhilabrus finifenmaa!
It's colorful like a flower!
The evansi anthias is also cute!
Maybe you might run into a school
of powder blue tangs!
Aoi sure knows her stuff...
There's also the yellowback fusilier,
and the dracula-shrimp goby...
Oh, right.
Try to keep watch for sharks.
Sharks, you say?
That kinda scares me a bit...
I wouldn't worry about it too much.
The region you're in
doesn't get sharks often.
Oh?
I think Komugi's hungry!
Talk to you later!
Thanks, Aoi!
I'll bring back a souvenir, okay?
Have fun!
Yuka, lunch is ready!
Oh! Coming!
Southern island cuisine, eh?
I wonder what to expect!
I can't wait!
Wait, bread?!
Sorry! We ended up just making bread.
We didn't even mean to,
we just started kneading dough by instinct!
Wow, it all looks delicious!
Thanks for lunch!
So good!
Bread is even more delicious
eating it on a southern island!
Thanks, Mom and Dad!
Nothing calms Yuka better than
some good pastries.
Thank you for this meal!
You two enjoy yourselves
while I go clean up, okay?
Oh no!
Airune and Tomorune have drifted out
into the middle of the ocean!
Oh? Tomorune seems pretty
relaxed about this.
"We'll reach somewhere eventually."
I see! The earth is a round,
squishy planet, after all.
Hey, show some concern...
What was that?
Oh no!!
C-Could it be?!
This is bad!
Um, now you're riding it?
It does look kind of fun...
Oh no!!
Going for a squishy swim in
squishsterious bubbles
looks very fun.
Huh?
Airune! Tomorune!
Did you get hungry from playing?
I made you an appuni pie
and puni burger!
Eat up!
Guys, look!
Wow! It's a dolphin!
I gotta show Aoi!
Well, well!
So it wasn't a shark,
but a dolphin all along!
Bye, dolphin!
Airune and Tomorune made a lovely puni-pal
out here on the south seas.
On that note...
where did those squishsterious bubbles
come from?
Punirunes Album
Punirunes Album!
One sunny day,
the Punirunes walk through the forest,
smiles on their faces.
Oh? Is Tomorune the only one
who doesn't know where they're going?
"Where are we going?" it asks.
They arrive at their destination.
Tomorune's eyes gape open
in surprise!
Where did its friends take it?
It's Squishy Park,
beloved by all!
Tomorune looks very happy.
Its friends wanted to make it happy,
and kept their destination a secret.
The surprise paid off!
What will they do here
in Squishy Park?
The Punirunes' fun never ends.
Punirunes Album
What memories do you think
they'll make next?
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
I love sushi! It's so yummy!
We were gonna go get sushi,
but now we can't...
Next Time
Oh? What is it, Tomorune?
You want to call some puni-pals?
Wow! They look just like sushi!
Next Time
So they're called Sushirune!
Next time: "Comin' Right Up! Sushirune♪"
Comin' Right Up! Sushirune♪
"Puni" in next time!