Coming up on Punirunes...
The show is squishing!
Punirunes.
They're squishsterious creatures
you might find just nearby.
They all love to be squished.
When the Squishsterious Antenna glows,
a new puni-pal might come to hang out!
Squish!
Let's Puni-Pal Link♪
"Squish! Let's Puni-Pal Link♪"
Wow! Amazing!
What's wrong, Tomorune?
Oh? The Squishsterious Antenna
is glowing in response
to Tomorune's desire to see someone!
This means Tomorune's calling
someone with Puni-Pal Link.
Puni-Pal 5
This is a dance group from Puniland:
Puni-Pal 5!
Puni-Pal 5?!
Tomorune wanted to dance with them.
Oh wow!
Those are some great moves!
Awesome!
You're gonna go dance outside?
Sounds fun!
Have fun!
Huh? Where's Airune?
What's wrong?
Huh?
You got into a fight with Enerune?
You disagreed on whether you should eat gummies
from the top or the bottom?
Uh... What's the difference?
I mean, there, there.
Don't be so grumpy.
Yuka's squishing calmed it down.
Want to go apologize to Enerune?
Bye, Airune!
I'm sure you two will
patch things up smoothly.
It's okay.
Enerune, want to go apologize?
Goodbye, Enerune!
Enerune?
Airune went to Aoi's house
to see you.
Enerune just left to see you.
Huh?! Enerune went back to Aoi's place.
Hey, just wait for it to come... back.
Look up!
No, look down! Look up!
Come on, you two!
Notice each other!
You okay, Enerune?
Are you hungry?
Here, some gummies.
I see. You want to eat them with Airune.
Hold on, just wait here!
Airune's power is completely drained.
It wants to see Enerune.
Airune's desire is so strong
it squ-ivers.
It doesn't want to give up!
Run, Airune!
Enerune, run for it!
At last...
their emotional reuni—
Why'd you pass each other again?!
You never came across Enerune, huh?
Airune makes a strong wish.
"I want to be taken straight to Enerune!"
And then...
Oh, Enerune...
What?!
Oh gosh!
Enerune's house got an antenna of its own!
Oh my!
The antenna starts to glow in response
to Airune's desire to see Enerune!
Airune?!
They're finally together!
Huh?!
Airune's in Enerune's house?
Yeah!
I'm not sure how.
It just showed up out of nowhere!
Oh, it's back!
Enerune vanished too!
And now it's here!
Puni-Pal Link lets them jump
from house to house—how squishsterious!
I'm glad you got to patch things up!
Must be nice to be with your puni-pals!
Hmm?
Tomorune suddenly wants to see
even more of its puni-pals.
Tomorune's made lots and lots of puni-pals
from traveling all over the world.
I think it might have called too many, though.
What a day!
Enerune used Puni-Pal Link
to sleep over.
Airune, Tomorune, time for bed!
They sleep together very peacefully.
Sweet dreams.
The Puni Channel!
And squish.
Today, I'll be introducing
Puni-Pal Link.
Puni-Pal Link
Puni-Pal Link has two features.
Number one:
It calls your puni-pals
when you want to see them.
Number two:
It lets you jump from house to house.
Time for the question.
Tomorune called these Punirunes
with Puni-Pal Link.
What is their name?
Here's the answer...
Here's the answer!
Puni-Pal 5
Puni-Pal 5!
This dancing group
from Puniland is...
Whoo! A real fun bunch!
That's all for today!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Squishing you with my finger feels so good.
I wish you were bigger, then I could hug you
and get some real squish contact!
Next Time
Wait, what? You two seem bigger than usual...
Wait, did I get smaller?
Where am I?
Oh my gosh, it's Puniland!
Next Time
I Love ❤
Squish Contact♪
Next time: "I Love ❤ Squish Contact♪"
"Puni" in next time!