Coming up on Punirunes...
The show is squishing!
Punirunes.
They're squishsterious creatures
you might find just nearby.
They all love to be squished.
When the Squishsterious Antenna glows,
a new puni-pal might come to hang out!
Cuprune the Pastry Chef
Eats Too Much♪
"Cuprune the Pastry Chef Eats Too Much♪"
I tried making a new squishy
desert pastry! Is it good?
Thank you!
I can't help but feel like
something's missing.
Cuprune
This is Cuprune.
It's a famous pastry chef
in Puniland.
Tomorune asks if Cuprune can lend
some of its dessert-making expertise.
Wow! It looks all fancy now!
Alright, let's make some more!
Wow, amazing!
Time for a taste!
Time for a Tasmanian devil!
It's delicious!
And super pretty!
This is going straight on our menu!
Yay!
Very well Dundee!
I think we made a little too much, though.
Cuprune loves to eat
yummy foods.
"There's a subtle taste underneath
the sweetness.
"Vanilla beans, maybe?"
Wow! You can even taste out
secret ingredients?
What's this, Cuprune?
What about this?
Oh! "This has a good taste too!"
"Honey might make it
taste more mellow!"
"For this one, the dough
could use more squishiness."
Amazing!
A master pastry chef indeed.
But it ate a little too much.
Huh? Did you get bigger?
What? You can't fit in your cup?
Cuprune's cup is very important to it.
It takes it out to play,
and on walks,
and even sleeps with it.
Don't worry!
Dad sometimes eats too much
and grows out of his pants too!
A little exercise should get you
back into your cup!
Oh?
Tomorune has an idea.
Let's squish-cercise!
Jump rope!
And...
Look at you go!
One, two! One, two!
You should fit in your cup now.
Hey, guys!
What's that? Aoi bought a souvenir?
What could it be?
Whoa! The seasonal Humongous Gummy!
Alright, everyone dig in!
You're already eating?!
"I see! This gummy is 100% fruit juice.
"No wonder it's so juicy."
You know your stuff, Cuprune!
Maybe you shouldn't
eat so much, though...
All that squish-cercise,
out the window.
Huh?
What's this?
They all went into Airune's house.
What are they doing?
Oh my! Loverune's hearts
spiked the temperature,
making the room into a hot sauna!
Looking good!
You'll fit in your cup in no time.
Oh my! Coolrune prepared
some punieam soda!
No better way to cool down
after a sauna!
Wait, stop!
Saw that one coming...
Alright, then...
Cuprune! Everyone!
On your feet!
Go! One, two. One, two.
One, two. One, two.
Keep it up.
Go! One, two. One, two.
One, two. One, two.
C-Could it be?
Let's squish-cercise:
super-ultra special hard version!
That's it.
You can go further!
Pick up the pace!
One, two. One, two. One, two.
Go! Come on, now!
Come on, now! Come on, now!
One, two. One, two. One, two.
Faster! You can go faster!
You can go even faster!
Keep going!
Is that all you've got?!
Stop!
Good work, everyone!
Especially you, Cuprune!
Following up a squish-cercise
with a squish-massage.
Now Cuprune should fit.
It's a success!
Great!
As a reward for your
squish-cercising...
I squ-ooked up some cuppunicakes!
Huh? It's filled with my kindness?
Thank you!
Oh! Since you worked up a sweat,
wanna take a bath?
What's wrong?
Don't tell me...
Now Cuprune can't get out of its cup.
Punirunes Album
Punirunes Album!
Splash!
The cold water feels so good.
Energetic little Enerune
goes down the water slide
and hides itself underwater.
What's Enerune going to do
when it comes back up?
Its friends peer into the water
with anticipation!
Enerune, you have their attention!
Come on out, now!
Enerune makes a magnificent jump!
And it strikes a pose too!
Brilliant!
Everyone loved it!
Thanks to Enerune's spirit,
their day at the pool
got even more fun.
Punirunes Album
What memories do you think
they'll make next?
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
It's Valentine's Day yet again!
I'll tell you about it,
Tomorune!
You see, Valentine's Day...
Next Time
is a really fun holiday
that comes once a year!
You look raring to go, Tomorune!
Next Time
for Everyone♪
Valentine's Day Gifts ❤
Next time:
"Valentine's Day Gifts ❤ for Everyone♪"
"Puni" in next time!