Coming up on Punirunes...
The show is squishing!
Punirunes.
They're squishsterious creatures
you might find just nearby.
They all love to be squished.
When the Squishsterious Antenna glows,
a new puni-pal might come to hang out!
Airune and Tomorune's Fight♪
"Airune and Tomorune's Fight♪"
What's going on, you two?
I see.
Airune forgot you were planning
to go to Puniland together.
"I'm sorry!" Airune pleads.
"You made a promise!"
scolds Tomorune, unforgiving.
Come on, Tomorune.
You forgive it, right?
Calm down, guys!
"Consider us puni-pals no more!"
Tomorune, wait!
I've never seen Tomorune
so mad before.
What now, Airune?
Airune, you're the one
who broke your promise.
I gotta go to school.
You two patch things up, okay?
See you later!
Tomorune.
So you had a fight with Airune.
Will you make up with it?
You should...
or you'll feel lonely.
Airune's looking for Tomorune.
This is Unirune.
This legendary Punirune
is seldom encountered,
has squishsterious powers
and can fly freely in the sky.
"What brings you here?"
Airune says in surprise.
"Will you make up with Tomorune?"
begs Unirune.
But Airune cannot find it in itself.
"Is this what you want?"
asks Unirune.
That's the star headband
Airune and Tomorune won
in the Squish'n Jump!
Airune followed the squishsterious
light into the park.
They both feel awkward.
It looks like the crow has its eyes
on the star headband.
There it is!
Airune and Tomorune are jumping in sync!
They're jumpuning!
"I'm sorry, Tomorune."
"I shouldn't have broken my promise...
"or said we weren't puni-pals."
"You're a really good puni-pal!"
Airune and Tomorune reconcile at last.
"Aren't you here to see Tomorune?"
asks Airune.
"We can make up!"
Punirunes Album
Punirunes Album!
This is Ururune's art studio.
It looks like it's drawing portraits.
Everyone's striking cool poses.
I can't wait to see them
all finished.
They're finished! Wait...
What? You're cutting up
your finished pieces?
Looks like Ururune has a puni-plan up its sleeve.
Just what could it be?
Oh? Something seems different here.
Airune's become Coolrune,
Enerune's become Ururune...?
Oh, I get it now!
They're becoming one another
by swapping masks!
Time for some impressions!
The Punirunes are having a lot of fun.
Punirunes Album
What memories do you think
they'll make next?
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Hold on. Airune's become a bully?
Ururune's a troublemaker?
Coolrune's a slob?!
Next Time
Enerune's a prince?
And Loverune's a fairy?!
What the heck is going on?!
Next Time
Next time: "Once Upon a Punirunes♪"
Once Upon a Punirunes♪
"Puni" in next time!