Last Time
Strange. Tomorune's not with them today.
Tomorune has resolved to see Unirune
after wanting to talk to it for a long time.
Last Time
Unirune is a legendary Punirune
with squishsterious powers.
But its powers cannot turn
Tomorune back to normal.
Last Time
Isn't that the Puni-Pal Link glow?
Oh, my. Unirune used its powers
to summon Airune and its friends.
Last Time
I'm glad your friendship was patched up,
Tomorune and Unirune!
Tomorune and Unirune♪
"Tomorune and Unirune♪"
"Thank you,"
says Tomorune to Unirune for saving it.
Tomorune begins telling the story
of how it and Unirune met.
Before it knew Airune and its friends,
Tomorune was a wayfarer Punirune
traveling around Puniland.
In the many places it visited,
it met many Punirunes,
and made many puni-pals.
When one day...
it got lost in the Squishsterious Forest.
That's when it met Unirune,
a legendary Punirune.
Unirune used its squishsterious powers
to heal Tomorune's bruise.
It appears Unirune hates gummies.
Tomorune and Unirune
had lots of fun together.
Through these memories
they became puni-pals.
"Let's travel outside Puniland someday, together!"
"We're doing it!" said Tomorune with a smile.
"So why didn't it come with you?"
"Why hasn't it come to see you
this whole time?"
"I'll tell them," says Unirune.
"I have a reason."
The forest is kachi-kachi freezing over!
What's going on?
"Everyone, get out of here
while the freezing is stopped!"
"You have to come with us!"
"I can't! I have to protect the forest!"
Indeed. Unirune is protecting this forest
from being frozen over.
Unirune used nearly all of its powers earlier
to save Tomorune.
They're about to be frozen in ice!
What are they to do?
Tomorune says...
"We'll share our energy...
our squishiness with you!"
"I never stopped thinking about it."
"I couldn't go with you back then...
"because I had to stay and keep the forest
from being frozen over,
"and I didn't want you
to have to stay here."
"That's why I couldn't give you a reason."
"But I got worried about you,
so I would come out from time to time,
"and helped you with the Link."
"But really...
"I wish I could have gone with you!"
"I promise I'll save all of you!"
Even Unirune's final spurt of power
could not stop the freeze from spreading.
"I guess it's time to say goodbye."
"Tomorune, please take care...
"of all your amazing puni-pals."
"Farewell."
You're back!
Oh! Tomorune's here too!
What a relief.
Uh, did I miss something?
Tomorune wants to go save Unirune
right away!
The antenna's gone!
N-Now you can't use the Link!
Does this mean they can't
see Unirune anymore?
Punirunes Album
Punirunes Album!
Their amazing day ends with a dazzling parade.
As they go around Squishy Park,
they look back on the dazzling memories they made.
Oh, time really flies when you're having fun.
They get some souvenirs on their way out.
Time to bring the memories home!
But it looks like Airune and Tomorune
couldn't wait that long.
Oh, my. They're all tuckered out
and went fast asleep.
The Punirunes look so happy,
with bouncy legs and smiles on their faces.
I bet they're having lots of fun
even in their dreams.
From now on, they'll make plenty more
happy... nay, happuni memories
to fill up their album.
Punirunes Album
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Oh no! Unirune got frozen in ice!
And the antenna vanished...
What do we do now?
Next Time
Huh? Airune, Tomorune,
do you have an idea?
Next Time
Puni-Pals Forever♪
Next time: "Puni-Pals Forever♪"
"Puni" in next time!