Last Time
The forest is kachi-kachi freezing over!
What's going on?
"I have to protect the forest!"
Last Time
Indeed. Unirune is protecting this forest
from being frozen over.
Last Time
"I promise I'll save all of you!"
N-Now you can't use the Link!
Puni-Pals Forever♪
"Puni-Pals Forever♪"
The Punirunes return to the Squishsterious Forest
to save Unirune.
But it appears they're blocked off
from going further in.
Does this mean they'll never
see Unirune again?
Airune tries to cheer everyone up.
Wait, what? Watch out!
That's right. Unirune gave them
these star headbands.
What is it?
Huh? You think these headbands
might have some of Unirune's power?
Which means...
if you send out your desire to see it,
Unirune will receive it?
That's it!
It's up to you now!
And I know for sure it'll reach Unirune!
After all, sending and receiving
is what it means to link with someone!
"Let's send our feelings
Unirune's way!"
You've got this!
Let's join in!
Yeah!
Puni-pu...
Wait, not like that!
Look!
Their headbands...
they're glowing!
The antenna!
It came back!
Hooray!
Unirune received your feelings!
Good luck!
Go save Unirune!
I believe in you!
The Punirunes are back
in the Squishsterious Forest.
What in the world?
The glow of the antenna
is spreading across Puniland!
Everyone's feelings...
are what make a Link!
Tomorune shouts out...
"Unirune! I'm here for you!"
"And I have lots of things
to talk about with you!"
"Unirune, you're the best
puni-pal ever!"
And so, the Squishsterious Forest
returned to normal,
and everyone worked together
to keep it that way.
How'd they come out?
Yummy!
Nice to meet you, Unirune!
Nice to meet you...
but it feels like we've met before, no?
Yeah, strange.
Huh, you all want to be squished too?
Alright, here I go!
All at once! Puni-puni-puni-puni...
puni-puni-puni-puni-puni...
This is beyond normal squishing!
It's super-squishing!
Here you go, Airune!
Everyone gets one!
You too, Unirune!
And so, everyone's puni-squishy days
squished onwards.
"See you!"
The end!
The End
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!