Coming up on Punirunes...
The show is squishing!
Punirunes.
They're squishsterious creatures
you might find just nearby.
They all love to be squished.
When the Squishsterious Antenna glows,
a new puni-pal might come to hang out!
Tomorune's First
Merry Squishmas♪
"Tomorune's First Merry Squishmas♪"
We're throwing a Christmas party today!
We decorate the Christmas tree,
and make a cake and a feast!
Sounds like it'll be fun.
"I hope I get a present from Santa Claus!"
says Airune.
Oh, Tomorune doesn't know who
Santa Claus is.
Santa Claus...
They're all teaching Tomorune
about Santa Claus.
"But he won't come if you're
naughty... Heh." it says.
But you're nice, so you don't
have to worry about that.
Alright!
We're done making cakes for the shop!
So we'll help you out!
Thanks, Mom and Dad!
They're all having a lot of fun
preparing for the party.
Almost done!
We're all gonna eat together!
You all really want some cake, huh?
Tomorune's overjoyed!
What is it, Tomorune?
Huh? You want to eat cake
with your puni-pals?
Hey, it's Pikarune!
And Nyarurune!
Oh dear! There's so many!
Come on and eat with us!
Hikarune!
Even Angelrune!
Bakerune?!
It called so many friends...
They're all doing squish contact!
Though it's more like a cuddle puddle if you ask me.
Wh-What now?
We don't have nearly enough cake...
Fear not!
Huh?
Whatever you need...
we'll make it!
Alright, let's make some cake!
Yeah!
Togerune hears all the noise
coming from downstairs.
Keep it up, up and away!
We might actually have enough
for everyone!
That's good.
Oh, no!
Calm down, everyone!
What now?
Little bit too excited there.
Through everyone's hard work,
the Babyrunes have finally calmed down.
But unfortunately...
We'll just have to remake it.
Thanks to Airune cheering it up,
Tomorune's eager again!
Airune, are you okay?
You've been hard at work
all day long, huh?
I guess it got worn out.
Even Tomorune's squish contact
isn't energizing Airune.
Airune is taking a nap in its house.
Are you alright, Airune?
Tomorune is thinking about how
it's its own fault Airune fainted.
"I'm naughty..."
Tomorune...
You did nothing wrong, Tomorune.
You just wanted to share the cake.
So don't call yourself naughty.
You're nice.
Very nice.
And I think Airune would agree.
So hang in there.
Tomorune's back in action!
Alright! Let's get back to cake-making!
Let's go, everyone!
Yeah!
Keep your nose to the cobblestone!
We've got work to dooby-do!
What the heck? I don't get it!
All done!
You did great, Tomorune!
Greater than a cheese grater!
Now all that's left is for Airune to get better.
Airune?!
You're already better?
It was so excited for cake,
it hadn't eaten all day.
D'oh!
S-So you were just starving.
Tomorune got an idea!
What'cha doing, Tomorune?
You made the Christmas cake
even better!
Not quite, Dad!
This here's the result of Tomorune's
and our hard work: a Squishmas cake!
I like the sound of that!
A Squishmas cake, eh?
Now that the cake is done,
the party can begin!
One, two...
Merry Squishmas!
...And cut!
Tomorune...
It may not have been Santa Claus's doing,
but Tomorune still got a wonderful present.
The Puni Channel!
And squish.
Today, I'll be introducing Punirunes.
Punirunes
They're squishsterious creatures
who began living in our world one day.
They're very curious about
what humans do.
They often mimic our behavior,
but in their own strange ways.
They're very different
from one another.
There's even some rare Punirunes
seldom seen by others.
Time for the question.
What are Punirunes known to love?
Here's the answer...
Here's the answer!
The answer is...being squished!
Punirunes are still full of squishstery.
That's all for today!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Blue skies, blue seas...
I can't believe we get to stay somewhere
so beautiful! It's amazing!
Airune, Tomorune, are you ready
to play in the water?
Next Time
Looks like you're good to go!
I hope we get to see some cute fish!
Oh, but watch out for sharks.
Next Time
A Tropical Trip on the South Seas♪
Next time: "A Tropical Trip on the South Seas♪"
"Puni" in next time!