Coming up on Punirunes...
The show is squishing!
Punirunes.
They're squishsterious creatures
you might find just nearby.
They all love to be squished.
When the Squishsterious Antenna glows,
a new puni-pal might come to hang out!
Enerune Melts♪
"Enerune Melts♪"
You enjoying it, Enerune?
Glad to hear it.
Oh boy!
Awesome!
To the aquarium!
Enerune's very excited
to go to the aquarium with Aoi.
See you later!
What a surprise!
Aoi left Enerune behind.
Airune and Tomorune are about to
go hang out with Enerune.
They went to Enerune's house
using Puni-Pal Link.
Strange. Enerune's nowhere to be seen.
Oh no!
Enerune melted outside its house!
Punirunes melt when they're lonely.
They have to squish it
to turn it back.
Airune and Tomorune's squishes
aren't changing it back.
Aoi's not home, so Yuka
must squish Enerune!
Thank goodness...
How come you melted, Enerune?
Mm-hmm.
So you didn't get to go to the
aquarium with Aoi? That stinks.
Just explaining its situation
made it feel sad again.
Don't worry. She'll be back soon!
Remembering Aoi made it sad again.
Seriously, relax.
Aoi will be home...
Seriously?!
The name "Aoi" made it sad again.
Okay!
Let's move on from this!
I know!
Some good food will cheer you right up!
I'll make you some puning à la mode!
Wait here, okay?
It was reminded of the
puning à la mode Aoi made it.
Airune and Tomorune desperately
try to cheer Enerune up.
Tomorune has a good idea!
Enerune has to become a sea animal!
That should make Aoi like Enerune again.
Operation: Bring Back Aoi's Squish...
begin!
First, they're doing
mental training.
Wow! Enerune became a fish!
So adorable!
Now I only have eyes for Enerune!
The mental training worked great.
What's this?
Why does Airune have origami?
Oh! Could this be?
It's a dolphin!
Enerune is embodying
a dolphin!
Now for the final touch:
swimming for real.
So relaxing...
Wait, no!
Enerune has become a perfect dolphin!
Now that Enerune has become
a sea animal,
Aoi should come back.
Enerune!
But she didn't.
Oh no!
They better call Yuka
and get her to squish it!
Enerune! Aoi's here!
Sorry! Yuka called me and... what?!
You melted again?!
Oh dear!
I'm sorry, Enerune!
I went to the aquarium
to buy you something!
I wanted to give you it
as a surprise.
Oh?
What's this one, you ask?
This is the oriental butterflyfish!
Isn't it cute? It's your color too!
I love it too!
These gummies are limited,
so I rushed to go get one
before they sold out.
I just wanted to make you happy.
I love you, Enerune.
I'm sorry for making you
feel lonely.
It turned back!
Thank goodness.
Next time, we'll go
to the aquarium together.
Glad things worked out,
Enerune!
Enerune is very, very happy.
Punirunes Album
Punirunes Album.
This is a food stall
created by Loverune.
The Punirunes are stuffing
their mouths with popunicorn.
Oh? Something's wrong
with the popunicorn machine!
What's going on?
P-P-P-Popunicorn!
Spreading all over!
They're bursting into the air
like a water fountain!
Oh my!
It sent Loverune and Babyrune
flying up with it!
They're enjoying the world up above.
Look at that! It's a whole sea of popunicorn!
Now that must feel magical!
Loverune's chaotic creation
turned into a lovely surprise!
They had a very fun snack time.
Punirunes Album
What memories do you think
they'll make next?
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Hmm... I tried making
a new dessert,
but it feels like it's
missing something.
Oh my! So this one is called Cuprune!
Next Time
Whoa! It made my dessert
super fancy like nothing!
Yeah! Let's eat! Wait... what?
Huh? What?!
Are you sure you can fit that much...?
Next Time
Next time: "Cuprune the Pastry Chef
Eats Too Much♪"
Cuprune the Pastry Chef
Eats Too Much♪
"Puni" in next time!