Coming up on Punirunes...
The show is squishing!
Punirunes.
They're squishsterious creatures
you might find just nearby.
They all love to be squished.
When the Squishsterious Antenna glows,
a new puni-pal might come to hang out!
Punirunes Go Camping♪
"Punirunes Go Camping♪"
The Punirunes are heading out.
Where could they be off to?
The backyard?
Is that a tent?
Oh, hey Yuniko!
Glad to have you!
Glad to be here.
What are you all doing?
You see...
Something super fun!
Camping?
Yup, that's right!
Airune saw a camping video
and wanted to try it itself!
On a camping trip,
you get to eat yummy food outdoors!
I love sleeping in a tent too!
Not to mention, gazing up at the night sky
and wishing on a shooting star!
Hee, so dreamy!
Wishing on a star?
They say if you shout your wish
three times before the star disappears,
it'll come true!
I'd wish to see a Sloane's viperfish
preying in the deep sea for myself!
What kinda wish is that?
Wow, you look like
a real camper!
You must be having a lot of fun.
We should throw our own sleepover!
Oh, good idea!
Yeah!
A sleepover?
Let's chat for hours!
You're gonna fall asleep first.
Nah, I'm gonna be having
too much fun to sleep.
You sure about that?
What do you take me for?
Fun!
The Punirunes are probably having
a lot of fun chatting it up right now!
Togerune's about to play a prank.
"Then, I heard squishy footsteps,
"and when I turned back..."
Togerune hates scary stories.
Everypuni shows fear
in their own way.
They think something is
outside the tent.
"Let's take a look outside!"
"If we stick together, we'll be okay!"
Tomorune says to encourage its friends.
Airune gains courage
through squish contact!
All squished up and off they go.
The rustling they heard
was simply the wind blowing the leaves.
There's nothing to be afraid of any...
"Run, I'll handle this!"
Looking like a real hero, Airune!
Oh, it's just Komugi.
His eyes were glowing in the dark.
Huh?
Where's Yuniko?
She said she was going
to go stargaze.
Stargaze?
It's a shooting star! Their wishes might come true
if they say them three times!
Another one!
They have to say their wishes
before it disappears!
"I wish for a ton of appuni pie!"
"I wish for love to spread
around the world!"
"I wish to make many new puni-pals!"
Seems like they all...
have many wishes.
But they didn't get them
out in time.
Oh? What's this squishsterious shooting star?
Did someone bring this
big shooting star their way?
Punirunes Album
Punirunes Album!
So cold!
Oh! It's snowing!
Little by little it builds up,
and suddenly it's a winter wonderland.
What are the Punirunes
going to do together?
Wait, what?
They're clearing the snow?
Not just the tidy Coolrune,
but all of them are doing it?
That's squishsterious.
Oh?
Looks like they're finished
with something.
They made a snow hut!
It's very warm inside.
They've gotten themselves cozy,
but, oh my, they've gotten it very messy.
They're still learning how to keep things tidy.
But don't worry,
they cleaned up after this.
Punirunes Album
What memories do you think
they'll make next time?
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
What's wrong, Airune?
Huh? Tomorune went missing?
Next Time
You think it went to see Unirune?
What is Tomorune up to?
Next Time
Next time: "Meeting Up with Unirune♪"
Meeting Up with Unirune♪
"Puni" in next time!