Coming up on Punirunes...
The show is squishing!
Punirunes.
They're squishsterious creatures
you might find just nearby.
They all love to be squished.
When the Squishsterious Antenna glows,
a new puni-pal might come to hang out!
Tomorune's Many Puni-Pals♪
"Tomorune's Many Puni-Pals♪"
What's this?
What could Tomorune be
looking for?
Oh, it's Airune!
I see. They're playing hide-and-seek!
Too bad. You got caught, Airune.
This is Togerune. It loves playing pranks.
Togerune
You never know when it'll pop out.
Oh no! A crow has its eye on them!
Oh? Tomorune was right next to them,
but it vanished.
Where did it go?
My. Tomorune is trying to make puni-pals
with the same crow that went after it!
Can it actually get through?
It assumed the crow
wanted it to ride on its back!
Tomorune ahoy!
Oh no, Tomorune!
It's flying!
Tomorune is flying!
Tomorune's convinced
that it made puni-pals with the crow!
Komugi, the house cat,
is going out for a walk.
Now Tomorune is trying
to make puni-pals with Komugi!
It assumed again that Komugi
wanted it to ride on its back.
Airune's getting worried.
Tomorune loves the softness
of Komugi's back.
Nice! Splendid landing, Tomorune!
Tomorune ahoy!
Oh no, Tomorune!!
Never mind. Komugi just wanted to squish!
Do you suppose Tomorune
and Komugi are puni-pals now?
You're reunited at last! How wonderful.
"I'm gonna prickle you two!"
says Togerune.
"Oh no you won't!" cries Airune.
My, now Tomorune's trying
to make puni-pals with Togerune!
Seems like Tomorune's convinced
Togerune wanted a game of tag!
Tomorune really enjoyed the game.
A present as thanks
for playing with it.
Togerune decided to give up
on prickling them for now.
Must be lots of fun
having tons of puni-pals, Tomorune!
Oh? Someone swiped the wing away.
This is the attic in Yuka's house.
And that vase is where Togerune lives.
Togerune, isn't that wing...?
Looks like the gift made it really happy.
The Puni Channel!
And squish.
Today, I'll be introducing
Enerune and Loverune.
Enerune and Loverune
Tomorune made puni-pals
with the crow, Komugi, and Togerune,
but it has many other
puni-pals as well.
One is Enerune.
It's very energetic
and athletic.
It lives with Aoi.
Another is Loverune.
It makes everyone fall for it
with its big love.
Tomorune quickly made
puni-pals with both of them.
Time for the question.
Loverune makes hearts.
What shape does Enerune make?
Here's the answer...
Here's the answer!
The answer is stars!
It's very good at dancing, too.
That's all for today!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Have you ever heard of
a supermoon?
It's when a full moon appears
the biggest all year!
Next Time
We'll get to see it tonight!
At least, I hoped so,
but it's behind the clouds...
Oh? What is it, Tomorune?
Next Time
Who's that? Hikarune?
Next time: "The Punirunes Watch the Moon♪"
The Punirunes
Watch the Moon♪
"Puni" in next time!