Sometimes you might get lost
Or find yourself frozen
On a thorny path, although
You must push forward
Will you find a legendary kingdom?
Perhaps mysterious lands?
A town you’ve dreamed of visiting?
Who knows what you’ll come across
Here, you’re free, we all are
We can go wherever pleases us
As long as there’s hope for the future
It’ll go on forever
That’s right, we’re writing this story together
And it’s only just beginning
“Nuts’ Love Story”
I win!
Get back here!
As if!
What was that for?
Oh?
Hey, Anzu!
Hi, Rosemary!
H-H-H-He...
Hello!!
Hi, Nuts...!
I just said hi to Anzu...
Oh-hooo!
See you later!
Did you see that?
Yeah...
Nuts is really awkward at this.
Oh, Anzu...
Okay! Now for the next group.
Are you okay, Nuts?
Just peachy!
Good!
Way to go, Nuts!
You actually held
a conversation with her!
So what?
But you still have a long way to go!
If you cover up your face
with a towel like that,
Anzu won’t be able to tell
you’re having feelings.
Feelings? Huh?
My feelings?
Huh?!
So Anzu’s not the only one who
hasn’t caught on to the fact you love her!
Huh...?
Nuts...
I have a good idea, everyone!
We’re going to invite Anzu out to a picnic
on our next day off! All of us!
I see!
At the picnic...
you’ll make the perfect chance...
for them to get...
to know each other!
Right on the nose!
Yay, a picnic!
I’ll bring the food!
The futile Nuts and
the dimwitted Anzu, huh?
This’ll be worth the watch.
It’ll be fine!
Nuts just has to show off his best traits!
Well...
Let’s do it!
Why did you cheer too...?
Dear Granny,
Tomorrow, I’m having
a picnic with my friends!
I can’t wait.
I hope Nuts can tell Anzu he loves her.
Oh, no! What do I do about the food?
All ready! My homemade chicken basket!
Bring this with you on your picnic!
Yay!
Here you go, Hana!
Thank you, Jeff!
It smells yummy!
Stay safe, okay?
And have fun!
Goodbye!
Have a safe trip!
Good luck, Nuts!
Huh?
How does even Jeff know?
Oh, y’know.
Y’know!
We may have slipped it to him!
We’re here!
Hi!
Hello!
Hi the—
Well, go on!
Go on!
Greet her already!
H-H-H-He...
Hello!!
What a dummy.
Get a clue already, will you?
Anzu is sensitive to your yelling!
Wait, what?
Anzu...
doesn’t like it...
when you yell!
Such a birdbrain.
Don’t worry about it!
You see, these red flowers...
Are you okay, Nuts?
Anzu doesn’t hate you!
You just startled her a bit by yelling!
Hana, Sakura...
Eek!
A weird bug got on me!
Get it off, get it off!
Azami, stay still!
I can’t! I can’t!
What is that thing?!
Throw it away!
I couldn’t do that...
Here you go.
Good for you, little caterpillar!
Huh?
A-Anzu...
S-So cute...
Nuts?!
O-Oh, Anzu...
Looks so good!
Jeff from Clara’s lodge is a master cook!
Help yourself to some of
the sushi rolls my mom made!
Thank you!
So good!
I baked some sweets for dessert!
Did you make them by yourself?
Hmph, I’ll take one.
You too, Nuts!
Huh?
Nuts here...
doesn’t like...
sweet things!
How is it? Is it too sweet?
It’s delicious!
I’m glad!
Looks like my picnic plan
was a resounding success.
Oh, whatever.
Ooh, butterflies!
Let’s dance together!
“Azami’s Secret”
Hana!
Let’s go!
Okay!
Nuts!
Yo!
Coming through!
What’s her deal?
So rude!
She never changes...
Why does someone as mean as her
get to be so good at ballet?
Her dancing so much this early
can only mean one thing...
She must be doing her stretches
somewhere else!
Ivy...
I can’t dance comfortably
if you stare at me like that!
You were dancing just fine!
How adorable!
Forget ballet, you should be doing
an elementary play!
Excuse me?!
Say that again, I dare ya!
Don’t let her get to you.
You two make the perfect combination!
Yeah! She’s a big meanie.
You said it!
She’s a meanie!
The earring you’re wearing
today is so cute!
You think so? I bought it when I was little.
Are you sure it’s not too childish?
Of course not! It really suits you!
She’s not wrong!
It’s just as childish as your dancing!
Why do you have to be such a bully?
Me, a bully?
I’m just being honest!
Coming through!
What’s so funny to her?
That was awful!
Rose!
Mary!
That’s it!
Today’s the day...
we give it to her straight!
You’re gonna need a plan!
Ivy?!
Yeah!
Nuts.
We’re having a meeting.
We’d love for you to join.
Welcome!
Would you like to try
our chocolate banana cake?
I would!
Me too!
Us too!
I’ll have it too!
How about you, Nuts?
Sure...
I’ll have your order in!
You have to endure this meal, Nuts!
Good luck, Nuts!
Good luck!
What’s the luck for, Nuts?
Anzu, sit down with us!
Huh?
Go on!
Azami’s rudeness has always been a problem,
but now it’s worse than ever before!
So now, we have to make it clear to her
how this makes us feel...
Wait, was she...
...holding herself back?
Come to think of it, Azami’s never ordered
any cake or sweet drinks before.
Huh?
I went to kindergarten with Azami,
and she gobbled down
on her birthday cake.
She has to have a sweet tooth, unlike m—
You don’t like sweet food, Nuts?
Umm, Anzu—
Oh, no! Nuts here...
loves cake!
Mhm!
It’s more fun...
to keep this up!
You know...
My mom told me that holding back
on things you like
can make you stressed and frustrated.
Is that why she’s being so mean?
It has to be!
Then I have just the idea
to stop her bullying!
Here you go, Nuts!
Thank you...
Anzu...
We’re all set!
The mission is on!
Where did Azami go?!
Hana, do you know where she might be?
Maybe she went back to her dorm?
We can smell her!
She’s this way!
Rosemary’s noses are very strong!
Let’s follow them!
Aah, wait for me!
She’s here!
We just know it!
Aha, there she is!
She’s amazing!
So she’s been practicing here
this whole time!
I know!
Beyond the fields and mountains
is the bottom of a gorge!
Oh, this one’s good.
Try and try as you may,
no talent means no reward.
She said that to us before...
I got one!
Stars will fly high in the sky,
trampling the talentless below them!
This is kinda freaky.
Is this what she does
in her free time?
I’m getting the urge to dance again!
Don’t let her get to you!
Put the plan into motion!
Alright!
Azami!
Hana...!
Come eat with us!
Azami!
Come on over!
What’s the big idea?
Don’t worry about it!
Go on!
You like cake, don’t you?
Are you trying to get me to put on weight?
It’s fine, we’re all eating it too!
Second time today, anyways!
Yeah!
So good!
You said it!
We’re still growing, so it’s all A-OK!
That’s what my mom told me.
Delicious!
You’re so cute, Azami!
You’re cute when you smile!
You’re just noticing?!
I’ve always been the cutest of all!
Azami really does have a cute side!
“The Pre Mier Festival I Look Up To”
And so, the Pre Mier Festival
is a great opportunity to showcase
this school to people outside the city.
I want you all to decide what you’d like
to present amongst yourselves!
Okay!
I’ve always looked up
to the Pre Mier Festival!
Really? Me too!
Did you hear? Class Rouge
is putting on Coppélia!
Coppélia?!
And Flora’s the star!
Aah! I can’t wait!
Last year, they did The Nutcracker!
I came here with my Granny last year!
I’d love to meet your grandmother!
You should ask her to come!
I will!
Hey!
What are we gonna put on?
A haunted house is the way to go!
Good idea!
Aww, no way!
I want to wear a cute apron
and be a waitress!
Good idea!
Pick a side, Rosemary.
Well, I’m always working as a waitress...
But there’s no way
I’m doing a haunted house.
Well, well!
Selling food does seem like a good idea!
How about crêpes?
I like it!
Aren’t those hard to make?
We’ll need someone skilled.
Someone who can bake thin dough.
Anzu’s perfect for—
Skilled, you say?
Obviously, you mean me, right?
You can cook, Azami?
That’s perfect!
Leave it to me!
Yay! We get to make crêpes!
Alright, then!
Nuts, Ivy! You two make a sign
and attract customers!
– You’ve got it!
– Leave it to us!
Azami and Anzu will handle the crêpes!
Rosemary and I will be waitresses!
Hooray!
What do you want to do, Hana?
Let’s see...
I want to make crêpes!
That’s your job, then!
You’re a very good director, Sakura!
Just selling stuff is lame.
Azami?
We’ll set up a stage by the tables
so people can watch me dance!
Just you?
How about we all dance!
I’m in!
Sounds like a plan!
It sounds a bit embarrassing...
Don’t worry, A-A-Anzu!
I love your dancing, Anzu!
It’s beautiful!
Thank you!
Nuts, Ivy!
You two set a stage
for me to dance upon!
I’m gonna lose it...
Anyone want some delicious crêpes?
Come on over!
Order up!
Thank you for waiting!
I ripped it!
This one’s all charred!
Grr! This griddle must be broken!
Oh, Azami...
So much for those skills of yours, huh?
Grrr! Put a sock in it, Nuts!
Hello!
Granny!
Are you doing well?
Yeah!
Hana!
Granny, this is Sakura!
She’s my best friend!
It’s good to meet you!
I’ve heard all about you
from Hana’s letters!
What a wonderful young lady you are.
Granny, this way!
Take a seat!
Welcome!
I take it you’re Rosemary?
Bingo!
We’ll go make you a crêpe!
Be gentle, Nuts!
Okay...
Good, just like that!
Grrr!
I told you, they’re specialty crêpes!
So you better come back and buy one!
Gosh, this work is so tiring.
When do we start dancing?
Azami...
There!
Granny, this is our specialty crêpe!
It looks delicious!
It’s wonderful, Hana!
Yay!
Hey, guys! Flora’s play is starting!
Let’s go watch!
That was beautiful!
I wanna be able to dance just like that soon!
Flora’s Swanhilda was amazing...
Azami...?
It’s time to dance!
Oh, yeah! We made our own stage!
Let’s go!
Yeah!
Hana, you’ve really improved!
Granny, I want to be able to perform
Swanhilda the way Flora did today!
I’m sure you will!
And I can’t wait until then!
“A Star Arrives”
Rosemary, what are you listening to?
Rosemary!
Oh?
Y’say something?
Yeah! I wanted to know
what you were listening to.
Is that Idaho?
Do you know this music, Sakura?
Huh?
You don’t?
Look!
This just came out today, right?
Lemme see!
Corn!
Amazing!
Oh, Corn!
Hana! This is Corn, the most popular
member of Idaho!
I’m a bigger fan of Chip.
Do you like them too, Anzu?
Yeah!
You are such children.
Azami!
Say that again!
What is there to like about
those American boys?
You’re so immature.
Wait, she knows who they are!
So this is Auntie Clara’s house!
Is this where she’s staying?
I smell a star!
Huh?
Corn!
I’m Rose!
I’m Mary!
Nice to meet’cha!
What’s all the fuss?
Oh!
Corn, you made it!
Hi, Auntie Clara!
It’s so good to see you!
Come on in!
Welcome to my lodge!
Is that...?
Corn?
Welcome!
Wow, you’re 100 times
more stunning in person!
This is Jeff, our chef!
Nice to meet you!
N-Nice to meet you...
I’m Hana! Nice to meet you!
I am Azami!
Hey! I’m Corn!
Nice to meet’cha!
As I’m sure you all know,
Corn is a singing and dancing
pop star from the U.S.
He’s also my nephew.
He’s going to be starring in a movie
as a boy who wants to be a ballet dancer.
Amazing!
I love dancing, but I’ve never
actually done ballet.
So he’s going to be getting special training
done here at Pre Mier for the next month.
Are you in our class?
Yes! You got that right, Hana!
Can’t wait to train with you!
A movie? This could be the perfect chance!
Cut!
That was perfect, Azami!
You’re a natural star!
I’m amazing!
Are you having another
weird daydream...?
Dear Granny,
I have big news!
Corn from the popular American boy band
Idaho is studying here at Pre Mier!
He’s dorming with us at Clara’s!
I actually didn’t know about
Corn or Idaho at all until now.
I’m not sure I’m a “fan” yet,
but I like his singing,
and he’s kinda cool... or whatever.
I can’t wait for our classes together!
You’re very good, Corn!
That was wonderful, Corn!
Oh, Anzu...
Sakura and Anzu are great!
Their dancing is wonderful!
Azami is so cool!
She’s amazing, isn’t she?
Oh!
Hana must really love ballet!
I’m getting the urge to get up and dance!
All right!
Hana!
You’re amazing, Hana!
It’s fun to dance alone,
but it’s even more fun with someone else!
That was wonderful!
No fair!
Corn, please...
dance with us next!
Sure! Oh, well.
Okay!
Yay!
I hope I can dance with him next!
Yeah!
I wanna dance with Anzu...
Don’t worry!
Anzu said she likes Chip
more than Corn, anyways.
Huh?!
Oh, Anzu...
How do you like Pre Mier?
It’s so much fun!
I got to dance with a lot of girls!
You’re very good, Corn!
I wouldn’t have thought
it was your first time!
Thank you! I appreciate it!
I wish I could practice
and get even better,
but my movie’s filming dates
got pushed up,
so I have to go back to the states.
Wait, already?
Nooo!
My big break!!
I see...
Hana, promise me something!
Huh?
I’m going to work hard on my ballet,
so when you’ve gotten better,
let’s dance again!
Okay!
Dear Granny,
And so, I made a promise with Corn!
It would be amazing if I can
dance with him on-stage someday...
“It’s a mighty power!”
“So that we can keep at it tomorrow!”
When I look up above
There’s many stars twinkling
It feels like time has slowed down, hasn’t it?
It’s so relaxing
Although we can’t see each other right now
We always see eye to eye
It’s a mighty power
So let’s relax and take a break
So that we can keep at it tomorrow
We’ll take a break for now
Let us spread out our arms
Take a deep breath
And gaze up at the same sky