A blank page awaits through that door
Have you decided what path to take?
Then now’s the time to take off
Now hoist the sails
Will you go on an adventure?
Will you seize your dream?
Will you find happiness?
Who knows what kind of journey to expect
Here, you’re free, we all are
You can go wherever pleases you
That rush of excitement
Will go on forever
That’s right, you’re writing your own story
And it’s only just beginning
Good day, Hana!
Hi!
Here, a letter for you
from Étoile Isle.
Hoping you hear good news!
Thanks!
Well, goodbye!
Goodbye!
And thank you!
I can’t! I’m too nervous
to look at it alone.
Granny!
Granny, I got a letter from Pre Mier!
My, my! Congratulations, Hana!
It says you made it!
Starting tomorrow, you’ll be attending
Pre Mier in Étoile Isle!
Yay!
My name is Hana!
Pre Mier is a ballet school in Étoile Isle.
And starting today,
I’m one of their students!
I’ll do my very best to become
a beautiful ballerina!
“Nice to Meet You, I’m Hana”
Let’s see here...
The trolley stop should be...
Is that it? So cute!
You lose again, Nuts!
Take that back!
Oh no!
Watch out!
Oh no! Come back!
Hey, wait!
Sounds...
...juicy!
Let’s go after them!
Trolley, please stop! Wait!
Was that thing important?
Yeah, a map!
A map?
A treasure map, isn’t it!
Huh? Umm, not quite...
I smell trouble!
Ivy!
What’s the matter?
You see...
This girl’s treasure map got into
the window of that trolley.
That’s no good!
Just hold on one second.
Alright. Nuts, use your skateboard to take
a shortcut to the road ahead.
With your speed, you should be able to
catch up to the next stop!
Got it! I’ll give it a go!
I, umm...
Fear not, that treasure map of yours is as good as recovered!
That Ivy...
Does that nerd really think...
...he’s getting in on the treasure?
What’s this?
Please, I have no use for this!
Huh, what’s this thing?
Anzu! Can I get more coffee?
Coming right up!
There’s no need to rush.
Nuts will get it back!
Hey!
If we find the treasure,
you’ll share a bit with us, right?
What do I do? I can’t tell them
the truth about the map...
Ivy, Rosemary!
What’s going on? You look all worn out.
This girl lost her treasure map.
A treasure map?
I... Umm...
Oh, it’s no treasure map,
but that reminds me...
Huh? Where’d it go?
Wait, you had it?!
I’ll be off!
Oh? What’s this?
Hey, guys!
Hello, Nuts!
Oh—hi, Anzu!
How did it go?
Are you all treasure-hunting?
Oh, umm, it’s nothing...
You won’t fool us, boy.
I caught up to the trolley,
but it wasn’t there...
Aww, what?
Could this be the map you’re looking for?
Aha! My map!
There it is! We saw it!
The sparks of friendship!
That means they’re going
to become best friends!
Aw. So the map was just for Clara’s house
at the Pre Mier dorms?
And who was it that claimed
it was for treasure?
Who did it?
It was you, wasn’t it?!
What a coincidence, Rosemary
and I are lodging there too!
Wait, really? We’re staying together?
That’s good news!
My name’s Ivy! If there’s ever trouble,
just give me a shout!
Nice to meet you!
I’m Nuts!
We’re Rosemary!
My name’s Anzu!
I’m not staying in the dorms,
but I go to Pre Mier too!
I’m Sakura! Nice to meet you!
I’m Hana! Nice to meet you!
So beautiful!
Right, right? It’s even more
beautiful on the inside!
Oh, wow!
Beautiful, right? Right?
Welcome, Hana!
I’ve been expecting you!
This is Ms. Clara!
She’s the housemother!
I look forward to staying with you.
Feel free to set your bags down.
We’ll assess your class placement in the afternoon.
Your room is right next to Rosemary’s.
See you in class!
Our rooms are this way!
Hurry up!
Who would that be?
Hey, Azami!
This is Hana, she’s new here!
I’m Hana! Nice to meet you!
Don’t be naïve. You’ll never stand
a chance against me.
Move aside.
Don’t let her get to you.
She’s like this with everyone!
Come on!
This is our room!
That one’s yours!
Okay!
See you later!
Whoa!
Dear Granny, I’ve made it
to Étoile Isle safe and sound!
And I’ve already
made some new friends.
They’re all so nice.
I think I’ll settle in just fine!
Hana, are you ready?
Hana!
I’ve made it to Pre Mier!
I’ll do my very best to become...
...a beautiful ballerina!
“My New Best Friend”
Come in!
Hana!
Let’s go!
Okay!
Coming!
Your earring...
is so cute, Hana!
Who knew you were so fashionable!
Eat my dust!
Nuts... Get back here!
Oh, Rosemary...
Hana!
Oh, Ivy!
That earring is quite beautiful.
G-Good morning.
It has a hidden fragrance to it.
You think so?
Hana!
Ivy!
Hi, Sakura! Hi, Anzu!
Your earring is so cute!
There she is.
Good morning, class.
Please get on the barre.
Port de bras!
Hana, your arms are too stiff!
Demi-plié!
Tendu!
Ms. Simone is teaching us
new students the foundations.
The fundamentals come
first and second in ballet.
And stop.
Now, gather in the center
of the room.
Pirouette!
Good work, Hana, Nuts!
Wonderful, Azami!
You’re amazing, Hana!
Développé arabesque!
Good work, Sakura!
Great, Azami!
That was tiring...
I can’t turn very well.
You’re much better at
adagio than me, though!
Watch it.
Hana!
That was mean, Azami!
Try being a terrible dancer
somewhere else, then!
Are you okay?
Yeah...
Did she break your earring?
My special earring...
When I was little,
I went to see Coppélia,
and the prima donna
Swanhilda gave it to me.
It’s special to me...
You got it from Swanhilda? Amazing!
Please don’t cry anymore!
I know! My mom might
be able to fix it!
Huh?
My family runs an accessory shop!
Wanna go there?
Okay!
Welcome!
Oh?
Sakura, and... Hana, is it?
Mom, can you fix this?
Here it is...
Looks like the clasp came loose.
I can handle this!
Just one second.
Such a beautiful store!
I help out whenever it gets busy.
Really? That’s amazing!
All finished!
How is it?
Thank you so much!
It was no trouble.
Good for you, Hana!
Thanks!
Thanks for helping me, Sakura!
What are friends for?
I’m your friend?
Yeah, my very first!
Sup, guys!
Oh, Nuts!
Get back here!
See you later, Hana, Sakura!
Get back here, Nuts!
As if!
Those three are always chasing each other around.
They get along very well!
Stop!
Oh! It’s Anzu...!
Get this, Nuts has a crush on Anzu!
Take this!
But Anzu doesn’t seem
to have caught on.
Hey, Sakura!
Hm?
Wanna meet up at school early tomorrow
and practice doing the pirouette?
You’ll teach me?
Yeah!
The turn is really all I’m good at.
Then I’ll teach you the arabesque!
Yay!
Try and try as you may,
no talent means no reward.
What’s her issue?
She’s so rude!
Azami...
I-Ivy?!
Azami appears to view you as her rival!
And that makes her
even more passionate.
Dear Granny.
Today, I made
a new best friend: Sakura!
She’s very kind and talented.
The earring Swanhilda gave me broke,
but her mother fixed it for me!
Just like a swan...
I’ll practice my hardest tomorrow...
...to become a beautiful balllerina!
“The Legendary Red Shoes”
Hana, I’m going to go buy some ballet shoes.
Do you want to come with?
You are?
I was gonna do the same thing!
We’re so...
like each other!
Oh!
It’s Swanhilda from Coppélia!
So that’s Swanhilda!
She’s so pretty!
I hope you get to see her again, Hana!
Me too!
We can buy shoes over at that store!
Red shoes?
Welcome!
Oh, wow! So many pretty
colors to pick from!
Étoile Isle is amazing!
You can wear whatever color
you want to during class!
Which one do you want?
What about you?
I’m going with pink, like always!
I know!
I’ll go with these yellow shoes!
Please come again!
These red shoes...
What’s wrong, Hana?
These shoes are catching my eyes.
Ahh, the legendary red shoes!
“Legendary?”
Indeed!
Those red shoes are considered
a legend in the ballet world!
Ivy...!
Hello, Hana! Hello, Sakura!
Are you two shopping?
Yup!
What kind of legend?
They say a ballerina that puts them on...
will be able to captivate everyone
with an astounding dance!
Wow!
But there’s more to it.
Indeed. The catch is,
when you put them on,
you can’t take them off, and you’ll be forced
to dance for the rest of your life.
Oh yeah, my grandma read me that story.
Indeed.
It seems like that may have actually
happened at Pre Mier a long time ago.
Want to stop here for a bit?
Sure!
Welcome in!
Oh, you’re all together!
Hello!
Welcome!
Hana, Sakura, Ivy!
May I take your order?
I’m not sure...
Me neither...
But we have to resist the cakes.
Aw, we do?
A little bit should be fine.
We’re still growing.
That’s what my mom told me.
Really?
Then I’ll have the chocolat banane
and an iced tea!
A cranberry tart and a milk tea, please!
I’ll have peach jelly and
a sparkling mineral water!
I’ll get your orders in.
Ohh, it looks so good!
Thanks for the food!
Yum!
You said it!
So what were you saying about the red shoes?
Right.
So there was this girl attending Pre Mier.
She was an attention seeker
and a real sore loser.
Sound familiar?
When they were assigned
roles for a recital,
she was told she wasn’t fit
for the lead role.
So she put on the red shoes
and danced for her teachers.
But they had already picked the lead,
and weren’t going to change their minds.
Then what happened?
In a fit of despair,
the girl danced her way out of the academy,
still wearing the shoes.
And that’s how it ends.
That’s it?
She went missing after that.
Huh?!
That is the legend that’s passed down
through Pre Mier.
Mom sent me a text!
I better get home!
See you tomorrow!
Bye!
Goodbye, Nuts!
A-Anzu...
Hey, did’ja hear?
Did’ja?
Huh?
The legendary red shoes...
vanished from the store!
What?!
They were just there yesterday!
Which means someone
must have bought them!
Those shoes were a kid’s size,
so whoever bought them
must go to Pre Mier!
Keen eye,
Ivy!
Next, do them in combination!
The legendary red shoes
can’t be taken off ever, right?
And you keep dancing for life...
Good posture, everyone.
Change!
Who could’ve bought those shoes?
I wonder...
And stop.
Today, we’re going to be
specially observing Class Rouge.
Class Rouge?
It’s Flora’s class! She’s the most
popular girl in school!
Class Rouge is telling the story of
the red shoes through interpretive dance.
They’re in the middle of practicing,
so please be quiet and don’t interrupt, okay?
“Red shoes,” huh?
That was wonderful!
I can dance even better than that.
After all...!
In the end...
the legend of the red shoes...
...was no more than a tall tale.
Oh, Anzu...
The red shoes gave me a bit of a scare...
but that was such a beautiful dance.
You said it!
I almost thought she was actually cursed
and couldn’t stop dancing...
Eek! Someone stop me!
Stop it!!
So Azami was the one who bought the legendary shoes...
That Azami...
Where are you taking me?!
“It’s a mighty power!”
“So that we can keep at it tomorrow!”
We live our lives
Dreaming of a happy ending
But we won’t get there alone
We should do it together
Although the finish line is out of sight
We believe in each other
It’s a mighty power
So let’s relax and take a break
So that we can keep at it tomorrow
We’ll take a break for now
Let us stop
Look into each others eyes
And hold hands