Hey everyone, gather around!
Chibi Maruko-chan is about to start!
"Happy Premonition"
I always see a smile
Chibi Maruko-chan
Every time I look in the mirror
Because the angel that cast this spell
Is right here with me
The girl who wept back then
I have to go cheer her up
I had this dream the other day
And I hope that it comes true today
It will, I know it
I'm positively certain
Maruko Can Taste the Differences in Water?
"Maruko Can Taste the Differences in Water?"
Oh?
Water Pipes Construction
Looks like they're doing construction
on the piping today.
Water Pipes Construction
I better get the laundry done
before we lose water.
Oh, no! We're gonna lose our water?
Only until construction is done.
It should be all patched up
by the time you get home.
But you won't be able to
wash the dishes after lunch, will you?
It's only for an hour, I'll figure something out.
Y'know, we used to get our water
from wells all over the place,
so we wouldn't have to worry about this.
It sure tasted great back then, though.
Did well water taste different from normal?
Hrm, well, it's a bit of a distant memory,
but I'm pretty sure I loved it.
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
Wow!
I wonder how good well water tastes!
Did someone say something
about good tastes?
Yeah, water.
Water? I hear you.
There's lots of good-tastin' water out there.
Oh, wow! You can taste the differences in water?
Sure can.
I was out the other day and had some
of this famous spring water.
And it was amazing!
It's like my body was just soaking it all in...
I could drink that water forever!
Interesting.
Water always seems to taste better
with a plate of curry.
Not like that.
Man, talking about it
is making me thirsty for more!
Now I want to try some for myself!
Yeah, I have to know!
SAKURA
I'm on my last legs.
What I'd do to have that well water
just one more time...
Where do you even find a well?
And even if we find one,
surely we can't just take its water?
No way.
Why don't we try looking anyways?
It's so hot out today...
We couldn't find any wells,
and all this walking has worn us out.
Feels like we're wandering in the desert here.
I'm so thirsty... I need water!
Sakura-san, Maru-chan! Hello!
– Grandpa Sasaki!
– Sasaki-san!
I see.
It's no well, but would you like me
to get you some spring water?
Wow! Can you really?
Of course. I happen to have business nearby.
Yay! Thanks, Grandpa Sasaki!
You're like an oasis flower
in our desert.
Grandpa, you're dripping.
Yeah, doesn't it make me look stunning?
Sure, how about you wipe it off now?
What would you like to order?
More water!
Grandpa...
I'll go get you a refill.
Oh, and an iced coffee.
Orange juice, please!
The service here is great,
and their water tastes amazing...
What bliss.
Alright!
This establishment shall be recognized
for having the best water in Shimizu!
But then we won't need Grandpa Sasaki's water.
SAKURA
Oh, really?
Who knew Grandpa Sasaki had access
to such good-tasting water.
But don'tcha suppose he's just using it
to water his plants?
Huh?
So we're just going to be getting
the plants' leftovers?
That'll do.
A little bit of extra plant water is all we need.
Oh, yeah.
Didn't we once try to use pyramid power
to make water taste better?
It just tastes like normal water.
And I tried using it to make me smarter.
Please, as if wearing some weird triangle
is going to make you smart.
I remember that!
No matter how good Grandpa Sasaki's water tastes,
there's no way you two
will be able to tell the difference.
Aren't you being a bit rude?
Yeah! We won't know until we try!
Then let me test you.
Behold.
I heard something about water tasting better
when you shake it 100 times in a jar.
So guess which one I shook up!
I've never heard that one before.
They both taste exactly the same...
I know!
This one is just like Christmas!
Look at the way it's bubbling.
It's champagne!
Is it?
All that shaking must've mixed in the air,
causing these bubbles.
So this one must be the shaken water!
Are you sure?
Give it a taste with your ears, Maruko.
You can hear "Silent Night" playing
behind the champagne bubbles.
Silent night, holy night...
I think I'm starting to see what you mean.
I'll pick this one too!
So, Dad? Which one is it?
Neither! They're both plain old water.
What?!
You think I'd shake a jar of water 100 times?
That sounds like a pain in the butt.
I totally got you guys!
That's dirty, Dad!
What did we do to deserve this?
Pay the price for messing with us
by shaking it 100 times for real!
What she said! 100 times!
Oh come on, you know I was only kidding... right?
Shake it 100 times!
96, 97...
98, 99, 100...
All this annoying work has pooped me out.
Let's see how it tastes shaken up.
Do you think it'll be any different?
Man, it beats me.
Same here.
Dad, you try it.
It tastes better shaken up.
You mean it?
Well, yeah!
I shook it 100 times!
I'd think anything tastes good
after going through that.
Whew, so good!
SAKURA
A few days later...
Are these what I think they are?
Yep, it's the delicious water
Sasaki-san got for us!
He brought two bottles.
Oh, are they both different kinds?
Grandpa Sasaki
really pulled out all the stops.
Shizuoka does have a lot of springs
with good-tasting water!
So which bottle is which?
He told me, but I can't remember.
He labeled the one with the
longer description "one",
and the shorter description "two"...
How is that supposed to help...?
Now, we can still compare them in practice.
Oh, I know!
Can I invite Tama-chan and Kosugi?
I was talking to them about the water,
and they both said they wanted to try it!
The more the merrier!
I'll go call them!
They'll be over soon!
This'll be exciting.
Now that we're finally having good water,
we better get a good taste of it
so we don't get fixated on imaginary bubbles.
How about we do some light exercise
before they arrive so we get thirsty?
No way!
That'll just make anything taste good,
like what happened to Dad.
Maybe we can brush our teeth?
If we do that, all we'll be able
to taste is the toothpaste.
I was thinking it should feel more natural!
Natural, you say...
We can sharpen our senses
and get in touch with the flow of the universe.
Good idea, Grandpa!
You know cosmic powers like nobody's business!
Let us accept the powers!
Maru-chan!
So good!
You can really taste the difference
between the two of them.
No kidding!
This feels very bright and poppy,
like Jogasaki-san.
While this one feels gentle,
like something Yamane could drink it all in one gulp.
I think I can get what you mean!
They both certainly taste good,
but no matter how much I try,
I can't tell the difference...
I wasn't sure when you told me
that well water was all that,
but you were right after all
that there's many tastes to water.
A-Ah, yeah, I see.
O cosmic powers!
Please grant me the ability
to tell these tastes apart!
Hey, why don't we try
tasting them with our eyes closed
and guessing which one is which?
At least make it a challenge!
We'll add tap water to the mix.
That sounds fun! Let's do it!
Oh, man...
I can hardly tell the difference,
let alone guess it!
Yay, I got them all right!
So did I!
Me too!
I...
...got them all wrong.
On that note, you said you liked
the second one the best...
...that was the tap water.
Shock!
Who would've thought you'd have
such a hard time telling them apart?
I need to go to the bathroom.
Everything from cosmic powers
to good water
passes right through this aging body of mine...
I'm like a worn out rain gutter
letting the water run off.
Y'know, what's wrong with thinking
the tap water tastes the best of them all?
It's the stuff you drink every day, right?
It's proof that Shizuoka has good water!
Thank you!
You're all so kind.
Maruko began to feel he was hopeless
no matter how much good water he had,
but she didn't want to be
the rain on his parade.
Thank you, TARAKO-san
My name's Momoko Sakura
and I'm in third grade.
I've always been kinda small,
so they call me "Chibi Maru",
and since I'm a girl,
you add "ko" to the end.
Put it all together and you get
Chibi Maruko-chan!
There's six people in my family,
Grandpa, Grandma,
Mom and Dad, too...
...and also, my old sister.
Aw, it's looking all weird...
I don't think I wrote enough...
Mom's gonna be so happy
when she sees this!
And if we did fight,
I'm sure it'd be my fault.
So please wait for me until
I come to you to apologize.
I'm sorry for always troubling you.
We'll be best friends forever.
Yes, we will.
Thank you, TARAKO-san
Payapapa Papayapapa Payapaya
Arara
Spell
Arara catabra tsururinko
Arara
Spell
It's a bit of an odd spell
Allow me to teach it to you
I assure you it's no tongue twister
Arara
Spell
Arara catabra tsururinko
Even if you get lost, worry, and burst into tears
The sun will always
Shine brighter tomorrow
Tripping to the floor
And standing back on your feet
Is all a part of life – things happen!
Just let whatever be what it will be
Que sera serasera serarinko (The heck's a serarinko?!)
It's a spell that gives you courage
Arara catabra tsururinko (Yep, that's the ticket)
Remember it when you're crying all to yourself
It'll bring a smile
Right back to your face
Funny how that works, huh?
I think our wishes will come true!