Greetings, everyone!
Welcome to the movie theater!
I am...
Hold on.
Come on! Get off!
Plop!
I am Whisper,
the butler Yo-kai extraordinaire!
I'd like to take it straight to you in seat E8!
Are there any Yo-kai in your vicinity?
Whis? Who's that Yo-kai next to you?
My bad, that's your mother.
Ehem!
Moving forward!
In this world, strange occurrences
are all caused by Yo-kai.
As such, anything strange that occurs
within this theater...
may be their doing as well!
I've been looking forward to this movie.
Yeah, we're in it!
Yeah! This movie's so awesome!
Whoo!
Why is Fumi so riled up?
Is it really that good?
Hey!
Whisper?!
People are excited to see Whisper?
That doesn't add up.
A Yo-kai must be behind this!
Say whis?!
Pop!
That was uncalled for, Keita!
Yo-kai might be positively everywhere,
but they're certainly not here!
Clearly, the audience is enamored
with my handsome movie star charms!
Explain that.
Huh?
He's out like a light.
Nyo kidding, I'd do the same
if I saw Whisper.
Hey! Falling asleep out of nowhere...
happens all the time in theaters!
What about that?
Whis?
He's just eating his popcorn!
And that?
There have to be Yo-kai here!
Harumph! Nose-picking is natural here!
These dim lights make it the perfect environment
to pick without anyone noticing!
That can't be it.
Goodness gracious. If you keep
pointing fingers at Yo-kai like this...
There you are!
Say whis?!
Yeah!!
Mera-mera!
Meramelion
Isamashi tribe
It's Meramelion!
He's pumping people up!
Baku.
Baku
Pretty tribe
It's Baku!
She put him to sleep.
It's just a bite!
Tsumamiguinosuke
Pokapoka tribe
Tsumamiguinosuke!
He's making him
go to town on his popcorn!
Dig-dig...
Hanahojin
Fushigi tribe
Hanahojin!
He's making him pick his nose?
What in the world's going on here?
Why are there so many Yo-kai?
They're watching the movie up there...?
Keita! Whisper!
Our meow-vie's starting!
Gera gera po, gera gera po
Gera gera po-po, gera gera po (Come on!)
YO-KAI WATCH
How Keita and Jibanyan Met, Nyan♪
A-And Whisper Too! ♪♪
Got a text coming in, zip-zip
Everything's on track, zoom-zoom
Hope my phone doesn't die
They'll lose it if they can't reach me
What's convenience about anyways?
And why fret about the future?
Just laugh it off gera-po, whip out your watch
And turn back the clock
From atop a temple backed by the sunset
Looking over our towns
A mother crow once cawed out
Gera gera po, gera gera po
Gera gera po-po, gera gera po (ZZ, come on!)
The clouds dance and the winds sing
In this world, strange occurrences
are all caused by Yo-kai.
A wristwatch called a Yo-kai Watch
enables people to see these creatures.
Ever since he obtained the Yo-kai Watch,
average young Keita's fate
took a turn for the stranger!
But how did the Yo-kai Watch
fall into Keita's hands?
That would be his emotional encounter
with me, Whisper!
He also had a run-in with a Yo-kai named Jibanyan.
How did this former cat become a Yo-kai?
We will present his secret story to you!
Now, down memory lane we go!
Yo-kai are Real!
I gotcha!
Kuma! Kanchi!
Look, a stag beetle!
So puny. Check this out!
Whoa! What's that thing?
A sawtooth stag beetle.
And a pretty big one,
based on my data.
Hear that?
Hey, guys!
F-Fumi!
Wh-What are you doing here?
I'm working on a research project.
Did you catch anything, Keita?
Oh, this.
Wow, it's just like you!
It's so average!
What?!
Average, average, average...
I'm gonna catch something real good!
NO ENTRY!
Stay out!
There should be some deeper in!
That's gotta be rare!
Huh? Where'd it go?
What's this thing?
Insert a coin.
Who's saying that?!
What the heck?
What do you mean "insert a coin?"
Insert a coin.
You mean insert it in there?
Heck no! I don't even know
what's in that capsule machine...
Insert a coin...
Fine! I'll do it!
Insert a coin, or forever regret it
Ooh-hee-hee-hee-hee...
What the heck?
Why, hello!
You may call me Whisper.
Whis!
Whisper
Greetings!
I am what's known in your world
as a "Yo-kai!"
A Yo-kai? You sound so posh...
Indeed. Yo-kai, you see...
are strange beings
behind strange phenomena!
Why was I inside a capsule machine, you ask?
The answer to that lies 190 years ago!
A self-righteous monk
declared us Yo-kai evil beings
and sealed us away!
Why in a capsule machine?
Those are miniscule details.
Let's move on!
What matters is...!
After aaaall this time...
I have been freed from my seal,
thanks to you!
You saved me!
Hold it right there!
Ouch...
You're supposed to listen!
I'm busy looking for bugs.
Breaking your 190 year-long seal
doesn't change that.
Oh, you were listening.
Oh, right!
Urp!
Gimme back my 100 yen!
Seriously?!
I wanted it to buy soda.
Sorry, what goes in
never comes out!
That's the nature
of the capsule machine!
Whatever. I'm outta here.
Have a lovely day.
Hey!
Hold it right there!!
Ow! Pah!
Bagh!
Floop...
What is it now?
Listen to me until I'm finished!
You are quite the...
lucky boy!
You call this lucky?
I come from a particularly
courteous tribe of Yo-kai!
Therefore, I shall reward you
for breaking my seal!
How?
I shall become your steward.
I don't have any sheep.
Not a shepherd.
You're not fluffy.
I'm not a—
Or mutton?
I'm not made of sheep either!
I am your butler! Buht-ler!
Here's the gist.
Whatever problems you have,
I'll take care of them—
Zip! Zang! Zapow! Huzzah!
in my own fantastical spooky way!
Again?!
I told you to hold it!
Bugs, right? You want bugs?!
Bugs, o bugs, rare bugs...
Come on out!
It's back!
Take as many as you wish!
O-Okay, I get it! Thanks!
Now make them go away!
Well then. As you wish.
Bugs, o bugs, rare bugs,
off you go!
Shake.
Yuck!
What the heck?
Man, I didn't even manage
to catch any rare bugs.
And now I'm being followed by a weirdo.
Whis!
Look, I'm not allowed
to bring any pets home...
A p-pet?! I'm sorry?!
I am a Yo-kai!
Have you been told
not to bring Yo-kai home?
I guess not...
Then it's okay!
I didn't say that.
It's no matter. Nobody else
can see me anyways!
Wait, really?
I'm home...
Ugh, you're always like this!
Can you blame me?!
I've told you countless times!
It was right there!
Anyone would do it!
They're fighting?
I can't believe you ate my pudding!
I was saving it!
Would you stop nagging
about pudding?!
O-Over that?
They're not usually like this!
Let me take a look.
Just as I suspected.
That Yo-kai is the culprit.
Huh?
You know how much I look forward
to eating my pudding!
What Yo-kai?
Ah, you can't see it, can you?
You'll need this.
What's that?
The Yo-kai Watch.
The Yo-kai Watch?
It's a communication tool
for humans and us Yo-kai.
With this, you should
be able to end their fight.
Put it on!
Push the button on the right.
Now shine the light in their direction.
Yikes! Wh-What is that?
The Yo-kai Donyorinu!
She brings a gloomy atmosphere
wherever she goes.
Donyorinu
Bukimi tribe
Gloooom...
Simply, she dampens the mood
of everyone in the room,
causing a fight to break out.
Donyorinu
I can't believe you ate my pudding!
This is a Yo-kai scare known commonly
as a sudden martial argument.
If it gets worse, it could lead to a divorce.
No way!
That's it.
I'm done!
No!
You cannot see Yo-kai,
but they are everywhere.
And they have many such effects
on humankind.
How do I get her to leave?
Hmm, you could either reason with her,
or make her leave by force.
Reason or force? Guess I'll reason with her.
Then, leave it to your butler!
I'll resolve this situation
swiftly and smoothly!
Thanks.
Good day to you, fair mademoiselle.
Would you perhaps mind
shooing off?
Eek!
She ignored him!
There's no reasoning with her!
What reasoning?
We'll just have to force her out!
Fighting her is our only option!
Pow pow pow!
Hold on! Let me talk to her.
Oh?
Hey... my mom and dad really love each other.
So could you please leave?
Hmm...
I wish I could, gloom...
But I have my reasons, gloom...
What are they?
I left my home after
a fight with my husband, gloom.
Huh? Yo-kai couples fight too?
He must hate me now, gloom...
Hey now, that can't be true.
Gloom?
Sometimes people fight
even though they love each other.
I think you'll patch up just fine
if you talk it out!
But I have no idea where he is, gloom...
I see...
Here he is!
Already?!
Honobo...
There you are, buono!
I was too harsh, buono!
Honobono
Pokapoka tribe
Is that her husband?
Yes, the Yo-kai Honobono.
He makes his surroundings jovial.
Buono!
Donyorinu makes things gloomy,
while Honobono makes things jovial.
They counteract one another,
creating a normal atmosphere.
Dear.
Honey.
I'm sorry.
No, I'm sorry.
Let's go home, buono.
Yeah, gloom.
Sorry for causing you trouble,
monsieur, gloom.
Buono!
The two of them made up.
So Yo-kai really are real.
Indeed they are.
Yo-kai live in their own dimension
overlapping with the human world,
and they always cause troubles
for humans like they did today.
You just can't normally see them.
Wow. That's kinda crazy.
But you can rest easy now that you have me!
Rest assured, young Keita,
I shall protect you from any Yo-kai harm.
You didn't help at all before, though.
Urp!
I gave you that Yo-kai Watch!
For free, no less!
Now you can use it
to see Yo-kai all around you!
Oh yes.
How will meeting Yo-kai affect your life?
That, I cannot say.
This Yo-kai Watch I got...
might change my life forever.
YO-KAI WATCH
Yo-kai...
Watch!
The Spooky Intersection
Hey, Whisper. Supposedly there's been
some weird accidents going down here.
Weird, you say?
Yeah.
They're called near misses.
Near misses!
People almost get run over...
Run over!
but the cars stop just in time.
Just in time!
Yeah, hence "near miss."
I see. That must certainly be...
the work of a Yo-kai.
Huh?
There must be a jibakurei
haunting this intersection!
What's a jibakurei?
Allow me to explain.
They're spirits bound to the spots
where they died.
These spirits are usually unable
to compro... compro... compre...
What'cha reading there?
Huh?
The Yo-kai Freakypedia?
Jibakurei
You're reading it word-for-word!
It's just for reference!
Yeah, sure.
Now, young Keita.
Go on and bring light to the Yo-kai
hiding away in the darkness!
With your Yo-kai Watch.
I don't see anything.
Search the whole area!
You won't see the Yo-kai
if the light never hits it.
There it is! It's the jibakurei!
Nya!
Jibanyan!
Jibanyan
Pretty tribe
Wha...?
That's a jibakurei?
Huh? Um...
His name is Jibanyan.
Nya...
Nyan?
Nya!
What was that?
H-He possessed that man!
Nya... nya!
Watch out!
Take this, stupid truck!
One Hundred Paws of Fury!
Nya-nya-nya-nya-nya...!
Nya-owch!
Blegh!
What's wrong with you?!
My legs moved on their own!!
That was close...
That must be the cause
of those near misses.
"Jibanyan" is causing them
by possessing people!
We have to stop him!
What do you say, reason or force?
Nya-ow...
Nya?
"Nya," he says.
Nya!!
You can see me, nyan?!
Uhh, yeah.
Nyo way!!
Do you know a girl named Emi?
Huh?
No, no, I'm not ready for that yet!
If something's troubling you,
then rest assured...
my master will help you!
Hey, now!
We have to stop those near misses!
Oh, right.
Hey, why do you all that?
Nya...
When I was still alive,
I lived with a girl named Emi.
My name is Jibanyan nyow,
but I had a different nyame
back then.
What was it?
It was a cool, wonderful,
and gentlemanly nyame!
Okay, what was the name?
I forgot, nyan!
You what?
But we did everything together!
Like sleeping,
and sleeping, and especially sleeping!
I was so happy back then...
All you did was sleep!
Well, he's a cat.
One day...
Nya-nya... nya?
Nya!!
I suddenly died after getting hit by a truck.
Then Emi said to me...
You died from a truck, just like that?
So lame.
Lame. Lame.
What?!
How despicable!
Don't say that!
Emi's a good girl!
She must've said that for a reason.
Like what?
It's gotta be something!
I have my doubts.
If anything...
she wouldn't have said that
if I hadn't gotten hit by a truck!
That's why I'm training!
So I can be a cat who can't get run down!
But you're putting other people
in danger.
That's a good point, nyan.
Guh...
I'll do it all by myself!
Nya!
Nya!!
Oh dang!
You got hit like nothing.
Sorry you had to see that.
That was my mistake.
I got caught up in the meow-ment.
He ran out with his eyes closed.
This is how I do it on my own.
I won't di...
Nya!!
Lotta trucks running through here...
What were you trying to shout?
"I won't die!"
It's a famous quote in the field of near misses.
There's a field for that?
I don't believe so.
Third time's the try!
I won't die!
One Hundred Paws of Fury!
Nya-nya-nya-nya-nya...!
Nya!!
Nya-owch!
So close...
See? I can't do it myself.
And why do you suppose so?
Because I'm lonely.
Huh?
I'm always doing it alone.
But I'm stronger when I'm not alone!
That's why I possess people!
But if that's a bother, then I guess...
I'm better off being alone forever!!
Wait, Jibanyan!
If that's what you need,
then you can possess me!
Nya...
Nya-nya?
I'll train with you!
Keita!
But why?
Because it's awesome
how hard you're training!
You must really love Emi to go this far.
Nya... nya!
We're in this together now!
So let's be friends!
Nyan!
What's this?
A Yo-kai Medal!
It's a sign you've made friends
with a Yo-kai.
We're friends nyow!
Yeah!
Keita!
Jibanyan!
Nya-owch!!
I won't die!!
He's hopeless.
4-Panel Komasan!
4-Panel Komasan
Movie Theater
"Movie Theater," y'all!
Big bro, the movie's about to start!
I can't wait!
This tastes real good!
Big bro, don't eat it so quickly!
Darn...
The movie ain't even started yet,
and it's all gone...
I had a feeling this would happen!
Amazin'! Komajiro, thanks a bunch!
4-Panel Komasan!
The End
O
And now, time for the movie...
The End
O
The movie resumes
The End
O
The movie resumes
The End
O
The movie resumes
The End
O
The movie resumes
to resume, y'all!
Hello everyone!
Have you been enjoying the strange
yet wondrous world of Yo-kai thus far?
I see. That means the world to us.
The world of Yo-kai will only
expand even further from here on out!
So please enjoy the show.
On to today's topic.
Memories are quite the curious thing.
From happy memories
to sad ones,
humans can reshape them in their heads
to suit their needs.
The star of today's story
locked away an extremely precious memory,
one that he cannot do without,
to forget the pain of the reality he is in.
Just what could that precious memory be?
Jibanyan's Secret
Flap your arms up and down like wings!
Up, down, up down
Work those deltoids! Watch, two, three, po!
Let's work on those abs! Feel your belly button!
Watch, two, three, po...!
Up, down
Make like a seesaw!
Just like life's a seesaw!
Count it down! Watch, two, three... po!
Watch!
Two!
Three!
Po!
That's enough!
Would you quiet down?
I'm trying to read manga here!
Whis?
Why are you so worked up, nyan?
You should join us!
It's very refreshing.
That's right!
Lolling about all day reading manga
isn't good for your body, nyan.
You don't know that!
You know, most cats sleep quietly
in their room.
You're basically a freeloader.
A-A-A freeloader?!
Did you just call me a freeloader?!
Either that or a pet!
A-A pet?!
Which makes me your owner.
E-Excuse meow?!
I'm nyo freeloader nyor a pet!
Then what are you?
A jibakurei! I haunt this place!
Allow me to recap.
A jibakurei haunts the spot where it died.
Jibanyan here died at the intersection
and became Jibanyan,
the cat jibakurei!
Would you believe it?
He was told the most horrible thing
after he died!
You died from a truck, just like that?
So lame.
Lame! She called me lame!
Keita, that's awful!
Said the one who brought it up.
Just make like a cat and be quiet!
I don't take commands from nyobody!
Nya-nya-nya-nya...
That's enough, you two.
Don't you knyow, Keita?
Dogs have their people,
but cats have their homes!
Cats aren't supposed
to be tamed by humans!
Uh-huh.
Nya!
Nya-nya... We're through!
Come on. This is childish, for both of you!
Well, I am a kid.
Oh, right.
Keita never listens.
Gotta think of something else...
Chocobars are so good!
It's Fumi.
Fumi must be super kind.
Maybe I've been haunting the wrong house.
That's it!
I'll crash at Fumi's house for a bit
and see what it's like!
Nya!
A cute girl is the best fit for a cat!
Where did he go off to?
Whis...
Maybe I was too harsh.
We don't really get along,
but I'm kind of worried now that he's gone.
He doesn't seem like he would
do anything rash.
I know!
You could force him back
by summoning him with his medal!
Will that really help?
Good point.
Though you know,
regardless of what he said,
he definitely loves you a whole lot.
You think so?
Yes!
He has respect for you
all over his face every day,
and you're the only one who can console him.
I see.
Uh-oh.
I can't wait to get to Fumi's house!
We're gonna be best friends!
What's wrong?
Wah-wah-wah-wah-wah!
Keita, look over there!
What is it?
No, over there!
I don't see anything.
It's a UFO! I just saw a UFO fly by!
There's no UFO.
There is so!
Where's your proof
there wasn't a UFO?
Huh? It's Jibanyan, and Fumi!
What's he doing?
Young Keita, I hate to break this to you.
But it appears Jibanyan has abandoned you
to go live with Fumi.
What?! He has?
It's hard to take in.
But such is to be expected
from a fickle, sorrowful cat,
so please do not let it sour your...
What?!
Why are you so happy?!
You're supposed to feel sad!
But now we'll stop running out of chocobars,
and he won't annoy me
when I'm reading manga!
It's a win-win!
He matters that little to you?!
Wait, this is bad...
There! That's the compassion
I expect from a hero!
Now Fumi has to deal with him.
Gah! Seriously?
Gin, that appears to be Keita Amano.
It seems that way, Kin.
It's the boy who possesses
the Yo-kai Watch.
He does appear to be quite average...
But perhaps a little too average.
What does our leader see in this boy?
That is not for us to worry about.
We must follow our orders
and separate him from those abhorrent Yo-kai.
It is to rescue that cat Yo-kai as well.
Gold, silver, shimmer, shimmer...
Nya? Nya?!
Nya-nya-nya-nya-nya...
Nya-nya! Nya!!
Where'd Jibanyan go?
That's odd. He disappeared into thin air.
Nyan!
Dear, would you say something already?!
Umm, I'd rather not.
Ugh, you're always like this!
Where am I, nya...?
Nya!!
Wh-What's going on here?!
I turned back into a nyormal cat!
It can't be...
Is this...?
It's my old house!
It's Emi's house!
Did that clock send me back in time?
You're wrong!
That sounds like...
Nya!
It really is Emi!
Your grades are low because
you keep goofing off.
No! I really did have a stomachache!
Don't lie to me!
They're fighting, nyan?
Nya!
Gloooom...
I certainly don't remember
raising a liar!
Why don't you believe me?
Hey! This is her fault!
Wait! Emi, listen to me!
Emi! She's the one doing this!
Let me talk to her!
Nyan!
Hmph.
YO-KAI WATCH
Yo-kai...
Watch!
I was telling the truth,
but they didn't believe me...
She's so lame.
That Yo-kai was behind it, I swear!
You're the only one
who understands me, Akamaru.
Oh, Emi. I feel so happy.
But it's still itching at me...
You died from a truck, just like that?
So lame.
Emi's such a kind girl.
Why would she say something like that?
It doesn't make any sense.
I really do think there was a reason...
but I also can't help but worry
she might have meant it.
Hey, Akamaru! Wanna get some fresh air?
Nyo way, it's hot outside...
Great, let's go!
Nya! Nya!!
Whoo!
Nya-nya-nya-nya-nya...!
Nyaaan!!
Nyan!
Stuck the landing!
That was scary, nyan...
Akamaru, was that refreshing or what?
Nya!
This is so relaxing.
I like this spot.
It feels like I have the whole sky to myself.
I feel you. This hits the spot.
Hey, Akamaru.
You know how I'm the class president at school?
You are?
I have to be someone
people can rely on.
But that means I don't have anyone
to complain to.
That's why I always go to you.
Is that okay?
Thank you!
Nyan!!
Akamaru!
We'll be together forever.
And a good kitty has to take good care
of their loving master!
Got it?
I can't find him anywhere.
You don't suppose he ascended?
Ascended?
Just as one ceases to exist when they pass,
jibakurei will go to heaven
when they lose their spiritual purpose.
So you're saying Jibanyan's
no longer with us?
Nyan...
Akamaru, do you like this?
Hmm, something doesn't feel right.
Yeah, that's it.
I declare this outfit totally lame!
Nyaow...
Ice Cream
Here!
Nyan!
Nyan...
No overtime on R, I, or P Days
All Grim Managers please report
to the Grim Center.
We shall now let the wheel of fate
pick a human
who falls victim to the "died in a flash" scare.
Needless to say,
this is an important task to maintain the balance
between heaven, the human realm, and hell.
Let us carry out this task with caution.
Yes, sir.
Dear me...
Must it pick such a young girl?
Although, this is how it must be.
The Grim Parliament must remain impartial
to the souls it sends to heaven.
Some of them will be
young and kind-hearted souls.
Sending those predetermined souls away
to build the future...
is painful work, but it must be done.
That can't be right.
Have we not discussed this girl
in the past?
Nya...
Here!
Nya! Nyan!
Wow!
Nya!
What a beautiful outfit!
You're right! It is beautiful!
Akamaru, I want to be a designer!
A designyer?
It's my dream to make
lots of amazing outfits!
Nya!
I believe in you, Emi!
You've got good taste in pets, after all!
Nya! Nyan-nyan! Nya, nyan-nya!
Over here, Emi!
Oh!
Miki! Sayaka!
Hey, guys!
Nya!!
You're the only one
who understands me, Akamaru.
That's what happened...!
Akamaru! We'll be together forever.
Akamaru, I want to be a designer!
Akamaru!
It's all coming back to me!
I remember why I got hit by that truck!
Emi!!
Nya-nya-nya?
What is this?
Don't be hasty, cat.
Who's there?
Why would you sacrifice your own life
for the same human twice?
Why repeat the same mistake?
We're giving you a second chance.
You get to live a normal life,
instead of becoming an abhorrent Yo-kai.
That is why we sent you back in time.
Give it some thought.
You'll come to regret your mistake.
I...
We'll be together forever.
Right, Akamaru?
I regret nothing!
I love Emi, nyan!
You foolish cat!
Why, you!
Emi!!
Akamaru...
What happened to you?
Emi, I'm over here!
Are you... dead?
Right...
This is where I died.
Akamaru...
Did you die to protect me?
You died from a truck, just like that?
That's...
so lame.
Huh?
It's so lame...
It's so, so lame!
Oh, right...
Emi didn't hate me because of this at all.
I painted her as an awful person
and tried to forget it all...
But I'm the awful cat!
Why? Why did you leave me, Akamaru?!
Oh, Emi...
You're so sweet, nyan.
Goodbye, Emi!
Akamaru!
Emi!
This is goodbye!
I know you'll become a great designyer!
Emi! Goodbye, nyan!
Goodbye, nyan!!
Nya!!
Where could he have gone?
Nya-nya-nya-nya-nya!!
Whis!
Jibanyan?!
Whi?
Jibanyan, are you okay?
Ouch...
I just went through something weird.
But I feel so much better!
Whi?
Alas, we could not separate
that cat Yo-kai from Keita Amano.
How should we report this matter
to our leader?
This foolish cat is not a matter
worth reporting.
I agree.
I'm sorry, Jibanyan.
Nyo, I'm sorry.
I'll try to be a better cat!
You let me live here,
so I shouldn't be cocky about it.
I'm glad you understand!
Jibanyan!
Keita!
Oh, the beautiful rekindling of their bond!
Jibanyan!
Keita!
Keita! Do you know what happened
to the pudding in the fridge?
It was yours, so it's fine if you ate it.
Huh? I didn't eat...
Hey! Jibanyan...!
Good cats can eat pudding too!
You little monster...!
Cats have the right to eat as they please!
No they don't!
Say that again!
I see things haven't changed one bit.
I'm my own cat, nyan!
I'm your owner!
I'm nyot your pet!
I'm a jibakurei!
Yo-kai Exercise!
"Exercise" is written in hiraganya!
Yo-there, yo-there, yo-there, yo-there
There's Yo-kai about, so don't go out
Alojoi, alojoi, join along in the fun
Make some friends!
Yo-kai, Yo-kai, Yo-kai
Watch-tch-tchee!
Kai kai kii kii
Kui kui kei kei
Come on Yo-kai
Watch-tch-tchee!
I overslept this morning
Even though I dreamt I woke up!
Why'd you sleep in, nyan?
Why'd you sleep in, y'all?
Bwa-ha-ha!
A Yo-kai must've done this!
You mean me?!
Watch! What time is it?
Emergency o'clock!
Whis!
Yo-there, yo-there, yo-there, yo-there
There's Yo-kai about, so don't go out
Alojoi, alojoi, join along in the fun
Make some friends!
Yo-kai, Yo-kai, Yo-kai
Watch-tch-tchee!
Kai kai kii kii
Kui kui kei kei
Come on Yo-kai
Watch-tch-tchee!