A-B-C-D-E-F-G
H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P
Q-R-S-T-U-V-W
X-Y and Z
Now you know your ABCs
Isn't it bizarre, the way we string together
letters from A to Z?
Whether it be out loud or by text,
let's find something to talk about!
How will the world end? What's for dinner?
Let's share those moments of laughter and tears
I decide what I like and hate
But that too is a barrier I can break down
Don't you see? Our words make us who we are
There's something I want to talk about with you
Just thinking about that gets me all giddy
Whether you're right next to me or not
You always brighten up my day
Of all the things you've spoken to me
I cherish every last word
It feels good to think about somebody
And it feels good to put that into words
carpe diem
Carpe diem.
If I miss this chance,
it may never bless me again.
So I must seize the day while it lasts.
I have to seize each day
so I can live without regrets!
Yeah! That's what I'm gonna do!
"Carpe diem"
is my new life's motto!
Carpe diem!
Coming!
Oh, hey Moon!
Huh?!
James!
Aah, I'm so, so happy we met, James!
Wh-What's wrong?
I want to seize this encounter with you
while it lasts. As they say, carpe diem!
O-Okay. Not sure what that means,
but come on in.
I just got a new video game
if you wanna play.
Here I come! Take that!
You won't beat me that easily!
Enjoying the game?
You sure look like it.
Huh? Is there something on my face?
Oh, no. It just hit me, I've never seen the face
you make when you're focused on a game before!
What?
Come to think of it, I don't think I've
ever stared at you up close before!
I... really don't like being stared at.
Can you overlook it please?
O-Oh right!
I could go for a bath!
Okay! I'll wait here!
Don't! I'm very meticulous,
so I'll be in there for ages!
You can just head out when you're done
with the game, alright? Au revoir !
Man. Something's off about him today.
Want some help washing
your back?
Aagh! What the heck? Non merci, please!
No need to be shy.
We're both guys, so you have
nothing to be worried about.
Get out of here!!
What's your problem?!
I'm sorry, but can you blame me?
You can't just walk in on me like that.
Don't worry — I'm making an exquisite dish
that'll turn your mood around!
You should've said so sooner!
I'll help you cook! Oh-ho-ho!
You really don't have to!
Then I'll stay here and watch!
It's ready! James-style Italian pasta!
I added lots of cilantro for you!
Oh, you want some cheese?
Shoot! I forgot Moon hates cilantro!
Sorry! I can make you a new one!
This is so good! Ulp!
A-Are you sure?
You went out of your way
to make me this!
I won't complain about it!
You don't have to eat it...
But I have to seize this moment too!
I may never meet this cilantro again!
Unbelievable...
Thank you, James!
That tasted amazing!
I'll never forget it as long as I live!
That's a little dramatic...
Are you home, Cony?
Hey, Moon! Check this out!
This just came in.
It trains your inner muscles.
It's supposed to help you lose weight!
One, two! One, two!
What's with the stare-down?
Do you wanna give it a try?
Oh, sure!
Go ahead.
Ack! What just happened?!
Don't spread your legs so wide!
Close them!
That's hilarious.
You're such a ditz, Moon!
Cony...
You mad? You know I'm right... Huh?
Thanks for that. It was real fun.
Uh, what's wrong?
Nothing. I'm just fine.
I see. You scared me for a sec.
All this exercise is making me thirsty!
Can you get me something to drink?
Here you go! It's calorie-free!
Huh?! Normally you would've gotten mad at me...
Are you sure you're alright?
Maybe you have a fever.
I must seize this day
while it lasts! Carpe diem!
Uh, parfait what now?
Ugh, thanks for that.
Now I'm craving a strawberry parfait!
Wanna come with?
Alas, I'm running out of time.
Goodbye!
What was that about?
Ouch, that smarts...
What's a rock doing here?!
Why, you...!
Brown, I didn't see you there!
You were taking a nap?
Talk about a real chance encounter!
If I hadn't tripped here,
I would'a walked right past you!
Ain't that something, Brown?
I'm so glad we met! Whoo!
Hold up!
I can't forget about the rock.
If I hadn't met this,
I wouldn't have met you.
This really is its own special encounter!
Thank you, Brown!
You too, little rock!
We'll meet again!
See you!
Ow!
Watch where you're going!
Excuse me?
Hold on. This, too, is an encounter...
Are you hurt, good sir?
Huh?
Our meeting is no happenstance.
It's a miracle on our planet,
nay, in this galaxy!
I'm sorry?
Oh? Is that Moon?
The chance of the Siding Spring comet
colliding with Mars is 1/250,000.
And a meteorite large enough to wipe out the dinosaurs
only hit Earth once in 100 million years.
It's possible those are the same odds
that we would run into each other today,
making this nothing short of a miracle.
I see?
Really? I wonder what's gotten into him.
Something is up with him.
I just know it.
He said some weird stuff to me earlier.
Like "I won't forget this as long as I live."
Oh yeah. He told me he was
"running out of time."
Huh? He told you "we'll meet again?"
What's going on?
He's acting like he's leaving us for good.
Maybe he is.
It sounds a lot like he is
saying farewell to you all.
Huh? Farewell?!
Yes. He must be leaving Line Town soon.
Aah, how could you, Moon?!
Why wouldn't you tell us directly?!
Maybe he was so sad
he couldn't get himself to.
Phew. I feel like I really seized the day.
It's from James.
"I'm holding a party tonight.
Come on down, we're all waiting."
A party?
Come in!
What the?!
Juby-julee! The special guest has arrived!
Huh?!
What took you so long, Moon?
We were getting tired!
Come on, this way!
Here!
Wh-What kind of party is this?!
Don't worry about it.
Have some juice!
Cheers!
Huh?
Huh?!
This is a present from me to you!
Say what?
This one's from me!
This is from the both of us!
Wait, hold on. I didn't get you guys anything.
It's a farewell party.
You don't need to give us anything.
A farewell party?
For who?
Wait...
What?
What?! It's for me?
I'm sorry I didn't notice, Moon...
It didn't occur to me you had come
to say goodbye earlier.
Please don't forget about us, Moon.
Kn-Knock it off already!
Oh, I see. So you were just inspired by a movie.
Thanks for misleading us, dude.
You better give back your presents!
You misled yourselves!
It's a pretty normal takeaway
from your weird behavior.
But I'm glad you're staying for real.
Of course I am.
Where am I supposed to go?
I made strawberry parfaits!
Awesome!
Yum!
Carpe is overrated—parfaits are where it's at!
Same here!
Hi-yah!
Yeah! That's what I'm gonna do!
"Don't think, feel"
is my new life's motto!
Hi-yah!
happiness
This man is the star
of tonight's special.
He spotted the blue butterfly,
a rare specimen said for generations
to bring happiness to people.
Since then, happiness and success
have blessed him many times,
earning him the name
of the happiest man in Line Town.
Perhaps you will be the next person
to be graced by the blue butterfly!
That was a nice special!
I gotta find that blue butterfly!
Blue butterfly, oh blue butterfly...
Oh blue butterfly!
Oh, hi Cony! I take it you saw
last night's special too?
Sure did! You too?
Of course!
Hey guys! Are you looking for bonheur too?
Let's go find that blue butterfly together!
Yeah!
I hope I find the blue butterfly
and it grants me eternal beauty!
I want to buy out a clothes store!
I can't decide what I want most!
Brown! Sally!
Are you all looking for the
blue butterfly of happiness too?
Didn't think you two would be here too!
I was just taking a walk,
and Brown asked if I wanted to come along.
You brought quite a lot there, Brown.
That can't be necessary.
What is this, an overseas trip?
Hey, how about we all work together
to find the butterfly?
Yeah!
I think the blue butterfly
might show up here!
Right, it'll come here to suck the nectar!
Blue butterfly, oh blue butterfly!
Papillon bleu !
Blue butterfly!
That one's yellow...
No sign of it.
What's wrong, Jessica?
L-Look over there.
Oh? Calm down, everyone.
Take a look.
Honey, that tickles... Stop it...
Honey who?
I'm so happy...
Did he catch the blue butterfly
in his dream?
Where are ya,
blue butterfly?!
You awake now?
Uh, hey, guys.
Why were you sleeping out here, Moon?
Last night, I saw this special
and came out here to look for the blue butterfly!
But I forgot to bring my butterfly net.
...And then I got lost,
and now I'm starving.
Then I passed out here.
So you went out without a plan?
That checks out.
You'll lend me your net, Brown?
Thanks, Brown. How 'bout we go
catch us some happiness?
Alright, guys!
Let's look for the blue butterfly!
And no secrets! If you find it,
you alert the rest of us, kapeesh?
Like you're one to talk!
You better alert us, ya hear?!
There it is!
Wait, what? Where?
Where is it?
Oh shoot.
What the heck, man?
It was there, I swear!
Now, Moon, look closer.
That's no blue butterfly—
it's an aqua butterfly.
Seriously?!
I'm sorry, Brown!
Can you lend me another one?
I'll pay you back!
Why thank you, Brown.
I'll remember your deeds
for the rest of my weekdays.
Blue butterfly? Oh blue butterfly?
Blue butterfly! Blue butterfly!
Blue butterfly, blue butterfly
Blue butterfly! Oh blue butterfly!
Papillon bleu !
Where are you, blue butterfly?
I'm so thirsty...
Is there a vending machine nearby?
Out here in the mountains?
Don't count on it.
Dang, Brown! You brought so many!
Are you sure we can have them?
Thanks, Brown!
Thanks a ton!
That hits the spot!
Let's go home.
What do you mean go home?!
Well, we kinda gotta stop here.
Gotta stop? More like you got bored of it.
He has a point though, Cony.
We should really head back before the sun sets.
Aww, but I thought we'd get to be blessed
by the blue butterfly together!
Huh? You'll keep searching on your own?
Good idea. You're far more
prepared than the rest of us.
Are you sure?
Take care, Brown!
I feel bad making him do this alone...
I'm gonna stay and help!
Cony, wait up!
Oh, let her. She'd probably go
even if we stopped her.
I'm sure she'll be safe with Brown.
I just hope she doesn't
cause a burden to him.
Guess who!
Hey, look at the grassland!
What if the butterfly's down there?
Oh, yeah.
I stayed behind so I could help you!
Come on, let's go check!
Sorry, Brown.
We couldn't find it at all.
You're right! We've got happiness
to catch for everyone!
So we better find that blue butterfly!
I got a grass cut on my finger!
Thank you, Brown...
I'm so glad I'm with you.
Good thinking, Brown!
Now we can get through the grass!
But we still can't find it.
And now I'm hungry.
Everyone else is probably having
a yummy dinner at home about now...
Oh wow, canned dinners!
Great thinking, Brown!
Let's make this a feast!
It's gonna be so fun!
I'm stuffed...
Now I'm getting sleepy.
Brown, you're amazing!
Don't mind if I do.
Hup!
Oh my, sorry. I must've eaten too much.
Now hold on. This is no camping trip.
We're here to find the blue butterfly!
Yay! We're finally out of the grassland!
Now I feel like having a late-night picnic!
The night breeze feels so good!
Why me?!
Head back? But I can't even walk!
You'll carry me?
That's the North Star?
And it'll lead us back to Line Town?
Thank you, Brown...
Blue butterfly...
Oh blue butterfly...
of happiness...
Blue butterfly...
That was a good rest.
Wait!
What the heck?
Why was I asleep on Brown?
Oh right. I sprained my ankle.
You must've carried me a long way, Brown.
Thank you, Brown.
I feel a lot better now.
I had a really good dream!
I saw the blue butterfly fluttering
and dancing about in the sky.
But it felt so lifelike!
I can't help but wonder if it actually happened.
Eh, doesn't matter.
'Cause I realize now
I'm happy either way!
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
I dreamt I was flying through the night sky
mahou no juutan ni notte
On a magic carpet
tondeku yozora no yume
And I just wanted you to see it
kimi ni mo
kimi ni mo misetakute
misetai
Oh, did I wake you? I'm so sorry
okoshichatta kana? gomen ne
I thought you sounded half-asleep
neboketa kotobatachi ni
And it made me swoon
nandaka
nandaka kyun to kita
kyun kyun
Just like the glittering scent of rose tea
kirameku kaori no roozu tii mitai ni
When my heart starts pounding, I lock up
dokidoki no sono shunkan
tojikomeru
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
Even though I could just type a <3 and send it to you
yubisaki haato wo nosete
tsutawattara ii no ni
It's hard to sum up the way I feel for you
kimi e no kono kimochi
hitokoto ja tarinai
It's like a millefeuille
egao mo namida mo zenbu
With all of my smiles and tears mixed in
tsumikasaneta mirufiiyu
I feel happy, I feel painful
ureshii setsunai itoshii
I feel longing — I'm in love
koishiteru
errand
clones
Next time on Line Town...
We have a situation!
Clones of Cony came out from her nose!
You heard me.
errand
clones
That's right—clones from her nose!
Cony clones came from her nose!
Nose clones!
Tune in next time!