This is Snack World, the hallowed ground
of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam
and people have handy smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
And my name's Chup!
My village was burnt down by
the evil land-destroying merchant Vinegar Khan,
so I've embarked on a journey
to get my revenge 1000-fold!
At last, my journey has brought me
close to Vinegar.
In order to defeat him, I will overcome
any impossible mission that comes my way!
Alright, let's go on another big adventure today!
Episode 31: The Test of the Dragon Knight—Come at Me, Tough Guy!
What was that?!
Another one of Vinegar's goons?
Oh, it's just you, Sir Darefalcon.
Thought you were Vinegar.
I'm going back to sleep.
Up with you!
Tell me, what time is it?
What is it?
8:00.
Got it. Five more minutes.
I'm telling you to get up!!
Surely you know from today on
begins your Dragon Knight training?!
Shoot, you're right!
But I told you that breakfast begins at 6 A.M.!
Since you couldn't make up your minds,
I made both the hot spring eggs
and the omelette and waited for your arrival!
Ouch, you really peeved him off...
Chup, you would best apologize.
My sincerest apologies,
Sir Darefalcon!
So, is there any egg and omelette left?
The Dragon Brothers ate all of it.
Aww...
I would prefer they be eaten
when they're freshly hot.
Man...
Didn't think you were the picky type.
Wait, did Vinsant get to eat?
He did not appear either.
That's a relief.
How is that a relief?
He asked so little of you,
and neither of you showed up!
I would be mad too if I were him.
Where could Vinsant have gone off to?
There you are! What are you doing?
Boiling pork bone soup.
Pork bone soup?
Princess Melora messaged me
on SnaLine last night...
Vinny, can I have pork bones tomorrow morning?
vinny! can i have
pork bones tomorrow
morning? <3 <3
Princess Melora
Pretty please!
So, let me guess. You spent all night boiling that
and forgot to meet with Darefalcon?
Sniff sniff...
Not yet! These pork bones need more time!
Attention!
Listen here.
Do you desire to be Dragon Knights?
Yeah...
Yes.
Look at people when they're talking to you!
Can't you tell you've made Darefalcon mad?
Not anymore.
Huh?
I can sense it.
Their words, their souls...
They speak no lies.
Yeah...
Yes.
Doesn't sound like you're taking this seriously at all.
Not that we'd understand this stuff,
but this might be what he meant by purity.
It's lookin' more and more like
they'll be able to take down Vinegar!
Is that what you think?
The road to becoming a Dragon Knight...
that is, the Way of the Dragon,
invokes battling fierce enemies
and raising your rank
by bringing out your feral strain
from deep within.
Who will we be battling?
Several people from various places
around the world.
I'll stamp your card
for each you defeat.
So that's how becoming a Dragon Knight works?
I'm here!
Princess Melora! Is everything okay?
I really should've gotten a treatment at the castle.
Now my skin feels so dry...
So let's go home together!
Home?
Sorry, Princess. We have training to do...
Hold on.
Could one of the various places
we're going possibly be...?
Indeed, French Toaster.
What?!
There's a tough guy in French Toaster?
Who is it?
Maybe it's Cinderella!
Oh, yeah! Maybe!
Can we please get going, Darey-kins?
Darey-kins?
Surely you're overstepping your boundaries
giving him a cute nickname.
Huh? You don't mind, do you, Darey-kins?
I could get used to it.
I envy him...
Give me a nickname too!
I wanna be Chuppy-kins!
What happened to the guy
prepared to become a warrior?
Also, with all due respect, Darefalcon,
surely it wouldn't kill you
to knock some sense into her just once?
I couldn't possibly say no to Princess Melora.
What's going on here?
The legendary Darefalcon
has fallen head over hells for that broad.
Off we go.
Time to take the Transcontinental Railroad?
That won't be necessary.
Huh?
Destination: French Toaster!
Dragon Warp!
I recognize this street!
We made it to French Toaster
in the blink of an eye!
Hooray, what a breeze!
Do not worry.
You will be the only ones
who can see me.
Now, I shall show the way.
Your first opponent is...
Oh, Shibuchin!
Did you come to greet me?
You really had to go, huh?
Welcome back, Princess.
Happy to be home!
Let us head to the castle.
His majesty awaits.
Okay!
See you all again!
You did say no one else could see you...
But it certainly felt like Shibuchin could.
Animals and monsters have much better
sensitivity than humans.
So perhaps we can't rule out
that Shibuchin could tell he was there.
Oh, wow! Darefalcon,
you really took a hit from that, huh?
So, where's the first tough guy we're up against?
Huh?
Carbonara's Weapons?!
Hey, good to see ya, Chup!
It's been some time.
Hey, Mr. Carbonara!
What are you in for today?
Weapons, snacks?
Your toughest tough guy, please!
You want a tough guy?
You can have it!
Pinocchio!
Coming.
So Pinocchio's the tough guy
they're fighting?
Ugh, not you guys...
Always waltzing in with empty wallets
and looking poor.
I see you haven't changed.
Just as rude and snarky as ever!
Sorry, I can't help it.
I only speak the truth!
Hm? One second...
Uh, what?
Did they mess up your face in surgery?
As if!
He lost to Mayone...
He's not looking too tough right now.
Not the robot. That man.
Say what?!
Mr. Carbonara's the tough guy?
He's just a greedy old man.
Knock it off. Who are you kids talking to?
Young warriors. Look at him with your soul.
The truth lies deep in his heart.
What on earth?
Badges?
Oh, my bad.
I must've left on my
beigoma grand champion badges.
You're a beigoma...
...grand champion?
Well, cat's out of the bag.
Guess I'll brag a little.
I'm a pro beigoma player—
or as they say, a beigomer.
I'm a legend who's won the World Championship
five years in a row and counting.
Not to brag.
That was definition bragging...
You weren't even wearing those badges before.
Five years in a row?
You must be a real tough player!
Does that mean we must
battle him in beigoma?
Trial I: Beigoma Showdown with Carbonara.
Did I hear that right?
You wish to beigoma battle with me?
Knock yourselves out.
This will be your grave.
That was a fast catch!
Don't make me laugh.
I will come out on top.
I'm gonna fully, flawlessly win!
You couldn't even catch it.
Get them, my beigoma!
Oh no, our beigoma!
Ouch, he wiped the floor with them.
Hmph. You thought you could take me on
with those skills?
Dang it...
Let us fight you one more time!
As you wish.
As it happens, they're hosting
the next Championship
right here in French Toaster tomorrow.
Huh?
That will be our stage.
Alright!
So you'll have to get better by tomorrow?
If we must!
Indeed.
I respect your passion for beigoma,
so I'll let you in on something.
Master of the cord and the cold
is master of the beigoma.
"Master of the cord and the cold
is master of the beigoma"...
By cord, I assume he means
the one around the top?
If you can handle the cord
the way you want,
I reckon you could make the tops
battle the way you desire.
Handle the cords the way we want...
I have an idea!
Time to call a friend!
Candoll!
Wonder-la-la-la-la-la
Wa-la-la-la-la-la
Wonder
Why Candoll?
What'chu want?
Candoll, teach me the way you whip!
The way I whip?
I get it! If he can handle a whip
the way Candoll does,
then he should be able to launch
a beigoma at his will!
Pretty please, with a cherry on top?
Sure thing. I'll teach you
whatever you want to know.
Sweet!
However...
It won't be a quick skill to master.
Gulp...
Okay. So a whip is a living creature.
You must become one with it,
and use it gracefully...
Like this!
Awesome!
Give it a try.
Okay!
I did it!
We mastered it!
Way to go!
Well done.
Candoll!
You've perfected your whip.
Thank you!
Next, we need to master the cold.
The cold?
You'll want to find a monster
called Sylph-san in the woods.
She should teach you what you need to know.
Sir Darefalcon,
take us to the woods!
Okay. Destination: forest!
Dragon Warp!
Candoll, I'm making stew for tonight!
Oh? Hey, Master Panpan!
I guess he's not on the run anymore
and moved in with Candoll!
Why do they look like a happy family photo?
Can someone please push me...?
Let's look for Sylph-san!
Hold on, we don't have any leads.
How are we supposed to find her in this big forest?
Hey, Sylph-san! Come on out!
Please, like that's going to...
I'm here!
Did you call me?
She came out like it was nothing!
Are you a monster
that controls the cold?
That's right! I'm Sylph-san!
Sylph-san
Wait, where are you going?
Sorry, I let the cold get the best of me!
Are you sure we can rely on her?
Seems like the cold winds
are controlling her if you ask me.
I'm sorry? Are you badmouthing me?
You heard all that?
I was trying to whisper...
I can hear every whisper through the cold winds!
That's creepy.
But amazing!
You really can control the cold!
That's right, I can control the cold!
I can also control the colds!
Huh?
You can control the cold winds, right?
That's right! I can control the cold,
but I can also control the colds!
Why are you repeating yourself?
Just see for yourself!
I feel so sick all of a sudden...
D-Don't tell me...
Yep! I controlled the colds
and gave them to you!
You make people sick?
That's what you meant by the colds?
I wouldn't wanna make her mad...
Y-Yeah...
What's wrong, you guys?
Did the cold not get to you?
The cold? Are you all sick?
Oh, wow! So colds really do exist!
Have you never gotten one, Chup?
Nope!
So you're the kind that manages to avoid it...
Huh?
Did it not affect you either, Darefalcon?
Wait a minute...
I am a holy dragon.
Why would I get sick?
Of course, that's what I figured...
Shoot.
Chup, we have to hurry,
or we won't be ready by the tournament!
Right!
Sylph-san, can you teach us
how to control the cold?
Can do!
Yay!
Please make this quick.
Let's see...
You do this, then this, then this!
That certainly teaches us nothing.
This, this, and this!
So close, but not right!
It's this, then this, then this!
This, this, and this!
No! This, then this, then this!
This...
...then this...
...then this!
You did "that" very well,
but maybe do it more like this.
This, then this, then this.
You think they'll actually
master the cold by tomorrow?
Who knows...
This...
...then this...
...then this!
You're almost there!
This, then this, then this!
Thi—
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The winner of the
6th World Beigoma Championship is...
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
The 6th
World Beigoma
Tournament
Mr. Carbonara!
For the sixth year running!
Wait right there!
Hmm?
Hmph. So you came.
We're gonna fully, flawlessly win this time!
I hope you're prepared, Carbonara!
Alright.
A round of applause for these boys
brave enough to take me on!
I accept your challenge.
I hope they can win...
After all that, our colds only got worse,
and they weren't able to master
controlling the cold.
They'll have to rely on their whipping skills.
Carbonara Thunder Spin!
It's Candoll!
He's possessing them!
No, that's not it.
He's just watching from behind!
Well, well.
Go!
Knock 'em out!
We're not done yet!
There we go!
Strike back!
I'm impressed.
But I can feel it...
The cold winds of victory.
Now!
The gust of wind is speeding up his top!
It's approaching Vinsant's top!
Vinsant lost!
Raise your head, Vinsant!
I won't give up!
I'm... no, we're gonna be Dragon Knights!
And I'm gonna win
to see that happen!
Chup...
Yes... You're right, Chup.
You've got this, Chup!
Yeah!
You're all talk.
It's time to face reality!
This, then this, then this!
Vinsant's sneeze took the win...
He controlled the cold...
Ch-Chup is the victor!
No way...
I did it!
Hip, hip, hooray!
shobokure gao no mobukyara domo ga
On and on these tired old NPCs
iiwake shinagara aruiteru
Keep walking around excusing themselves
itsumo miteiru michisugara
As I took the same old path again
mita koto mo nai wakuwaku wo mita
I found the thrill I've sought for my whole life
itsumade shibonda mama nano
Just how long will I keep drooping around like this?
minikui ahiru no mama nano
How long will I stay an ugly duckling?
ima no reberu wa ichi dakedo
I'm still only level one
ima ni mitero yo sono uchi JUMP UP
But watch me, soon I'll jump up
saikin no wakai mon wa tte
"Why, kids these days..."
toshiyori domo ga boyai teru kedo
...Our old boomers grumble and complain
soro soro omei henjou da
But it's not too late to clear my name
iya ga ou ni mo mattanashi daze
I might not like it, but I can't wait any longer
ketsu no ana kara jetto funsha daaa
I gotta blast free from my cowardly shell!!
ore wa itsuka hana ni naru
Give me time and I'll bloom like a flower
sora ni nobiru hana ni naru
A flower spread out to the sky
kimi ni todoku hana ni naru
The flower that reaches you
Are you hanging in there?
Yeah.
Good job out there, Chup.
Couldn't have done it without ya!
It's like my grandmother said!
You can't make an omurice
without breaking a few eggs!
You can't make
an omurice
without breaking
a few eggs.
If the flag
stands up,
it's a good omen.
You can't make
an omurice
without breaking
a few eggs.
If the flag
stands up,
it's a good omen.
If the flag stands straight up,
it's a good omen!
-Tome
I'm pretty sure that's tea stalks...
But hey, you won in the end!
And that's a good omen.
Huh?
You've bested me.
Mr. Carbonara!
Please take this.
The prize from this year's championships:
the Dettonic Axe.
Thank you so much!
Hey, look! An axe!
Yep, it definitely suits you better.
I can have it?
Of course!
I'm so happy!
I finally have a brand new axe.
This shine, this weight...
it's all just so beautiful!
Hey, Pepperon! Your nose is dripping!
That's just from the cold.
Good work.
Oh yeah, the stamp!
Here you go!
You've magnificently cleared
Trial I of becoming a Dragon Kni—
You really did catch a cold!
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone!
What are you teaching us about today?
Today's lesson is on Yamajeni-Inn!
Yamajeni-Inn
Yamajeni-Inn is an inn in French Toaster
run by Jennifer Yamamoto.
She cooks the most delicious meals!
Chup used to work at Yamajeni-Inn.
Yep! She gave me my favorite outfit!
She's the best, I love her!
Next Time
Tough guys are coming out in swarms!
We're starting with a dance battle!
Oh, yeah!
Then we're doing a cooking battle!
Our opponent is...
Huh, Ms. Yamamoto?!
A Battle for the Ages?! Jennifer Yamamoto!
Next time:
"A Battle for the Ages?! Jennifer Yamamoto!"
Alright, time for a big adventure!