A-B-C-D-E-F-G
H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P
Q-R-S-T-U-V-W
X-Y and Z
Now you know your ABCs
Isn't it bizarre, the way we string together
letters from A to Z?
Whether it be out loud or by text,
let's find something to talk about!
How will the world end? What's for dinner?
Let's share those moments of laughter and tears
I decide what I like and hate
But that too is a barrier I can break down
Don't you see? Our words make us who we are
There's something I want to talk about with you
Just thinking about that gets me all giddy
Whether you're right next to me or not
You always brighten up my day
Of all the things you've spoken to me
I cherish every last word
It feels good to think about somebody
And it feels good to put that into words
old man
Whew!
Today's the best day for a barbecue!
I gotta get some grub in my tum!
Are these all the veggies?
I'm pretty sure I have some fresh farm corn.
I'll go get it!
Hmm, corn, corn, corn...
What could that be?
Here they are!
Thanks a ton!
Huh? Sally?!
What?
Where'd that corn run off to?
Right here, of cornse!
Get it?
What the heck?
Dad jokes in an old man get-up?
That's hilarious!
Look how a-maize-ing this corn is!
Get it?
This corn's the cream of the crop!
S-Sally, I think we get it.
Got any corn jokes? I'm all ears!
Get it?
Since we laughed at one of them,
she just keeps going...
Just like a real old man.
The barbecue!
Hey, it's not all burnt!
Yeah! Let's eat up!
Yay, barbecue!
So good!
Dang, overcooked meat tastes super good!
You really shouldn't eat so fast.
When will we meat again?
Get it?
Hey, uhh...
Wow, isn't this corn just the best?
"You think so? Aw, shucks!"
Get it?
Don't enable her, James.
S-Sorry...
What's gotten into you, Sally?
What do you mean?
You're acting like an old man.
You want an old man? I'm your man!
Get it?
Thanks for having me over!
Ciao, good-diós!
Is it just me, or is Sally acting strange?
Did she get food poisoning or something?
I'm sure she'll be back to normal by tomorrow.
She didn't change!!
Of course they won this game.
If anything, it feels like
she's leaning even harder into this.
Sally, it's pretty sunny outside!
Want to come with us to an outdoor café?
An outdoor bar?
No, a café!
A bar?
I said a café!!
That's how an old man reacts
when a young girl gets upset at him...
Her pose is filled with sorrow.
Sally's turning into an old man?
She was acting up yesterday.
But she's acting even worse today!
Right, Cony?
Yeah...
Sally?
Ay-o! Sorry, can't talk right now,
got places to be!
Like where?
Thought I'd go take a dip.
Take a dip?
Sure am!
Gonna take a hot bath
and sip a cold one!
What a thrill!
You see?
No kidding...
She really is an old man.
If this keeps up,
it's only a matter of time
before she's all pops and no Sally!
Why is this happening to her?
It'd be one thing if she were an old lady,
but she's an old man.
This goes beyond even her gender.
I'll look it up...
...in my expansive beauty database at home!
There might be something
about this phenomenon!
Mind helping me, Brown?
In the meantime, we'll keep
Sally's old man-ness at bay!
How though?
Uh, how, Moon?
Hey, don't ask me!
It was your idea!
Oh?
It's Sally in her favorite skirt.
You want us to remind her
that she likes girly things?
Good thinking, Brown!
Nice idea!
Let's bring back Sally's ladylike heart!
Yeah!
Mister—I mean, Sally!
What's it?
Sally, put this on!
Huh? No way, José!
Why not?
It's your favorite!
Hey, I don't wear skirts!
Don't skirt the line!
Get it?
Hang in there!
Don't let her dad jokes get to you!
How about these?
They're your favorite shoes!
Oh, shoo off! My fit fits me just fine!
Get it?
She's laughing at her own bad jokes...
I don't think I can take much more!
Her dad jokes are a real mighty force.
We'll just have to dress her ourselves!
Sally, calm down and just put it on!
Stop fighting, don't resist!
Aww, you're adorable!
Is she now?
O-Okay, you're right,
this isn't working.
She looks like she's crossdressing.
It's not crossdressing, she's a girl!
Right!
Sally, you're a girl!
You have to remember!
What's that now?
I remember!
You do?
I was off to go take a dip.
'Twas early day, as poets say
Just when the sun was rising
Ugh... Sally...
Guys, I figured it out!
Wait, really?!
Sally's become an old man
because of those Groucho glasses!
The Groucho glasses?
Yeah!
They're from an online store:
the Old Man Groucho Glasses,
which can easily make an old man out of anyone!
"Anyone can be an old man,
"and so can you!"
What the heck is this?
Why would Sally have it?
Because I bought them!
I thought it would be real funny
if I stuck them on Moon during a party!
But I forgot all about them,
so Sally must've stumbled upon them at the barbecue,
and then put them on without thinking!
What a stinker.
Yeah, for us!
Moon's right! It's your fault, isn't it?
I suppose you could look at it that way.
Quit playing cool!
Calm down, you guys.
So how do we turn Sally back into a girl?
A dip and a cold one, gotta have it.
If we can just get those glasses off,
she should turn back to normal!
Mister—I mean, Sally!
What'cha want with me?
Sally, you have to take those glasses off!
Why?
It'll stop you from becoming an old man!
Becoming?
You're on track to be an old man for real!
Fine with me!
Huh?!
Old men take ages to get things done!
Get it?
Sally, you don't really want
to be an old man, do you?
Why shouldn't I be?
I mean, you can...
Being an old man is as fun as pie!
Get it?
Like "easy as pie,"
but it's "fun" instead!
Being an old man is fun?
I guess I could see the appeal...
They're always practicing their golf swings
at the train station and during their breaks.
And pitching imaginary baseballs.
They're kind of...innocent, in a way?
They're able to make fun out of nothing.
That's probably where those dad jokes come from.
Yeah!
What a sight.
I think if someone asked me
what I wanted to be in the future...
I might just say an old man!
Me too! I want to be one!
Then let's do it!
Let's all become old men!
Yeah!
Fun as pie...
This is the life.
Ack. Can't see a thing.
What the?
Why am I in a bath?
Guys!
I baked a cake!
Want to come over and have some?
Nothing better than caking a bake!
Get it?
Wh-Wh-What?
What's going on?
My bed's lost its sheets!
My cat's not kitten around!
My curry's in a stew!
Get it?
Whaaat?!
Get it?!
beach
Yay, the beach!
We're here at last!
Blue skies, blue seas!
Nothing beats it!
Oh, where's James?
Not far behind!
James!
What's that get-up?
I'm a prince of a desert kingdom!
When I'm on the beach..
I relax elegantly...
and gorgeously!
Elegantly? Really?
It goes beyond the fashion.
Parasol!
Chair!
And everything else!
There's no other way to enjoy
a shoreside resort!
Wow, you really pulled out all the stops!
It's the gorgeous way to go!
So tropical!
You're really committed to this.
Take that! Yeah! Go!
We're on the beach.
What's with the video game?
I just thought it was nice
to play it somewhere spacious.
Take that!
Brown, let's go swim!
Yay!
This feels great!
Take that, ha-ha!
Is that all you're gonna do?!
Away it goes!
No!
What was that for?!
You little...
You asked for it!
Take that! And that!
James! Come on, join us!
Non non, I'll pass.
But why?
The prince of the desert
needs not swim—
he enjoys the salty smell
and the nice breeze all the well.
Roast squid? It's ink-redibly good!
Get it?
Don't give me that!
James, come in the water!
Think fast! I'm taking this out to sea!
Hey, that's mine!
Get back here!
This ship waits for no man!
Wait up!
Dear me, this sunlight is strong...
If my skin gets burnt in its rays...
Aah! I'm so ugly!
Anything but that!
James, what are you doing...?
Dude, you swim in the water,
not the sand.
I-I wasn't swimming!
Just having one of those daydreams.
We're gonna go play beach volleyball!
Wanna join?
In this sunlight?
My fair white skin will crumble!
Oh, come on. We need you so
we can have even teams of two.
Join us, will ya?
No means no!
Like it or not, underneath this parasol
is where I belong!
Well, that stinks.
Let's just play without him.
There!
Hyah!
Nice pass, Brown!
Cony... attack!
Juby-julee!
What's the big idea?!
Sorry, James!
It's Cony's fault. She stinks at this!
No, it's yours, you didn't receive my shot!
How am I supposed to?!
D-Don't worry about it...
Why not relax elegantly like me?
Juby-julee!
Oh, come on, guys!
Sorry!
Y'see what happens when it's 2-vs-1?
It'd be a lot more fun
if you played with us, James!
Fine, I'll do it, okay?
Yay!
Our plan worked!
However...
I must prepare first.
I am ready.
J-James, what the heck?
You're really gonna play like that?
I must, if I wish to protect
my fair white skin!
I... see.
Behold!
The desert prince's special
Sandstorm Serve!
And...!
Aah, you're flying away!
Juby-julee!
O-Oh no! I'm exposed!
I need help!!
James! Are you alright?
Jessica! Sally!
We got a lot of seafood
at the harbor!
You guys wanna have some?
This stuff is great!
Thanks so much, Jessica and Sally!
You're welcome! I'm glad you like it!
I almost got sunburned back there...
Thanks for saving me!
Of course.
What'cha wanna do when we're done?
I think I'll go for a swim!
I wanna ride on the boat
with Jessica and Sally!
How about you, James?
I have more elegant relaxation ahead of me.
Hello! Would you be interested
in sea collecting?
What's that?
You go snorkeling in the rocky area just nearby.
It's a very beautiful experience.
You can see all sorts of fish!
We have gear you can rent too!
Sounds like fun!
I'm sold!
Let's do it!
You too, James!
Sure, if I won't get sunburned!
This is great!
Hey, that's my turban snail!
I took it first!
Huh?! Oh no!
Aah! I'm doomed!
I'm gonna get sunburned!
That was so much fun!
Wait, where's James?
Huh?
Yeah, when's he gonna come up?
It's just me!
James!
Désolé! I didn't want to get sunburned!
You still care that much about it?
Uh-huh, I see how it is.
What?
It never had to do with
getting sunburned at all.
You just can't swim!
Am I right, Seaweed Monster?
Seaweed Monster?!
That's ridiculous. I can swim!
In fact, I can swim better
than anyone else!
You're all talk.
I mean it!
Then let's prove it!
I can't let him insult me like this,
it hurts my pride!
But I can't get sunburned!
Wait, he can't swim?
With a face like that?
He really can't, huh?
Some man he is.
Stinks to be him.
I accept your challenge!
First one to that lighthouse wins.
The loser treats the winner
to a frozen mango yogurt on our way home.
Deal?
Deal.
Thanks in advance for the yogurt.
No, thank you!
Alright, on your marks!
Ready, set... go!
Juby!
Good luck!
Aah! I didn't think you'd be so fast!
I told you so! See ya at the finish line!
What the heck?!
James, watch out!
There's a shark in the water!
A shark?!
No way.
Get away, James!
Well? Still think I can't swim?
What?! No one said there were sharks out here!
We have to help him!
I know! Get some of the leftover fish!
Oh, I see! You want to use it
to lure the shark away!
Hey, shark! Over here!
Get away from James!
Wait a minute!
What?!
Oh great! You drew in a bunch more of them!
James, get out of there!
Which way is out?!
Aah! Stay away from meee!
Say what?
Really? They just have weirdly
large dorsal fins...
That was terrifying.
Phew... I'm safe now...
Thanks, Brown!
Huh? What is it?
Gah!
The horror! The horror!
On second thought, I kinda like it!
I look like a super hero.
You bounced back quick!
Well, I got to swim a ton,
have lots of fun,
and really enjoy the beach!
That's the spirit!
Gotta make the best of a beach trip!
Embrace the tan!
Did you make great memories?
Yeah! Very fun memories!
Okay!
Next time we come, I'm gonna get
the hottest tan out there!
Oh yeah!
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
I dreamt I was flying through the night sky
mahou no juutan ni notte
On a magic carpet
tondeku yozora no yume
And I just wanted you to see it
kimi ni mo
kimi ni mo misetakute
misetai
Oh, did I wake you? I'm so sorry
okoshichatta kana? gomen ne
I thought you sounded half-asleep
neboketa kotobatachi ni
And it made me swoon
nandaka
nandaka kyun to kita
kyun kyun
Just like the glittering scent of rose tea
kirameku kaori no roozu tii mitai ni
When my heart starts pounding, I lock up
dokidoki no sono shunkan
tojikomeru
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
Even though I could just type a <3 and send it to you
yubisaki haato wo nosete
tsutawattara ii no ni
It's hard to sum up the way I feel for you
kimi e no kono kimochi
hitokoto ja tarinai
It's like a millefeuille
egao mo namida mo zenbu
With all of my smiles and tears mixed in
tsumikasaneta mirufiiyu
I feel happy, I feel painful
ureshii setsunai itoshii
I feel longing — I'm in love
koishiteru
big
small
Next time on Line Town...
Cony pulls through with her diet?
What's her weight now?
How about in apples?
Wait, half a strawberry?
But I weigh six strawberries!
big
small
How many apples does James weigh?
Huh?! Five hundred watermelons?
I can't-aloupe imagine that! Get it?