A-B-C-D-E-F-G
H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P
Q-R-S-T-U-V-W
X-Y and Z
Now you know your ABCs
Isn't it bizarre, the way we string together
letters from A to Z?
Whether it be out loud or by text,
let's find something to talk about!
How will the world end? What's for dinner?
Let's share those moments of laughter and tears
I decide what I like and hate
But that too is a barrier I can break down
Don't you see? Our words make us who we are
There's something I want to talk about with you
Just thinking about that gets me all giddy
Whether you're right next to me or not
You always brighten up my day
Of all the things you've spoken to me
I cherish every last word
It feels good to think about somebody
And it feels good to put that into words
dorothy
Hula, hula-hula
Hula-hula-hu-hu-hu!
Oh, it's Moon.
"We're going to the supermarket.
Need anything?"
Let me think...
Oh, got a response.
Huh? What the heck?
"TP, CJ, GA plz."
What does any of that mean?!
Make sense to you?
Huh? I'm not sure...
Ugh... Is it some new
shampoo brand?
It ain't shampoo!
"TP" means toilet paper.
TP
"CJ" means carrot juice.
CJ
"GA" means green asparagus.
GA
GL!
Oh, they're abbreviations.
Now I get it.
How are we supposed to tell?!
Oh, y'know. Abbreviating words
is just more convenient!
It's annoying to type out long phrases
like "toilet paper" and "green asparagus."
But if we don't understand,
you inevitably have to explain it anyways.
Is that not more annoying?
But you just learned three of them!
Which means I don't have to
explain them again.
That's a win for efficiency!
Is it really more efficient
to say "plz" instead of "please,"
and "GL" instead of "good luck?"
He's right.
When you're asking someone a favor,
it's not very polite to speak in abbreviations.
Dang, Moon, you sound like an old man!
Say what?!
It's the thought that counts.
You're a pain in the neck.
Jessica! SG?
What's wrong, Jessica?
Your hips are gigantic!
Oh no...
It's Dorothy the gossip!
I can't stand her...
Don't you know
to greet someone when you visit them?
Huh? I just did.
Are you saying my hearing has gone bad?
How rude.
I said no such thing.
Then repeat your greeting.
Huh?
Go on.
SG!
"Geez?" Show some respect!
Not "geez." "SG!"
SG
It's short for "'Sup, girl?"
Oh, dear.
Kids these days and their
"hip" abbreviations.
How hard is it to just say
"Hello, how are you?"
Come on now.
You like sales, don't you, old lady?
Who doesn't?
I'm sorry, "old lady?"
You will call me by my name!
W-Well, Dorothy...
Yes, hun?
My point is that abbreviations
are like sales.
You get your words 50% off!
Like a good bargain, yeah?
Oh, I understand...
Wait, no I don't! You don't sell words!
You're here, Cony!
Oh, Jessica...
Oh no! Did you get injured?
Not too bad. Just sprained it a little doing yoga.
Are you alright? It must hurt real bad.
Want my help with anything?
You're so kind.
I came here to pitch in myself.
You... came here to play baseball?
Of course not. I'm pitching in.
It means she's been helping me.
Oh, I get it. Then I'll help too!
Much appreciated!
Here, have one.
Hard candy, for you, hun!
Huh? Oh, uh... Thank you.
Scrub scrub, swiff swiff,
tidying up, tidying up...
Stop right there!
You have to move the furniture!
But I don't wanna!
It's so heavy.
You're still talking like that?
The phrase you're looking for is "don't want to!"
And this is nothing for me.
Now, go on! Knuckle down!
What's that mean?
It means less talky, more walky!
Fiiine.
Scrub scrub, scrub scrub, hup.
I can't believe Dorothy.
She W2B'd me!
Uh, what's that?
W2B: Work to the bone.
W2B
Oh, yeah! Did Dorothy
write anything in her notebook?
Her notebook?
I remember now...
She was writing nonstop.
I knew it! That huge gossip
wrote down everything you said!
Oh no! That's RRS!
RRS
Really, really scary...
Cony, please say you didn't
feed her a bunch of lies about us.
A bunch of lies? I would never!
I only told her things that are true!
What'd you tell her?!
Nothing serious.
Stuff like how girls always dump you,
how you're always gaming all day long,
and how you once ate
30 chicken nuggets in one sitting.
You said too much!
But it's all true!
That doesn't make it okay!
My personal details are gonna spread
all over Line Town by tomorrow...
Huh?! I'm getting messages
from chicken restaurants?!
These are from all the chicken places in Line Town!
Wow, it's already spread?
She's good.
This is all your fault, Cony.
Huh?! But why?
I didn't do anything wrong.
Moon's such a meanie.
He should know it's Dorothy's fault.
We oughta stay away
from Dorothy.
Right, Brown? Huh?
Hey, let me listen too!
I love this song "SM!"
That means "so much!"
SM
Hey! Your music is too loud!
It's frankly quite annoying when people
turn up their music in public, especially on transport.
Don't jump us like that!
That old lady's just so obnoxious.
I understand how you feel,
but she hasn't said anything wrong, has she?
Huh? I guess not...
But just because it's right
doesn't always mean it has to be said!
That's surprisingly profound,
coming from you.
Surprisingly?
Sorry, uncalled for.
Putting that aside...
Are you sure you want to open those here?
Yeah, why not? I'll eat 'em all.
Okay then.
See you tomorrow!
CY! See ya!
CY
Darn, now I'm stuffed.
Now what?
Here.
Oh! Thank you!
Huh? Wait... what?
Oh, Dorothy...
Now wipe your hands off.
They're all sticky.
Thank you.
And you must be thirsty after
all those potato chips. Here.
That bag sure can fit a lot, huh?
I have to be prepared
for any emergency.
I'm not sure I'd call this
an emergency...
Oh right!
You forgot this yesterday!
Oh, thanks! I guess I left it at Jessica's!
It's been too long, but I've still got it!
Huh? You've used one before?
Yes, hun! These were all the rage back in my day.
Let me show you how we
spring chickens did it!
Whoo!
Whoo-hoo!
Whoa, she's actually really good!
And she's just so awesome!
She taught me her skills,
but I can't quite...
Get back here!
Come back! Wait up!
What the heck was that?
Hey, stop laughing!
You're totes peeving me off!
Aah, Dorothy, stop!
Don't write about me!
She's gonna tell everyone about me!
Calm now. Dorothy wouldn't
spread a rumor like that.
How do you know?
Someone falling on the ground
isn't a big deal.
The others said the same thing.
But it's still an SEM to me:
SEM
a super-embarrassing memory!
Okay, okay.
I can talk to Dorothy for you. Sound good?
Plz, Jessica! TY!
You're welcome.
Ugh. I can't believe that old lady.
Sneak... sneak...
Found her notebook!
Nope, no peeking! I can't peek! But...
Hey, I'm not reading it
on purpose!
Ack, it's about me!
Even though my scolding upsets her,
Cony still follows what I tell her to do.
She really is HAH:
Honest and hard-working.
HAH
"Honest and hard-working"
would be HHW, you old...
HHW
I mean, Dorothy.
weather
My skin's so rough...
Now just stay put!
Don't move, okay?
Jessica, will this really make
my skin silky smooth?
Of course it will!
That's what this magazine says!
Ew, so salty!
Oh dear! I accidentally put
salt in instead of sugar!
What the heck, Jessica?
That's silly!
You're not supposed to
laugh in that face mask!
Huh?
Sorry, Jessica.
I don't really like these masks...
You'll have to put up with it.
If only my skin would stay smooth
so I didn't have to do this.
You said it.
But I'm afraid with the lack of rain around here,
it's not going to get much better.
Wait, what?
Rain has an effect on the skin?
Huh? Of course it does!
The weather affects the body
in many ways.
So if there's no rain and it's dry outside,
it's only natural our skin gets dry too.
I had no idea.
I see! So we just need rain!
Doesn't seem like
it's going to rain any time soon.
Huh? How do you know?
Take a look.
What's this?
A weather map.
Line Town is in the middle of high pressure,
so there's no rain clouds in sight.
You can tell based on this map?
That's right.
So don't expect any rain.
Aw man...
This is what my skin's turning into!
I could really use some rain right now!
You get it!
Yeah! How do we make rain?
We really need it, don't we?
Well...
Oh?
Hey, Cony! What are you—
Shh!
Huh?
What are you doing...?
Watching a frog climb a ladder.
Huh? Is it actually climbing it?
Nope, not at all!
I've been watching it for hours,
but it hasn't climbed one rung.
Huh?
This old farmer told me that if
a frog climbed a ladder, it would rain.
That can't be true.
Probably not.
He couldn't tell me for certain anyways.
Figures.
But we really need some rain.
No kidding.
I'm sure many others do too.
Please, we don't need any rain!
I get to go out without an umbrella,
and play outside without getting rained on!
I don't mind the lack of rain either.
I can drive with the top down
and feel the wind in my hair.
Yeah! And Brown says his laundry
dries better without any rain.
Of all the nerve!
You people are only thinking about yourselves!
Don't you realize how rough
little ol' Cony's skin has gotten?
This is really, really bad!
Now who's only thinking about themselves?
Wait, you mean me?
But without any rain, vegetables won't grow,
so we can't buy any produce.
The tomatoes in my garden
withered too...
Wait, they have?!
But your tomatoes are so good...
And you just bought a new umbrella
and raincoat, right, Brown?
Don't you wish you could put them to use?
It's not like we can make it rain
ourselves, though.
No one can control the weather.
Yeah...
But Sally said rain comes from the clouds!
Duh, everyone knows that.
So we just gotta make clouds!
That's just impossible!
The smoke?
I see! This is sorta like clouds!
Oh yeah!
Clouds are made of water vapor. So...
That's more like it.
Can't let boiled water go to waste.
Yeah.
Hello!
Hey, Jessica! Please take a seat!
Still using those face masks, I see!
I'm starting to run out...
Gonna have to buy more.
This drought is really running
my wallet dry!
I'm not sure if this will help, but...
What is it?
Look at this!
What's this?
It looks just like Moon!
I thought the same thing.
This is called a weather doll.
If you make one of these and hang it up,
it'll bring sunny skies the next day!
Whoa, interesting!
Alright, let's make a bunch of them!
Yay, sunny skies!
Wait, that's ridiculous!
We don't need more sun!
Now, don't worry. Take a closer look.
It says if you want to bring rain,
you have to hang the doll upside down.
Oh, just hang it upside down! I see!
Alright, guys!
Time to make some weather dolls!
I don't know how.
I've never made one before!
Then I shall teach you how.
Fold it into a ball,
then tie the head with a rubber band,
then draw the face with a marker...
and it's done!
Magnificent!
Looks just like you, Moon!
I'm more of a looker than that.
Like looking in a mirror!
No it ain't!
Now, let the weather doll making begin!
Okay!
Will these things actually work?
Not if you don't believe.
Faith will lead us to salvation!
Sally's words, anyways.
How original.
All done!
Now, let's go hang 'em up
all over town!
Yeah!
It kinda looks like I'm hanging myself...
I don't like this.
This is really hard...
But we're counting on you, weather dolls!
Make it rain!
We're counting on you!
This goes against my aesthetic...
But it'll have to do until it rains.
So you want me to hang those
upside down, correct?
Yes, please!
Hup-two, da-da-da...
There... there!
Juby... julee...
Whoa-ho!
Wow! What a view!
They're so cute!
We put up so many!
What a beautiful sunset.
Oh no! A beautiful sunset
is a sign tomorrow will be sunny too!
Relax, guys!
We've done what we can!
I pray for rain tomorrow.
So cold!
Oh right!
What in the world?!
What in the world?
Super cold! Feels so good!
Order up!
No matter how old you get, you can't help
but look up and gasp when snow finally comes.
Looks like it went straight past rain
and brought us snow instead!
Didn't think we'd get to snowboard!
This is awesome!
It worked better than I thought!
It's amazing. This wasn't even on the weather map!
Thanks a lot!
You asked for it, Jessica!
Take that!
Yeah, juby-julee!
I'm gonna get ya!
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
I dreamt I was flying through the night sky
mahou no juutan ni notte
On a magic carpet
tondeku yozora no yume
And I just wanted you to see it
kimi ni mo
kimi ni mo misetakute
misetai
Oh, did I wake you? I'm so sorry
okoshichatta kana? gomen ne
I thought you sounded half-asleep
neboketa kotobatachi ni
And it made me swoon
nandaka
nandaka kyun to kita
kyun kyun
Just like the glittering scent of rose tea
kirameku kaori no roozu tii mitai ni
When my heart starts pounding, I lock up
dokidoki no sono shunkan
tojikomeru
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
Even though I could just type a <3 and send it to you
yubisaki haato wo nosete
tsutawattara ii no ni
It's hard to sum up the way I feel for you
kimi e no kono kimochi
hitokoto ja tarinai
It's like a millefeuille
egao mo namida mo zenbu
With all of my smiles and tears mixed in
tsumikasaneta mirufiiyu
I feel happy, I feel painful
ureshii setsunai itoshii
I feel longing — I'm in love
koishiteru
galaxy
Next time on Line Town...
I've always wondered about this!
We're finally going to learn the secret
of the "juby-julee" ditty James hums!
What is "juby-julee?"
galaxy
Is it an ad-lib? It's not even in the script.
What does it mean?
Please do enlighten us next week!