A-B-C-D-E-F-G
H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P
Q-R-S-T-U-V-W
X-Y and Z
Now you know your ABCs
Isn't it bizarre, the way we string together
letters from A to Z?
Whether it be out loud or by text,
let's find something to talk about!
How will the world end? What's for dinner?
Let's share those moments of laughter and tears
I decide what I like and hate
But that too is a barrier I can break down
Don't you see? Our words make us who we are
There's something I want to talk about with you
Just thinking about that gets me all giddy
Whether you're right next to me or not
You always brighten up my day
Of all the things you've spoken to me
I cherish every last word
It feels good to think about somebody
And it feels good to put that into words
ice
I want... to have...
legendary shaved ice...
Legendary shaved ice?
I think that's shaved ice
made from the ice in the Ice Forest.
You mean the forest at
the bottom of Line Mountain
where everything is frozen
all year long?
That's the one.
"Legendary shaved ice" is made
from the ice in that forest,
and it's soft and crunchy.
That sounds so good!
I want... legendary...
legendary shaved ice...
How about we go fetch some ice?
Great idea.
Some legendary shaved ice
might heal Sally right up!
Yeah.
Jessica, you keep an eye on Sally!
Okay! Take care, you guys!
Got it!
We've got your back, Sally!
Get ready to have some legendary shaved ice!
By everything being frozen,
do they mean like, everything?
Yep! The flowers, the grass,
the trees—everything!
Now that sounds like a sight.
Have you been, James?
Yeah, just once!
We should be there by noon.
Allow me to lead the way!
You go, James!
I know we can count on you!
Please, you flatter me.
Thank goodness we have you!
James, we're going the right way, right?
I-I think so!
I didn't ask what you think!
C'mon, you said we'd be there by noon!
We've been walking for ages!
Also, what kind of route is this?
You have no idea where you're going.
Th-That can't be!
This is why we can never count on you.
Wow!
Here we are! The Ice Forest!
See? I knew where I was going!
And we wouldn't be here
if I hadn't led the way!
So shiny!
Dang, no kidding,
it is frozen over!
Sure, go on...
Wow! It's a triple axle!
I'm gonna do it too!
Triple axle!
Some axle that was!
I don't think you're cut out for ice skating.
Me neither!
Juby-julee!
Let's go!
Yeah!
This is awesome!
Oh shoot! Sally!
Oh, right! We got sidetracked hard...
What should we grab?
Enough for all of us,
so it's gotta be a big one!
Agreed!
How's this look?
Phew! Now that'll make
a whole bounty of shaved ice!
Sweet! So how do we bring it back?
Ack...
You mean none of you brought
anything to carry it in?!
We brought nothing, period.
Ouch.
We totally overlooked
how we'd bring some ice back.
Oh?
Wow! Unbelievable!
Huh?
"Please take one!"
Perfect, handcar rentals!
Let's take the biggest one they've got!
This looks like it'll hold
a ton of ice!
We're coming, Sally!
Let's get Sally some ice!
Yeah!
Who picked out this
huge chunk of ice?!
You did!
So heavy...
Can't we scrap half of it?
And just let it go to waste?!
Huh? What is it?
Oh no! The ice is melting!
We gotta hurry!
Moon, is that you?
Mister?
Hey, it's good to see you!
What're you up to?
Lugging ice...
Oh, ice? From the Ice Forest, I take it?
Y'know, I've been once!
Its shaved ice is to die for!
Is this a relative?
Nah, my ex-girlfriend's...
Father?
No, my ex-girlfriend's friend's
cousin's neighbor across the street.
So a stranger?
Wrap it up, the ice is gonna melt!
Yeah, yeah.
Alright, got places to be!
Okay! Goodbye!
Oh, I forgot!
I ran into your ex-girlfriend's
friend's friend just yesterday!
Y'see, I put on a bit of weight,
so I started going on jogs!
I really did, just a little!
But y'see...
I guess I gotta watch my health!
Alright!
And then, y'know...
Yeowch!
Agh, I have a stomachache!
Are you alright?
I just need to get home
and rest it off.
I better get home soon!
Dangit, it shrunk like crazy!
We'll make it! Just run!
Let's take a shortcut!
Go!
Ack!
The chatterbox monster!
I want ice...
The rest will be back
with some ice soon!
They're sure running late though...
I hope they get back soon.
Where the heck are we?!
Definitely not the route
we took here!
Cool it, man!
Don't push me! I'm gonna fall!
We gotta keep moving
before the ice melts away!
So high up! So scary!
James, we get it, now shut up!
Let's talk about something fun!
Sure, let's!
What are you gonna put
on your shaved ice?
I'm going strawberry syrup!
Can't eat if we fall down.
I'm putting red bean syrup!
That, sticky rice cake,
and condensed milk!
Man, I can't wait!
Can't wait if we fall down.
What about you, Brown?
Mango and ice cream?
Good choice!
Won't be good if we fall down.
Stop being such a buzzkill, James!
Let me help you...
Just shut up and stay put!
It's no help if you keep freaking out!
Sorry... I just hate being so high up...
Yeah, we know.
If you can, look up directions for us.
Just don't look down.
Okay...
Once we pass these mountains,
Sally's house should be straight ahead.
So a little more climbing
then it's an easy trek downhill!
Hang in there!
We did it!
We made it to the top!
Hip hip hooray!
Crud!
James!
Juby-julee!!
James! Where are you?!
O-Over here...
James!
I-I kept the ice safe...
Are you okay?
Yeah...
Thanks a lot, James!
I knew we could count on you.
Juby-julee!
It sure shrunk...
Doesn't seem like
the sun's going down.
Wow!
Good thinking, Brown!
If we keep it out of sunlight,
we should have some left when we get back!
Let's move!
Sally! Jessica!
We've got ice!
Let's run!
Thank you!
It's delicious!
The perfect legendary shaved ice!
That's good to hear!
Get better soon, Sally!
The others got that ice
straight from the forest,
all for you!
Huh? You only got ice for me?
Why don't you all have some?
Oh?
Legendary shaved ice is so good...
They're having some
in their dreams.
Thank you all.
robuddy
And it was on backwards!
And then guess what?
Huh?
What?!
What's that thing?
That's real steel!
Could it be a robot?
But who made it?
And what's it doing here?
First off, let's turn it on!
Where's the power switch?
Guys, are you sure we should be
messing with it all willy-nilly?
Maybe it was left here by mistake!
Who would leave behind
a giant robot like this?
It's all alone here!
And helping it find its owner
is the right thing to do!
That's nice coming from you!
That was uncalled for.
Doesn't seem to have any switches.
Oh, I see how it works!
It must be voice-activated!
I'll handle this!
Moon-Robot, power on!
Man...
Oh, is that a cockpit?
Whoa!
So cool!
Don't get on that thing,
it's dangerous!
Up I go...
Wow!
Let's see...
Oh! It says "welcome!"
See? That thing doesn't care who climbs on.
Cony, move it around!
I bet she fails.
Like this?
Whew! Run, robot, run!
Now jump!
That was so cool!
This is a blast!
You guys gotta try too!
I wanna go!
Run!
Huh?
Juby-julee...
There's nothing Cony can do
that I cannot!
Alright! Let's go!
Snap to it, you bucket of bolts!
Huh?! What's that?
This is so much fun!
Wh-Why is she the only one
who can steer it?!
Maybe it authorized her
because she was the first one to board?
That's no fair.
Hey, how about we call this guy Robuddy?
Robuddy?
I came up with it myself!
I like it!
Be sure to look after it
until its owner turns up!
Ugh. I can't take any more of this.
Aah! Oh no!
Oh no! This is bad...
Don't worry, I'll get it down!
Oh, thank you so much!
Hm? What's this about?
Oh dear!
I really loved those swings...
Let's do this, Robuddy!
Wow! Way to go!
Thank you, Robuddy!
It went up again.
Hey, Robuddy?
I have a favor I must ask of you!
You see, when I dry my hair
with one hand,
it's hard for me to brush it.
Do you mind holding my hairdryer for me?
What kind'a request is that?!
Sure thing!
Here!
Lovely, now I can brush with both hands,
and keep my hair lustrous!
Thanks a ton, Robuddy!
It did it again!
Oh, I see! You want Robuddy
to fish you some salmon, right?
You got it!
Power on, Robuddy!
Now, Robuddy!
And... there!
Sweet!
Hmm, it's missing something...
But I'm not sure what.
Weird, it tastes much better now.
Huh?!
Thank you, Robuddy.
You added the perfect amount of salt!
It went up even more!
This is my house!
Down!
You wait there, Robuddy!
How's Robuddy doing?
Robuddy?
I'll sleep out here tonight!
Aw, you happy?
Where are we going?
So pretty!
Did you want to show me this?
Thank you, Robuddy!
There we go, one, two...
Go!
I hear Robuddy was all over today!
Yeah! And the meter in the cockpit
rose a lot too!
What do you suppose
that meter is for?
I'm not quite sure.
This is my chance!
Let's do this!
Go!
One, two, one, two...
How dare she hog this baby to herself?
I'm gonna mod this
so only I can ride it!
Aah! Not again!
That won't work on me twice!
Help!!
Somebody help me!
Moon!
Robuddy Mat!
Are you okay, Moon?
Uh, yeah, thanks.
Oh, it's full!
I get it! It's a good deed meter!
A good deed meter?
Yeah! It went up every time
you did something good!
You're right!
What's going on, Robuddy?
Perhaps now that the meter is full,
it has to leave?
Is that it?
Oh, I get it!
So you're gonna visit a new town
and do good deeds there!
Goodbye, Robuddy!
Take care, Robuddy!
Farewell, Robuddy!
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
I dreamt I was flying through the night sky
mahou no juutan ni notte
On a magic carpet
tondeku yozora no yume
And I just wanted you to see it
kimi ni mo
kimi ni mo misetakute
misetai
Oh, did I wake you? I'm so sorry
okoshichatta kana? gomen ne
I thought you sounded half-asleep
neboketa kotobatachi ni
And it made me swoon
nandaka
nandaka kyun to kita
kyun kyun
Just like the glittering scent of rose tea
kirameku kaori no roozu tii mitai ni
When my heart starts pounding, I lock up
dokidoki no sono shunkan
tojikomeru
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
Even though I could just type a <3 and send it to you
yubisaki haato wo nosete
tsutawattara ii no ni
It's hard to sum up the way I feel for you
kimi e no kono kimochi
hitokoto ja tarinai
It's like a millefeuille
egao mo namida mo zenbu
With all of my smiles and tears mixed in
tsumikasaneta mirufiiyu
I feel happy, I feel painful
ureshii setsunai itoshii
I feel longing — I'm in love
koishiteru
bottle opener
ninjas
Next time on Line Town...
Do you know what ninjas are?
They're a food you make by emptying things
onto a griddle with cabbage!
Wait, that's monja.
bottle opener
ninjas
They've got big gates!
...Jinja shrines.
It goes very well with soy sauce!
That would be ginger.
Next time: "Ninjas!"
See you then!