A-B-C-D-E-F-G
H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P
Q-R-S-T-U-V-W
X-Y and Z
Now you know your ABCs
Isn't it bizarre, the way we string together
letters from A to Z?
Whether it be out loud or by text,
let's find something to talk about!
How will the world end? What's for dinner?
Let's share those moments of laughter and tears
I decide what I like and hate
But that too is a barrier I can break down
Don't you see? Our words make us who we are
There's something I want to talk about with you
Just thinking about that gets me all giddy
Whether you're right next to me or not
You always brighten up my day
Of all the things you've spoken to me
I cherish every last word
It feels good to think about somebody
And it feels good to put that into words
job
A delivery job?
Yes. A friend asked me to recruit someone
since they're short-staffed.
I wish I could help, but I have gigs
as a reader model.
And I want to be free in case
I get offered a reader model gig!
I've got video games to play.
I'll take it on, then!
I'll deliver your packages
with a beautiful smile!
If you're up to it,
I can help out a little bit!
Me too!
And I can help you navigate.
Fine. Guess I better pitch in too.
You'll take the job, Moon?
That's wonderful!
Hope you can find time for it!
Thanks!
Huh?! What the heck, guys!
Huh? You'll take the job, Brown?
Wow!
You've got this, Brown!
Good luck, Brown!
How beautiful!
Thank you, Brown!
Coming!
Oh, Brown!
I forgot your delivery job
started today!
Right, gotta sign.
Done.
You look so cool, Brown!
Like a real hard-worker!
Gotcha, lots of other packages
to deliver still.
Keep at it!
Wait, didn't I have something
I needed mailed?
Thank you for your service, Brown!
You've really gotten used to this role.
Clearly, you're the best man for the job!
Good luck!
Thank you, Brown!
While you're here,
I have some packages to ship.
Oh! That's a pickling stone!
I have to return it because it's too heavy.
Be careful.
Oh dear...
That's a cushion, it's for...
...a friend. It's very light.
Thank you again!
You look so cool, Brown!
Clearly, you're the best man for the job!
Thank you, Brown!
Hah! Take that!
Yo, Brown!
A delivery? I'm inside.
Say what?! You tripped off the cliff?
Oh my gosh!!
Found you.
Hold tight, Brown. I'm on my way!
C-Close call.
I-I'm alive...
You expect me to take that here?
Or sign it?!
Hey, Brown! It's James!
Sorry I was out.
I'm home now, so I can
sign for my package!
Who is it?
James?
James, you gotta help us!
I'm lost, but that looks real bad!
You think so?
Aah! Brown, I need you to come
do a pick-up!
I forgot to return this trampoline
I was renting for my diet!
If it's not sent today,
I'll be charged a late fee!
How is that our problem?
You want Brown to take it,
come meet us here!
All these people
only care about themselves!
Guys!
We're up here, James!
Come help us!
I'm on my way!
How do I look? Smashing?
You look fine, now come get us!
Juby-julee... juby-julee...
Juby-julee... ju—
Juby?!
So how do I get you up?
Can't you do rock-climbing
to get us?
I don't know!
Look, hammer a hook
into the crack in the rock,
then tie the rope on your back to it.
Here goes...
My hammer...
Just drive the hook
into the rock wherever!
I give up...
Ugh, that's enough out of you!
Wait, did I just climb up?
Whatever.
James, I'll show you how it's done!
You're amazing, Moon!
Please, it's only basic
survival skills!
We're coming, Brown!
Alright, bring it in!
What?! Your hand,
not the package!
J-Jeez, that was close...
Huh? For me?!
How am I supposed to accept it here?
James, why did you come with me?
I felt bad making you go down
by yourself!
Oh no. Brown!
Just toss the packages,
or we're all goners!
Alright, here's an idea.
Give me my package.
Why, thank you.
There.
Oh, relax.
Now we're more likely to survive.
What was in the package anyways, Moon?
Crud!
It was the easy-go hot air balloon
I bought from an infomercial!
I'll take my package too!
Juby-julee...
Thank you!
How's tossing away
such a small package supposed to help?
It's a health tonic I won in a giveaway!
We'll drink this to keep up our stamina!
Hanging like this is all
our stamina can take!
Ah, right...
I'm done...
Where are you, Brown?
Cony, up here!
Look up!
What?!
Wait one second!
Jump down on this!
No way, Cony!
We can't land on that!
It's too small!
Hey! Cut it, Brown!
Don't struggler!
Brown!
There.
Are you messing with us?
No!
Don't tell me!
Who wants some high-quality comforters?
Huh?!
W-We're saved...
Juby-julee...
What in the world?
Where did you all come from-ter?
Huh? You'll return my package today?
Thank you so much!
Brown!
You're so cool!
pickiness
So relaxing
My beautiful shampoo-shampoo
Oh deary me! My shampoo is empty!
Shampoo, sham—ack!
Shampoo, shampoo, shampoo...
None?!
I'm all out of shampoo!
How could I mess up like this?
It's unlike me to let
my shampoo stock run out!
Dear, I'd hate to have to go out
without washing my hair...
But that's your fault for not
keeping your shampoo stocked, James!
I'm sorry!
Shampoo, shampoo, my dear shampoo
Wait, what?!
Wait-wait-wait-wait, what?!
What's the matter?
There's no ultra-beautiful shampoo
Powerful Purple Floral!
My deepest apologies.
We're out of stock at the moment.
We should have more next week.
Next week?!
Are you insinuating I shouldn't bathe
until next week?!
Not at all, no?
How am I supposed to wash my hair
without any shampoo?
You could just use a different shampoo.
How about this Mystic Mistral Green?
No!
Powerful Purple Floral is my fragrance!
If you need a similar scent...
the Super Wonderful Shampoo series
should do the trick!
No way!
That series doesn't have any
bis aminopropyl dimethicone!
Bis amino...?
Propyl dimethicone.
Let's see what we have...
Let's see, let's see, let's see...
Hey! This Miracle Cuticle Shampoo
say it has bis amina blah blah...
No way!
It has to be my
ultra-beautiful shampoo!
They're not all that different
from one another...
They absolutely are!
From their fragrance
to their compositions!
Not to mention the feel
of your scalp afterwards.
If you say so.
I won't take anything but the ultra-beautiful shampoo,
Powerful Purple Floral.
Then you have to wait until next week!
Are you telling me not to wash my hair
for a whole week?
Those are your words, not mine!
If I go a whole week without washing my hair
and it gets all dirty and smelly,
it'll be because of you!
You'll pay for running out of stock of
the ultra-beautiful shampoo,
Powerful Purple Floral!
What?
You're blaming me?
Then, I said...
"Miss, don't let your guard down
around eggplant tips and manhole covers."
You're totally making that up!
No, it really happened!
I give up...
I give up on this world...
'Sup, James?
Uhh...
We're gonna go get lunch.
Wanna join us?
Uhh...
What's wrong?
You look glum.
Mmm...
Rough morning or something?
Can I vent a bit?
I took a trip to...
my usual drug store, but they didn't have
my ultra-beautiful shampoo
Powerful Purple Floral in stock!
Ridiculous, right?
That stinks. Sorry to hear that.
Aren't you shocked?
Why should I be?
They're sold out of your shampoo.
So what?
So what? So what?!
It's an outrage!
Without my ultra-beautiful shampoo,
Powerful Purple Floral,
I can't wash my hair!!
Say what?
Why not...
just use a different shampoo?
Yeah.
Are you insinuating that
all shampoo is the same?
They're similar enough.
They are not!
My ultra-beautiful shampoo
Powerful Purple Floral isn't like the rest!
Okay, we get you like
your ultra-beautiful... whatever.
But why can't you just use something else
until they're restocked?
You guys just don't get it.
Maybe it doesn't matter
to you blockheads,
but I'm particular, and I need to use
the same shampoo!
I don't like where this is going.
I can't wash my hair with anything
but my ultra-powerful shampoo,
Powerful Purple Floral!
Uh-huh.
You cannot wash your hair
without your ultra-beautiful shampoo,
Powerful Purple Floral, correct?
Yeah.
And you claim your ultra-beautiful stuff
is unique from other shampoos?
Spot on!
I smell a contradiction.
How?
If it's different from other shampoos,
then clearly you've used other shampoos!
Which means you are capable of washing
your hair with something else!
Good eye, Detective Moon.
You're correct, I have used
other shampoos before.
But that's in the past!
The moment I tried the ultra-beautiful shampoo
Powerful Purple Floral,
I knew I'd never use anything else ever again!
I fell in love with it like a girlfriend!
Like a girlfriend?!
He's madly in love with his shampoo?
Phew.
When did I gain so much weight?
That's for binge eating.
You were just cramming stuff down.
What is it, Brown?
Tinned salmon?
Can we tell the difference
between these two?
Aren't they the same?
But they're from the same brand.
Their marks are different?
This one was manufactured
at the East Line Factory,
and this one at the West Line Factory?
And the factory it was made at
changes the flavor in subtle ways?
So even though you prefer
the ones made by East Line Factory,
you have to return West Line Factory
tins that get mixed in?
They can't be that different.
They are?!
Brown! You know how I feel!
This is ridiculous.
I can't go a whole week
without washing my hair.
No! If I get frustrated, my scalp gets itchy,
which just makes me want to wash my hair more!
Gasp! Wait...
That store isn't the only place
I can buy my ultra-powerful shampoo!
Excuse me!
Do you have the ultra-beautiful shampoo
Powerful Purple Floral?
I'm sorry, we don't have it right now.
Do you have ultra-beautiful shampoo?
What's that?
Any ultra-beautiful shampoo?
Oh, we do!
Hoora—wait, this is super wonderful shampoo!
What's the difference?
I said ultra-beauti... Oh, just forget it.
Any ultra-beautiful shampoo?
Sir, zis is a butcher.
Aah! Sorry about this!
Why can't I find it anywhere?!
Where am I?
How is no one selling it
all the way out here?
Is someone conspiring
against me?
Refusing to let me have my
ultra-beautiful shampoo at any cost?
Huh?
What was that thing?!
Was it some sort of divine message?
It must be! My love for the ultra-beautiful shampoo,
Powerful Purple Floral, is being tested!
God has bestowed me with a trial!
I won't give up.
I'll go as far as I must!
Even to the ends of the Earth!
I'm coming, my ultra-beautiful shampoo!
Yummy!
You make the best salmon sandwiches, Brown!
Mhm! And it's even better
with those East Line Factory tins!
I don't get the difference,
but it tastes real good!
Hey, guys!
Been a while, dude!
What've you been up to
this whole time?
I went to get shampoo.
It was rough. I had to go straight
to the main factory.
The main factory?! Seriously, man?
You went overseas
just to get shampoo?
Yeah.
You've gotten real brave, James.
Your hair's a real mess.
Yeah, I've been camping in my car
the whole trip through.
But if it's for my ultra-beautiful shampoo,
Powerful Purple Floral,
I can take a messy hairdo.
I think you might have
your priorities backwards.
Hey, Sally!
You go shopping?
Yeah, they had a bargain sale,
and I ended up buying a lot.
It was cheap, so I want to share it.
What?! Is that what I think it is?
It is! Ultra-beautiful shampoo,
Powerful Purple Floral!
Where'd you get that?
At the drug store over there.
But how?!
Dude, it's been a week,
so they got more in stock.
I... I've been away
for a whole week?
What was the point of all that?
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
I dreamt I was flying through the night sky
mahou no juutan ni notte
On a magic carpet
tondeku yozora no yume
And I just wanted you to see it
kimi ni mo
kimi ni mo misetakute
misetai
Oh, did I wake you? I'm so sorry
okoshichatta kana? gomen ne
I thought you sounded half-asleep
neboketa kotobatachi ni
And it made me swoon
nandaka
nandaka kyun to kita
kyun kyun
Just like the glittering scent of rose tea
kirameku kaori no roozu tii mitai ni
When my heart starts pounding, I lock up
dokidoki no sono shunkan
tojikomeru
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
Even though I could just type a <3 and send it to you
yubisaki haato wo nosete
tsutawattara ii no ni
It's hard to sum up the way I feel for you
kimi e no kono kimochi
hitokoto ja tarinai
It's like a millefeuille
egao mo namida mo zenbu
With all of my smiles and tears mixed in
tsumikasaneta mirufiiyu
I feel happy, I feel painful
ureshii setsunai itoshii
I feel longing — I'm in love
koishiteru
train
where?
Next time on Line Town...
Have any of you seen Brown?
Describe him? Well, he's round and brown.
Wait, round and brown...
No, he's not a mud ball!
train
where?
Anyways, he's round and brown!
If you spot him, reach out ASAP!
You'll get a thank you
as a reward!
Tune in next week!