A-B-C-D-E-F-G
H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P
Q-R-S-T-U-V-W
X-Y and Z
Now you know your ABCs
Isn't it bizarre, the way we string together
letters from A to Z?
Whether it be out loud or by text,
let's find something to talk about!
How will the world end? What's for dinner?
Let's share those moments of laughter and tears
I decide what I like and hate
But that too is a barrier I can break down
Don't you see? Our words make us who we are
There's something I want to talk about with you
Just thinking about that gets me all giddy
Whether you're right next to me or not
You always brighten up my day
Of all the things you've spoken to me
I cherish every last word
It feels good to think about somebody
And it feels good to put that into words
reunion
What?! Cony's fallen ill?!
You say she keeps sighing?
I'll see him...
I won't see him...
I see now...
Brown, that there is lovesickness.
L
O
V
E
LOVE!
Love!
It's when one falls for another!
That is the beginning of a love story!
Hey, Cony!
James?
Who is the one you're in love with?
Huh?
I know it very well!
You're worrying over a crush, aren't you?
That's cray-cray!
We're not there yet, not at all!
Oh, James! You so cray cray!
You crack me up!
Huh?
So who's your crush?
Well...
An old pen pal of yours?
Yeah. He moved away when we were little.
I haven't seen him in-person since,
but we've exchanged
lots of letters.
Exchanging letters in the modern day...
Now that's what I call romantic!
This is Michelle when he was young!
D'aww!
He was so cute, he was doing
modeling gigs and stuff as a baby!
He's also very smart!
He was a prodigy!
He can speak five languages,
he's good at horse-riding,
and I'm sure he's much taller now too!
Hey, Cony!
He's gotta be way cuter now than before!
"I'm going to be in a horse-riding contest
not far from your town!"
"I can't wait to see you again
after all this time!"
Wow!
You're finally going to see Michelle again!
I guess...
Huh? Aren't you excited?
Keep reading.
"You told me you were a good cook,
and knew a lot about classical music..."
"and that you would get scouted for idol work
just by walking down the street in cute clothes..."
"Sounds like you've grown into a perfect lady!"
Cony, what is all this?
I might've stretched the truth juuust a bit...
This is all lies!
I just wanted him to think of me
as a perfect girl!
What do I do?
A lie's only a lie
because it's a lie!
Just make your lies the truth!
You think I can become a perfect girl?
Of course you can!
And I'm gonna help.
You?
No one else more qualified!
The beauty master,
the king of beauty, James!
I don't follow,
but you're blowing me away!
Leave it to me, and you'll be
a perfect lady—guaranteed!
I will?
You will!
But if you want to be a perfect lady,
the road ahead is a steep one!
I'll do it!
I will become a perfect lady
worthy of Michelle!
First up, fashion check!
You have to put care into your looks!
How do you want to look
when you're with Michelle?
I have a skirt that's just perfect!
Huh...?
Weird...
Looks like this skirt shrunk!
No it didn't!
Have you gained weight?
Erp!
Hmm...
No, I haven't!
I'm gonna prove it to you!
Brown, your phone!
Look for yourself!
Pics of Cony?
Oof, she's swelling up!
I gained... 5 pounds...
Have you?
I gained 15 pounds...
Why do you have
all of these pics of me anyway?!
This has to go...
Never mind that, Cony!
You've gotta get to work!
Huh? On what?
James' diet program!
Step 1, exercise!
Step 2, exercise!
Steps 3 and 4, exercise!
Step 5, exercise!
H-Hold on!
You don't want Michelle
to think you're fat, right?
I do this everyday,
and it's kept me beautiful!
How much further...?
To the other side of that mountain!
And after this, we'll be working on thosle muscles!
Move along, daylight's burning!
I can't do any more of this...
What's this sweet aroma?
Is it what I think it is?
Welcome, welcome!
We're giving out ice cream samples!
Would you care for a taste?
Samples?
Does that mean it's free?
Here you are!
Yippee, this is my lucky day!
All for me!
You fail!
Huh...?
No matter how sweet the temptation,
you have to overcome it!
I expect to hear...
"I'm on a diet, so I'll have to pass!"
...from you.
James!
I can see through...
your every move!
Whaaat?! Aw, man...
Let's get running!
You've still got a ways to go
to be a perfect lady!
Cooking class with James!
Crash course on the classics with James!
What's this song called?
You fell asleep
with your eyes open?!
Crash course on makeup
with James!
Go! Go! Go!
Come on! Come on!
Alright! Next, you'll be learning
table manners!
Huh?! There's still more?!
Plenty more!
It's like I told you! If you want to be perfect,
the road ahead is steep!
Cony!
Time for your morning training!
How long do you plan on sleeping in?! Wake...
...up?!
I can't take it anymore!!
Hey! Get back here, Cony!
I'm done, okay?
I give up on being more ladylike!
Put it on.
Huh?
It fits...
Hard work always pays off, Cony.
Good to see you again, Cony!
Looks like you've become
a perfect lady!
Michelle...
I'll do it!
I'll become more ladylike
for Michelle!
I won't run away anymore!
Good, let's go!
Now give me 10 sprints!
Yessir!
Moo-moo-moon, moo-moo-moon...
Cony?!
Why, hello, Moon!
It's good to see you!
You look like a totally different person!
You think so?
You look like a model!
Moon, you scamp!
Oh, this is Violin Sonata No. 569
in G minor!
Huh?! G minor?!
You're correct!
I have nothing left to teach you!
Onwards, Cony!
Thank you for everything, James!
Off I go!
Oh, Michelle.
I wonder how he'll react when he sees me!
I'm on my way!
My Michelle!
What the?!
What happened to you, Cony?
Was he gone by the time you got there?
No, he was... but...
But?
...So was his girlfriend.
Wanted his good friend
to meet her...
His good friend...
He had a girlfriend, did he?
So basically, the guy dumped you.
Well, I'm glad she's not
beating herself up over it...
I'm so full, it's making me all sleepy...
Just like that...
...she's already 200% less ladylike
than before.
Brown, what're you blushing for?
shadow
Moo-moo-moon, moo-moon...
Oh my, the moon is so beautiful...
Moon, what's the "big thing"
you wanted to tell us?
Take a look at this!
Hm? "Seeking cute, attractive hula girls?"
Oh, Moon, you could never
pull that off!
You're an awful dancer,
plus you're not even a girl!
Not that,
the thing above it!
Above that?
"Monster sighting."
"A suspicious shadow lurks around in the dark
making strange noises."
"Night after night it comes out,
plunging those who see it into pure terror..."
And I saw it for myself last night!
Will y'all help me bust this case?
Bust it?
Yeah... This monster put me through so much...
Must I live on with this regret?
I'll have to pass.
Monsters give me the creeps.
Same here.
Not like this is our problem.
What took you so long, Brown?
Are you coming with us?
We're gonna find out who this monster is!
Attaboy, Brown!
See, he gets me!
Brown?
He's asleep...
Anyways, now that we're all here,
let's head to where I spot the monster!
Is this where you saw that strange shadow?
Yup.
If we poke around here,
we should find some leads.
The investigation is on!
Off we go!
If you insist...
Hey!
I'm so beautiful!
Find anything?
Nothing over here.
How about you, Brown?
No luck, huh?
This case is shrouded in darkness!
That's Cony!
Cony!
That was close...
Are you alright?
Yeah...
But it looks like the road ends here.
Not quite.
Huh?
Look! Whatever it is must've crossed this bridge!
Which means our strange shadow
is beyond this point!
There's no way anyone's using this, right?
What she said! What kind of monster
could get across this old, rickety bridge?
Yeah, that's what makes it weird!
Let's go!
You're actually making us walk on that?
I'm not taking that risk.
After me, guys!
I don't even know what's happening anymore!
We really should turn back...
C-Cut it out, Moon!
Oh, calm down!
This bridge is very sturdy!
Whew, I'm sa—
I told you we should've turned back!
Nope, falling from the bridge was the right choice.
Look, over there.
That's just some old dude!
And what would an old man be doing here?
Fishing, duh!
He's even got a rod out.
He's not foolin' me.
That's just camouflage
to mask his true form.
Oh, he casted his line!
Also part of the camouflage!
He caught one!
Camouflage!
He's getting tangled up!
We have to save him!
Still camouflage!
He fell in!
All part of the camouflage.
No, it isn't!!
I'm glad he's safe and sound...
...But now we're no closer
to finding anything on that shadow.
Alright then, Plan B!
We'll do a stakeout.
You can try,
but it's never gonna show.
If you're tired, go ahead and rest.
I'll keep watch on my own.
You clearly want me to take this one...
So I'll take this!
It's the joker!
Gotcha!
Keep it down!
What's with the games?
It was either this or sleep!
Wanna join in?
Me?
Not a chance!
I did it!
Brown, where're ya goin'?
I fell asleep!
Bad news!
Take a look at this!
Hm? What is it?
"We received over 1,000 hula girl applications?"
You're still going on about that?
We told you already,
you aren't even a girl!
Not that! Above it!
Above?
What is it?
"There have been more sightings
of the shadow lurking in the dark."
It must've shown up while we were snoozing away!
What took you so long, Brown?
And you just had to leave us outta nowhere last night.
I don't suppose you saw the shadow, did you?
He fell asleep?
Oh, well.
Have you been staying up late, Brown?
What could Brown be doing up late at night?
Wait, he was up late?
Wasn't he like this yesterday too?
Hold on...
Alright! We stakeout again tonight!
Huh?!
All normal.
So what do you wanna play tonight?
We're not here to play games!
I'll put my bed right here.
We're not here to sleep either!
Wait a minute.
If my theory is correct,
then tucking in early might be the right call.
Alright! Everyone, it's bedtime!
Huh?!
Alright!
Now I just have to stay still and wait.
There!
I knew it!
Guys, wake up!
I'm stuffed...
Cheers to my eyes...
What are you dozing off for?!
I figured out who's behind the shadow!
Moon, why are we following Brown...?
He may have fooled everyone else,
but he won't fool me.
Don't you think it's strange?
The shadow appeared
after he went missing last night!
Then today, he shows up looking sleepless!
It was like that the day before too!
Are you saying that Brown...?
No way, dude.
The shadow didn't even look like his, right?
Look!
Look at his backpack.
It carries all the tools for his monster disguise!
That's crazy.
How could you throw your friend under like this?
Brown's getting dressed!
It begins!
He's wearing a skirt?
A skirt...?
I hear some noise...
This music is so calming...
Calming music? Huh?
This is nothing like the sound I heard before...
Brown?
This is the suspicious shadow?
No, rather...
You're applying to be a hula girl?
So you were just getting your practice in at night.
No wonder you're sleepless.
Then who's really behind the strange shadow...?
Who's that?!
This way!
Aah, wait for us!
That shadow! It has to be!
It's the strange one I saw before!
What the...?
Jessica!
Sally!
Oh! What brings you all here?
Do you guys want to stargaze with us?
I-I don't suppose you two were here last night...?
We were!
The stars look so pretty out here.
Yeah!
So the ones behind the strange shadow...
...are you two?
What strange shadow?
Forget about that.
Take a look up at the sky!
So many stars!
Whoa!
We gotta make wishes!
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
I dreamt I was flying through the night sky
On a magic carpet
And I just wanted you to see it
Oh, did I wake you? I'm so sorry
I thought you sounded half-asleep
And it made me swoon
Just like the glittering scent of rose tea
When my heart starts pounding, I lock up
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
Even though I could just type a <3 and send it to you
It's hard to sum up the way I feel for you
It's like a millefeuille
With all of my smiles and tears mixed in
I feel happy, I feel painful
I feel longing — I'm in love
art
fortunes
Next time on Line Town...
Unfortunately no fortunes for me,
for fortunes aren't in my favor.
A forsaken fortune
is naught but forsaken!
But if I ask for my fortune,
don't tell me the unfortunate!
Read my for-tuuune!
Unfortunately, no fortunes! For fortunately,
my fortune's been forgivenly fortold!
Nailed it.