A-B-C-D-E-F-G
H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P
Q-R-S-T-U-V-W
X-Y and Z
Now you know your ABCs
Isn't it bizarre, the way we string together
letters from A to Z?
Whether it be out loud or by text,
let's find something to talk about!
How will the world end? What's for dinner?
Let's share those moments of laughter and tears
I decide what I like and hate
But that too is a barrier I can break down
Don't you see? Our words make us who we are
There's something I want to talk about with you
Just thinking about that gets me all giddy
Whether you're right next to me or not
You always brighten up my day
Of all the things you've spoken to me
I cherish every last word
It feels good to think about somebody
And it feels good to put that into words
car
Juby-julee!
Beautiful! Just beautiful!
And tonight is my big night!
Because I've been invited to the premiere
of a highly-anticipated new movie!
Not only that, but they're going to
roll out the red carpet!
The world's eyes will be on me
as I beautifully waltz down!
Just the thought of it is exhilerating!
Juby-julee...
James!
Hey, Cony!
Can you do something for me?
I have to meet up with Jessica.
Can you drive me into town?
Huh?
Hm, I guess I have time before the premiere.
Sure thing!
Sweet! Thanks, James!
Uh-huh! I'm on my way, okay?
You're a lifesaver.
So are you and Jessica
hitting up a gorgeous party or what?
Nope, a bargain sale
at a big store in town.
It's a real big fight to get
anything in your cart!
So I better prepare with some exercises!
Huh?
One, two, three, four, five, six...
Seven, eight, nine...
Oh dear, oh dear, oh dear! Aah!
C-Cony, can you save the exercises
for after I drop you off?!
Thanks! Later, James!
James.
Huh?!
Whuh? Moon?
Wh-What are you...
Move. We're being tailed.
What? But my red carpet...
Oh no! There's snipers locked on us!
Get driving unless you
wanna get shot!
O-Okay!
Wh-What's going on?
Just shut up and do as I say.
But my red carpet!
Take a right there.
But my house is straight ahead!
Aah! There's a sniper on the
building up ahead!
A-juby!
Next left!
A-julee!
Diagonal right!
A-juby!
A-julee!
Juby-julee-juby-julee-juby-julee!
Moon, who are you being
tailed by anyways?
I don't see anyone behind us.
Stop.
A-juby!
Good. 100%.
My phone was dead!
Thank goodness I came across your car.
D-Don't tell me...
you came into my car just for that?
Sure did! Thought the spy game
would help kill time.
While you're at it,
mind driving me home?
I don't have time for your dumb spy games!
Isn't this Cony's phone?
Hey, it's Moon.
Got it. I'll let him know.
Cony forgot this,
so she wants you to go back.
C'mon!
Thank you so much!
Alright, got places to be!
You're going home now, right?
Hop in.
Can I?
That's great!
Jessica, he'll give us a ride!
Thanks, James!
I bought a bit too much.
Being here with all of you
makes me wanna do a road trip!
How about we hit up the beach?
Let's do it!
Yeah!
I hate to break it to you,
but it'll have to wait!
I have to get home!
My red carpet is waiting for me!
Slow down, James!
Are you trying to kill us?!
Désolé ! I'm running out of time!
Time for a shortcut! A-julee!
The heck was that?
Brown?!
Were you chasing after that thing?
That was a snake, wasn't it?
Yeah, and a blonde one at that!
Wait, could it be?!
The reincarnation of a hermit
dwelling in the mountains since ancient times,
the rare Hermit Snake?
The Hermit Snake?!
You realize how big it is
if that's true?!
We gotta go after it!
Get in, Brown!
W-Wait a minute!
I already told you, I have plans!
If we go off on a hunt...
A red carpet, or a find of the century?
Which one comes first?
Besides, if you find
the rare Hermit Snake,
you'll be branded as a hero!
You'll be in the global news!
Please.
Even the Hermit Snake
was no match for my beauty.
O-Okay, fine.
But only for a little bit.
Great!
Alright! Hermit Snake hunting team, go!
Any sign?
No, sir.
Did it run off?
Hey! I saw something over there!
You were right!
After it, James!
Before it gets away!
Are you going to let this
slip through your fingers?
That way!
Over there!
What are you doing, James?!
There!
I can't drive any further!
Let's go find it!
We'll find the snake. Count on it.
Sorry for all the trouble, James!
No worries! Good luck!
I'm off.
Oh no. Is it stalled?!
Huh?
One, two...
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Now I'll never get onto the red carpet...
Huh?
Wait, really?!
James, Brown says there's a cliff!
I can't take anymore of this...
Thank goodness I'm safe.
Are you alright?
Aah! There it is!
S-Someone catch that thing!
There you are. I've been looking
for you all over, Cobtaro.
What?!
Cobtaro? The one from the burger joint?
Strange. Where'd you pick up this thing?
You're such a scamp.
So it was just a wig all along!
Got us all worked up for nothing, huh, James?
That was your fault, Moon!
So much for the rare Hermit Snake.
So much for a find of the century.
And now my red carpet
has gone belly up!
Red carpet, you say?
By any chance, did you receive
an invitation to my joint's premiere?
Say what?
Then you're just in time!
I was waiting to find Cobtaro
before we began.
It's just this way, come along.
You know, I didn't check the venue...
It says it's at the hamburger joint!
What does that make my red carpet?!
I-Is this...?!
That would be the red carpet.
Be sure to wipe your shoes off!
No way!
It's all over...
My premium and gorgeous day is no more...
Now, it is time for the premiere
of the highly-anticipated brand new film,
The Adventures of Cobtaro!
Way to go, Cobtaro!
This is pretty cool!
C'mon, James, eat up!
Hang in there, Cobtaro!
Don't give up!
I may as well forget everything
with some food.
Great idea!
Then let's party to feel better
about missing a gigantic find!
Let's raise the roof!
I'm gonna eat so much!
Excuse me! I'll take an extra-large burger
and a mountain of fries!
jessica
Aww! Jessica, you're so pretty!
And this was an impromptu shoot
by the street corner?
They just happened to approach me!
Of course they did,
you're super beautiful!
Oh, stop!
She's right! You've got a great body
and great fashion taste!
You're as beautiful as they get!
You're a knockout!
That's not true!
You're on a whole different level from us!
Yeah! You're the trendiest girl in town!
What he said!
What am I doing wrong?
Yeah!
Feels off.
The fit, maybe?
It has to be.
If I wear the same clothes,
I'll be just like her!
Hey guys!
What'cha up to?
Yeah!
Oh yeah!
Oh-ho!
Right back at you, Cony!
Oh! Isn't that Jessica's outfit?
Yup!
I copied it!
How's it look?
It looks great on you!
Copying trendy fashion
is an easy way to match the trends!
A good fit goes a long way!
Oh, Moon, you flatterer.
Slurp...
Aw, how cute!
Oh, this? It is, isn't it?
Basic designs like that are in right now!
Where's it from?
I have no idea!
It was a souvenir.
Who gave it?
Who'd you get it from?
Ms. Smith on 3rd Street...
Hello, this is Cony!
Is this Ms. Smith?
I wanted to ask about the bracelet
you gave Jessica!
Yeah! The cute one with the basic design!
Where'd you buy it?
Africa?!
A souvenir from a trip to Africa, eh?
Doesn't matter, I gotta have it!
It's gotta be somewhere!
I'll find it!
That's why I always fall out of bed
every morning!
Oh, silly Moon.
What's wrong, Cony?
You look dead-tired...
Dat-dah!
Hey! Isn't that...?
Yup! I copied it!
Jessica, that was a souvenir, correct?
Yeah! I asked Ms. Smith over the phone,
and she said it was from Africa!
So I looked online for shops nearby
I could get African accessories from,
searching like crazy
for an identical bracelet...
and found one in the third town over!
How's it look?
It looks great on you, but...
Hey guys!
I got some cake! Wanna eat some at my place?
Absolutely!
Looks delish!
Pick whichever one you want!
Really? That's a hard choice!
Oh, I'll take the strawberry!
It's the only one.
Do you want any, Jessica?
No thanks, I'm on a diet.
Huh?!
None for you, Cony?
I-I'm also on a diet...
Then I'll take the strawberry!
Well, I guess I can make
an exception for today.
I guess I can make
an exception for today!
Yum yum in my—
I love strawberry!
I'll have the melon cake!
What?!
Good thinking!
The melon cake is this shop's top flavor!
Really? I gotta try it too!
I'll have the melon cake!
What's the big idea, Cony?!
You can have the strawberry, Moon!
Let's eat, Jessica!
Yes! Time for some cake.
Time for some cake.
It's delicious!
The melon tastes so divine!
Thank you, James!
You're absolutely welcome.
Check it out, I got a really good shot!
Silly James.
Ahahaha!
What's that?
Cony keeps copying Jessica?
There's nothing wrong with that.
Tip-toe, tip-toe...
Jessica!
Oh, it's just Sally and Brown.
What's the matter?
Cony's been creeping me out lately.
Cony being creepy?
The other day, she came to my house...
Hey, Jessica!
Wait, isn't that...?
It looked super cute, so I copied it!
But your name starts with a "C."
I know, but I wanna be like you!
Or really, I just wanna be you!
I'm sorry?!
You have a really good eye for everything!
Talk about taste!
What shampoo do you use, Jessica?
What body soap?
What toothpaste?
Aww!
This is so cute!
Huh?!
Mind if I copy it?
Ever since then...
Cony?
What in the world?!
I saw you buy it,
and ended up copying you!
You saw me buy it?
Aww!
That's super cute!
Mind if I copy it?
Uhh...
Hey, Jessica!
What'cha eating today?
Mind if I copy?
I'm sorry?
She shows up wherever I go.
Mind if I copy?
Mind if I copy? Mind if I copy?
Mind if I copy you, Jessica?
Jessica!
Stay away!
I'm even having nightmares
about her...
Cony's really creeping me out.
That's definitely crossing the line.
We must intervene.
Coming!
What did you do, Cony?!
I'm cute like Jessica, am I not?
It even looks like Jessica's house.
Darn...
I wish I had big, pretty eyes like Jessica's...
Maybe I should get surgery!
What?!
Cony, this has to stop!
You're plenty pretty the way you are!
There you go again.
I mean it!
Don't you agree, Brown?
But Jessica is way prettier,
and more fashionable,
and she picks out all the best items.
I love her so much!
I want to be just like her!
She's even deeper than I thought.
We have to get her to stop copying Jessica.
I'm dressed just like Jessica today!
Cony!
Hey, Jessica!
I was just on my way to see... you?
Bleh-leh-leh-leh!
Yo'sup!
I'm confused.
About what?
Uh... everything, I guess?
This outfit's the latest trend!
It is?!
It's super fashionable!
Feel free to copy!
Uh, okay...
Thanks.
You're super pretty!
I am?
Bleh-leh-leh-leh!
Bwah?
Yo'sup!
Wow! You two are really rocking
this year's must-have accessories!
You're beautiful!
Thanks.
Hey, um...
What's the deal with that
"bleh-leh" sound?
Huh? Are you living under a rock?
It's only the trendiest
way to say hi!
All the trendsetters are saying it!
They... are?
Cony!
Hey, Sally!
Bleh-leh-leh-leh!
Um, guys? What's...?
Yo'sup!
Y-Yo'sup...
Oh, Brown!
Bleh-leh-leh-leh!
Yeah, that's past my limit...
I guess being Jessica's
not in store for me.
Huh? You made up that trendy greeting?
We had to do it. We thought
you'd keep copying Jessica forever.
Sorry, Cony.
No, I am.
Hey guys! I got more cakes!
Wanna go eat?
Absolutely!
I'll have melon!
Then I'll have strawberry!
It's better to be yourself
than to try and be someone else!
Time for cake!
Hey, guys! Bleh-leh-leh-leh!
Yo'sup!
You guys living under a rock or somethin'?
It's only the trendiest way to say hi!
Why the laughs?!
Hey! I want cake!
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
I dreamt I was flying through the night sky
mahou no juutan ni notte
On a magic carpet
tondeku yozora no yume
And I just wanted you to see it
kimi ni mo
kimi ni mo misetakute
misetai
Oh, did I wake you? I'm so sorry
okoshichatta kana? gomen ne
I thought you sounded half-asleep
neboketa kotobatachi ni
And it made me swoon
nandaka
nandaka kyun to kita
kyun kyun
Just like the glittering scent of rose tea
kirameku kaori no roozu tii mitai ni
When my heart starts pounding, I lock up
dokidoki no sono shunkan
tojikomeru
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
Even though I could just type a <3 and send it to you
yubisaki haato wo nosete
tsutawattara ii no ni
It's hard to sum up the way I feel for you
kimi e no kono kimochi
hitokoto ja tarinai
It's like a millefeuille
egao mo namida mo zenbu
With all of my smiles and tears mixed in
tsumikasaneta mirufiiyu
I feel happy, I feel painful
ureshii setsunai itoshii
I feel longing — I'm in love
koishiteru
pickiness
job
Next time on Line Town...
Are you picky about anything?
Like insisting on going in the bath beak-first,
or liking ice cream a lot better
when it's all melty.
pickiness
job
Pickiness comes in many forms!
Personally speaking,
I'm picky about eating ground natto
with Tobasco sauce.