A-B-C-D-E-F-G
H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P
Q-R-S-T-U-V-W
X-Y and Z
Now you know your ABCs
Isn't it bizarre, the way we string together
letters from A to Z?
Whether it be out loud or by text,
let's find something to talk about!
How will the world end? What's for dinner?
Let's share those moments of laughter and tears
I decide what I like and hate
But that too is a barrier I can break down
Don't you see? Our words make us who we are
There's something I want to talk about with you
Just thinking about that gets me all giddy
Whether you're right next to me or not
You always brighten up my day
Of all the things you've spoken to me
I cherish every last word
It feels good to think about somebody
And it feels good to put that into words
early bird
I can't wait to eat some sushi-sushi-sushi!
Oh, how long I have waited for this day!
Chirashi sushi made with the freshest ingredients,
limited to 10 a day at a popular sushi place!
I need it right now!
Good morning, Cony!
Hey, Jessica!
Where's Moon and Brown?
They shouldn't be too much longer, no?
We said we'd meet up at 5:00.
Boy, being up this early makes me tired.
Only five minutes left!
I can't wait to eat my fill of sushi!
This might end up being
the longest five minutes of my life!
Aw, who is it?
It's so early.
Five more minutes.
Come on, what?!
Brown, what's your problem?
Let me sleep in a bit longer.
What time is it?!
Aagh, I overslept big time!
Cony, Jessica!
Do you know what time it is?!
Yeah?
That would be 5:30.
Didn't I say we'd meet at 5:00?!
We better hurry to the sushi place,
or they'll sell out!
Wait!
Moon!
You're just gonna ignore the fact
you held us up?
Oh, come on.
For the record, I wouldn't have minded
if you just went without me.
Went where?! You've never told us how to find it!
Oh, really?
Here we are!
This is the place!
Hello.
We're sold out.
What?!
Aw, man. We just got here!
Uh, are you mad, Cony?
Well, yeah! Thanks a lot, Moon!
Why me? Brown should've called to wake me up earlier!
He tried calling you tons of times!
Now, now.
Well, you know where the shop is now,
so you can come whenever you want.
Cony, how about I go with you tomorrow morning?
Yeah, that's a good idea!
That's not the problem!
We all woke up early for this,
but you didn't!
I'm mad because you broke our promise!
Oh, come on! I sleep in one time!
Just you watch, I'll be up early tomorrow!
As if.
It'll happen! Waking up early is nothing for me!
Calm down...
Go for it.
But if you oversleep,
you have to pay for our sushi.
Wh-Why do I have to do that?
Huh? But I thought waking up early was "nothing"?
Uh, y-yeah, got it.
We'll meet up tomorrow morning at 5:00.
Brown, we've got this!
Relax, Brown.
I can guarantee you I won't oversleep.
I have a trick up my sleeve.
Presenting my foolproof trick
to getting up in the morning!
I'll start sleeping right now!
Early to bed, early to rise!
Good night!
I can't sleep!
Well, I guess I only did just wake up.
But if I get in some exercise,
it should wear out my body!
Now, Brown! Let's go for a jog!
The breeze by the ocean is so refreshing.
Juby-julee...
Hey, guys! Going for a jog?
How healthy!
Oh, yeah! How was your sushi this morning?
I don't think I could eat any more sushi myself.
James, if you keep driving around in that car,
you'll get out of shape!
Unfortunately, exercising isn't for me.
It's so unrefined.
Ciao, see you!
What's his problem?
I'mma try to catch up to his car.
Alright!
Come on!
I'll have to take a shortcut!
Sweet, I beat James' car!
We've made it!
Huh?!
When did you get there, Brown?!
Bye, Brown! Until we cruise by the sea next!
Brown, we're supposed to be running on foot!
Well, if we're gonna wear our bodies out,
may as well have fun doing it!
Alright, Brown!
Score on me, if you can!
Now, slow down!
If I can't even take one step,
how am I supposed to get any exercise?
Make it easier on me.
That's more like—
Let's swap.
Alright, Brown!
Catch it if you can!
Dang it! I'll try again!
Watch this!
Man!
Oh, are you playing soccer now?
James! This is perfect!
Huh?
Here I go!
Juby-julee!
Aw, come on!
Well, at least I tired myself out like I intended.
Now I can finally sleep...
Ugh, it hurts too much!
I can't sleep!
Just relax, Moon.
Stay calm!
Brown saves my shots...
James does too...
Juby-julee!
Even the sushi shop owner
just passing by saves my shots!
Welcome!
Welcome!!
Why is the sushi shop owner in my dreams anyways?!
There's no way I can sleep like this!
I have to count sheep!
One sheep...
Two sheep...
Three sheep...
We're at...
One trillion, nine hundred billion,
seventy eight million,
six hundred three thousand,
three hundred twelve.
One trillion, nine hundred billion,
seventy eight million,
six hundred three thousand,
three hundred thirteen.
Aw man, I was just falling asleep!
Hey, Moon!
Better go to bed now,
or you'll oversleep!
I don't need you to remind me!
Dang it, and I was just about to fall asleep.
Oh, what is it now?!
Hi, Moon!
Don't forget: we meet up at 5:00!
Yeah, yeah. 5:00.
I'll be there on time
and everything will be fine! Good night!
Oh, what now?!
Y'know what day it is tomorrow?
Who cares?!
They just had to wake me up, dang it!
Looks like I'll have to just stay up all night long!
Brown, neither of us sleeps, you got it?
If one of us starts nodding off,
the other will wake them up!
Sound good?
Shoot! That was close.
If I fall asleep now, I'm bound to oversleep.
I told you to wake me up!
What was that for?!
Wait, did I fall asleep?
Get up!!
What was that for, Brown?!
Wait, did I do it again?!
Five more minutes...
Shoot, when did I nod off?
What time is it?
Let's go!
It's almost 5:00...
Was Moon able to get up?
Hey!
Good morning, you two!
You woke up on time!
See? I told you!
I think you can forgive him for yesterday.
Yeah.
Sorry, Moon. I was a bit harsh on you.
Oh, gosh! Cony, Moon, your eyes are all red!
I was worried you might oversleep...
So was I.
You worry too much.
Now why would I oversleep?
We're all together now,
so let's go eat some sushi!
Yeah!
So when's it gonna open up?
diet
I've been coming to this buffet almost every day!
Their food is so good and cheap!
I can't get enough!
So what have you two been up to?
Cony, did you gain weight?
What? If anyone here gained weight, it's you!
What do you mean?
Dude, you're as round as a full moon!
What? There's no way.
I'm telling you, you're fat!
Overeating like that isn't good for you!
I'm not fat.
I'm not fat...
I'm not fat!
I am not fat!
Like I said, I'm not fat.
But why?!
Is it because I'm fat?
Did you dump me because I'm fat?!
I better lose weight...
I'm gonna get so slim!
Today, I start dieting!
Diet, diet...
I'm... on a diet...
Man, dieting is a real pain...
I wish there was an easier way to lose weight.
I know one!
You do?!
Of course.
The "Make-You-Look-Slim Mirror"?
Yeah, see?
That's not real!
He looks all messed up!
I've had my eye on it for a while,
but never took the chance to buy it.
Why don't you, Moon?
Huh?!
Look at this one!
The "Lose-Weight-in-Your-Sleep-atron"?!
And if you buy now,
you'll get 50 of 'em for the price of one!
Jeez, what a steal!
She sold me.
Time to lose some pounds!
First, the Make-You-Look-Slim Mirror.
Is... that me?!
Wow, I've already lost weight!
I look like a stud!
Gah, I forgot it only makes you look slim!
I almost let that thing fool me.
Good thing I also bought the
Lose-Weight-in-Your-Sleep-atron.
Did Moon end up getting the
Lose-Weight-in-Your-Sleep-atron?
Hey, Moon! Did you buy the machine?
If you got 50 of them, can I have one, pretty-please?
Help me!!
Help me!
Never mind.
Don't leave!!
You haven't lost one pound!
I'm not gonna take that from you.
Looks like the best option
is to stop eating entirely.
Today, I start fasting!
Hey, Brown.
Huh? You have a coupon for the buffet
and want me to come with you?
I'm on a diet.
No eating. No eating.
I guess I could have a little...
I-I mustn't...!
I want some...!
I'll have to stay here at home.
I'll never lose weight
if I keep giving into the temptations!
But I'm sure that hamburger Brown had
was super tasty...
And the pizza, and the donuts,
and the fried chicken, and the curry and rice...
Hang in there!
Coming...
M-Moon, did you lose weight?
More or less.
I lost 10 pounds.
I-I'm impressed,
but you have a pretty bad aura...
Do I?
We're heading over to Jessica's.
Wanna come with?
Huh?
Jessica said she made something called vegan donuts!
V-Vegan?
Hey there!
Vegans are people who don't eat
food made of animals,
including meat or fish.
So "vegan" donuts
are donuts made without eggs, dairy, or butter!
Have you ever had them?
Donut... Donut...
Let's go eat some vegan donuts!
Donut!
Oh, do you not like donuts?
No, I love them!
I'll gladly eat it!
M-Moon, eat the donuts, not me!!
Sorry, Donut—I mean, Cony!
What's gotten into him...?
That was close...
I almost ate Cony!
Maybe I can treat myself to a little something...
No, don't! You've made it this far!
But what'll one little bite do?
Maybe just for today...
If I continue my diet tomorrow,
everything will be okay!
It's weird... I hope he's okay...
What's wrong?
Oh, Sally.
We can't get in touch with Moon.
What?!
He's not picking up any calls
or answering his texts.
He doesn't answer the door either.
What could've happened?
Moon, Moon!
I'm coming in.
Are you there, Moon?
Moon? Moon?!
Moon! What on earth happened to you?
Oh, Sally...
So you ate everything you had under your roof.
Once I started, I couldn't stop.
Sorry, but do you mind pushing me?
Moon...
I'm sorry for causing you trouble.
Look at how you've rebounded.
This wasn't how it was supposed to be...
I was gonna get handsome and slim
and revisit the girl who dumped me...
You need to get outside a little.
I don't want anyone to see me like this...
Why don't you start dieting again?
Just forget it.
I'd rather stay here all by myself,
getting fatter and fatter
until I'm round as a ball.
Stop it, Moon!
You can't give up because of one setback!
B-But Sally...
Your friends are worried about you!
But I...
You don't have to do it alone!
Let's diet together!
Th-Thank you...
I'm hungry...
No! From now on, your meals
will be managed by our chef.
Who's that?
Yeah, yeah!
How could you forget me
when you're dealing with appearances?
Anyone would rebound
after going on such a sudden diet!
That's why...!
I've made James' special lunch!
Wait, I can eat all that?!
When you're on a diet,
it's important to balance your meals.
You can't just fast!
So, dig in!
Gladly!!
We'll keep track of your progress.
We'll weigh and write down your weight every day.
What the heck is this...?
A visualization!
I want you to picture your ideal you!
Huh? I can become as jacked as him?!
No doubts!
I believe you can!
Aww, you guys...
Do your best!
No!
I did it!
I'm still alive!
What's that about?
Whoa!
Is that you, Moon?
Good to see y'all!
Y-You got slim!
Sure did.
I shrunk out of all my clothes
and had to buy a bunch of new ones.
That's awesome!
How did you do it?
You wanna know?
I do!
Do you?
Yeah!
Do you really?
Yes!!
I got dumped by a girl because of my weight,
and this is how I got slim.
Wanna learn how?
Well, yeah! I said "yes" plenty of times!
Maybe I should write a book about my diet.
Look at how much of a hottie it's made me!
What?!
I severely doubt that girl
dumped you because of your weight.
Don't be like that.
Moon worked really hard,
so let him have his moment.
Oh, yeah!
I'm so handsome!
I'm awesome!
Oh, yeah!
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
I dreamt I was flying through the night sky
mahou no juutan ni notte
On a magic carpet
tondeku yozora no yume
And I just wanted you to see it
kimi ni mo
kimi ni mo misetakute
misetai
Oh, did I wake you? I'm so sorry
okoshichatta kana? gomen ne
I thought you sounded half-asleep
neboketa kotobatachi ni
And it made me swoon
nandaka
nandaka kyun to kita
kyun kyun
Just like the glittering scent of rose tea
kirameku kaori no roozu tii mitai ni
When my heart starts pounding, I lock up
dokidoki no sono shunkan
tojikomeru
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
Even though I could just type a <3 and send it to you
yubisaki haato wo nosete
tsutawattara ii no ni
It's hard to sum up the way I feel for you
kimi e no kono kimochi
hitokoto ja tarinai
It's like a millefeuille
egao mo namida mo zenbu
With all of my smiles and tears mixed in
tsumikasaneta mirufiiyu
I feel happy, I feel painful
ureshii setsunai itoshii
I feel longing — I'm in love
koishiteru
leader
bed hair
Next time on Line Town...
Someone once said,
"sow a habit, reap a character."
The way you think affects the things you do.
But it leads me to think of the phrase
"you reap what you sow."
leader
bed hair
So many phrases about sowing and reaping.
What's the deal with those?
That's all! Good night, everyone.