A-B-C-D-E-F-G
H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P
Q-R-S-T-U-V-W
X-Y and Z
Now you know your ABCs
Isn't it bizarre, the way we string together
letters from A to Z?
Whether it be out loud or by text,
let's find something to talk about!
How will the world end? What's for dinner?
Let's share those moments of laughter and tears
I decide what I like and hate
But that too is a barrier I can break down
Don't you see? Our words make us who we are
There's something I want to talk about with you
Just thinking about that gets me all giddy
Whether you're right next to me or not
You always brighten up my day
Of all the things you've spoken to me
I cherish every last word
It feels good to think about somebody
And it feels good to put that into words
mud balls
Aw man, another rainy day...
What?!
Look at me!
Who do you think I am?
And what about you?
It's so refreshing after rainfall!
Hey, Brown!
What are ya up to out here?
What's that?
An iron ball?
Or is it bronze?
Mud?
A mud ball?
Nah, you're joshing me.
That's obviously gotta be some sort of metal.
I mean, look at it! It's all smooth and shiny!
Though it's sorta light for metal.
A ball of mud can't look this polished.
Where on earth did you find this?
What?
You rolled that soil into this ball?
That's a good one.
There's no way you made such a clean ball
just by rolling mud!
...No way.
It really is made of mud!
Oh, sorry, uh...
You can just make another one?!
My word... You're an artisan.
I'm watching an artisan at work!
Master! That is, Mud Ball Master!
Please make me your apprentice!
I moon-st know your ways of making
such beautiful mud balls!
Thank you very moon-ch!
So, what first?
Knead the soil like clay.
Knead, knead, knead.
Then grip it firmly
to squeeze out the water.
Sprinkle some dry soil on it...
and shape it into a nice, round ball.
Master, it's not getting any rounder!
I need to have patience?
Take it one step at a time...
Devote myself, have patience,
make it nice and round...
Make it roooound...
I got impatient.
Lesson learned.
May as well make it a big one
while I'm at it!
What's that?
I shouldn't be greedy?
G-Got it.
Huh? Free myself of my inhibitions?
Empty my mind and focus on rolling it into a ball...
Becoming an artisan is real tough!
I did it!
Say, Master.
I got the round part down,
but it doesn't look very smooth or shiny.
Start polishing it with a cloth?
Geez, no way!
Becoming an artisan is no feeble task,
is it, Master?
It's finished! Master, look at this!
After all these years,
I've finally become a mud ball artisan of my own!
Hear that, Ma?!
Hm?
You want me to roll the mud ball
down this slide?
Did you see that?
That was marvelous!
What?!
I was naïve...
My mud balls still have
a long way to go...
The path to being a mud ball artisan
is not kind to my inexperience.
But I won't give up, Pa!
Not until I've become a shining star
among mud ball makers!
I'll have to start from square one!
Watch me, Master!
I'll make an even better mud ball than yours—
the ultimate mud ball!
Jessica, did you see Sally's text?
Yeah, she invited us to have dinner
at her place tonight!
I wonder what kind of food she's making!
Could it be Italian?
What about French?
I can't wait!
I could go for Chinese
or Japanese too!
Oh, did you know?
Apparently German chocolate cake
isn't German at all!
It's an American cake named after Samuel German!
Oh, now I'm craving German chocolate cake!
Well, not really.
Cony, you'll gain your weight back like that.
Hey, Moon, Brown!
Are you two gonna be there too?
Why are you ignoring me?!
Quiet.
Don't get in our way.
Rude much?
What are you up to?
We are busy crafting.
Crafting?
Crafting what exactly?
Mud balls.
Mud balls?
Look.
It's certainly mud.
And it is a ball.
Got that right!
So, what are you making them for?
I'm sorry?
Well, you can't eat them.
Of course not!
So what are they for?
Uh, what was it for again...?
They serve their own purpose!
That's disgusting!
It's that "disgusting" mud
which gives birth to a beautiful mud ball!
This is what all men dream of!
Right, Brown?
Beautiful, you say?
It just looks gross to me.
It hasn't become beautiful yet!
We're about to give it the ultimate beauty treatment!
Oh, okay.
Well, have fun with that.
Later!
Those girls just don't get it.
I'm going to make the ultimate
beautiful mud ball.
It'll be as beautiful as the
full moon in the night sky.
Full moon?!
I'd like this, please!
Sir, we have these smaller packets
for home use.
I want this.
Why, though?
Dreams, that's why!
Beams?
Dreams!
And I've got big ones!
Check this out, Brown.
I'm gonna make a special mud ball.
The ultimate mud ball: Moon Special!
It's done!
Behold!
My round ball, beautiful and white
as the full moon!
The ultimate mud ball: Moon Special!
The salty version!
Wow!
The Brown Special is beautiful as well!
My Moon Special!
Your Brown Special!
Which one will come out on top?
Ready, go!
Look at that! They're neck-in-neck!
Huh?
Moon, Brown, what are you two doing?
We... We were just...
...reflecting on how fleeting life is.
What..?
What's gotten into you guys?
Are you poets now or something?
Anyways, did you get Sally's text?
Huh?
What's wrong with them?
They keep talking about
what men dream of.
But I don't understand.
Maybe it doesn't matter, then.
Who else is hungry?
Okay! It's time for us to make dinner!
Huh? You're not making it?
It's more fun if we do it together!
Cony and Jessica, I want you to
cut the vegetables for the salad.
Okay!
Boys, I want you to knead the hamburger meat!
Nice and round!
We can get even rounder!
Guys, burgers are supposed to be flat, not round!
Like this!
Oh, no...
It's not going to cook well
if you keep kneading it like that...
Quiet! Stay out of our way!
Hamburgers are what all men dream of!
Are the burgers ready yet?
I'm hungry...
I know, but these guys...
Alright, I'm gonna make the ultimate,
perfectly-round hamburger!
The Moon Special!
Knead-knead, knead-knead, knead-knead!
faking sick
Yes, I finally got one!
A ticket to the Silk5's dream concert!
And it was the last one in stock!
And it's a front row seat!
I can't believe I get to meet them in person!
Yippee!
Huh? What's Moon texting about?
"Don't be late to the bus tour
tomorrow, you hear?"
Please, you don't gotta remind me.
Tomorrow?
Whaaaat?!
What? No way! Huh? Oh, no, oh no!
Play with the dolphins,
a day-trip bus tour of the aquarium...
It really is tomorrow...
What do I do now?
She's late!
Wasn't she the one who picked this out?
I had a feeling this would happen,
so I sent her a text, and she still forgot!
It's Cony!
Hey, we're waiting for you!
Where are you?
I think I have a cold...
I woke up this morning with a fever
and a cough...
Aw! Are you alright?
I think it'll get better with some rest.
Sorry! Please play with the dolphins for me, okay?
We will! Take care, okay?
She's staying home with a cold.
Say what?
I can see dolphins any day,
but meeting Silk5 in person
is a once-in-a-lifetime experience!
All done!
Cheering fan, finished!
Happi coat, check!
Headband, check!
And lastly, all five glowsticks
so I can go nuts!
Silk, silk,
soy milk and salt!
It's a bit early,
but I just can't wait!
Oh?
"'I'm on my way,' from Moon".
Cough-cough!
Hey, Moon! Where are you on your way to?
Where do you think? Your house!
Wh-huh? Why?
My house isn't near the aquarium!
Cough-cough...
The bus is having troubles,
so it got called off!
What?!
It's not too far away, so we'll be there soon.
Huh?
She hung up!
Why did it turn out like this?!
Sorry, were you in bed?
You look terrible.
Thanks for coming here, but my cough is real bad,
so maybe you shouldn't...
'Sup.
Don't just come in!
Game time!
What's your problem?
Aren't you here to check on me?
Check up on you? After you stood us up?
Why would I do that?
What was I supposed to do?
Cough, cough, cough...
I just came here because I remembered
you had this new video game.
That's why you're here?!
I'm getting dizzy...
Are you alright, Cony?
Should I carry you to your bed?
Thank you...
Let's go!
I kinda want to get some sleep!
The porridge is almost done,
so you can sleep after you eat!
Porridge for lunch, huh?
How about we have pork cutlet for dinner, then?
What d'ya mean dinner?!
This is my house! So scram!
Why is she mad at us?
We're just looking after her.
La-la-la, Silk!
Better than cotton,
it's silk!
What's that?
Jessica?
Hey, what's up?
I'm in a bit of a rush.
A rush? Where are you going?
I heard you were in bed with a cold,
so I came to come see you...
Huh?
I'm at your door,
but you didn't respond to the doorbell,
so I got confused.
I'm here...
You're covered in sweat!
You must be very sick...
Cough, cough...
Sorry to bother you...
Sleep is important for a cold!
I'll have a delicious treat prepared
for when you wake up, so hang in there!
A treat?
Yep!
I've been meaning to try making this salmon paella
recipe my friend taught me!
How long will that take?
I still have to make the clam broth,
so it'll be a few hours.
Sorry, I have no appetite!
Bye, another time maybe!
Maybe I shouldn't have said
I'll "try" making it...
People keep getting in my way left and right!
I have to hurry up or I won't make it in time!
Another call?!
What now, Moon?
Wait, James?
I had to borrow Moon's phone.
Looks like I left mine at your house by mistake.
Whaaat?
I've been calling my phone nonstop since I noticed.
Didn't you hear it ringing?
Oh, uh, no...
Ah, no worries. You were asleep, right?
I'll come and get it now!
Aaagh, wait, hold on!
I'm feeling much, much worse than earlier...
In what places?
My throat, my head, my joints...
Practically my whole body!
So don't come!
It's that bad?!
I'll be right over!
I just said don't come!
Would you like a special burger?
Huh, what was that? Are you outside?
Huh? Did you hear something?
I-I sure didn't!
You cray-cray!
Ayyy...
Are you at the hospital?
Huh? The hospital?
O-Oh, yeah, yeah, that's it.
I'm actually at the hospital!
So I can grab your phone tomorrow,
if you don't mind waiting.
I'm actually driving near the hospital now,
so let me pick you up!
Wait, James!!
Why is it all the way up there?!
CLOSED
Huh? It's closed!
Cony! The hospital seems to be closed.
CLOSED
I begged hard enough
and they let me in.
CLOSED
We have to hurry!
There's not much time!
CLOSED
Huh? Not much time for what?
Doesn't matter!
CLOSED
Okay!
What the?!
Wh-Why are you guys here?!
You left your door unlocked!
You're so careless.
Oh, I see. I guess I forgot to lock it on my way out.
Thanks for pointing—
No, that's not the point!
You can't just waltz into my house!
Think nothing of it.
I'll think everything of it!
I'm thinking about that cherry.
Nah, just messing.
Wasn't that a funny bit, Cony?
If it was, feel free to laugh.
It absolutely wasn't!
My house isn't an arcade!
Now scram already!
Not until I'm finished with this game!
Get outta here! Scram! Shoo!
What've you got there, Brown?
Why, you little...!
D-Don't worry about that!
H-Huh? It's so late!
I gotta pee!
I won't give up, even if I only make it for their final song!
Silk, silk, silk!
Soy milk, salt, cold tofu,
boiled tofu, soy pulp!
Yeah!
...Huh?
It's already over?
My Silk5...!
Oh, is that you, Cony?
Huh? Sally?
The concert was postponed
because one of the members was feeling sick.
Huh? For real?!
I just found out too!
But I'm surprised to see you here!
I was gonna say that!
I didn't know you were into Silk5!
I saw their videos and fell in love!
Huh?
What's up?
Do you have a cold?
No, I was just faking it...
What the?
Your temperature is very high!
That's what you get for lying to us!
You should've just told us you wanted
to go to the concert over the aquarium!
But I...
Good evening!
The salmon paella came out
better than I expected!
I was hoping you would get to
have some with us, but...
You need to rest, don't you?
I'm so hungry...
Nope. Sorry, Cony, but you need to get some sleep.
We'll eat it for you!
Aw, what?
It's time for a paella party!
Let's raise the roof, guys!
W-Wait, come on...
Don't listen to him.
We'll leave some leftover.
So rest your head and relax, okay?
This is great!
It's exquisite! Juby-julee-bonne!
I really like the mussels!
I'm glad!
Brown, you're making a mess!
Brown!
Hey!
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
I dreamt I was flying through the night sky
mahou no juutan ni notte
On a magic carpet
tondeku yozora no yume
And I just wanted you to see it
kimi ni mo
kimi ni mo misetakute
misetai
Oh, did I wake you? I'm so sorry
okoshichatta kana? gomen ne
I thought you sounded half-asleep
neboketa kotobatachi ni
And it made me swoon
nandaka
nandaka kyun to kita
kyun kyun
Just like the glittering scent of rose tea
kirameku kaori no roozu tii mitai ni
When my heart starts pounding, I lock up
dokidoki no sono shunkan
tojikomeru
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
Even though I could just type a <3 and send it to you
yubisaki haato wo nosete
tsutawattara ii no ni
It's hard to sum up the way I feel for you
kimi e no kono kimochi
hitokoto ja tarinai
It's like a millefeuille
egao mo namida mo zenbu
With all of my smiles and tears mixed in
tsumikasaneta mirufiiyu
I feel happy, I feel painful
ureshii setsunai itoshii
I feel longing — I'm in love
koishiteru
typhoon
headline
Next time on Line Town...
Gâteau au chocolat,
framboise choux à la crème...
Desserts can sound so sweet
just by their names alone!
On the other hand—boiled eggs,
fish cakes, pig's trotters... don't sound as sweet.
typhoon
headline
Oh, not to wage a war on oden!
Next time: "The Oden Strikes Back!"
Wait, nope.