A-B-C-D-E-F-G
H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P
Q-R-S-T-U-V-W
X-Y and Z
Now you know your ABCs
Isn't it bizarre, the way we string together
letters from A to Z?
Whether it be out loud or by text,
let's find something to talk about!
How will the world end? What's for dinner?
Let's share those moments of laughter and tears
I decide what I like and hate
But that too is a barrier I can break down
Don't you see? Our words make us who we are
There's something I want to talk about with you
Just thinking about that gets me all giddy
Whether you're right next to me or not
You always brighten up my day
Of all the things you've spoken to me
I cherish every last word
It feels good to think about somebody
And it feels good to put that into words
ninjas
A ninja movie?
Yeah. A friend of mine is directing,
and it's going to be shown
all over the world.
Wow!
And he wanted me to bring him
someone fit to play the ninja.
But I don't know anyone
very ninja-li...
Th-This is my chance!
I'm gonna be a global star
as a dazzling beauty ninja!
A dazzling beauty ninja?
Yeah, the best kind there is!
I'll go change into my costume
and meet you in the park, Sally!
Juby-julee!
Sally!
Oh?
Tis I, the shiny beautiful ninja!
Take mine heart shurikens!
Juby-juby-juby!
Flap, flap, flap...
Looking great, James!
So I'll get to play the ninja, right?
Hold your horses!
It is I, ninja Moon!
Hah!
Ouch, that hurt...
Moon!
You want to play the ninja too?
Well, duh!
You think I'm gonna let you
swipe the role for yourself?
I'm the most fit to play a ninja!
No, I am!
Say what?
The kunoichi Conymaru hath arrived!
Cony?
You want it too?
Yeah, ever since it came up!
I gotta do it!
No way!
Both of you are way too flashy
for "ninjas" anyways!
Ninjas are subtle,
always calm in the face of...
What the heck?
Salmon roe?
Brown?!
Oh my! You're more ninja-like
than anyone else!
Huh? You want to become
a global ninja star
and eat salmon steak every day?
Listen here.
One does not become a ninja
for such frivolous reasons.
You just want the fame too.
I do not!
Okay, Sally, I know I haven't
brought this up before,
but my ancestors were ninjas!
There he goes, lying through his teeth.
The Moon bloodline spans
generations of ninjas.
My great-great-great grandfather
was named Igano Moonmaru.
Thus, it is grave that I take on this role.
The pride of the Moon bloodline
is at stake!
Huh?
I wanna be the ninja!
I'm perfect for the role!
I'm more perfect!
No, I am!
Hmm... This is a toughie...
Aha! I have an idea!
We'll compete for this ninja scroll
each making use of our ninja skills.
For the ninja scroll?
Yes. Whoever takes the scroll
and brings it to Jessica's house
will be deemed the best ninja.
Nice, sounds like a plot
from a ninja comic!
Oh, I'm gonna win this!
I know a lot about ninja skills!
Then let's do it.
Sound good, Sally?
Yeah.
Then I'll call Jessica
to let her know.
Hello?
Huh? You're coming over
with this roll of yours?
O-Okay, then.
A roll of sushi?
Better get started on a broth, then!
Let's begin!
Ready, set... go!
I've got it!
No, I do!
Hehe, all mine!
Hey!
Cheater!
That's a ninja for ya!
Get back here!
I bought a bunch of ninja stuff online!
Ninpo, slippery-slide!
Oh no! Oil stains won't come out easily!
I have to get this cleaned quickly!
Brown!
Stop!
D-Dang!
When did he get so good?
Stop admiring him!
Nowhere left to run!
Hand over the ninja scroll!
Wow!
L-Look at him go!
H-He's running on water!
Hey, I can do it too!
Gotta get my left foot in
before my right foot goes under...
That was close...
Oh! Hey, James!
Yeah?
Way to go!
You're a legend!
Yeah!
You look awesome!
Do a spin!
Wow!
I got it!
Juby-julee!
Hey!
Get back here, James!
Oh no, they're catching up!
I know!
This calls for... Juby!
Ninpo, pretend!
James! Wait...
What?
Where'd he go?
I don't see him.
Dang it, he got away.
Ow!
There you are.
I can't believe James got away!
Oh, well. Let's rest up instead!
I'm taking a seat!
Sit, guys, let's have tea!
That sounds good.
So... heavy...
I hope I don't drop my scorching hot tea!
Whoops!
Gah! Hot, hot, hot!
Got it!
Hey! Stop!
I shall stay here until morning.
I cannot make a single sound.
Ack! No sleeping!
Wh-What is that?!
C-Cony...
Wake up, Cony!
Th-There's a beast!
I'm scared! S-So scared...
Man, that was some good sleep.
Alright! Let's finish the job!
Wake up, James.
You too, Brown.
I could hardly sleep...
Rise and shine, gang!
Catch me if you can!
Hey! Get back here!
Why's he going up the mountain?
Is he plotting something?
Moon?!
I'm gonna fly straight to Jessica's house!
Time to be a ninja star!
Oh no.
Sweet!
W-Wait, don't...
Moon!
Oh no!
Hang in there!
We'll pull you up!
One, two...
Almost there!
I'm so glad you're okay.
Me too.
Thank you, guys!
I'm in your debt!
If I win $1 million in the lottery,
I'll let you stare at it behind glass!
Uh, thanks?
Hey, why don't we ask the director
if he can make four ninja characters?
It'll be even more fun
if we all get to be in it!
Agreed!
Yeah, I'm down.
Bravo, bravo!
This is the movie director!
Huh?!
A story of fellowship among ninjas
sounds absolutely beautiful!
But unfortunately,
there's been a change of plans.
We decided to do a kaiju film instead!
My apologies.
Roar!
Oh my gosh!
When's the sushi coming?
bottle opener
Huh? Are you kidding me?
Who gives away a bottle opener
for a store anniversary?
Oh, well. At least it's cute,
so I can put it up in my room.
Ouch, jeez...
Dang it! It won't budge.
C'mon, open!
Oh, Cony. Just as happy-go-lucky as ever.
Wait! Is that...?
It is!
Cony!
Hey, don't scare me like that!
Is that a bottle opener you're holding?!
Huh?
What's it to you?
Could you lend—I mean, gimme it?
I need that more than anything!
Why's that?
Why else? I would like to drink this
cold and refreshing squash now!
I won it in a giveaway...
but I don't have a bottle opener!
So please, give it over!
I'll give you something
good in exchange!
Good? Like what?
Uhh...
It's good, I promise!
Oh, fine. Take it.
Yeah! Thanks!
So good!
Nothin' better than
some refreshing squash!
So what've you got for me?
This.
I'm sorry?
It's a rock-hard cookie!
So hard, I can't even break it
with my hands!
You said it would be something good.
So refreshing! I feel full'a energy!
See ya later, Cony!
Hey, wait up, Moon!
What's so good about
a rock-hard cookie?
Hello?
Ow...
Deary me.
Agh! I crashed it again!
Man, why can't I drive this
RC car right?
It's so ugly of me...
What's wrong, James?
Get this, Cony!
My skin's been rough all day,
and my hair's been all messy,
and it's driving me insane!
So I thought it would be nice and relaxing
if I took this car out for a cruise!
But it's driving me even more insane.
I'm so pent up! It's getting real bad!
James, stop biting your fingernails!
I know!
Try biting on this cookie instead!
Yo, dial it back a bit...
It's so hard! As hard as a rock!
But when I bite down on it,
I can feel my frustrations fading away!
Y-You do?
I feel so much better now!
Thanks, Cony!
To repay the favor,
you can have my RC car!
I can?
I'm so cookie I met you!
I mean, lucky.
Bye!
What a strange turn of events.
Huh?
S-Sally, hang in there!
What's wrong?
Hi, Cony...
I bought too many things,
and it's too heavy to carry.
I'm too worn out to go much further.
I can carry it the rest of the way.
You don't have to do that for me!
Oh! Sally, I have just the thing!
Why don't you load your bag on this?
It's a perfect fit!
This is great!
Can I have it, Cony?
Oh!
Sure.
Thank you so much!
Up!
Well, alright then!
Glad I got to help her out!
I feel so happy!
Cony!
Sally?!
This car is so handy!
I already unloaded my things!
Already?!
And I brought something
to repay your favor!
Huh?
I was given a very rare salmon,
but I don't have room in my fridge for it.
I can have that?
It's the least I can do!
Am I on a lucky streak today or what?
This is pretty heavy, though...
Hey, Brown!
You want it?
That adds up.
No one else would want this
more than you, Brown!
All yours!
Can I have something in return?
What the heck?
What am I supposed to do with these?
Why does Brown even have all this?
I could get used to these.
This is super fun!
Cony's big grinny samba!
Oh?
She's got a big smile! Cony samba!
Cony!
Why are you dancing?
Dunno, it just happened!
It's a lotta fun though!
C'mon, join me!
I'll pass, thanks...
A-one, a-two, a-three...
Apologies for interrupting
your fun, ma'am.
What could it be?
If you don't mind,
would you please give me
those instruments and your costume?
You mean mine?
Yes. We were watching you dance,
and since you seemed to be having
a very fun time,
our little lady is enamored with your belongings.
Sounds fancy.
If you choose to give it to me,
we will recompensate you fairly!
See this.
What is it?
A gift certificate you can use anywhere.
You can buy yourself positively anything with it.
I can?
That's amazing!
So, do you accept?
Yes! Absolutely!
What a deal!
I'm so happy!
He said I could buy anything at all!
That's a tough choice to make!
Wonder what I should buy?
I heard from Jessica
you got an amazing gift certificate?
See for yourself!
Bam!
To think trading that bottle opener
would lead me to such a big treasure!
It's a dream come true!
It is for me too!
Hard to decide what I should buy!
Huh? Who says you get to use it?
What? Don't I get a say?
Why should you, huh?
You're hogging it?!
Of course I am. It's all mine!
If I hadn't traded my rock-hard cookie
for your bottle opener,
you would've never gotten that!
I deserve some of the credit!
My magic certificate!
I'm so thirsty...
Can I have some juice?
Water it is.
Wait, what?
What are you doing...?
I-I don't know! Help me, Moon!
Stop the water!
No way. Don't you have anything
to shut the faucet?
Why would I?
Oh, right!
I have just the thing!
The bottle opener!
Thank gosh!
Work its magic already!
You want it so badly,
I need something in return.
Is this really the time?
Gift certificate for the bottle opener.
Shut up, Moon, just do something!
Do we have a deal?
Just stop the water!
No deal? Then I'm leaving.
W-Wait, don't go!
Fine! We have a deal!
Alright!
It's over...
Sweet! The gift certificate's all mine!
Gonna go buy something! Whoo!
Wonder why he's all giddy.
Cony, what happened here?
You're sopping wet!
Sop... sop...
That's rough.
So Moon took the certificate.
Yeah. Guess he was the lucky one here, not me.
I'm not so sure.
Thanks to you,
I got my shopping home
without getting crushed.
And if I hadn't come across you,
I'd still be frustrated!
And you wouldn't have given
Brown that amazing salmon!
You made us all very happy,
so I think you're very lucky today.
Aw, that's great.
Now I'm hungry!
Then let's eat! Brown didn't want
to waste all the salmon on himself,
so he prepared it à la meunière!
Let's eat!
Wonder what Moon decided
to buy with that certificate.
I get the last laugh!
I bought a whole batch
of refreshing squashes!
Time to drink one!
Oh shoot.
I don't have a bottle opener...
Help! I need a bottle opener!
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
I dreamt I was flying through the night sky
mahou no juutan ni notte
On a magic carpet
tondeku yozora no yume
And I just wanted you to see it
kimi ni mo
kimi ni mo misetakute
misetai
Oh, did I wake you? I'm so sorry
okoshichatta kana? gomen ne
I thought you sounded half-asleep
neboketa kotobatachi ni
And it made me swoon
nandaka
nandaka kyun to kita
kyun kyun
Just like the glittering scent of rose tea
kirameku kaori no roozu tii mitai ni
When my heart starts pounding, I lock up
dokidoki no sono shunkan
tojikomeru
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
Even though I could just type a <3 and send it to you
yubisaki haato wo nosete
tsutawattara ii no ni
It's hard to sum up the way I feel for you
kimi e no kono kimochi
hitokoto ja tarinai
It's like a millefeuille
egao mo namida mo zenbu
With all of my smiles and tears mixed in
tsumikasaneta mirufiiyu
I feel happy, I feel painful
ureshii setsunai itoshii
I feel longing — I'm in love
koishiteru
jessica
car
Yo'sup!
Next time on Line Town...
Jessica has a great body,
she's super pretty,
and she's a reader's model!
She's our idol!
But trouble is in store
when Cony gets a little obsessed!
jessica
car
Jessica becomes terrified
of the strange monster Cony!
Hey, this isn't a horror movie.
Bleh-leh-leh-leh!