A-B-C-D-E-F-G
H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P
Q-R-S-T-U-V-W
X-Y and Z
Now you know your ABCs
Isn't it bizarre, the way we string together
letters from A to Z?
Whether it be out loud or by text,
let's find something to talk about!
How will the world end? What's for dinner?
Let's share those moments of laughter and tears
I decide what I like and hate
But that too is a barrier I can break down
Don't you see? Our words make us who we are
There's something I want to talk about with you
Just thinking about that gets me all giddy
Whether you're right next to me or not
You always brighten up my day
Of all the things you've spoken to me
I cherish every last word
It feels good to think about somebody
And it feels good to put that into words
galaxy
Juby-julee,
juby-julee-julee-julee-julee!
Hey, James.
Hi, Cony! Hi, Brown!
I've been wondering for a while,
what does "juby-julee" mean anyways?
It's a tune passed down
from my ancestors!
Dang, your ancestors?
Yeah! My mom, dad, grandma
and grandpa all sing it!
A tune passed down from your ancestors, eh?
Real interesting.
I don't suppose it has
any meaning, no?
Nope!
There's a lot of different melodies for it,
including forbidden ones I musn't sing no matter what!
Forbidden melodies? Like what?
I wanna hear those!
Here's one of them.
Unh! Juby-julee! Juby-julee!
Juby-julee! Unh!
"Juby-julee?"
"Juby-julee..."
Huh. But you said it was forbidden, right?
What happens now?
Beats me. I've never tried before!
It's just a myth anyways.
Just a myth, huh? Makes sense.
Juby-julee! Juby-julee! Juby-julee!
Huh?!
What in the world?
Are you the one
who declared "juby-julee?"
We accept.
Accept what?!
I-I don't understand what's happening here!
You declared "juby-julee!"
Which means we must
go to war over your territory!
Go to war?!
Yes! A war for the Milky Way!
And if you lose, the Milky Way
will belong to us!
Say what?!
We can't just give away
a whole galaxy!
Then you'll have to win.
P-Please, hold on a minute!
I had no idea I was signing up for this!
That's on you!
Bad! Bad!
I'm so sorry! It was just an accident!
Please, can I withdraw my declaration?
You may, if you cover our travel expenses.
Huh?
Transportation, fuel,
and other expenses add up to...
$400 million.
$400 million?!
Juby-julee...
How's he supposed to cover that?!
Then fight us.
Only way out is to win the game.
What game?
Volleyball, what else?
Wh-Why volleyball?
You chose it!
Huh?
You said: "I request a volleyball war
over the Milky Way galaxy. July-julee."
That's what my juby-julee meant?!
Your words! Your words! Your words!
Volleyball?
Yeah. If we don't beat them,
they're gonna take the Milky Way galaxy.
So that means they get the Earth?
And the moon and the sun?
We can't do this...
What are we supposed to do?
Isn't it obvious?
We kinda have to take them on!
Get serious, James.
But I've never played volleyball before!
I'm scared! I don't wanna do this!
Okay. Then pay 'em the $400 million.
But none of you guys have
played volleyball before either!
They're gonna wipe the floor with us!
Oh yeah! Didn't Moon say once
that he's done volleyball?
You're right, he did!
"Did you know I used to do volleyball?
I was an attacker."
I lost count of how often
he's told me that.
Come to think of it,
where is Moon?
He's not picking up your calls?
I bet he's sleeping in. It's just like him
to be useless at a time like this.
Okay, okay. How about we go
spy on the other team?
I'm down!
That's it!
There!
Go!
You think you'll win
with plays like those?!
Moon?!
Oh, hey guys!
What are you doing here?
Teaching the aliens how to play volleyball!
Did you know I used to do volleyball?
I was an attacker.
I was a real crowd-pleaser,
which was a real me-pleaser.
Why are you helping the aliens?
They recruited me!
Said if their team wins, they'll give me the moon!
The moon?
Yup! The whole satellite, all for me!
Whew, I can't believe it!
Hold on, Moon.
You know if we lose,
the aliens get the Earth, right?
Hmm... Not sure if I like that...
But I can't pass down a chance
to get the moon!
Once I get the moon,
I'mma build a vacation home there!
And you're all welcome
to come down and hang with me.
Why would we visit you?
I was wrong about you, Moon.
How could you betray us?
You're a monster.
Juby-julee!
Ow-ow! What's your problem?
It's the moon!
Anyone would cave for that!
Cut it out, boys!
Stop it! Stop!
Moon, listen. None of us
have played volleyball before.
We could really use your help.
Huh?
I understand how much
you want the moon.
But could you please set it aside
and fight alongside us?
Coach us! Coach us!
I'm sorry.
This is all my fault.
All of this is because of me.
I'm really, really sorry
for doing this to all of you.
We just have to win.
Sally...
There's no use getting glum
before we even try.
We can't give up yet.
Let's practice, and do whatever we can.
There's still time.
Well said.
Alright! We're gonna win so hard,
Moon's gonna be gobsmacked!
"Gobsmacked?"
That's pretty old-fashioned, don't you think?
I guess so.
Aw, you guys...
We won't let anyone take
the Milky Way!
We will win this!
Yeah!
Guys! We found a substitute for Moon!
You did?
Oh yeah, since volleyball is played
with a team of six.
It's the part-time worker
from the burger joint...
Cobtaro!
Huh? Cobtaro?
He can play volleyball?
Tsk tsk tsk.
Cobtaro's abilities
are nothing to sneeze at.
Magnificent!
Whoa, awesome!
Cobtaro is a libero!
What's that?
They handle the receive.
Glad to have you on board, Cobtaro.
There!
You've got it!
I got it!
Ouch...
Are you okay, Cony?
Darn, Cony, you jumped too late.
James, you gotta straighten your arms.
Jessica, keep your eyes on the ball.
And why oh why
did you substitute me with Cobtaro?
Yours!
Go!
One more!
Hmph. They're wasting their time.
They don't stand a chance.
This is my big chance!
The moon's gonna be all mine!
We will soon begin the game
for the Milky Way galaxy.
We're gonna win!
No, we are!
Whoever wins three sets first
will win the game.
Tails.
Heads.
Tails. Team Alien will serve.
Great!
Let's go!
Cobtaro, you receive the ball.
I will toss.
Cony, James, be ready to attack.
Jessica, Brown, be ready to
save the ball if they block it.
We will win this!
Yeah!
Here I come!
Cobtaro!
Oh dear...
Do you forfeit?
Huh?
If you all leave the court mid-match,
it will be considered a forfeit
and Team Alien wins,
granting them the Milky Way galaxy.
That can't be...
Those are the rules.
We win! We win! We win! We win!
We will continue.
Huh? But what about Cobtaro?
He'll be back. We'll have to
do what we can for now.
With a team of five? Just forget it.
You may as well forfeit.
Not happening!
We have this in the bag.
Oh, you're on! Even without a full team,
we're still gonna beat you!
Yeah! I can handle the work
for two members!
Let's go!
Team Alien wins the first set.
I tried to warn you.
Don't expect my sympathy.
Ouch...
They're way better than I thought.
I don't think five of us is enough...
Hey, it's from Cobtaro!
Let's see here...
"There's no ships until tomorrow morning,
"so I won't be back in Line Town until then?"
What the heck?!
Where on earth did Cobtaro land?
At least he's fine and well.
Huh? Oh, I just bumped it a bit hard.
But don't worry about me.
Show them what we're about, Brown!
Block!
We did it!
What was that, huh?
Th-They just caught me by surprise.
Are you okay, Jessica?
Y-Yeah. Don't worry.
They're attacking Jessica!
Toss!
Are you okay, Jessica?
Wait, did you sprain your ankle?!
Shh! They'll hear you, Cony?
Why didn't you tell us earlier?
Because if I sit out,
you'll be down to a team of four.
That's just not enough to win.
I see...
Please don't worry about me.
The aliens win the second set!
I'm sorry, guys.
Please don't apologize, Jessica.
How ugly of those aliens to attack
a weak damsel in pain!
We have this in the bag.
And soon the win will be ours.
When we get the Milky Way,
let's turn the Earth into a donut factory!
Good call! Good call!
Since you're getting the moon...
If you win us the game,
we'll throw in the M79 cluster.
Huh? Oh, uh, cool.
What's the matter?
You look mighty glum.
What are you talking about?
I'm super happy!
We've got this!
Oh, okay!
I'm worried about them...
Jessica...
Brown?!
Thank you, Brown.
Are you okay?
I knew five of us
wouldn't be enough!
Jessica's likely going to hit her limit soon.
Is this it for us?
Time out!
I will be swapping teams.
Moon?!
Get it together!
You can't give up now!
Don't you care if they swipe
the Milky Way from you?
Moon...
Traitor!
Bad! Bad! Bad!
Did you give up on the moon?
Wouldn't have been any fun anyways
if no one came to visit.
Thank you, Moon!
You are such a wonderful friend, Moon!
It's too late.
Good luck, guys!
Got it!
Moonsault Scramble Attack!
Wow!
Amazing! Look at you go, Moon!
I told you I was a crowd-pleaser
back in my volleyball days.
You're so cool!
Team Line Town wins the third set!
Yeah!
If we keep this up,
we can win the next set too!
Twirling Spinning Rolling Attack!
Team Line Town wins the sixth set!
Yeah!
Magnificent!
Curse you!
Time to bring out our last resort.
Whoever wins this set
will win the game.
If Team Line Town loses,
the Milky Way will belong to Team Alien!
We're gonna win!
We are!
Got it!
And...
Wait, what?!
Shoot?
What in the world?
We blocked it.
You can't grow! That's cheating!
Nothing in the rules about that.
Seriously?
The Milky Way is ours.
Oh no! We're gonna lose...
Calm. I have a plan.
I call this one the
You'll Never Guess Who's Gonna Attack Attack!
You're wasting your time!
Excuse me.
What the?
Sweet!
Keep it up, guys!
Brown's feint attack!
Dazzling Eyes Block!
I can't see!
Take this! Sahasrabhuja Attack!
Game over! Team Line Town wins!
Yeah! We did it!
We... lost?
I was worried sick...
But I'm so glad we won!
Yeah. Now we can go back
to living in harmony.
How did this even happen anyways?
It's all James' fault!
He sang a forbidden tune!
A forbidden tune?
Yeah. There's this tune passed down
through my family with a bunch of different melodies,
including ones we're forbidden to sing.
So there's more of them?
You bet! Like this one...
Juby-julee! Juby-julee!
Wait, isn't it forbidden?
Ack!
What's going on?
Are you the one who sang "juby-julee?"
Face me in rugby!
Aagh! I'm sorry!
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
I dreamt I was flying through the night sky
mahou no juutan ni notte
On a magic carpet
tondeku yozora no yume
And I just wanted you to see it
kimi ni mo
kimi ni mo misetakute
misetai
Oh, did I wake you? I'm so sorry
okoshichatta kana? gomen ne
I thought you sounded half-asleep
neboketa kotobatachi ni
And it made me swoon
nandaka
nandaka kyun to kita
kyun kyun
Just like the glittering scent of rose tea
kirameku kaori no roozu tii mitai ni
When my heart starts pounding, I lock up
dokidoki no sono shunkan
tojikomeru
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
Even though I could just type a <3 and send it to you
yubisaki haato wo nosete
tsutawattara ii no ni
It's hard to sum up the way I feel for you
kimi e no kono kimochi
hitokoto ja tarinai
It's like a millefeuille
egao mo namida mo zenbu
With all of my smiles and tears mixed in
tsumikasaneta mirufiiyu
I feel happy, I feel painful
ureshii setsunai itoshii
I feel longing — I'm in love
koishiteru
hiking
mr. mush
Next time on Line Town...
Let's have mushroom green onion
misoyaki for dinner!
Pick some shiitake mushrooms,
mix it with miso, sweet sake, and sugar,
then finely chop the green onion
and put it on top.
hiking
mr. mush
Finally, toast it until it's golden brown,
and it's finished.
Personally, just half a mushroom
will fill me up!
Whew, now I'm starved.