A-B-C-D-E-F-G
H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P
Q-R-S-T-U-V-W
X-Y and Z
Now you know your ABCs
Isn't it bizarre, the way we string together
letters from A to Z?
Whether it be out loud or by text,
let's find something to talk about!
How will the world end? What's for dinner?
Let's share those moments of laughter and tears
I decide what I like and hate
But that too is a barrier I can break down
Don't you see? Our words make us who we are
There's something I want to talk about with you
Just thinking about that gets me all giddy
Whether you're right next to me or not
You always brighten up my day
Of all the things you've spoken to me
I cherish every last word
It feels good to think about somebody
And it feels good to put that into words
clones
There's some yogurt stuck on the lid!
I can't help but lick it off,
even though I'm full!
Time for a break.
It's so nice out.
Brown told me taking a nap outside
on a day like this feels really good.
Not like I should do that,
I am a girl.
Oh, hi Cony!
'Sup?
Huh? Cony, what are you up to?
What's it look like?
I'm practicing baseball.
Baseball?
A draft's comin' up.
So I gotta be in top shape for them
to call on me at any time!
I-I'm not sure I understand
what you're saying.
This is so so heavy...
W-Well, I'm glad to see her
so enthusiastic, I guess.
Why hello!
Good day!
Huh?! You were just practicing baseball over there!
Me playing baseball?
Oh, Sally. You can be so funny sometimes.
What on earth...?
Whew, that was a good nap.
Huh? Are you... me?
Unfortunately.
Huh? What's going on?
You see...
Huh? Why is there another me?
What the heck? Huh?!
I can explain,
if you would please calm down.
Ah. I'm sorry.
I am a clone of you
created from your snot bubble
while you were sleeping.
My snot bubble? Like, from my nose?
That doesn't make any sense.
You look like me,
but kinda different.
We degrade a bit when
we leave your nose.
I came out on the good side, at least.
As for the others... Eh.
Wait, there's more of you?!
Mhm. Five, including me.
Though the rest ran off ages ago.
Not good!
Juby-julee!
Sorry I'm late, Cony!
I was exfoliating my feet
and lost track of time!
Cony?
What is this?
S-So many complex formulas...
Need somethin'?
Don't you remember? We were supposed
to get our nails done together.
Seriously? You got time to care for your nails,
you can memorize the periodic table.
Happy Henry likes beans, brownies...
What's gotten into you, Cony?
Do you have a fever?
I would like to study for this test,
if you don't mind.
What test?!
She's not me, James!
Cony? Huh?!
What's going on here?
So this is a clone of you?
Makes sense. You're not this smart.
You're a lot more...
Lot more what, huh?
Forget that!
So, uh, what do we do about this clone?
Naturally, we gotta eliminate her.
Eliminate me?
After I memorized the periodic table
and all these complicated formulas?
Come on, I can't just have fake mes
wandering around the place!
How am I supposed to study
if you eliminate me?!
Get back here!
Stop right there!
Strum, strum the mandolin!
Hey, did I just see you litter?
Get off my tail.
Cony, is that you?!
Oh, Moon! Glad I ran into ya.
I've got a heist planned.
You in?
A height?
Like the mountains thataway?
What? Of course not!
Y'see...
Huh?! You're gonna rob a bank?
Keep your voice down, idiot!
Y'wanna get caught by the fuzz?!
Wh-What's gotten into you, Cony?
This isn't like you!
Oh, is something the matter?
Aah, Cony! Thank goodness you're here!
Cony's acting weird!
Wait, Cony?!
Oh dear, that's no good!
What the heck? There's two Conys?
Go!
Whoa, what the?!
Another Cony?!
Unfortunately.
There's six of them?
Moon, stop her!
She's a fake!
A fake?
So they're basically your clones?
She's trying to eliminate us!
Say what?
Well, yeah, I kinda gotta!
How come? Can we not live in harmony?
I believe that we can!
You heard her, Cony.
Let's be friends, what d'ya say?
Not a chance!
Excuse me.
You may speak, Cony.
Why is it the clones have to be eliminated?
Huh?
Your clones are more studious than you.
And better at sports.
And cuter.
And stronger.
Your clones outperform you
in every way.
If anything, the original Cony
should be eliminated instead.
That's not true!
I'm way smarter, way more athletic,
and way cuter! Right, guys?
Don't you agree?
Y-Yeah, that's right!
Also, would you rather have gloomy Cony?
Sorry I'm so gloomy.
I just don't have any purpose for existing.
Help! I'm getting sucked into the gloom!
It's terrible for my skin!
I must eliminate my fakes.
You've left us no choice!
Huh?
Wh-What are you doing?
We're making it harder
to figure out who's who!
Oh no! I can't tell which one's real!
Are you kidding?!
The Conys must have come from here.
Good shot!
Hey, quit enabling the clone!
Even in the winter,
I must wear sunscreen!
Same here. Can never let your guard down
around sun rays!
You too, James?!
My bad! I got caught up
in the beauty talk.
It seems a lot like you guys
like my clones better than me!
How do we get rid of them anyways?
Huh?
C'mon, you didn't figure them out?
Guess we can't eliminate them, then.
No, there's a way.
Let me think...
Hmm... How do we eliminate them...
Cony?
Ack, she fell asleep!
Yup, that's our Cony. Only she would
doze off after thinking too hard!
Gander at that snot bubble too!
Look, she startled herself awake
by popping her own snot bubble!
She's like a walking cartoon character!
Oh yeah, didn't you say your clones
were your snot bubbles?
Yeah. They came out while I was asleep.
Which means...
Juby-julee...
A-julee!
She's gone!
I knew it! We just have to pop them!
I see!
We're gonna eliminate all of you!
Run for your life!
Gotcha!
Freeze!
Look! The ball's coming back to home plate!
I did it!
Where is she?
You're finished!
Found you!
You're the real one!
I'm so sorry!
Get back here!
Don't move or the girl gets it!
No! Let me go!
Resistance is futile!
Stand down and be eliminated!
Nuh-uh!
Don't do it!
You realize how sad your mother will be?
What mother? I'm a clone!
Oh right!
Save me!
Juby...julee!
They're gone!
Man, I'm pooped...
I've so had it with clones...
Sally?!
Brown too?
There's so many!
How are we supposed to tell
the real one apart?!
errand
Dang it!
C'mon! No, no, no!
Man, Brown won again?
Whew... All that excitement
made me peckish.
I could go for something sweet.
How about it, Moon? Got anything?
Sure thing, valued customer!
I'll have it out shortly!
Who do you think you are?!
Silly me.
"Silly me" my foot!
I should have some sweets around here...
Holy cow!
What's this?
It's my treasure chest!
Oh yeah?
I packed it with a lot of toys
and collections I loved as a kid!
This brings me back!
These Getcha Monster Cards used to be all the rage!
Oh, Moon. It's so cute you held onto
stuff like this.
Huh? You mean boys don't
throw things like these away?
Strange.
Hmm, what's this thing?
Oh, yeah!
Is it what I'm thinking of?
Yup, that's the one!
What is it?
One, two, three, four...
Who did that?
Sorry, guys.
Let's go again!
One, two, three, four...
Moon, you again?
The rope was too fast.
You have to jump!
One more time!
One, two, three, four...
Moon!
The rope comes before I can jump...
You jump before the rope comes!
Come here, Moon!
It's Mom!
What's up, Mom?
Moon, can you run an errand for me?
Huh? An errand?
I need you to deliver this
to your aunt on 3rd Street.
But I don't know where that is.
We went together a while back, no?
I don't remember!
I drew you a map.
But we're playing jump rope!
You can continue later.
I'm busy right now,
so I need you to do this for me.
No way! I'm busy playing jump rope!
Please, Moon?
No way! Nuh-uh! Not happening!
What's wrong?
Mom's telling me to run an errand!
I'm sorry, kids.
You can play with him again later!
An errand sounds like fun!
Huh?
Let's all go together!
Yay! Let's go!
Errand time, errand time!
I'm er-running an errand!
Cony, are errands really that fun to you?
Of course, it's my very first one!
Cony, do you know the way?
Don't worry.
Which way is it?
Huh?!
What's wrong?
This isn't on the map.
Let me look.
Cony, it's upside down!
Ohh! I thought it seemed kinda off.
Silly me!
So which way do we go?
Let me think...
Where even are we?!
Huh?
Where are we?
No! We're lost!
This is your fault, Cony!
I wish I hadn't come on this errand!
I wish I didn't have to go either!
What's the matter?
We're lost.
Oh dear!
We're trying to go here.
Let's see. Right now, you guys are...
here.
That far away?!
I can lead the way if you'd like.
It's fine!
What?
We're good on our own!
Are you sure?
It's our errand, after all!
It's more like mine, though.
Cony, are you sure we won't get lost?
Don't worry about it!
That person before drew us a new map!
Aah, who are you?
My, you're beautiful.
Oh, it's just me.
What a beauty!
Huh?
Where's James?
Wait, what?
Where am I?
James!
Where did you go?
Help us!
Moon!
Cony!
Brown!
That was scary...
Y'see why I didn't want to go on this errand?
Huh? We have to find James? Right!
I can't walk anymore!
Seriously? You wanted to come with me, Cony!
I'm so hungry!
Hey Moon, what's in that anyways?
This?
Is it sweets by any chance?
Don't you dare!
This is for my aunt!
I just wanna peek! Lemme see it!
No way!
You hear that crinkle?
It's gotta be cookies!
Keep your hands off!
I just wanna take a peek!
Not happening!
I'm sorry!
Wait!
We can't catch up!
We can catch up!
Wait!
Which one is it?
I can't tell.
This is bad.
Mom's gonna be so mad.
I'm so sorry, Moon!
Huh? It's that truck?
How can you tell?
You memorized the license plate number?
You should'a said so!
Wait!
Guys, where are you?
Wait up, guys!
Wait!
James!
Where are you going?
After that truck!
Excuse me!
What is it?
We did it!
There you go.
Thank you, sir!
Hold up.
This is my aunt's house!
Coming!
Greetings, delivery!
Delivery!
Here!
Oh my!
Thank you all! You did very well.
Take this home with you.
What's up, Moon?
Here!
For you!
You too!
Are you sure?
Don't you have to give this to your mom?
It's fine!
Such a pretty sunset.
You said it.
It's so round!
It's the same flower.
Then on the way home, Cony started
complaining about how hungry she was!
Oh yeah!
Really now?
Guess what?
I kept mine too!
You too, Brown?
We all thought alike!
Huh? I, uh...
I kinda... still have it!
Yeah, I have it in a safe place at home!
To remember our past by!
You don't sound very convincing.
Silly me...
"Silly me" my foot!
How about we all play
jump rope together again?
One, two, three, four...
You never learn, do you, Moon?
Of course I do.
You're just not matching my rhythm.
Alright. Let's go again!
One, two, three, four, five...
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
I dreamt I was flying through the night sky
mahou no juutan ni notte
On a magic carpet
tondeku yozora no yume
And I just wanted you to see it
kimi ni mo
kimi ni mo misetakute
misetai
Oh, did I wake you? I'm so sorry
okoshichatta kana? gomen ne
I thought you sounded half-asleep
neboketa kotobatachi ni
And it made me swoon
nandaka
nandaka kyun to kita
kyun kyun
Just like the glittering scent of rose tea
kirameku kaori no roozu tii mitai ni
When my heart starts pounding, I lock up
dokidoki no sono shunkan
tojikomeru
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
Even though I could just type a <3 and send it to you
yubisaki haato wo nosete
tsutawattara ii no ni
It's hard to sum up the way I feel for you
kimi e no kono kimochi
hitokoto ja tarinai
It's like a millefeuille
egao mo namida mo zenbu
With all of my smiles and tears mixed in
tsumikasaneta mirufiiyu
I feel happy, I feel painful
ureshii setsunai itoshii
I feel longing — I'm in love
koishiteru
weather
dorothy
Next time on Line Town...
Dorothy, a wrinkly, gossipy old lady
makes her debut!
weather
dorothy
Oh, dear... I hope she doesn't
find out my secret.
I'll try to keep my distance.