A-B-C-D-E-F-G
H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P
Q-R-S-T-U-V-W
X-Y and Z
Now you know your ABCs
Isn't it bizarre, the way we string together
letters from A to Z?
Whether it be out loud or by text,
let's find something to talk about!
How will the world end? What's for dinner?
Let's share those moments of laughter and tears
I decide what I like and hate
But that too is a barrier I can break down
Don't you see? Our words make us who we are
There's something I want to talk about with you
Just thinking about that gets me all giddy
Whether you're right next to me or not
You always brighten up my day
Of all the things you've spoken to me
I cherish every last word
It feels good to think about somebody
And it feels good to put that into words
bed hair
So beautiful!
Even more beautiful!
Beautiful as well!
Beautiful in a whole different way.
Why am I so beautiful?
My body, my face...
My hair!
It's all beautiful!
Goodbye, today!
Good night, James.
What awful bed hair!
This is so not beautiful...
I can't let anybody see me like this...
If Cony and Moon saw me right now...
That's awful!
Look at this!
You gotta see this!
I can't bare the thought...
I'd better stay put for the day.
James!
Moon?!
Cony?!
That scratching at my door...
Brown?!
Are you still asleep, James?
How dare you hold us up?!
Hold them up?
I forgot!
I agreed to go to that popular burger joint with them!
Oh no, what do I do?
We're coming in!
Huh?
Oh, you were just getting ready?
Hey! Morning, you guys!
Why are you standing like that?
Huh?
It's only the hottest pose this year!
Do I look dashing?
I can't wait!
They're supposed to be really good!
Just thinking of those burgers
is making me drool...
Ew, Moon! Cut that out!
I fooled them for now...
Hurry up, James!
Juby-juby!
It's very bright out today, isn't it?
Why are you trying to show off?
That was close...
Here it is!
Welcome!
May I take your order?
I ordered ahead! Four special hamburgers, please!
Huh? I can't possibly...
No need to hold back!
You won't get to have these burgers
all too often, after all!
Yeah! She's been calling them nonstop
for the past month to place this order.
Mhm! I really wanted you all to have it.
Oh, wow! Really?
Sounds amazing!
I-It's huge!!
That's what makes them special!
Y-Yeah, that makes sense.
Chow time!
So good!
It tastes so good!
Why did I have to get hot tea
on a day like this...?
What's wrong, James?
Huh? Oh, I just...
Don't tell me you already ate!
I-I would never!
I'm just feasting it with my eyes first!
Its elegance shines from every angle!
Oh, no... There's no way I can get out of eating this!
Breaking news.
A cobra has escaped from the Line Town Zoo.
According to its caretaker,
its name is Cobtaro,
and is a 4 year-old male.
It is considered violent.
Yikes!
His face is so creepy...
If you spot it, please contact the zoo immediately.
This cobra is very dangerous.
Now's my chance!
We will now interview the caretaker.
That's terrifying...
Cobtaro managed to get away
while I was cleaning its room.
Scary...
Please keep in mind that Cobtaro is, in fact, poisonous.
I'm used to it, though.
Wh-What's that supposed to mean?
Oh, gosh...
Wow, this tastes great!
You mean it? I'm glad you think so!
Huh? Brown, what'cha looking at?
Ants!
Dang, they're taking our fries!
Can't you make them go away?
Alright, now! Go on home!
Aah, there's some big ones too!
Aah, there's ones over here...
More of them?!
Safe...
Hey, doesn't that person look familiar?
That's that superstar Lady Gaba!
For real?! Let's ask for her autograph!
Now's an even bigger chance!
Brown? You're not going with them?
Oh, yeah! I'm pretty sure this place
has salmon soup by the beverages!
It was just some old lady
in wacky clothes.
Hey, you started this!
Huh? You already finished your burger?
M-Mhm...
Ugh... I-I need something to drink...
I can't do it...
What on earth is he doing...?
Juby-julee!
It's still like this...
Well, I already ate my burger.
I may as well take my leave.
Is it just me,
or has James been acting strange?
It's not just you... he's always strange!
You got a point.
Hey, guys...
I think I'm gonna go home n—
Congratulations, sir!
What?
You're the 10,000th customer
to enter our restroom!
To celebrate, you will all get
big special hamburgers on the house!
So lucky!
Thanks, James!
Chow time!
What's wrong, James?
Are you not hungry?
It's not that, I...
I can take it off your hands.
Knock it off, Moon.
Else I'm the one who's taking it.
I'm only kidding.
You couldn't possibly give away
a delicious burger like this, right, James?
You can have it.
Huh?
James, do you mean it?
I'm okay, Brown.
Then could it be...?
C-Could it be what?
Is your side splitting?
M-My side?
Yeah!
N-No, that's not it...
Is it both sides?!
What?!
Yeah, are you okay?!
I-I'm fine!!
I'm just peachy!
See? I have an appetite!
It's so good, I don't even have time
to use my hands!
Man, he's going to town with that...
I can finally go home...
Huh? Is there a drawing on your plate?
A hamburger...?
Congratulations, sir!
What?!
The hamburger drawing on your plate...
...means that you win a mega special hamburger!
Hot dang...
Let's do this... I'm game!
It's the cobra!!
What are you doing?!
Get up here already!
Don't come near me!
Yikes!
Why'd you throw him at me?!
Come on, I just saved your butt!
You and your weird strength
saved nothing!
Oh, you wanna go?
Calm down, guys...
You big dimwit!
Say that again!
Also, I wouldn't have gotten hit
if Brown hadn't dodged!
That's enough!
Shut up! You couldn't even climb up the tree!
Yeah! Plus if you hadn't broken that branch... Huh?
That's awful, James!
Don't make us laugh!
It's over...
My beautiful life is crumbling before my eyes...
A good laugh really makes you feel silly
after an argument.
What were we arguing about anyways?
I wonder...
Well, whatever.
Thanks, James.
Huh?
Thanks for what?
You know!
You made us laugh!
All that laughing tired me out.
Let's go home.
Yeah.
That's it?
Huh?
What do you mean?
Aren't you gonna spread photos of me
and plaster it up all over town?
Why would we do that?
No, umm...
Never mind.
Let's go back and play some video games!
Sure thing.
I suppose it'll do.
Wait for me!
Thank you, come again!
leader
Hey, how about we go on a vacation together?
Watch out! Move to the right!
Okay!
Listen to me!
What is it?
We should go on a vacation together!
That sounds good!
Doesn't it?
How about we do a hot spring?
Attack that enemy!
On it!
Good job, James!
Hot spring?
What was that?
Let's go to a hot spring!
How does an amusement park sound?
I wanna go on a roller coaster!
I want to ride a merry-go-round!
I suppose we could do that...
I don't mind, as long as there's good eats.
I could go for some steak!
I want to eat sushi.
Tuna belly for me!
Flatfish fin is the best!
Brown says he wants salmon!
Sushi...
Fine, that works.
Well, if we wanna dip in the hot springs,
go to the amusement park, and eat sushi,
then we should probably go by train!
I wanna take a plane trip!
Sounds good!
Man, fine. We'll go by plane...
Now, hold on!
What are you doing?
You're in the way!
Why aren't you hearing me out?
Hm? We hear you loud and clear.
You want to take a bath on the train, right?
No, he said he wants to ride a sushi plane!
Oh, I see.
Of course not!
Who do you think is the leader of this group anyways?!
It's me!!
What?!
I don't remember agreeing to that.
Are you kidding?
You're literally under my roof right now!
Well, yeah. To play your new video game.
Yeah.
You came here just to play my game?!
Yeah!
Let's rock-paper-scissors!
For what?
Whoever wins is the leader!
That feels kind of shallow...
Maybe, but it does sound fun!
Let's do it!
Alright! One match to decide it all!
Show it with your body!
Rock-paper-scissors, shoot!
Paper!
Rock!
Scissors!
Paper!
Tiebreaker!
Rock!
Paper!
You win!
Looks like James is the leader!
Well, if you insist!
I'll be the leader from now on!
No!
Huh?
Rock-paper-scissors isn't enough
to decide the leader!
You were the one who came up with it...
Did not!
I cannot accept this!
So how do we decide it?
We'll hold an election!
Huh?
Don't "huh" me!
We'll decide for certain which one of us
is fit to be leader!
If I'm your leader...
I'll give you all strawberry rice cakes
every day!
And in exchange, you will all give me
three strawberry shortcakes every day.
Thank you very much!
Juby-julee!
Hi, I'm James!
I'm not very fit to be a leader,
but I'll do it if it makes you all happy!
If I'm your leader, I will try to make
your lives even more beautiful!
This is your beautiful candidate, James!
They clapped louder for me.
That was a great speech, James!
It made me feel very emotional!
You've got my vote for sure, James!
Me too!
Let's cast our votes!
Wait just a minute!
I appreciate the enthusiasm,
but you really should take the time
to think it over!
I think we're good.
You should, I'm telling you!
Aren't you worried whoever you vote for
might not deliver?
You think so?
Yeah!
So voting will begin in 30 minutes!
Moon, where are you going?
I'm making a ballot box!
A ballot box?
Alright! Write the name of your vote
and put it in the box!
There.
And in goes my vote.
Jessica, would you tally the votes?
Okay!
I will now tally the votes
for the very first...
leader election!
Moon!
Must be the one he put in himself.
Yeah, I'm sure.
James.
Knew it.
Well, we can't let our guards down yet.
James.
See?
I knew it!
James!
Perfect!
Thank you, everybody!
Moon!
Moon, Moon...
Moon, Moon, Moon, Moon,
Moon, Moon, Moon, Moon, Moon...
James: 4 votes.
Moon: 501 votes.
That makes me the leader!
How? There's only five of us!
That's just how much you all
want me to be your leader!
That makes no sense!
You put in 500 votes when
you made the box, didn't you?
N-No way...
500 votes is just overkill,
no matter how you look at it.
The more, the better!
So you did add them yourself!
Shoot, busted!
Why would you pull such a dirty trick?
Oh, hush.
It doesn't matter. I win.
This election is now void.
That's not fair!
Rich coming from you!
We'll do it over again tomorrow.
And it'll be done fairly this time.
I can't accept this...!
Let's all meet up here again tomorrow.
Hey. Wake up, Brown.
I was just going for a stroll,
and found someone had dropped
their high-grade salmon.
See?
Do you want it?
You can have it.
If you want it, we have to make a deal.
Does that sound good?
And that's why I'm the only one
who could lead this group!
Huh?
I'm James!
If I'm leader, I'll make Line Town
beautiful and litter-free!
Please place your votes.
Juby-julee.
I will now tally the votes.
You've got this in the bag, James!
Hey, I don't care if I win or lose.
Moon!
What?!
James.
James!
Yes!
The result is Moon: 2 votes,
and James: 3 votes!
James is our lea—
Wait!
Sally!
And...an old man?
Surely, we have the right to vote
in this leader election too, no?
Well, I suppose you do, Sally...
But the old man?
Can I?
I mean, I guess...
Alright! You two, step on up and place your vote!
There.
All according to plan.
Oh? It's you, Moon!
Hi, Sally!
Want some cucumber juice?
It's very good!
Have some!
I would love some! I just happened to be
craving some cucumber juice.
An extra-large cup, if you will!
Right away, sir! Extra-large!
She was right, this is very delicious!
I'll have to come by every day!
Oh, really?
I'm glad to hear that!
That reminds me. Sally!
I have this free karaoke ticket!
Thought I'd let you have it.
I'm so happy! Thank you, Moon!
How generous of you!
I get that a lot.
By the way,
I have a favor for the both of you...
I'll do another count.
M-Moon?
What?!
And last, but not least... Huh?
Go on, Jessica! Cry my name!
Cry the name of your great new leader...!
It's blank!
What is the meaning of this?!
I voted for you, I swear!
That was my vote.
Moon gave me a free karaoke ticket,
hoping that I would vote him in this election.
I knew you were using more cheap tricks!
This puts it at a tie, 3—3,
voiding out the election as a whole.
How are we supposed to decide on a leader now?!
Just tell me which one of us should lead!
Well, let's see.
I think James would make a good leader.
Huh?
M-Me?
Yes! A good beauty leader!
A beauty leader?
Cony knows a lot about delicious foods,
so she can be a gourmet leader!
Aww, gourmet leader?
Brown is good at hearing others out.
He's a kindness leader!
You like it?
As for Jessica...
Me too?
She's very fashionable,
so she can be the fashion leader!
Huh? You're making me blush!
Everyone is a leader of their own thing!
Is that okay with you, Moon?
Sally...
So what does that make me leader of?
You're the trickery leader.
I don't like the sound of that.
How about planning leader?
Planning leader, you say?
That actually sounds pretty cool!
There you have it!
Then let's hold a leader meeting!
Let's give some good thought
over our hot spring trip!
Sounds great! Let's do it,
trickery leader!
That's planning leader to you!
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
I dreamt I was flying through the night sky
mahou no juutan ni notte
On a magic carpet
tondeku yozora no yume
And I just wanted you to see it
kimi ni mo
kimi ni mo misetakute
misetai
Oh, did I wake you? I'm so sorry
okoshichatta kana? gomen ne
I thought you sounded half-asleep
neboketa kotobatachi ni
And it made me swoon
nandaka
nandaka kyun to kita
kyun kyun
Just like the glittering scent of rose tea
kirameku kaori no roozu tii mitai ni
When my heart starts pounding, I lock up
dokidoki no sono shunkan
tojikomeru
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
Even though I could just type a <3 and send it to you
yubisaki haato wo nosete
tsutawattara ii no ni
It's hard to sum up the way I feel for you
kimi e no kono kimochi
hitokoto ja tarinai
It's like a millefeuille
egao mo namida mo zenbu
With all of my smiles and tears mixed in
tsumikasaneta mirufiiyu
I feel happy, I feel painful
ureshii setsunai itoshii
I feel longing — I'm in love
koishiteru
hero
model
Next time on Line Town...
Manju-man—I mean, Moon-man to the rescue!
Will Pizza-man be able to preserve the peace?
You've got this, Porkbelly-man!
Don't back down, Handmade and Carefully Packed
by Workers from Hokkaido-man!
hero
model
Wait, who are we talking about again-man?
Your friendly neighborhood Moon-man!
That's the one. Tune in next time!