A-B-C-D-E-F-G
H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P
Q-R-S-T-U-V-W
X-Y and Z
Now you know your ABCs
Isn't it bizarre, the way we string together
letters from A to Z?
Whether it be out loud or by text,
let's find something to talk about!
How will the world end? What's for dinner?
Let's share those moments of laughter and tears
I decide what I like and hate
But that too is a barrier I can break down
Don't you see? Our words make us who we are
There's something I want to talk about with you
Just thinking about that gets me all giddy
Whether you're right next to me or not
You always brighten up my day
Of all the things you've spoken to me
I cherish every last word
It feels good to think about somebody
And it feels good to put that into words
together
Coming!
Hi, James.
Come on in.
Sorry about your house.
Can't even bake cookies
without my whole place going up in smoke.
You don't do that often.
Aw... My house...
Your house will be patched up in no time.
And you're welcome to stay here
until then.
Really?
Bien sûr !
Please, make yourself at home.
Thank you so much, James!
What the?!
What's going on?
Good morning, Moon!
I'm making my special green smoothie
for breakfast!
It's 5:00.
The morning hours are
essential for beauty!
Want some?
Uh, I'll pass.
One, two, juby-julee...
One, two, juby-julee!
Must you do that now?
Can't start the day
without moving your body!
One, two, juby-julee...
One, two, juby-julee!
Get a good night's sleep?
Y-Yeah.
What's wrong?
What's a wet towel
doing on the floor?!
Oh yeah, I just washed my face.
So?
So I dried off with a towel.
Is that good?
I mean, you can use the towels,
but I'd appreciate it
if you didn't toss it on the floor after!
Ah, sorry, hun. I'll keep that in mind.
Huh?!
Mind if I watch the Beauty Channel?
I tune in every week.
Sure thing.
Ack, Moon!
Don't touch the remote
with your greasy potato chip hands!
You'll get it all gross and sticky!
Really?
Alright.
What channel is it?
Juby!
Take that! Hah!
You're still awake?
I'm winning here!
Staying up isn't good
for your skin.
The skin's prime hours
are 10 to 2,
so it's best to be asleep by then.
When I'm done.
Turn the TV off before you sleep.
Good night.
Why must Moon be so uncouth?
Why must James pick apart
everything I do?
I can't sleep because of Moon!
James just had to butt in!
Moon, you little...!
Curse you, James!
Do you think James and Moon
are getting along?
No way, they're like polar opposites.
They've probably driven
each other insane.
Haha, you're totally right!
Hey, guys!
How many times do I have to tell you
to fold your own laundry?!
Well, you gotta stop
spreading your stink everywhere!
It is no stink! It's an elegant fragrance!
It's worse than I imagined.
Hmph!
Come on, guys,
get along!
No way.
Why are you fighting, anyway?
James keeps picking me apart.
Moon is being uncouth.
What was that?
You heard me!
Relax!
Hmph!
Why don't you set some rules together?
What do you mean?
Come up with rules you want
your housemate to follow,
and abide by those rules together.
Having some disagreements comes
with the territory of sharing a home.
It would make it more bearable
until Moon's home is repaired.
Fine, I guess.
Sure, whatever.
Now, we shall set the rules
for James and Moon's shared living.
Are there any requests?
Yes!
No mucking about
early in the morning!
Mucking about?!
It's called exercising!
How about you do your
morning exercises outdoors?
Yeah. Listening to someone shuffling around
in the morning would be annoying.
Okay...
Rule 1: Morning exercise goes outside.
Note that down, Brown.
Anything else?
Me, I have one!
No gaming late at night!
It's too loud for me to sleep!
Hey, it's not that loud!
Besides, I use headphones!
Sometimes you can still hear
sound from headphones.
Yeah, that's so annoying.
Fine...
Then Rule 2: No gaming late at night.
Okay, Rule 3: No bath towels on the couch!
Okay, Rule 4: Close the cap on the soda tightly!
Rule 5: Don't leave the toilet seat up.
Rule 6: Clean up your shedded hair.
Rule 7!
Rule 8!
Rule 9!
Rule 10!
Rule 11!
Rule 12!
I'm worried about them.
Rule 13!
Moon, James!
Hey, Sally!
You two are out on a walk together!
Did you start getting along?
Nope! Rule 128:
We have to go shopping together.
Say what?
Whenever he goes out on his own,
this dunderhead always comes back with something weird.
Hey! Rule 231: No name-calling!
Ah!
I didn't say that!
Oh yes you did!
No I didn't!
Yes you did!
This isn't looking good.
Rule 331: We take turns carrying things
every 100 steps.
We haven't even walked 50 yet.
Hey, now, that's against
Rule 14: No lying!
I'm not lying.
Uh-huh.
I'm serious!
Man, I can't believe it!
Oh?
What could be the matter?
Someone put graffiti all over my wall.
That's awful.
Hah...
I can't get rid of this by myself...
We can help you!
You can?
"We?"
Rule 67: If someone's in need,
we help them together!
Gosh...
A-juby, a-julee!
A-juby! A-juby-a-julee!
Whew. Good as new!
Yay us!
Yeah!
Wow!
Thank you so much.
I really appreciate it!
Please, have this.
Aw, thank you!
Hello? This is Moon!
Huh?!
My house is fixed!
Man, living alone is the best.
This is the life!
I'm gonna stay up super late
playing video games!
Ahh... It feels so refreshing
not having someone bothering me.
I'm gonna get some good rest.
I left something.
Found it!
Want some?
Uh, sure.
Don't forget Rule 32:
You must clean your tableware.
Rule 40: Dinner should be enjoyed.
You like it?
Heck yeah!
I'm glad!
Thank goodness your house
got repaired, Moon.
I thought you two would tear
each others' heads off or something.
Yeah, yeah.
Hm? Do we have
any of that stuff?
What stuff?
Salt's over here.
Wait, what?
I can't find it!
This can't be happening!
Where did it go?
What are you looking for?
Your phone's over there, dude.
Phew, there it is!
Whoa, it's like you're reading
each other's minds.
Hey! Rule 78: Watermelon seeds go in the trash!
Rule 88: Forget about it!
That's it!
I can't tell if they're getting along or not.
Well, if it works, it works.
card game
A-juby!
Yay, 1st place!
2nd place!
Which will it be?
Oh, which will it be?
This one?
Or this one?
No, this one...
Make up your mind!
I'm thinking!
That won't help.
Can you shut up?
This!
Get back here,
the game's still going.
Right! Moon still has to pick!
Bet you're so scared
you'll pick the joker!
You're delusional!
I'm gonna win!
No, I am!
Hi-yah!
Bring it on!
I can't take my eyes off this!
Who knew Old Maid
could be so intense...
Pick one!
Is it this one?
Or is it this one?
Or maybe this one?
Nope, it's this one.
You're an open book!
What do you mean?!
It's this one!
I win!
Moon, you're in 3rd place...
I got 1st...
Cony loses agian!
One more game!
It's so late...
Yeah.
Let's call it a night.
You said it.
Going off the total scores,
Jessica's in 1st place.
And I'm in 2nd!
I'm 3rd!
Which puts Cony...
in dead last!
W-Wait, I'm not done yet!
We're done for today, Cony.
No way! I want another game!
It's getting late.
We can do it another time!
Bye, Cony!
We're leaving.
Wait, don't go!
You can sleep over, can't you?
Right, guys?
Let's play cards all night long!
But I have a modeling gig tomorrow...
Staying up isn't good for your skin!
Then just one more game!
That's all I ask!
No one likes a sore loser.
You lost.
I... lost...?
Moon, you know saying things like that
makes her flip out.
I don't lose to anyone.
You came in 3rd, though.
Better than 4th!
Cony, don't get so worked up.
It's only a game.
No way! No way, nuh-uh!
Don't leave me!
I wanna keep playing!
We can't stop until I win!
I hate losing!
So childish.
Nooo!
You lost!
It was just a dream...
Ugh, I can't believe
I'm having nightmares now.
All over losing in a card game.
Right! It's just a game!
But it hurts so bad...
What's this place?
Card game classes?
"Learn the tricks to playing
and winning at card games"?
Hello there!
Gah!
Are you into card games?
I don't know...
Do you want to master them?
Yes!
So, how do I win at Old Maid?
Old Maid, eh?
Can I learn to master it?
Of course!
A beauty like you mastering a card game?
That would make you very cool.
Oh, please, I'm no beauty!
There's your weakness.
You're quick to show your emotions.
One little flatter
and a smile spreads on your face.
Flatter, huh?
And now you're angry.
You need a poker face.
Be it poker or Old Maid,
you want to put on a blank face
to avoid your expression
giving away your hand.
I get it.
Let us practice.
No matter what I say,
you must respond with "uh-huh" and a blank face.
Got it!
Aw, Cony, you're so cute!
Uh-huh.
You're very pretty.
You're such a dummy.
U-Uh-huh...
What a blockhead.
No wonder you keep
losing at card games.
Uhhuh...
Cony, have you gained weight lately?
Wait, did I?!
Don't react.
Hide your feelings.
Don't let anyone know.
Okay.
Also, read your opponent's expressions.
How?
One's inner thoughts can also
show through the slight movements
of their eyes, nose, mouth, and hands.
You want to observe those carefully.
I see.
You seriously wanna play
Old Maid again?
Lemme guess, you still
bummed about your loss yesterday?
Heck yeah I am!
I'm gonna wi—
Woops, forgot my poker face!
What's wrong, Cony?
Nothing. Doesn't matter
if I win or lose, so long as we have fun.
That's the spirit! Amusons-nous !
What are you doing?
Dunno.
Oldest trick in the book.
You're making that one look like the joker
so I pick a different card instead.
Am I?
But I will outwit you
and take that card instead!
...But what if that is the joker?
Is it?
I'll outwit your outwitting
of my outwitting!
Mine!
You outwitted my out-out-outwit?!
I wasn't planning anything actually.
I win!
Juby-julee!
Moon, can you let go?
I'm not holding them that tightly.
Oh, I'm sure.
You just want me
to pick another card, don't you?
Not really, no.
Then let me pick that one!
Go for it.
Then I will!
Oh no!
I tricked you!
I see it in Jessica's eyes...
Something is bothering her.
She has the joker.
I'll take this one.
Oh, I won!
Darn it...
Oh my oh my, I won yet again!
Cony's on fire...
Nah, she's just having
a lucky streak.
Yeah! I feel lucky!
Coming!
Why, hello, Brown!
We're playing Old Maid!
Let's see...
Dang, Brown's putting on
a top-notch poker face.
He's unbeatable...
I can't beat Brown!
Yo, Cony, it's your turn.
Don't gotta tell me twice!
Are you okay, Cony?
I-I feel like all of his cards are jokers.
You shouldn't take it so seriously...
Allez-y doucement, Cony!
Just hurry up and pick a card!
F-Fine, okay!
I'm sure I'll lose either way!
C-Cony?
Are you alright?
Come on out, Cony!
Brown!
Why are you so blank-faced
all the time, huh?!
Calm down, Cony!
It's just a game!
Nothing to get worked up over!
Put a sock in it!
I can't take it!
Looks like Cony here
isn't suited for card games.
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
I dreamt I was flying through the night sky
mahou no juutan ni notte
On a magic carpet
tondeku yozora no yume
And I just wanted you to see it
kimi ni mo
kimi ni mo misetakute
misetai
Oh, did I wake you? I'm so sorry
okoshichatta kana? gomen ne
I thought you sounded half-asleep
neboketa kotobatachi ni
And it made me swoon
nandaka
nandaka kyun to kita
kyun kyun
Just like the glittering scent of rose tea
kirameku kaori no roozu tii mitai ni
When my heart starts pounding, I lock up
dokidoki no sono shunkan
tojikomeru
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
Even though I could just type a <3 and send it to you
yubisaki haato wo nosete
tsutawattara ii no ni
It's hard to sum up the way I feel for you
kimi e no kono kimochi
hitokoto ja tarinai
It's like a millefeuille
egao mo namida mo zenbu
With all of my smiles and tears mixed in
tsumikasaneta mirufiiyu
I feel happy, I feel painful
ureshii setsunai itoshii
I feel longing — I'm in love
koishiteru
pirates
spies
Agents, next time on Line Town...
Super spy Moon of the Secret Intelligence Service
infiltrates the enemy HQ.
The enemies he's up against
is led by a beauty—that's me.
pirates
spies
And it's filled with other
familiar faces too.
Will he be able to make this near-impossible
mission possible?