A-B-C-D-E-F-G
H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P
Q-R-S-T-U-V-W
X-Y and Z
Now you know your ABCs
Isn't it bizarre, the way we string together
letters from A to Z?
Whether it be out loud or by text,
let's find something to talk about!
How will the world end? What's for dinner?
Let's share those moments of laughter and tears
I decide what I like and hate
But that too is a barrier I can break down
Don't you see? Our words make us who we are
There's something I want to talk about with you
Just thinking about that gets me all giddy
Whether you're right next to me or not
You always brighten up my day
Of all the things you've spoken to me
I cherish every last word
It feels good to think about somebody
And it feels good to put that into words
crisis
So emerald green is in this season, huh?
Jessica is a reader model?
Jessica really is the trendiest girl in town!
Oh!
Jessica!
Hey, Cony!
Go clothes shopping again?
Yes! I got lots of new outfits.
You like?
So pretty!
Gorgeous!
You've got a real good eye for fashion, Jessica!
Honestly, it's all just cheap knockoffs.
That doesn't matter!
You look stylish in just about anything!
You think so?
Just look at this dress!
It's fabulous!
Oh, that one's branded,
so it's a bit expensive.
Is it?
It totally wouldn't look good on me anyways.
That's not true.
Nah, it won't fit me at all!
It would!
Huh? Really? Can I try it on then?
Please? Please? Please?
O-Okay...
Yay, I get to try it on!
Oh, I'll go make some tea!
I-It's a bit tight...
See! It looks great on you!
Uhh, really?
You look totes pretty!
Th-Thanks!
I'm totes feeling it too now!
It fits you perfectly!
I-It does, right?
'Cuz, thing is, I have to ask you a favor...
What is it?
Can you lend me this dress for a bit?
Huh?
J-Just for a day!
But I just bought it...
I haven't even worn it myself!
I beg of you!
Why though?
I... It's just... Y'know, girl...
I'm going on a date today!
So I wanted to wear something extra purty.
A date? With who?
Oh, just some guy.
No biggie.
Please, pretty please!
With a cherry on top!
What's with the weird poses?
Huh? Oh, I'm just...
...doing the "pretty please" hula dance pose!
Never heard of it?
Aloha 'oe...
Pretty please, for'e...
Let me borrow this dress...
Thanks!
Cony?
I managed to throw her off...
I just have to fix it up before she notices.
Wah-lah!
Huh? Darn, I made one of the sleeves shorter...
I just have to match it on the other side.
Bam, all done!
Or not...
A bit over here...
Oh my God!
I made it sleeveless!
Put some of the cloth over here...
A bit of this and that...
Stitch it all together...!
I'm done!
Who's supposed to wear a dress this small?
Oh, shoot! I forgot I asked Moon to come over!
Cony? Cony!
The heck? Is she gone?
After asking me to come help you
set up your new computer, no less!
What do I do with this?
Excuse me!
Do you have the large—
I mean, the normal size of this dress?
Why, I'm afraid we sold out of that earlier.
Whaaat?!
Cony!
J-Jessica?!
Cony?
Hey, whash up?
That's what I was going to ask you!
What happened to your date?
Date? Oh, that date!
I had to cancel, my teeth randomly started aching.
Are you alright? Your face is awful swelled up.
Yeah, could be worse.
Oh. Well, sorry about the date.
Get better soon!
Oh, right!
If the date is off, I suppose
you don't need that anymore, right?
Can you return it?
You know, my dress!
I'm sowwy!
I'm sowwy, Jessica!
For what?
The dress...
Your dress...
It was stowen!
Someone stole it?!
That's right...
Some burglar snuck in while I was at the dentist
and they stole it!
Huh? A burglar?!
Y-Yeah...
We better call the police!
There's no need to exaggerate!
They didn't steal anything important!
What about my dress?
I-I guess that's important, yes...
I'll just pay you back for the dress!
Of course not!
You're not at fault here,
the criminal is!
And we can't let society's evils get off scot-free!
We better call 911 right away!
J-Jessica! Please calm down...
Cony, what are you doing?!
Please stop!
Juby-julee...
Wait, don't!
Oh!
We have to!
Please wait!
What's going on here?
What's all the fuss about?
Cony was attacked by a burglar!
What?!
You were attacked?!
Did they punch you?!
Oh, no! Your poor little face is all swollen!
I never said I got attacked.
Come to think of it, I've heard about a gang
of thieves making their way around town...
That must be it! It's that rotten gang of thieves!
H-Hold on, wait a minute...
I know who it is!
What?
Huh?
I saw him.
S-Saw who?!
The one who robbed Cony...
...was Moon!
Huh?
Moon?
Indeed. I saw it with my own two eyes.
He was getting very worked up
right outside Cony's house.
But...
Moon would never...
Oh, my!
Moon!
Brown caught this pic while we were passing by.
Moon...
He's a criminal...?
Guys, he's just...
Oh? Hey, guys, what are y'all up to?
Huh?!
Struuum!
The mandolin!
What's your issue, Cony?
I thought we had made plans.
Why'd you stand me up?
I was just busy with something...
Wait, plans?
Don't tell me your date was with Moon?
The date?
Oh, no. Nope. Not at all.
Not a chance.
I thought so.
It's a good thing he wasn't your date, at least.
Would've been very shocking
to get robbed by your boyfriend.
Boyfriend or not, it's still shocking!
Our good friend is a burglar!
A what?
Moon, I'm quite shocked, you know.
What's this now?
Shall we go?
Where?
To the police!
I'll bring you there so you can 'fess up for what you did.
And for what?
Stealing my dress, duh!
Everyone knows!
You snuck into Cony's room
and stole Jessica's dress!
I snuck into Cony's room...?
Also, why am I taking Jessica's thing
from Cony's house?
Makes no sense.
The point is that you're a rotten thief.
I'm sorry?!
We have proof too!
Umm, hey, you guys...
I think you might be getting the wrong idea...
Oh come on, why would I steal your stuff?
And even if I did,
why would I take a dress of all things?
It all makes sense.
I told ya!
So you're into that kinda thing, eh?
You don't mean...?
Of course, it all adds up!
What are you insinuating?!
One of you actually called them?!
End of the line, Moon!
You've gotta be kidding!
He's getting away!
Freeze, Moon!
No!
This is all my...
my fault...
Oh, I see...
I'm so sorry I kept this from you...
You should've just apologized from the start.
You're right...
It's alright.
I can always buy more clothes.
Please, no!
I'll buy some to make up for it!
I'll get a job to raise the money...
It's fine!
But...
I get paid modeling for magazines anyways.
You've got a real big heart, Jessica.
My, but I'm so thin!
You can have this, Sally!
Oh, wow! It's just the right size!
And that's that!
All's well that ends well!
I'm sorry...
It's quite alright.
How does it look?
It looks perfect!
Leave it to Jessica to make
the best fashion choices!
Huh?
Am I forgetting something...?
Why me?!
smile
Where oh where are you, Red?
Ever since you left me,
my life's been in utter shambles...
Get back here, Cony!
Give me back my dango!
No way!
Stop!
If only I could constantly smile
the way Cony does...
I'm so young and promising, and yet...
Oh no, I'm so ugly...
Maybe I should shave...
Well, that went terribly.
"Don't forget to buy some eggs?"
That's right, Cony's throwing
an omelet rice party at her place today.
Excuse me...
Sir...?
It's not enough?!
No, sir, your change!
This is just awful...
How could all this happen to James,
the spirit of charm, the king of beauty...?
Sally...
Maybe she knows how I can stop this cycle of misery...
Sally—
No one's there.
Could've sworn someone called me.
There she goes...
Open it up, Brown!
Would it kill ya to react?
What, unless you're frozen from shock?
Can you guys help out here?
Cony, I got a carton of ten eggs...
James, open this up!
A ghost!!
What are you two doing...?
That really knocked the wind out of you!
Oh, right. James, the eggs!
The eggs are in here...
Well, what now?
This is supposed to be an omelet and rice party!
It got on my Monthly Beauty...
Just ketchup and rice isn't too bad.
But it would've been even better
with that fluffy yellow goodness on top!
And whose fault is that, Moon?
Are you blaming me?!
Go on, James. Eat up!
What's your next vacation gonna be?
A theme park!
What about you, Brown?
An aquarium?
Brown, there are no salmon in the aquarium.
And you, James?
Maybe I'll go to the dump.
Wait, the dump?
What are you supposed to do there?
Watch as they take care of the trash.
Knowing that eventually I'll be
taken care of just like that trash.
What's all that about?
Why would you waste a vacation
on something like that?
Where would you go?
I dunno, maybe out camping!
Camping?
You remember that riverbed we went to last summer?
Oh yeah, where we barbecued
and played watermelon-splitting!
That's the one!
Then Brown went out and fetched some honey...
and he brought a swarm of bees along with him...
and for some reason the bees only came after me,
and my face got all swollen...
Take that! Haah!
Whoo, yeah!
Mind if I play too?
James looks kinda down...
He's just upset because of the broken eggs
spoiling his Monthly Beauty magazine, isn't he?
It can't just be that, right? He's depressed!
Agh, you beat me again!
How are you so good at this, Brown?!
Now hold on! That one doesn't count!
Aren't either of you worried
about James in the slightest?
It's not fun seeing him like this...
What are we supposed to do?
We don't know why he's depressed.
Let's try to make him smile!
James!
What?
We don't know what happened to you,
but you've looked out of it this wholet ime!
I can't help it.
Terrible things keep happening to me,
so I don't really feel like smiling.
But putting on that gloomy face burdens us too!
So we're going to force you to smile!
Huh?
What did you do to me?!
You ruined my naturally handsome face!
Why do I have to put up with all this?!
Goodness me...
What are you laughing at?
You're smiling even though you're angry...
That's your doing, you know that?!
It's like my grandmother once said:
"Good things come to those who smile,
even when you're sad."
How am I supposed to do that?!
Just forget it!
They just don't understand.
They don't even try to sympathize with me!
And I can't get this tape off, ugh!
Oh, Monthly Beauty.
The same one that got ruined by the eggs.
Here's your change, $4.20!
Thank you for coming in!
It's all so different from earlier...
Was it because I was smiling...?
James!
Oh, Sally!
Look down, you might've stepped on that!
That was close!
If you had stepped on that,
it would've ruined your smile!
My smile?
Oh, yeah. Sally!
I called your name in the park earlier.
Wait, really? When?
I didn't notice.
How strange, that I didn't notice
your lovely smile.
Lovely smile?
Yeah!
I know a photographer for a fashion magazine
who's looking for a model,
so I'll be sure to recommend you!
Huh, a fashion magazine?
You might know them! They're called Monthly Beauty.
Monthly Beauty you say?!
You mean this?
Yep, that's the one! You read it?
Yeah, I buy it every month!
I could model for Monthly Beauty...
Okay!
I'll be sure to get your name in!
Good smile!
My, oh, my...
My smile, forced together with adhesive tape...
is a good smile?
It's like my grandmother once said:
"Good things come to those who smile,
even when they're sad."
Is it true what Moon's grandmother said?
Does this mean...
I knew it...
Well, it makes sense.
Forcing a smile...
isn't going to make Red come back,
or clean my room for me.
Huh?
Red!
Jessica, is it true?
Had a feeling this was yours!
It was abandoned at the train station.
It was stolen last week,
and I thought I'd never see it again...
Thank you!
Thank you so so much, Jessica!
I wonder how James is doing.
Probably took a foot bath and went to bed.
Hey, you guys!
Oh, you're back!
And you look oddly happy.
I bought eggs!
Yay!
Now we can have a real omelette and rice party!
But we already ate the ketchup and rice...
Then we'll have an omelette party!
– Yummy!
– It's so good!
This is very good, Cony!
Thanks!
Oh, yeah!
Get this: I might be in the next issue of Monthly Beauty!
Whoa, how?
Thanks to you all!
Thanks to us?
What do you mean?
Thank you all so much!
Huh?!
Come on, tell us!
Hey, Brown, don't drop your plate!
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
I dreamt I was flying through the night sky
On a magic carpet
And I just wanted you to see it
Oh, did I wake you? I'm so sorry
I thought you sounded half-asleep
And it made me swoon
Just like the glittering scent of rose tea
When my heart starts pounding, I lock up
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
Even though I could just type a <3 and send it to you
It's hard to sum up the way I feel for you
It's like a millefeuille
With all of my smiles and tears mixed in
I feel happy, I feel painful
I feel longing — I'm in love
shadow
reunion
Next time on Line Town...
Cony's childhood friend Michele
is coming to Line Town?
Huh? Michele is a hottie?
Is he really? Really?!
If he's not hot, I won't care.
Oh, forgive me.
Next episode is called "Hottie!"
...I mean, "Reunion!"
Tune in next time!