A-B-C-D-E-F-G
H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P
Q-R-S-T-U-V-W
X-Y and Z
Now you know your ABCs
Isn't it bizarre, the way we string together
letters from A to Z?
Whether it be out loud or by text,
let's find something to talk about!
How will the world end? What's for dinner?
Let's share those moments of laughter and tears
I decide what I like and hate
But that too is a barrier I can break down
Don't you see? Our words make us who we are
There's something I want to talk about with you
Just thinking about that gets me all giddy
Whether you're right next to me or not
You always brighten up my day
Of all the things you've spoken to me
I cherish every last word
It feels good to think about somebody
And it feels good to put that into words
court
Ta-dah!
I got a pair of the latest and greatest roller skates!
Once I got these babies on...
Juby-julee!
I'll be so beautiful!
Here I go!
Take that!
I-I'm up...
I'm standing up!
And now, forthwards I go!
I scream, you scream,
we scream for ice cream!
Aah, stop me!
I'm finally stopped...
What the heck, James!
Watch where you're going!
I'm sorry, Cony!
Be more careful, dude.
Wait, huh? Where did...
Huh? No!
Not my ice cream!
James, how could you?!
I'm so sorry!
If you're so sorry,
then buy me a new ice cream!
Okay.
Take that!
What'd I miss here?
James went all crazy and ruined my ice cream!
Now that's rough.
James, what's wrong with you?
I know...
But I'm pretty sure this is your fault, actually.
I'm sorry?
This only happened because
you walked into me.
Say what?!
Oh, was that you?
I thought I hit something.
My apologies.
So you'll buy me an ice cream, then?
Huh? What's that gotta do with me?
You admitted it was your fault, no?
Only that I ran into James.
I didn't do anything to you, Cony.
Your fallen ice cream
was not my responsibility.
James just needs to get good
at roller skating.
That's the whole reason
I was practicing!
What happened here?
Sally, please listen!
Moon and James ruined my ice cream!
Can you believe them?
It's not like I meant to...
Hey, when you really think about it,
maybe this is Cony's fault
for eating while walking!
Seriously?
You weren't paying attention
to your surroundings.
That's purely on you.
I hadn't considered that angle.
How did it come to this?
It's your fault, Cony.
No, I ain't! Buy me a new ice cream!
Sally, what do you think?
Interesting.
Show of hands, who wants to take responsibility?
Then let's settle it in court.
Huh? In court?!
Court is now in session for the trial
over Cony's ice cream.
Counsel for plaintiff Cony,
please make your statement.
Cony's skipping with her ice cream, la-la-la!
When James bwooshes past,
and Cony goes bwam,
and the ice cream goes fwoop.
"Hey! Give me back my ice cream!"
"You better make up for it
or I'll sue you!"
Is that what happened?
Yes, exactly!
Now, counsel for defendant James,
please share your statement.
I shall now introduce myself.
I am Moon Mason,
the attorney of justice.
N-Now hold on!
Why are you my attorney?!
Please worry not, Mr. James.
Your case is in very good hands with me.
I will lead us to victory in this trial!
Ms. Judge!
I would like to sue Moon!
What the heck, man?
The defendant suing his attorney?!
What kinda trial is this?
Order in the court!
James, I hereby accept your request.
Say what?!
Moon is the root of this incident.
It wouldn't have happened
if he didn't run into me.
And why did that happen?
I dunno, why?
Because he was walking around
while playing a game on his phone!
Is that not extremely dangerous behavior?!
Okay, I will admit that.
It is extremely dangerous to walk
while looking at your phone.
Ouch!
Children, please do not follow my example—yeowch!
So, Moon, are you claiming responsibility for this case?
Hold on just a minute, Miss Judge!
Please take a look at Evidence A!
See here. This is a photo of the entrance to the park.
Mr. James, do you see this sign?
Please read it for us.
Uhh... "Park Rules..."
Louder!
"P-Park Rules:
"No... rollerskating?!"
That's right!
You're not allowed to rollerskate in the park!
Would that not put him in the wrong
for engaging in disallowed activity?
I had no idea!
I'm guilty...
I'm sorry, Cony.
Ms. Judge!
Yes, Ms. Cony?
I would like to abandon
my lawsuit against James.
But why?
Because he gave a sincere apology.
Understood. Well, then—
Instead...
I would like to sue Moon!
For what?!
For being such a tryhard.
So just for fun then, huh?!
You want a fight so badly,
then bring it on!
Ms. Judge! I would like
to summon a witness!
You may proceed.
My witness is the man
who sold the ice cream.
My pleasure.
Tell me something:
you sold Cony ice cream, correct?
I did! Thank you!
How did Cony behave
after her purchase?
She was so elated,
she started skipping about!
Thanks again!
Did you hear that, court?
She was skipping about!
Okay? So what?
Here's the thing:
This is ice cream we're talking about.
It's very unstable!
One little shake
would send it toppling over.
It takes some carelessness to carry it around
while skipping!
Does this reckless behavior
not show no care for her ice cream falling?
Now for the plaintiff's witness.
I'm Jessica.
Cony's on a diet right now.
So she was looking forward
to getting some ice cream in the park
as a weekly reward for herself.
So I know how she feels,
and it makes sense for her to skip.
Thank you, Jessica!
Then let me ask you something, Jessica.
What is it?
Have you bought ice cream
in the park before?
I have!
Where do you eat it?
Let me think...
On the bench, usually!
Indeed. You don't eat it
while you're walking, now, do you?
I guess not.
So do you go skipping
whenever you buy something you like?
I can't say I do...
You don't, do you?
How can you say you know how she feels,
when you don't act the same way at all?
Well... Cony's kind of goofy, I suppose.
I'm what?
Oh... sorry, Cony...
You heard that, Cony!
You're goofy!
Well yeah, Jessica. You're always calm
and collected and stylish to boot.
I guess next to you,
I'm nothing but a goofball, aren't I?
Ms. Judge! I think Jessica's a meanie!
Wait, why are you going after me?!
Alright, court, listen up.
Let's go back to the very beginning
to find out what caused this incident.
This wouldn't have happened
if there was no ice cream to begin with!
Huh?!
You shouldn't have sold her the ice cream!
What?!
Is that what you think of me, Cony?
No, I just got caught in the heat...
Calm down, girls!
Miss Judge, I would like to sue Brown too!
No particular reason!
Order in the court!
I hear all your complaints.
He's guilty. No, she's guilty.
You think you can rank everyone
from most guilty to least guilty.
But what will ranking other people's guilt do?
Is it not more important that we all reflect
on our own guilt?
But Ms. Judge, what's the point
of going to court then?
Well said, Moon.
You make an excellent point.
If you consider the other person's perspective
before putting yourself on a pedestal,
then there's no need to bring it to court.
I beg to differ, Ms. Judge.
Things ain't all sunshine and rainbows
in this world of ours.
"This" world you say?
Huh?
The world is what we make of it.
If our hearts are pure,
we can make the world pure.
That's the kind of place
I want Line Town to be.
Nay, it's the place I believe it can be.
Is that good enough for you?
Yes, ma'am!
Alright! Ice cream on the house
for everybody!
Sorry, Jessica.
No, I'm sorry, Cony!
Sorry, James!
No, ice sorry!
This is mega-sized to me.
wreck
Good job!
My turn now!
Phew, safe!
Taking the higher pieces is too easy.
Gotta take a lower piece.
Are you sure about that?
Be careful, Jessica!
I'm going for it...
Aah, it's gonna fall!
It sure will if you shout like that!
Sorry...
You're so dramatic, Cony.
Of course I am,
it's nervewracking!
Good job, Jessica! Ah—
Air claps for you! Clap-clap-clap!
Your turn, Moon!
Oh yeah, here I come!
You're taking from down there?!
I like a challenge.
No way, not happening!
Oh, relax.
It's gonna fall!
Shuddup!
I can't help it!
It's game over if it collapses!
I know how it goes.
Now let me do my thing.
Got it!
Told you.
Saw that coming.
I was so close!
No you weren't.
You lost... which means
you treat us to lunch!
Let's play again! Just one more time!
Really?
Moon, you lose!
One more time, please!
You're just gonna lose again!
This makes no sense.
Makes perfect sense to me!
Alright, let's go get some lunch!
Fine, whatever.
What's he gonna get us?
I wonder!
What's all this?
Is this the game console I lent you?
Yup, that's the one.
Hey!
Is this my music player?
Sure is.
What happened to our stuff?!
They broke, so I was fixing them.
You mean you broke them, right?
Heck no, they broke on their own!
I didn't do nothing!
You were treating them rough, weren't you?
These things don't break that easily!
Calm down. I was gonna fix them.
You better make them good as new!
I'm gonna, jeez!
Three years of planning,
five years of creation,
made on a budget of... never mind that.
Some of my finest work,
if I do say so myself.
How marvelous!
It's perfect from every angle!
Just like the real thing!
Nay, it's better than the real thing!
Coming!
We just had some Italian food!
We got you some pizza.
Merci !
I've been so focused on my art,
I forgot to have lunch!
Your art?
Take a look!
You made that, James?
That's right!
Wow!
My, this is very detailed.
Hey, what's the big idea?!
Keep your distance, Moon.
Hey, now, let him appreciate it up close!
See? James doesn't mind.
I wouldn't let him if I were you.
It'll break if he touches it.
Huh?
I see now.
It's just a coincidence!
No it isn't. You just suck at taking care of things.
What?!
I do wish you could see it up close
in its detailed glory,
but it is what it is.
Seriously, James? You too?
Look at it!
You see this part?
Uh-huh, I sure do.
I kinda see it... but I kinda don't.
Do you guys really gotta
put me through this?
Nooo!!
Nooo!! I didn't do it!
Three years of planning...
five years of creation...
made on a budget of...
Huh? This has happened before, you say?
Please get on the ride!
I'm in front!
Time to start!
Huh?
Looks like it's broken down.
Aw man, I really wanted to ride this!
I knew it. Moon's a bearer of destruction!
There's no arguing that.
I hear the café in town is serving Mont Blancs
at half off for its first ten customers!
Oh my! Let's go there!
Cony's too quick to jump to conclusions...
I see.
I don't blame him for feeling sad.
Come on, James, can't you come
in here and talk?
Shh! Do you wanna destroy
my masterpiece again?
Improve my concentration?
Yep! It'll make you a bit less uncouth.
Excuse me?
Don't be offended!
I just want to patch up your flaws!
After all, you always wreck things
because you can't keep calm.
If you train this way...
Juby...
Julee!
Keep your concentration!
G-Got it!
J-Juby...
You break before you can even shoot...
You're giving Moon a tea ceremony lesson?
Yeah. It should improve his concentration.
But what if he breaks this?
I got cups that don't break!
Oh, never mind then.
I hate sitting like this...
Are you hanging in there, Brown?
It doesn't hurt at all?!
Attention!
Here is your snack.
Whew! Looks yummy!
Do not say "looks yummy."
You must bow and say "thank you."
Thank you.
Good.
Hold it!
Wait, there's more?!
Place the dish between you and Brown,
bow and say "after you,"
take yours,
bow and say "thank you,"
and leave the dish between you and Brown.
Really? Sounds like such a pain.
Every last step is important!
Especially for you, Moon!
Why, you...!
Whew, now that's yum—
You serve excellent tea.
Thank you.
My feet fell asleep!
Moon broke himself!
Moon hasn't left his house since.
That's unfortunate.
Certainly unlike him.
This is a real pickle.
What's the matter, sir?
Oh? Well...
We have to demolish this building,
but we haven't figured out how.
For every struggle over things getting broken,
there's a struggle over not getting
to break something.
That's it!
Wh-What are you dragging me out for?
We need you for something! It's important!
If you're gonna call me the
"bearer of destruction" again, just forget it!
That's it! We need you to bear some destruction!
Say what?
Unleash your Moon Power on this building!
I don't think I can destroy this...
Believe in yourself!
Just do what you always do!
You're the man for the job!
I'm counting on you!
Alright! Let's do this!
Take this!
See? It didn't break.
Just a bunch of coincidences!
Don't give up after one blow!
Uh, okay. I really don't think
this is gonna work, though...
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
I dreamt I was flying through the night sky
mahou no juutan ni notte
On a magic carpet
tondeku yozora no yume
And I just wanted you to see it
kimi ni mo
kimi ni mo misetakute
misetai
Oh, did I wake you? I'm so sorry
okoshichatta kana? gomen ne
I thought you sounded half-asleep
neboketa kotobatachi ni
And it made me swoon
nandaka
nandaka kyun to kita
kyun kyun
Just like the glittering scent of rose tea
kirameku kaori no roozu tii mitai ni
When my heart starts pounding, I lock up
dokidoki no sono shunkan
tojikomeru
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
Even though I could just type a <3 and send it to you
yubisaki haato wo nosete
tsutawattara ii no ni
It's hard to sum up the way I feel for you
kimi e no kono kimochi
hitokoto ja tarinai
It's like a millefeuille
egao mo namida mo zenbu
With all of my smiles and tears mixed in
tsumikasaneta mirufiiyu
I feel happy, I feel painful
ureshii setsunai itoshii
I feel longing — I'm in love
koishiteru
happiness
carpe diem
Next time on Line Town...
What fruits do you like topping
a cake with?
Apples? Pineapples? Chestnuts are pretty good.
Not to mention oranges and blueberries.
happiness
carpe diem
But my favorite has to be strawberries!
Strawberries? Gotta have 'em!
Gotta savor 'em!
Gotta savor the memory...
and seize the day!