A-B-C-D-E-F-G
H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P
Q-R-S-T-U-V-W
X-Y and Z
Now you know your ABCs
Isn't it bizarre, the way we string together
letters from A to Z?
Whether it be out loud or by text,
let's find something to talk about!
How will the world end? What's for dinner?
Let's share those moments of laughter and tears
I decide what I like and hate
But that too is a barrier I can break down
Don't you see? Our words make us who we are
There's something I want to talk about with you
Just thinking about that gets me all giddy
Whether you're right next to me or not
You always brighten up my day
Of all the things you've spoken to me
I cherish every last word
It feels good to think about somebody
And it feels good to put that into words
corn
Look at all that corn!
What a big cornfield!
Thanks for comin'!
I brought my friends along!
Much appreciated!
I've been looking to harvest my corn,
but there's been a lotta crows flying around.
I need to harvest everything
before they can attack,
and for that, I need your help!
We're on it!
I've always wanted to do farming!
Let's get a move on, then!
Okay!
Now you give it a try.
Let's see...
Stand like this,
hold the ear of the corn...
I did it!
The corn is inside that husk!
It is?
It looks delicious!
It really does!
The kernels are golden
and brilliant...
like a jewel!
Juby-julee! Here I am!
You like?
What's all that for?
Protection from the sun!
A UV ray-repelling sun visor
and gloves!
And I put lots of sunscreen on,
so my skin is perfectly covered!
Let's get this heavenly harvesting on the road!
I love corn!
Oh yes I do!
I hate worms! Yucky yucky worms!
So gross!
James...
Someone's not cut out for farming.
Huh?
Are you seriously eating it raw, Moon?
Come on. Everyone knows corn is best fresh!
I wouldn't mind you taking one...
Stop eating so many!
How can I? It's so good!
Why can't you be more like Brown?
Whoa!
That's crazy!
Oh no!
Aah, Brown! Hang in there!
Guys, help!
We all harvested quite a lot.
But it's only around a third.
Let's keep it up!
Huh? The crows are coming!
What?!
I won't let you!
Ow-ow-ow! Quit it! Ow!
No! My hair is a mess!
Help me!
Ack! We're no match for those crows!
I have to disagree!
If we all work together,
we can put a stop to those crows!
Exactly! We'll put together a plan
and keep this farm protected!
Yeah!
Thank you all so much!
From now on, consider us...
the Crowbusters!
That's a team name I can vibe with!
We'll make you the captain, Cony!
Do your best, Captain Cony!
We're counting on you, Captain!
Oh, please, I'm no captain.
I don't like where this is going!
Even if we put up a fight
and drive the crows away...
Three cheers to Captain Cony!
Hip, hip, hooray!
Everyone, the corn is ready
for Captain Cony!
Bravo, Captain Cony!
Captain Cony!
Thank you, guys!
"Captain" Cony will get all the glory!
I object!
Huh?
Cony, I can't let you take on
such a dangerous job!
Crows are very intelligent!
They'll target you!
They'll treat you like prey
and tear you apart!
I can't let that happen
to a delicate young lady like you.
I am not delicate.
You are delicate.
I'll be the captain.
Say what?
I'm perfectly fine
being the crows' target.
You would sacrifice yourself?
When did you become such a hero?
You're so brave, Moon!
Thank you, Moon.
You're so kindhearted!
I'm your man-dolin.
You're the perfect captain!
Knew you'd think so.
Alright!
I am now the captain
of the Crowbusters!
Sir, you can count on me
to keep your corn safe.
I appreciate it.
Great! I expect all of you to follow my lead.
The captain's orders are absolute!
I will not allow any of you to disobey me!
Anyone else think
he's getting kinda cocky?
Typical Moon...
First off, we shall figure out a plan
to dispel the crows.
Do you have any ideas, Sally?
Let me think.
We should have someone on watch duty
who keeps track of the crow's movements.
And we should make a trap
to ward off the crows.
Good thinking!
So a watchman and a trap.
Hmm, that's not bad,
but it's not what I had in mind.
What's your idea, Captain Moon?
We need someone to watch
the crow's movements,
and to make a trap to
scare off the crows!
That's what Sally just said!
Great! Let's go with my plan!
Whatever.
Sally, you're on watch duty!
You see the crows,
you blow the horn. Got it?
Yes!
Jessica, James,
you'll intimidate the crows!
Okay!
You got it!
Go!
That's weak! Shake it harder!
Got it...
And Cony, you're on the water attack!
Shoot!
Great! Next!
Brown, you're on salmon roe balls!
Ow-ow! Don't throw them at me!
You guys really think you can
get rid of the crows that easily?
Go harder! Put your heart into it!
Stop bossing us around!
I'm the captain! That's my job!
So what are you gonna do?
I...
will supervise you guys
with some juice.
Slurp...
Yum, mixed juice!
Heave-ho, heave-ho...
The crows are here!
Prepare for battle!
Yeah! Go!
My hair! My hair!
We failed!
Cony, you're next!
I failed!
Brown, you're—
Aah, stay back!
Ow-ow-ow! I'm sorry!
Brown, help me!
You did it! Now finish him off, Brown!
Huh?
It wants us to give each crow
one husk of corn?
If we do, they'll help out with the work?!
What?!
Are you okay?
Huh?
Wow! You made a deal with
the boss of the crows?
Dang! You're awesome, Moon!
Way to go, Captain!
Um, actually, I...
Maybe just roll with it.
What?
Thank you all so much.
Have as much corn as you want!
Thanks! Bon appétit!
So good!
Yeah!
Here's yours.
So glad everything worked out!
You said it! All's well that ends well!
Bon appétit!
Ack, a worm!
Eww!
Juby-julee!
magic
If you could become anything,
what would you be?
Hm? What do you mean?
Like if you could turn into
anything that you like!
I wish I could be a world-famous model!
What about you, Brown?
Huh? Outer space?!
So you can cause a big bang
and create a new universe?!
It's kind of terrifying
how big your ideal is...
If I could be anything...
I wish I could be a witch!
As if.
It's just hypothetical!
It's more realistic
than Brown becoming outer space.
You said it, haha.
Miss Cony?
Are you there?
Eek! Who are you?!
I'm the boss of the
Shooting Star Wish Management Center.
Shooting star...?
Wish Management Center.
Cony, earlier tonight at 10:32:54 P.M.,
you made a wish on a shooting star
in Line Town.
I-I did?!
You sure did.
"If I could be anything...
I wish I could be a witch!"
Oh, I did say that.
I am here to grant your wish.
Ta-dah!
Wh-What the?
Here you are.
What's that?
The instruction manuals
for your magic items.
Read these over and—
Nah.
Can you give me the rundown?
Fine, if I have to.
First, open up the pendant
and transform.
Open it up?
Wah! Whoa!
Give your magic wand a shake
to cast a spell!
So I can use this to cast spells, huh?
Alright then. Let me fly!
I'm actually flying!
Wow! This feels so good!
It's Jessica! Hey—
You must not!
You cannot let anyone see you
using your magic!
Huh? Why not?
It says so in the instruction manual...
but if someone finds out,
you'll be turned into a tree for the rest of your days!
What?!
A tree? You mean like a fir tree
or a cherry tree?
Or a pine tree or a cedar tree,
for the rest of your days.
No way!
You will have a three-day trial as a witch.
Trial?
Yessiree.
Many get their wishes granted,
only to file complaints,
such as, "this isn't what I hoped for!"
or "this isn't what I meant!"
So we've set it up
so you can try it out first!
Oh wow.
Let's enjoy the magic life!
What a weird dream...
Huh?!
Wait! Did that actually happen?
It did!
I really am a witch!
That's when I said...
"No, belly button fluff
isn't made from marshmallows!"
What is it?
Huh? Uh, nothing at all.
Beg all you want,
I can't tell you!
If you find out I'm a witch,
I'll become a tree!
But man, I wish I could tell them!
You're creeping me out, Cony.
Something good must have happened.
I'm so jealous...
What's the matter, Sally?
You've looked out of sorts.
I've been unlucky lately.
Unlucky how?
My refrigerator randomly broke down.
It's awful.
Then I spent lots of time and effort
trying to make genuine curry
and bought all the ingredients...
That's awesome! So what's the matter?
It tasted terrible.
That's strange, right?
Curry coming out bad?
It's awful.
I also washed my favorite dress
and hung it up outside,
and the wind blew it away.
Sally seemed pretty gloomy today...
I have an idea!
I'll use magic to solve her problems!
Let's see... She said her fridge
broke down, right?
Refrigerator, fix up!
Dress, fly back home!
All that's left is the curry.
Be yummy!
I'll add a lil' extra...
A stack of Sally's favorite donuts!
I did a good thing.
Oh?
Oh, hey! Brow—
Woops, can't do that.
I'll turn into a tree.
It's bed time.
Can't wait to see Sally
all perked up tomorrow!
Thanks for the food!
Enjoy!
Wow, this curry is tasty!
Yeah! It came out great after all!
I could've sworn
it tasted bad yesterday.
Then again, curry is usually better
the second day.
I'll get some water.
Oh, Sally! Isn't that your favorite dress?
Yeah, it was inside,
even though I swore it flew off.
I guess I was wrong.
Oh yeah, didn't you say
your fridge broke down?
I suppose it didn't.
I was wrong again.
Weird. She doesn't look happy
about this at all.
Oh!
You bought donuts too?
I don't remember buying them.
They just showed up.
B-But they're from your favorite shop, right?
Bet it's nice to have them!
I feel weird.
Am I that forgetful?
I keep getting things wrong too.
Is something wrong with me?
Pleasing people ain't easy.
Boy, I'm hungry.
Right!
Feast, come to me!
Whoa-ho!
Time to eat!
So good...
All this, and three plates of curry and rice
for lunch...
Gah! I gained 6 pounds!
Hold up.
Let me lose 6 pounds!
Wow! It worked!
Now I can eat all I want
without getting fat!
Time to eat!
Ahh...
Magic is such a breeze.
I can lose weight without going on a diet!
I could get used to this.
Oh?
Brown? He was around here
last night too.
Down I go...
Brown! What'cha up to?
Aw! Those stones are so pretty!
You're making a necklace
to cheer Sally up?
That's so nice! So you were looking
for stones that shine in the dark!
I know!
I'll collect tons of stones for him!
Brown!
Here you go!
You like it? It's for you!
How did I get it, you ask?
Oh, I, uh, bought it online, I guess?
Don't worry about it.
Take it!
You don't want it?
You want to find stones yourself
to give it to Sally?
C'mon! What's the difference?
Can't find any.
I'll look over here,
so you check the other side.
We'll find 'em quicker
if we work together.
Huh? For me?
Yup.
To cheer me up?
We wanted to make a necklace,
but we only found enough for a bracelet.
It must've been a lot of trouble
to find these stones.
Not at all.
Well, Brown found most of them,
anyways.
How kind of you!
I'm so happy!
Thank you both!
I mean it!
She's happy, Brown!
Good evening!
Your witch trial has ended.
Oh, it has?
So what will it be?
If you want to be a witch,
please sign this form.
I change my mind.
Huh?
Magic makes life so much easier,
but I like my normal life a lot better.
Ugh, I gained 4 pounds...
If only I had magic to make me slim again!
Too bad I threw it away.
Hey, Cony!
Want some donuts?
Whatever.
Yes, please!
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
I dreamt I was flying through the night sky
mahou no juutan ni notte
On a magic carpet
tondeku yozora no yume
And I just wanted you to see it
kimi ni mo
kimi ni mo misetakute
misetai
Oh, did I wake you? I'm so sorry
okoshichatta kana? gomen ne
I thought you sounded half-asleep
neboketa kotobatachi ni
And it made me swoon
nandaka
nandaka kyun to kita
kyun kyun
Just like the glittering scent of rose tea
kirameku kaori no roozu tii mitai ni
When my heart starts pounding, I lock up
dokidoki no sono shunkan
tojikomeru
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
Even though I could just type a <3 and send it to you
yubisaki haato wo nosete
tsutawattara ii no ni
It's hard to sum up the way I feel for you
kimi e no kono kimochi
hitokoto ja tarinai
It's like a millefeuille
egao mo namida mo zenbu
With all of my smiles and tears mixed in
tsumikasaneta mirufiiyu
I feel happy, I feel painful
ureshii setsunai itoshii
I feel longing — I'm in love
koishiteru
card game
together
Next time on Line Town...
Trouble's afoot!
Moon and James are stuck together!
They're together 24/7!
Moon and James are together
from dusk till dawn!
card game
together
They're together today,
tomorrow, and forever afterwards!
Moon and James!
This can't end well.