A-B-C-D-E-F-G
H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P
Q-R-S-T-U-V-W
X-Y and Z
Now you know your ABCs
Isn't it bizarre, the way we string together
letters from A to Z?
Whether it be out loud or by text,
let's find something to talk about!
How will the world end? What's for dinner?
Let's share those moments of laughter and tears
I decide what I like and hate
But that too is a barrier I can break down
Don't you see? Our words make us who we are
There's something I want to talk about with you
Just thinking about that gets me all giddy
Whether you're right next to me or not
You always brighten up my day
Of all the things you've spoken to me
I cherish every last word
It feels good to think about somebody
And it feels good to put that into words
temptations
How did that happen?!
That was hilarious.
I'm feeling a bit peckish...
Oh, yeah! I have just the thing!
Aha! There you are!
Cake, oh cake,
cake for my tummy!
So glad I remembered.
It's the last day I can eat it!
Even so...
It's pretty late.
If I eat this now, I'll get fat again...
But I really want it!
Aw, what's a girl to do?
Gobble it up!
Forget how late it is!
Just gobble that whole thing up!
I'm really not sure I should...
If you hate the time so much,
just push the clock's hands back!
Wow, good idea! You're smart.
Turn it back!
Turn it back, turn it back...
and now it's 6:00 P.M.,
a.k.a. chow time!
No it isn't!
Wh-Who are you?
Tch, not you.
Cony, are you okay with
getting chubbier than you already are?
You must face reality!
We now bring you the 9:00 PM news.
It's nine?!
It is, and you can't change that
just by turning your clocks back!
That's enough from you, girly!
I'd appreciate it if you stopped
engaging with her.
Cony, you can burn them calories off!
Oh, yeah! I'll just get some exercise tomorrow!
Consuming sweets late at night
will only hasten your weight gain!
One piece of cake won't kill ya!
Got that right.
One? What about the cake
you ate during the day?
You wanna eat it, don'tcha?
You want to be slim, do you not?
So good, yum...
No cake for me tonight!
Good girl!
Ouch.
I know the seller said I had to finish it by today,
but I'd hate to have to toss it...
You mustn't throw it away!
Huh?
I won't stand for food being disposed of!
There are many people on this planet
who starve without food to eat!
I guess, but...
Dump it, girl!
Who else is gonna eat this stuff?
It would be wasteful!
None of our beeswax!
Stay out of this!
Cony, you must eat it!
Just dump it!
So do I eat it or not?!
I ended up eating the whole piece last night...
I guess I better exercise today,
even though I don't feel like it.
Nuthin' wrong with slackin' off!
You must work off the food you ate!
Not you guys again...
It's Jessica.
"Don't forget: pizza party at my place tonight!"
Oh, right! I told her I'd come!
I wanna have lots of pizza,
so I really should exercise!
Good call, Cony!
I can't go on...
How bout'cha take a break
and get some ice cream?
No! You will get slim!
You two aren't helping me at all
with your endless, ridiculous banter!
Watch this!
Nifty skateboard, eh?
It cost me a pretty penny.
It's super cool!
I should show you my collection!
I wanna see!
Whoa, what a cool skateboard!
Is this James'?
I've always wanted to ride one of these.
You must ask permission first!
Give it a whirl!
A quick joyride won't hurt'cha!
It doesn't matter how long you ride it for.
You need permission.
Get off my back already!
What? Huh? No! Aah!
But nothing tops my board, that's for sure!
Wait, what? Where'd it go?
It's gone!
A pit!!
Stop this thing!!
Stop!
Someone help me!!
Out of the way!
I scraped it...
Oh, no... James is gonna be so mad at me...
He'll never find out if you keep shut!
No! You must come forward!
Ugh, this again!
Here I am, at home, with the skateboard...
Now he'll never know
you scraped his board!
The longer you put it off,
the harder it will be to apologize!
I know...
But I'm pooped.
Huh?!
It's Jessica.
Right, the party! I forgot!
Man, I don't wanna go.
Just give 'em an excuse
and ditch 'em!
You said you would go, did you not?
You can come forward about the skateboard there, too!
That's a good point...
They'll never let you down for this, ya hear?
You're right.
But I'll go anyways.
It's raining?!
Ditch 'em, Cony!
Stop intervening!
Put a sock in it!
Cony, lie to them and stay home!
Maybe I will lie.
No! Cony, follow through on your promise!
I gotta go to the party!
And tell James what you did!
Nah.
You know you don't wanna
go to the party or spill the beans!
"I'm staying home, I got real sick all of a sudden."
Off you go!
Nooo!
Cony said she got sick and can't come.
That stinks.
I hope she's hanging in there.
Probably just overate.
Let's just do this party without her!
Aren't you worried about her at all?
Why should I be?
Do we really have to check in on her?
Who could that be?
Comin'...
Cony! Are you alright?
Brown's pizza is still baking,
so we thought we'd come see you.
Y-You were worried about me?
They are. I told them we should just wait at Jessica's!
Hey! My board!
That was yours?
So you took it!
N-No, that's n-not...
Did you really, Cony?
How come?
Go on, Cony! Tell them!
Didn't'cha say you wouldn't?
Only because you keep filling her
head with bad ideas!
I didn't do nuthin'!
It was all her decision!
You're quite despicable!
And you're stupid!
– Oh no you didn't!
– Oh yes I did!
Can you be quiet for five seconds?!
I'm so sick of your rambling!
But I haven't said anything!
Sorry, not you, Jessica...
Don't give me that ugly look!
Do I look that bad?!
Agh, sorry! Not you, Moon!
I get it, sheesh! Stop talking all fancy.
You're so lame, you know that?
I'm lame?!
Eek, sorry! Not you, James!
You really should just come clean!
Come clean about what?
Pipe it down!!
Cony, is everything okay?
Huh?
I'm sorry, Moon.
I didn't want to bring it home with me,
but I scraped it,
and was scared to give it back...
You what?!
Sorry, Jessica.
I lied because I was too exhausted
to attend the party.
Sorry, James!
You're the coolest guy in all of Line Town.
I sure am.
Sheen.
So you're not sick, I see.
Nope.
Holy cow...
I'm so sorry, Moon!
It's awesome!
What?
This scrape is so cool.
It looks like a lightning bolt!
Oh, Moon!
We're all in a good mood,
so everything's okay!
How about you come with us
back to the pizza party?
You forgive me?
Of course we do!
Thank you!
That's one more victory for me!
Whatever.
Brown's waiting with the pizza!
babysitter
Cony's got a grin on her face!
Oh?
"Urgently seeking a babysitter.
"You will receive a luxurious reward."
Oh, my!
Looks like the home of someone wealthy,
so that "luxurious reward" must be...
gold bars!
Nah, no way.
A babysitting job wouldn't pay that much.
Oh, but it would!
Huh?
If you take the job,
you'll be remunerated nicely.
I'm in! Put me down!
Then come back tomorrow
for a simple interview,
and I'll see what you're capable of.
Okie-dokie! You got it!
And despite all that...
I've never taken care of a baby before.
No way he'll accept me.
Wait, that reminds me!
Good thing I remembered
you used to be a part-time babysitter!
Do you really think I can coach you?
Of course! You're perfect for this!
Okay then! Lesson 1!
I want you to pretend I'm a baby.
We're jumping straight in?
Wah! Wah! Wah! Wah!
What do you want?
There, there. It's okay!
You're flying!
Peek-a-boo...
I see you!
Zero points.
Aw man...
Does it even cross your mind
why the baby is crying?
Ah...
Think about what makes a baby happy!
Okay.
Wah!
There, there, there...
Oh, I know! You're hungry!
Wah!
You need a new diaper!
Is it a boo-boo? Or an itch?
I'll scratch it for you!
Coochie-coochie-coo!
All wrong!
Huh? So what was it?
I was crying "I'm so glad I was born!"
Wh-What the heck?
Even babies feel joy from being alive!
I-I see...
Do you see now?
Childrearing is no easy job!
Yeah... I have a lot of work to do.
On to the next lesson!
Yes, ma'am!
Aw, so tiny! Adorable!
Exactly why you must protect me!
Bring out your motherly instincts
and be one with the mother in you.
Okay! I'll take good care of you!
A baby?!
Say what?! Cony had a kid?
When did that happen?
I'm not certain,
but I am certain that was her!
What in the world is happening?!
When's their birthday?
How much did they weigh at birth?
That's what you're concerned about?
Who is the father?
That's the real question.
Hmm...
When pushing a stroller,
keep your arms closed and take small steps!
Yes, ma'am!
Hey, Cony!
Ack, Moon?!
Haha, great weather today, isn't it?
What? Don't play dumb,
show us the baby!
What ever could you be talking about?
You don't have to pretend, Cony!
Yeah! Is it a boy or a girl?
Huh?! What are you guys talking about?
Just show us!
Congratulations!
I-I think you might be getting the wrong idea here...
Waaaaah!
Brown, stop it!
Sally!
Thank you, Brown.
A luxurious reward? Really?
So that was training.
And you didn't have a child.
Of course I didn't!
Why would that happen so fast?
So you were gonna take the reward
all for yourself, huh?
Like I'd let you!
Wait, what? Huh?
There, there. Your daddy is here!
Boo-boo-boo!
Why are you holding a pot sticker?
It's a crescent moon pillow!
I gotta practice for the interview.
I see...
I'm much better at taking care of children
than Cony is!
Hold it right there!
It's me, the beautiful, dandy man...
nay, father, the perfect fit for the job!
Boo-boo-boo... beh!
No, we are!
Time for your first cradle in the park!
Now, hold on! Sally's my coach, you hear?
Don't take her from me!
Stop hogging her to yourself!
Say that again!
Now, now, stop it.
You shouldn't fight in front of your cute children!
Right, my baby?
Goo-goo...
Oh, shut up!
Go play somewhere else!
Juby-julee-slide!
Goo-goo-gaga!
Don't worry, baby!
Daddy will avenge you!
Fly, baby, fly!
Wait, what?
Hey! What did you do to my kid?!
Cut it out! We're in the park,
you daddies need to get along.
Man...
I'm not going to coach you
if you behave like this.
Sally, please teach us how to be babysitters!
Please teach us!
Okay.
Wow!
But I don't want to hear anything,
no matter how hard it gets. Understood?
Yes, ma'am!
I didn't think we'd train like this!
So hard!
Entertaining children takes strong muscles!
Keep going,
no complaints!
A babysitter puts their child first,
no matter what enemy approaches!
What enemy exactly?
I already forgot how this is supposed to help.
Juby-julee!
I give up.
I can't take any more.
If this is enough to make you whine,
then you're not fit to be babysitters.
I'm sorry to say this,
but I don't think you'll pass the interview so easily.
Sally...
I guess it was a lost cause after all.
And just as I started to like
taking care of children...
And now that I can tell
why a baby is crying...
Wah! Wah! Wah! Wah!
Hold on.
Juby-julee...
Sally!
You all made it!
This is your graduation test!
Graduation test?
Do you know what I was crying for?
Your hair was a mess,
and you wanted a mirror!
Your throat was dry,
and you wanted some vichyssoise!
You were bored,
and wanted to play with a toy train!
Hm? What about you, Brown?
"You wanted salmon roe!"
You're kidding, right?
You obviously wanted the toy train!
Wrong.
What?
All of you were wrong.
Sally!
You were crying for milk!
It might need to cool down a bit, though.
That's correct, Cony!
Very well done!
Yay, I got it right!
You put the baby's feelings first
instead of your own!
You're beginning to seem more and more
like a mother at heart.
A mom at heart?
With that in mind, you'll pass the interview for sure.
You really think so? Yippee!
That all said, Cony...
Do your best for us too!
And split the reward with us!
I'll do my best!
I passed?!
Yes! We've settled on you as our babysitter
based on the results of your interview.
Yay! Wahoo!
So where's that luxurious reward?
Right away!
A year's supply of disposable diapers!
"Luxurious" my foot...
So where's the precious baby?
Huh?
Whaaat?!
This is the little master
you'll be looking after!
Eek! A monster!
Cony, why is he crying?
Milk, or a new diaper?
How am I supposed to know?!
The little master seems so happy!
How wonderful!
This isn't wonderful at all!!
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
I dreamt I was flying through the night sky
mahou no juutan ni notte
On a magic carpet
tondeku yozora no yume
And I just wanted you to see it
kimi ni mo
kimi ni mo misetakute
misetai
Oh, did I wake you? I'm so sorry
okoshichatta kana? gomen ne
I thought you sounded half-asleep
neboketa kotobatachi ni
And it made me swoon
nandaka
nandaka kyun to kita
kyun kyun
Just like the glittering scent of rose tea
kirameku kaori no roozu tii mitai ni
When my heart starts pounding, I lock up
dokidoki no sono shunkan
tojikomeru
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
Even though I could just type a <3 and send it to you
yubisaki haato wo nosete
tsutawattara ii no ni
It's hard to sum up the way I feel for you
kimi e no kono kimochi
hitokoto ja tarinai
It's like a millefeuille
egao mo namida mo zenbu
With all of my smiles and tears mixed in
tsumikasaneta mirufiiyu
I feel happy, I feel painful
ureshii setsunai itoshii
I feel longing — I'm in love
koishiteru
devil zombie
guest 7
Next time on Line Town...
Oh my gosh! Cony's become the Devil Zombie!
Wait, you don't know what the Devil Zombie is?
You know, the Devil Zombie,
the devil-zombie-like-guy!
devil zombie
guest 7
It goes "growl," and "roar,"
and "wham," and "crash!"
It's awful! Repulsive! Simply horrendous!
To put it simply, it's a Devil Zombie.