A-B-C-D-E-F-G
H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P
Q-R-S-T-U-V-W
X-Y and Z
Now you know your ABCs
Isn't it bizarre, the way we string together
letters from A to Z?
Whether it be out loud or by text,
let's find something to talk about!
How will the world end? What's for dinner?
Let's share those moments of laughter and tears
I decide what I like and hate
But that too is a barrier I can break down
Don't you see? Our words make us who we are
There's something I want to talk about with you
Just thinking about that gets me all giddy
Whether you're right next to me or not
You always brighten up my day
Of all the things you've spoken to me
I cherish every last word
It feels good to think about somebody
And it feels good to put that into words
where?
That's crazy, Moon!
You're such a mess, Moon!
Oh? What's the matter?
Something feels... missing.
Salt, mayhaps?
No, not salt!
Pepper?
I don't like spices.
What could it be...?
I wonder what's missing.
Does it taste bland?
Not at all! This food is the best!
A buffet like this,
you can't get any better!
I have to disagree.
It's three stars at best.
Why are you eating it like that?
Huh?!
That's it!
You can just pick it up with your fork.
Guys, it's Brown!
He's what's missing!
Weird, how could I miss he wasn't here?
Strange. You did invite Brown, didn't you?
I certainly did.
But he didn't seem interested.
He wasn't interested?!
Not interested in your invitation?
Or not interested in this buffet?
That's not the problem!
I needed Brown's help with something!
What was it?
I asked him to pump my bike tire.
Just do it yourself!
I'll give him a call.
No answer.
Oh, relax. He'll pop up eventually.
But what if he doesn't?
N-No way...
Brown loves buffets, y'know?
Isn't it kinda weird he'd skip out on this?
Sally!
Have you seen Brown?
Actually, no, not today.
Maybe Moon has?
I don't think anyone has.
Deary me.
Where did he run off to?
Oh! I know!
Yeah?
There it is!
Hah, there really is a tinned salmon
vending machine here!
Wow!
So many flavors to choose...
Hmm... Which do I go with?
Wait! Not the time for that.
I'll wait here for Brown to pass by.
Huh?
You waited there for 2 hours?
Yeah, but I dozed off for a bit of it.
He could'a showed up while you were sleeping!
Nah, I don't think so.
I slept holding a salmon tin.
Brown wouldn't have walked past that,
that's for sure!
He's not picking up!
Perhaps he's trying to enjoy
a nice vacation,
somewhere with a bad phone signal!
Huh?
Blue skies, blue seas...
Oh, how wonderful!
I wish I could go too!
Maybe he'll bring me back
a flower-patterened muumuu!
I want some chocolate Macadamia nuts!
Hold your horses!
Why would he go on a trip in secret?
Yeah, how could he?
The point is, we don't know he went away.
Oh, right.
You don't think he's sick in the hospital?
Then the hospital staff would'a called us.
I suppose... But where else?
He's not replying to my text either.
Juby...
Has he ever done this before?
You don't think he left town
without saying anything?
What?!
No!
It can't be!
It's not like him to ignore our calls!
But why would he leave?
What if one of us said something
to hurt his feelings,
and he got angry and ran away?
Oh dear...
That's all I can think of!
Well, Moon?
What, me?!
Did you do anything mean to Brown?
Huh? I don't think I did...
Think harder!
Maybe it was something that seemed
innocuous but hurt him deeply!
Ack!
You figure something?
But I dunno if it's bad enough
to leave town over...
It is.
I haven't even said it.
It was on a sunny weekend,
early in the afternoon.
Now, we'll add some salmon!
In it goes!
That salmon looks scrumptious!
Aha! Brown left some behind before!
Yup, there it is!
Phew, now that's a good smell!
I'll buy him more later!
Ack!
Ouch! Poor Brown...
Food grudges are some of
the strongest there are, you know.
I know who to blame.
Hey, I bought him a gold tin
to make up for it! Two of 'em, even!
What about you, James?
Haven't you hurt him before?
There's no chance.
Didn't you get mad at him
for messing up your car?
Huh?
You're right, I did...
Juby-julee...
Oh, so beautiful!
Juby-julee!
Ahh, juby-julee!
Oh, juby! Beautiful-julee!
So beautiful...
What'd you do that for,
you piece'a gsgsdk...
Ouch!
I think I know who to blame!
Wh-Why would he leave over that?
Because you hurt his feelings that bad!
Maybe he's more sensitive than we think!
What about you two, huh?
You have to have hurt him somehow.
Us?
Not a chance.
No way.
Right!
That reminds me,
just the other day...
Huh?
Hmm... Nope, that is not workin'.
Your outfit is a disaster.
It's all out of wack.
Just because you can wear it
doesn't mean you should.
I give you -5 stars.
That's awful!
You're monsters.
Come on, it was just constructive criticism!
We were trying to help him...
Right?
Maybe he's particularly sensitive
to that kind of criticism!
Yeah, he was feeling confident,
and you tore his pride to shreds!
Alright! Brown search party, head out!
Let's go!
Maybe he stopped at my house
while I was out.
It's possible.
It's locked.
And he didn't leave a note.
He didn't show up...
Guess not.
Let's check Sally's house!
Yeah.
Where art thou, Brown?
Times like these call for
searching from the sky!
Over there?
There.
We'll put one up over there!
Find him?
Nope.
No sign of him.
I haven't heard anything.
Where is he?
I can't believe he'd worry us like this!
A Line Town without Brown...
is like an ice cream float
without ice cream!
Here.
Try not to lose it again.
Brown!
train
Super speedy!
I never thought I'd get to ride
a luxury train like this!
And it's all 'cuz you won the top prize
in the lottery!
Thank you, Cony!
Shucks, it's nothin'.
Oh!
Aww! Your necklace is super cute, Jessica!
You like it?
When I heard we were going on a luxury train,
I had to wear my best one!
I love it! You really can rock anything!
Jessica's our fashion leader!
She matches the gorgeous environment
we're in perfectly.
Whew, I'm stuffed!
Let's work off the food
with some games!
I'm down!
Man, I ate so much...
We played some good card games.
And had our fill of video games too.
Are we there yet?
Feels like we've been moving for ages.
You just don't get it.
That's the best part of a long train ride!
Hey!
Wake up, Brown!
You're wasting precious time!
I'm getting sleepy too...
Guys, you can't fall asleep!
I won't give in! I'll milk every last moment
I have on this train!
Hmm?
Huh?
I... don't see it...
Oh no! It's gone!
What?!
You lost your cute necklace?
Yeah! I took it off
and left it right here!
Did you look around?
I looked everywhere for it!
Oh my goodness!
A necklace can't just
vanish by itself.
Which means...
it's a crime!
Huh? Did you say crime?
Yeah!
We're on-board a locked private room
on a luxury train.
Which makes this a locked-room murder!
A murder? But no one's dead.
And it's not locked.
It's all details!
I said a crime, so it's a crime!
We'd better give it a name
while we're at it.
What's this train called?
I'm pretty sure it's the
Yahooland Scenic Railway.
"Murder on the Yahooland Express?"
That sounds boring.
Alright! Let's go with,
"Murder on the Eastern Scenic Railway!"
I already said it's not a murder!
Where is this "Eastern Scenic Railway" anyways?
I deduce the culprit is here among us.
And it's...
Cony!
Huh? Why me?!
Why do you think it's Cony?
She thought Jessica's necklace was "super cute,"
and clearly wished she had one.
Yeah? So what?
Two!
She's mad at Jessica for wiping the floor with her
in that card game earlier.
That's our motive.
I'm not that mad at her...
Three!
Jessica left the necklace right in front of Cony.
So all she had to do was reach out
and grab it!
I swear with you.
I was asleep!
How was I supposed to take it?
You would know, wouldn't you, Cony?
Give me a break!
Fine, see for yourself!
Out with you!
You still think I did it?!
That was uncalled for, Moon!
Ah! I just remembered!
What is it?
I woke up for a moment earlier...
and saw Brown standing up!
Brown, eh?
Get back here, Brown!
What's that?
A sandwich wrapper?
You had a salmon sandwich left
and ate it out here?
Oh, I see! You came out
so you wouldn't disturb us!
That explains it!
Sorry for suspecting you, Brown!
Then who could have done it?
Tickets, please.
You're the passengers in Room 3, correct?
Did you rest well?
You saw us?
Now hold it, Conductor!
Why were you watching us?
Did you come in our room?
Uh... you see...
We found our suspect!
Allow me to inspect your belongings!
Hey! Stop!
May I come in?
Get back here!
Huh?
Where'd he go?
He's gone!
That's weird.
He didn't jump off, didn't he?
I can't imagine.
Then where is he?
He's on top of the train?
Juby...
Aah! He is!
Stop right there!
You think you can get away from me,
Detective Beauty, emissary of justice?!
Why'd you come down?
Some emissary of justice you are!
D-Désolé... Detective Beauty has one weakness:
he hates letting the wind mess up his hair.
Okay, then.
Leave it to the emissary of justice,
Detective Moon!
There's nowhere left to run!
You've got this, Moon!
You look like a movie star!
Confess!
Here? Now?!
I'll tell you everything!
Now, hand over what you stole!
Don't play dumb!
You stole that candy-shaped necklace!
What are you talking about?!
Huh?
Moon, watch out!
Duck!
That's far enough.
Hah!
We know you took it!
Now out with it!
I didn't take anything from you,
I swear!
Then why did you run away?
B-Because...
I'm still in my pajamas.
So you ran away because
you didn't want us to see that?!
Y-Yes, that's it.
All that over your pajamas?
Well yeah, it's embarrassing!
Agh!
Guess that's back to square one.
I'm still certain the culprit is one of us.
You're still doing that?
What about you, Moon?
Me?!
You were there too, right?
How come you only suspise us?
Uh-huh. What if you ate it in your sleep, Moon?
I can see that!
That's stupid!
Out with it! Confess!
Stop fighting!
Huh?
Friends shant point fingers at one another.
You'd best enjoy this trip together
while it lasts.
Um, who are you...?
What?!
Sally?
Why are you here?
I got a part-time job here!
When I saw you guys on board,
I wanted to surprise you!
Wow, I had no idea!
Me neither.
You're like a master of disguise.
It's my necklace!
It is!
Why is that there?
Ah!
I took a peek in your room earlier.
But I left because you were all asleep.
I guess I caught that in my wig
without realizing.
Oh, that makes sense.
I'm sorry, Jessica.
All of you too.
Don't worry.
I'm just glad we found it!
Which means no more pointing fingers!
The end. Case closed.
Cheers!
As an apology for trouble,
this meal is on me!
Eat up!
Thanks! Looks gorgeous and delicious!
Nothing beats a luxury train trip!
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
I dreamt I was flying through the night sky
mahou no juutan ni notte
On a magic carpet
tondeku yozora no yume
And I just wanted you to see it
kimi ni mo
kimi ni mo misetakute
misetai
Oh, did I wake you? I'm so sorry
okoshichatta kana? gomen ne
I thought you sounded half-asleep
neboketa kotobatachi ni
And it made me swoon
nandaka
nandaka kyun to kita
kyun kyun
Just like the glittering scent of rose tea
kirameku kaori no roozu tii mitai ni
When my heart starts pounding, I lock up
dokidoki no sono shunkan
tojikomeru
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
Even though I could just type a <3 and send it to you
yubisaki haato wo nosete
tsutawattara ii no ni
It's hard to sum up the way I feel for you
kimi e no kono kimochi
hitokoto ja tarinai
It's like a millefeuille
egao mo namida mo zenbu
With all of my smiles and tears mixed in
tsumikasaneta mirufiiyu
I feel happy, I feel painful
ureshii setsunai itoshii
I feel longing — I'm in love
koishiteru
magic
corn
Next time on Line Town...
What would you do if you
could cast magic?
I would ask for this and that,
and go do this and that!
magic
corn
I'll do this to that, then do that like this to this,
and finally, it'll be mine!
Would you like to cast magic?