A-B-C-D-E-F-G
H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P
Q-R-S-T-U-V-W
X-Y and Z
Now you know your ABCs
Isn't it bizarre, the way we string together
letters from A to Z?
Whether it be out loud or by text,
let's find something to talk about!
How will the world end? What's for dinner?
Let's share those moments of laughter and tears
I decide what I like and hate
But that too is a barrier I can break down
Don't you see? Our words make us who we are
There's something I want to talk about with you
Just thinking about that gets me all giddy
Whether you're right next to me or not
You always brighten up my day
Of all the things you've spoken to me
I cherish every last word
It feels good to think about somebody
And it feels good to put that into words
space,
part 1
Here she is, Cony with a grin on her face!
Huh?
What's that?!
Guys, what is that thing?
This wasn't here yesterday,
and now it is!
Is it some sort of art piece?
Can someone even build this overnight?
Let's take a look inside!
Huh?! Are you sure that's a good idea?
We'll never know if we don't try!
Sounds fun! I'm in!
Wait up, guys!
Cony!
What is this place?
Brown, this is one of those buttons
you don't push, no matter what.
Keep your paws off it!
This button is nothing but bad news!
Don't you dare!
Cony's house looks so small!
Where is this thing taking us?!
What do we do? What do we do?!
Calm down, James!
Why should I?!
We're high, high up in the sky!
What if we fall?!
Look, James!
Huh?
Wow!
It's so beautiful!
Does that mean we're in space?
So this was a spaceship.
What was this doing in the park?
What's wrong, Brown?
What? You think that's where we're heading?
What kind of planet awaits us?
Looks like we're in for a long trip.
Alright then! Let's kill time by touring 'round the ship!
I'm in!
Let's do it!
Hey! How are you guys playing this so calmly?!
We're all the way out in space
without any supplies or anything!
How are we supposed to get back to Earth?!
Beats me.
"Beats me"? Are you kidding?!
I had an appointment at the hairdresser today!
Not to mention a skin care appointment
at the beauty salon.
And now I'm here instead.
Now, listen, James.
You can get those treatments done
any other day!
Yeah! You don't get to go to space everyday.
It's exciting, isn't it?
Why are you looking at this
in such a good light?!
James, we're here now,
so you should enjoy it.
You too, Sally?
I'm starving.
Let's see if there's any food up here!
You coming?
No, I'm good.
Fair 'nuff.
None of them understand
the gravity of this.
I wanna go home...
I'm gonna get more split ends...
and my skin will get rough...
Spacesuits!
Dang! Ain't these those things
you wear outside the ship?
Don't they seem awful big?
They're pretty big on us.
Whew!
But we look cool!
Cut it out! Quit it, dude!
I have to wonder
who they're designed for, though.
Over here!
My, oh, my!
These suits are hard to walk in.
Oh?
It's the moon!!
Hey, someone get a picture!
Okay!
Get together!
Ready?
What's 1+2?
Three!
I could stare at her for hours on end.
Really?
All of space looks the same.
It gets pretty old.
Huh? What the heck are you eating?
This? It's a donut.
We're in the middle of space.
Where did you get a donut?
Over there.
Donuts!
Boy, I needed this!
Thank you, spaceship!
So good!
Oh, I know! I should bring one to James.
Donuts...
Don't do, do don't...
Donuts!
James, we're eating donuts!
Huh?
James?
Weird. Is he in the bathroom?
Where could he have gone?
What the?
This rocks!
Sally, you gotta try it!
Why are there all these donuts here?
How are we supposed to know?
And whose spacesuits were those?
What in the world?
What's that?
It looks like a pair of eyes...
Like someone is watching us!
But who?
Surely, it's not James...
Which means...
It's an alien!
Relax. You watch too many movies.
Yeah, that's silly.
If there were aliens big enough
to fit in those suits on this ship with us,
they'd swallow us all whole!
Don't push me, Brown!
Moon, you go first!
No way!
Let's all go in.
We have to stick together!
Ow!
Brown, I said don't push me!
W-Wait, what?
Brown?
James? Cony?
Where did they go off to?
They got eaten by aliens!
Cut it out!
Calm down, you guys!
Calm down! Calm down!
Take a deep breath!
Breathe out, breathe in,
breathe in, breathe in,
Breathe in, breathe out, breathe in, breath in,
breath in, breathe in, breathe in...
'Sup, guys?
James!
You were right all along.
I oughta live it up,
since we're all the way out in space!
James, behind you!
I'm not afraid anymore.
Let's enjoy life out in space!
So tiny...
Is this thing an alien?
Looks so weird.
I don't wanna hear that from you.
It can talk!!
Help me!
Cony!
Brown!
Bad Earthlings, bad!
Bad! Bad!
Let go of them!
You ate our donuts!
Bad! Bad!
Those donuts were yours?
We're sorry, we didn't know!
Bad! Bad!
Emergency! Emergency!
We're gonna crash!
Everyone hang on tight!
Are y'all okay?
I think so...
Huh? What the?
The aliens are gone.
Guess we can breathe here.
I was worried there for a sec,
but it looks like we made it safe and sound.
Over there! Bad guys! Over there!
space,
part 2
Bad! Bad! They're bad!
Run for it!
Slow down!
I can't take this anymore.
What are those things?
I told you guys!
That ship was bad news all along!
Brown, I told you not to press that button!
Brown's not the only one at fault.
That's right.
After all, they wouldn't be mad
if Cony hadn't eaten their donuts.
You're blaming me?!
But you ate them too!
Only because you ate them first!
We all ate them!
Not me.
Didn't you get all excited about seeing the moon?
And what's wrong with that?!
Everything!!
There's more pressing matters, you two.
We have to find a way home.
The spaceship might be our only option.
Let's investigate.
Investigate?!
I don't wanna! It's so scary!
And it's awful for my skin!
Someone save me...
No one is coming to our rescue, James.
We have to solve this ourselves.
Cony, Brown, you come with me.
James, Moon, Jessica,
you guys head that way.
Got it!
Fine.
Let's get back to Earth!
Yeah!
Tip-toe-tip-toe...
Seems like that spaceship
is our only way home.
Brown, hush!
You'll blow our cover!
We'll just have to steal it.
Steal what?
Uh, the spaceship?
What else?
Huh?
By now, I could've gotten
my hair done,
then gotten facial care,
and gotten my nails done...
Jessica, can't you shut him up?
He's ruining the mood.
James, you never know!
They might have salons on this planet!
You're kidding, right?
Even if they did,
I could never go there.
I'd rather die than be given
a weird haircut by an alien!
He's hopeless.
What is it?
I hear something.
What is it? I can't, I'm too scared!!
Shut your trap!
Are those the same aliens
we saw on the ship?
I'm not sure.
Wow! Are those diamonds?
Juby-julee!
James!
Wow!
Look at these!
How many carats are they?
They're marvelous!
Beautiful!
James, dude!
These are mine!
Stealing is bad! Very bad!
Bad! Very bad!
Help us!
We will now commence your trial.
For what?
You ate the donuts we went all the way
down to Earth to procure.
This one ate the most!
I didn't know!
On top of that, you did not
rinse your mouth or wash your hands before eating,
you left the box of donuts wide open,
and didn't say "thank you!"
What the heck?
These are so weirdly-specific crimes...
As punishment for your crimes,
I sentence you to a hundred years!
A hundred years?!
A hundred years behind bars?!
Yes!
We're very sorry!
We didn't mean to do anything wrong!
We got stuck on the ship on accident,
and we only ate the donuts
because we got hungry!
We wouldn't have eaten them
if we knew they were yours!
I wanna go back home!
Please let us go!
We'll give you lots of donuts!
Lots of donuts, you say?
Of course!
Ten? Twenty?
As many as you want! Right?
One hundred! Two hundred, even!
We'll give you however many
you can fit!
Can you defeat my enemy?
Enemy?
Defeat your enemy?
Do you perhaps mean
the red alien we encounted earlier?
There's only one spaceship on this planet of ours.
And my enemy is hogging it
for herself!
It took me 35 years
to pay off the loan on that ship!
It makes me so mad!
We get it, please calm down!
This ship won't move without that diamond fuel
which you can't find except in their land.
Even though this planet
used to be my land!
Aah! We get it, please calm down!
So you're saying if we defeat your enemy
and collect fuel for the ship,
you can take us back to Earth?
You have my word.
So you're saying,
if we defeat your enemy,
and we get your spaceship back,
you can take us back to Earth?
You have my word.
It's a deal then.
And if you lose, then as punishment
for stealing our diamonds,
I'll sentence you to a hundred years!
A hundred years?!
Juby-julee...
How exactly are we supposed to
defeat her?
We don't stand a chance
against that red one!
Do you have any other options
on getting back home?
And what about the others?
Forget them.
Let's focus on getting that spaceship.
What about the others, you ask?
Forget 'em.
We gotta focus on gettin' fuel
or the ship won't move.
Fireworks?
Here they come.
Huh?
The enemy we're fighting!
Let's go.
Go? Go where?
Into the fight!
Time to show them justice!
We've had 99 battles and 99 draws.
You've been going that long?
But it all ends here!
Who are those guys?!
Moon!
Cony!
What are you doing with him?!
I could ask you the same thing!
Look at you, making other people
fight your battles! Never playing fair! Bad!
So are you! Bad!
Here I come!
You're bad!
No, you are!
You're 200 times worse!
You're 20,000 times worse!
They're fighting verbally?
You're 200,000,000 times worse!
Well, you're... you're...
even worse!
Mom, Dad, please stop fighting!
Mom? Dad?!
A-Are we dealing with a married couple?!
We're one big family!
But Mom and Dad are always fighting.
You're worse! No, you are!
What are you fighting over?
I forget. But he's still worse!
No, you are!
Hold it!
Blaming each other back and forth
won't solve anything!
After all, before all the fighting,
you were madly in love with each other, right?
Madly in what?
Sorry?
You know!
Act it out!
Huh?
Catch me if you can!
We're madly in love!
We never did that.
Why would we?
That's embarrasing!
It is!
That's a little harsh...
That wasn't easy, y'know...
Hang in there.
See, you two share a sense of humor!
You do like each other!
She's right.
Yeah.
Mom! Dad! We're hungry!
Want to go eat donuts on Earth?
Sure.
Blast off!
Hurrah! We're goin' back to Earth!
We did it!
We're finally home!
I'm back! I missed you, Line Town!
I'll never leave you again!
Silly James.
Don't forget our deal.
Ah.
Why did you agree to give them
100, 200, however many donuts they can fit?!
It was that or 100 years!
I really wanted to go to the hairdresser...
Quit moaning, get kneading!
How long are you going to be on Earth?
Well, our ship's busted.
No fuel either.
So we're stuck here.
Whaaat?!
I get the feeling things are about to get
a lot more chaotic in Line Town.
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
I dreamt I was flying through the night sky
mahou no juutan ni notte
On a magic carpet
tondeku yozora no yume
And I just wanted you to see it
kimi ni mo
kimi ni mo misetakute
misetai
Oh, did I wake you? I'm so sorry
okoshichatta kana? gomen ne
I thought you sounded half-asleep
neboketa kotobatachi ni
And it made me swoon
nandaka
nandaka kyun to kita
kyun kyun
Just like the glittering scent of rose tea
kirameku kaori no roozu tii mitai ni
When my heart starts pounding, I lock up
dokidoki no sono shunkan
tojikomeru
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
Even though I could just type a <3 and send it to you
yubisaki haato wo nosete
tsutawattara ii no ni
It's hard to sum up the way I feel for you
kimi e no kono kimochi
hitokoto ja tarinai
It's like a millefeuille
egao mo namida mo zenbu
With all of my smiles and tears mixed in
tsumikasaneta mirufiiyu
I feel happy, I feel painful
ureshii setsunai itoshii
I feel longing — I'm in love
koishiteru
beach
old man
Next time on Line Town...
Beware the never-ending dad jokes!
The old man's on the run!
Nobody can stop him!
Don't underestimate him!
beach
old man
Keep fighting, old man!
Light your fire, old man!
It's an old man festival!
Cats aren't kitten around!
Get it?
Don't miss "Old Man"!