A-B-C-D-E-F-G
H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P
Q-R-S-T-U-V-W
X-Y and Z
Now you know your ABCs
Isn't it bizarre, the way we string together
letters from A to Z?
Whether it be out loud or by text,
let's find something to talk about!
How will the world end? What's for dinner?
Let's share those moments of laughter and tears
I decide what I like and hate
But that too is a barrier I can break down
Don't you see? Our words make us who we are
There's something I want to talk about with you
Just thinking about that gets me all giddy
Whether you're right next to me or not
You always brighten up my day
Of all the things you've spoken to me
I cherish every last word
It feels good to think about somebody
And it feels good to put that into words
headline
"Cony's Happy Talk"?
Oh wow, you started a blog!
Yup! I wanted a way to share
all the happy things I see!
I'll post this on it too!
Grinny-grinny-grin!
Aww!
"I saw some pretty flowers
blooming on my way home!"
Ooh!
"There was a pretty cloud too!"
I'm gonna blog about all of it!
A world filled to the brim with happiness!
So much happiness for me to talk about!
I already posted the sky pic...
And I wrote about my lunch yesterday...
I don't have anything else to write about.
My blog still only has one viewer...
And I imagine that one viewer is Jessica.
I wish I had a blog with more appeal.
That's easy!
My blog, "James' Beauty Days",
receives nearly a thousand visitors per day.
That's impressive!
What do you post about?
Skincare guides?
That, plus James-style exercises,
simple ways to give massages, and more!
It's filled with tips and tricks
to staying beautiful!
Fun!
You just have to write
what the people want to know.
What do the people want to know...?
Oh!
Hey, Moon, Brown!
Anything you don't know you wish you did?
There's gotta be something!
Wait, what's wrong?
You look like it's the end of the world or something.
Seriously, what's wrong?
Huh? Heartbreak?
Did you get dumped again?
Why?
I only wish I knew.
Moon got his heart broken again?
How come?
That's what I said!
But Moon doesn't know what went wrong either.
All ready!
Oh, wow! That looks amazing!
It's "pho"!
Those are rice noodles!
It's healthy and low-calorie!
Wow! Can I blog about them?
Go for it!
Good, I like that!
Lookin' good!
You should dig in while it's still hot!
Oh, Jessica!
Yes?
Can you get a shot of me eating?
S-Sure, if you wish.
Here's my camera.
Say cheese!
One more!
Again!
Now like this!
How's this?
Is she ever going to eat it...?
I'd hate to break it to Jessica,
but her soup was lukewarm
and didn't taste very blog-worthy.
How many times has Moon gotten dumped
this year alone?
I wonder what caused it.
Aha!
That's it!
This is what the people want to know!
Jessica was asking about it, too!
Good morning, brand new world.
I've finally recovered from the pain
of my heartbreak.
Right, Cony told me she started a blog.
What?!
Hurrah, my blog's visitor count
skyrocketed to nearly 1,000!
You!
Moon, check this out!
My blog hit #3 on the weekly blog popularity leaderboards!
What is the meaning of this?!
Huh?
"'M' gets his heart broken yet again"?!
This is obviously a picture of me!!
You think so?
I censored the pic, so who's to say?
"I asked 'S' why she dumped 'M',
and she responded,
'He's not my type'!"
Not her type?!
Didn't you say you wish you knew
why you were dumped?
I didn't ask to find out from your blog!!
Being dumped once is bad enough,
but it feels like I got dumped again!
I wonder if Cony's posted about
my delicious pho yet!
Huh?
"I went to a bargain sale
with my friend the other day."
"She's very fashionable,
but all of her clothes are bargains"...
What's that supposed to mean?!
Hey, what's new, Brown?
Hmm?
"This man frantically started exercising
after he gained 6 pounds."
Huh?
I'm in the frame!!
And I look...
positively hideous!
Hurrah!
Cony's Happy Talk finally hit #1
on the blog leaderboards!
I gotta hold this as long as I can!
Grinny-grinny-grin!
The new ice cream parlor that opened last week
is doing pretty well,
so I should go and find me a headline!
Hey, Jessica!
Wanna get some ice cream with me?
Huh? You mean the one that just opened up in Line Town?
You really stay up to speed, Jessica!
Let's go!
I'm actually on a diet right now...
Really? But you already have a good figure!
A little ice cream won't hurt you!
Plus, this place uses lots of fresh fruits,
and they're supposed to be
good for your figure!
Come on, let's go!
Another time! I'm sorry!
My nose hair was so long!
It even had split ends!
James, Brown!
What'cha talking about?
I-It's nothing! Nothing at all!
Then why were you laughing?
We weren't talking or laughing about anything!
Gotta scramble, we've got plans!
James! Brown!
Stop right there!
Why are you running from me?
We weren't running,
we're just in a bit of a hurry!
A hurry to where? Can I come with?
Huh? Um, well...
You know! We're gonna go move a boulder!
A boulder?
Yeah! I was thinking my garden
could use a big boulder.
Like a Japanese garden!
So we're going to go get one!
It's gonna be a great, big boulder.
You're a frail girl, so you might not want
to come along.
A boulder...?
There you have it!
Brown, off we go in search of
a beautiful boulder!
Juby-julee...
Juby-by-juby-juby-juby-julee...
Those two are hiding something.
If it's as juicy as I think it is,
it might make a good headline!
Hey, guys!
Hey, Jessica!
Huh? Jessica?
– I can't wait!
– Me neither!
What's going on here?
This is from that new ice cream parlor!
So fancy!
I've been wanting to try this!
Let's dig in!
Quiet, stealthy Cony...
– Marvelous!
– This is so good!
Are they all hanging out together?
...Without me?
It's delicious!
Cony!!
You have to explain!!
What happened to your "diet"?
You see...
And what about that "boulder" of yours, huh?!
Uhh...
How could you all?!
Well, you would've made this
your next headline!
Huh?
Yeah!
You would've taken pictures
and put them on your blog!
Huh?
Some people don't look good in your photos,
and it's ruined my beautiful image.
Huh? But I don't publicize anyone's names,
so no one knows it's any of you!
That's mean!
But it got me into #1 on the leaderboard!
People love me!
Cony!
Just because people don't know our names,
doesn't mean you can post pictures
of us without our permission!
Are you really satisfied with getting popular
by humiliating your friends?
All you have to do is reach out to us, really.
Yeah! Since you don't, we get worried
we'll end up on your blog,
and have to avoid you!
I didn't mean to make you feel that way!
I'm sorry!
I think Cony understands now.
You should forgive her.
Want some, Cony?
Are you sure?
Of course!
Thank you!
My makeup looks stunning today,
so feel free to get a pic
for your blog!
Nah, I think I'll take the day off.
I wanna chat with you guys!
Ice cream time!
It's so good!
It is!
Oh?
Hm? It's Moon.
What's this?
Moon started a blog too!
He did?
Look!
"C's Hidden Weight-Gain Past"...
Moon! What's the meaning of this?!
How do you know it's you?
I censored the picture!
Darjeeling!
I'm so sorry!
I won't post about you guys
ever again, I swear!
typhoon
Go! Go!
Yes! I picked up the secret key!
You beat me to it!
What?! You're kidding!
What in the world?!
It was just a drizzle earlier!
Very strong winds here!!
The typhoon's approaching
very close to Line Town!
Expect winds and rain
to continue picking up!
When did the typhoon get here?
I have no idea.
Welp, let's stay prepared for the storm
and continue our video game!
Oh, Sally sent me a picture!
I'm staying at a resort hotel
on vacation.
They have an amazing dinner!
What a luxury!
That steak is bigger than her waist!
No kidding...
Man, I'm so hungry!
Alright, let's fill our stomachs!
James, you get cooking!
You got it!
Juby-julee...
Huh?
What?!
There's no food!
Huh?!
Are you kidding?
What do we do now?
Don't worry! In times like this...
...your friendly beautiful hero
will come to your rescue!
I'll go pick something up,
so you wait right here!
Amazing! You're so cool!
We're counting on you, our hero!
Get me some katsudon!
Ciao!
You've got this!
Shut the door!
Brown, do something!!
I'm slipping!
Hurry up!!
Thank you, Brown...
Looks like we have to stay inside.
I'm so hungry!
I wanna eat something!
I want seafood pizza!
Or vegetable gyudon!
Or sea urchin pasta!
Shut it! You're going to make me hungry too!
I know! I might have a few snacks lying around!
Well, I did say it was a few...
It's better than nothing!
Let's split it!
Hold it!
How are we supposed to split
such a puny amount of snacks?
Every portion will be basically nothing!
What are we supposed to do, then?
We'll bet it on luck!
One of these has a red tip.
Pull it, and you can't eat!
Well?
So whoever wins gets to eat more!
A bit nervewracking,
but it sounds fun!
Let's do it then!
We'll take turns pulling!
Now hold on!
I know you, Moon.
You're planning to pull one over on us.
Brown's going to hold the sticks.
Are you implying that I can't be trusted?!
Yeah.
Me first!
Yay!
Brown, you go first.
It's just you and me, James.
You're going down!
Let's go!
So good!
– Marvelous!
– This is delicious!
And just like that, it's all gone.
It's not enough...
It's Sally again.
Dinner's over, now it's time for dessert!
I'm enjoying myself
at the cake buffet.
...She says.
What?!
Gulp...
I can't.
The starvation is getting worse.
Please look away...
The bavarois looks so jiggly...
It must taste so good...
That fruit tart looks tasty too...
I have my eye on that crème brûlée...
Just the combination of the crispy caramel
and the custard cream texture
is enough to make your mouth water...
Knock it off!!
Listen! From now on, you're prohibited
from talking about desserts in any capacity!
That includes snacks, sweet foods,
and anything inbetween!
That sounds like a fun game!
Y-You can't treat us like that!
James!
Huh?
I-I didn't say anything!
I know I said "treat",
but I didn't mean it like a sweet "treat"!
Silly James!
This game is easy as pie.
Cony!
Huh?
Easy as pie...
As pie?!
The best way to survive is to say nothing.
It's a low bar, but maybe I'll get some rest.
Jessica!
Huh?
A low bar?
A candy bar?!
Hmph.
Looks like you're getting your just deserts.
Moon!
Fine, so I let my guard upside-down cake!
That doesn't excuse all your tiramisu-takes!
You guys are hopeless!
This is all just macadamia nuts!
Just forget it.
Man, this is rough.
I'm starting to worry it might flood in here...
James, there's a leak over here!
On it!
What the?
Another one?
Thanks, Moon.
Y-Yeah, no problem.
Hm? What'cha doing with that blanket?
Oh, uh, it got wet, so I was gonna
put it in the wash.
Stop right there!
Wh-What's the problem?
What's this scent?
I know what it is!
It's a strawberry-flavored chocolate pie!
You were gonna eat it in secret!
I-I have no idea what you mean!
Where would I even find one of those?
Hey! I was planning to eat that earlier!
What's the big idea?!
Why do I have to get left out?!
I'm done hanging out with you guys!
How do we handle this?
If we split it evenly, it'd be pretty small...
A blackout?!
I'm scared!
Take out your phones!
Ow! Who stepped on me?
Sorry, that was me!
Let's see, where's that breaker...
What a scare...
Oh no!
The pie's gone!
Who ate it?
Is this your trickery, Moon?
Don't slander me!
I haven't moved from this spot!
Aah! It wasn't me!
And it certainly wasn't me!
So it was you!
Then who ate it?
It has to be someone inside this room.
The best course of action for this situation
is to reenact the time of the crime.
Please return to your prior positions.
Alright, then. Please begin!
A blackout?
I'm scared!
Take out your phones!
Oh, I remember now!
This is when I set off my camera by mistake!
Don't do it!
Huh?
What will we gain by sniffing out the culprit?
We're all friends here!
Good friends don't betray one another!
Cony did the crime.
Of course...
I'm sorry... for my crimes...
Aha! Something just hit me!
I planted tomatoes in my garden!
Down there!
I'm working on a vegetable garden!
Tomatoes, peas, potatoes, and radishes—
just ripe for eating!
How could you forget something so important?!
You didn't ask!
Whoopsy.
Cony! You ate our last stock.
Go pick those vegetables!
Gotta reap what I sowed, huh...
Huh? You wanna go instead?
Thank you, Brown!
Sorry, Brown!
Be careful!
Harvest as much as you can!
B-Brown!!
We gotta pull him back in!
Don't be stupid!
He's not coming back without the goods!
Whoa!
What a harvest!
Leave the cooking to me!
I'm gonna make the best dinner ever!
Hooray!
Tomato soup,
eggplant, bell pepper and cucumber marinade,
and simmered pumpkin!
Let's eat!
So good!
It's delish!
Wouldn't have been possible
without you!
Thanks a ton, Brown!
The typhoon is rapidly moving away,
so the rain and wind should subside with time.
Hello!
I heard a typhoon passed through.
Is everything okay here?
I loved the cake from the hotel so much
I brought some home for you guys!
I... I can't eat anymore.
I'm so full!
Juby-julee!
Dear me.
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
I dreamt I was flying through the night sky
mahou no juutan ni notte
On a magic carpet
tondeku yozora no yume
And I just wanted you to see it
kimi ni mo
kimi ni mo misetakute
misetai
Oh, did I wake you? I'm so sorry
okoshichatta kana? gomen ne
I thought you sounded half-asleep
neboketa kotobatachi ni
And it made me swoon
nandaka
nandaka kyun to kita
kyun kyun
Just like the glittering scent of rose tea
kirameku kaori no roozu tii mitai ni
When my heart starts pounding, I lock up
dokidoki no sono shunkan
tojikomeru
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
Even though I could just type a <3 and send it to you
yubisaki haato wo nosete
tsutawattara ii no ni
It's hard to sum up the way I feel for you
kimi e no kono kimochi
hitokoto ja tarinai
It's like a millefeuille
egao mo namida mo zenbu
With all of my smiles and tears mixed in
tsumikasaneta mirufiiyu
I feel happy, I feel painful
ureshii setsunai itoshii
I feel longing — I'm in love
koishiteru
audition
camp
Next time on Line Town...
Cony wants to be a pop star,
Moon wants to eat barbecue.
Being a pop star takes singing, dancing,
looking sharp, making good quips,
telling crazy stories,
being called a natural,
audition
camp
and posting makeup-less pictures on your blog
and going "I'm not very pretty..."
Eating barbecue takes going to a barbecue place!