A-B-C-D-E-F-G
H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P
Q-R-S-T-U-V-W
X-Y and Z
Now you know your ABCs
Isn't it bizarre, the way we string together
letters from A to Z?
Whether it be out loud or by text,
let's find something to talk about!
How will the world end? What's for dinner?
Let's share those moments of laughter and tears
I decide what I like and hate
But that too is a barrier I can break down
Don't you see? Our words make us who we are
There's something I want to talk about with you
Just thinking about that gets me all giddy
Whether you're right next to me or not
You always brighten up my day
Of all the things you've spoken to me
I cherish every last word
It feels good to think about somebody
And it feels good to put that into words
spies
Good morning, Agent Moon.
Here is your mission.
You must retrieve Line Town's data
from the criminal organization
and determine who is behind its leak.
Leaked Line Town data?
Who could possibly
have betrayed us?
You must infiltrate the enemy
headquarters to find out.
But I fear it is someone
you are familiar with.
Excuse me?
Your partner will meet you
at the café on Broadway.
Understood.
Black milk suits you well, Mr. Moon.
Who are you?
Cony, your partner on this mission.
A pleasure.
All mine.
No matter how dangerous the mission,
I see it through to the end.
I make the impossible possible...
An ultimate weapon, a spy among spies,
that is I—Moon.
Yum!
Don't ignore me!
We have company.
Huh?
Hold on tight.
Let's go!
You're not really gonna...?
Oh baby, I am!
Here we go!
Y'like my technique or what?
Wake up!
Cleaning services!
Here's up-to-date intel
on our enemies.
This is the criminal organization's
number 2, the tidy Jessica.
She has a real eye for fashion.
This is James, the hitman.
I'll skip the details.
Lastly, this is the boss of the criminal organization.
I've never seen you before.
Did we hire a new cleaning company?
Y-Yes! It's a pleasure to work with you.
C-Crap! Of all times to drop my gun!
May I ask why you have a gun,
cleaner?
Oh, I know it looks like a gun,
but it isn't.
It's just a shoulder massager
in the shape of one!
Bop bop bop!
Y'know what I mean?
Dang it! There's no way she'll buy it!
Nice shoulder massager.
Sh-She bought it?!
Move!
This duct will lead us
right on top of the computer room!
Are you certain we can get down
there in one piece?
No, but we have to try.
Whew, what a thrill.
I love it!
You do? Then you go first.
H-Hey now!
The computer room
is just below.
All clear! Let's go!
Stop!
Put these on.
It's full of security lasers!
You must get to the computer
and take back Line Town's data
without touching the lasers.
And how are we supposed to do that?
One of us will be dropped down
to the computer using this wire.
It's super cool, ain't it?
Yeah! Then I'll do it!
Aw, what?
A little to the right.
I said right!
Agh, too far up!
More to the left!
This thing's a lot harder
to control than I thought!
To the right!
To the left!
Right! Left! Right!
One, two, rock it, oh yeah!
Hey, cut it out!
Here we go.
I've hacked in.
I-It's all pictures of me?!
Why am I here?
Load that data
onto the microchip!
G-Got it.
Oh dear...
The skirt is so plain.
I should've picked pink...
Scram already!
B-Boss?!
Is Project Moon making progress?
Yes.
"Project Moon?"
We must find out everything about Moon
and make him ours.
Wh-What the heck?
Where's the spy we sent to Line Town?
He should be here soon.
Good work, Mr. Brown.
B-Brown?!
Here is your reward.
Huh?!
Get off of me!
Game over.
Allow me to spell your doom for you.
I'll end you stylishly
and brilliantly.
For I am the dazzling
prince of spies!
Juby-julee!
Cony, take this
and make a break for it!
I'll distract him!
Are you sure?
I love a little danger.
Good luck!
Alright! I'll handle things here!
Hey there! Follow me!
Weird room.
This room again?
Again?! Seriously?
Wh-Why do I keep circling
back to this room?
Wh-What the heck is going on?!
Huh?!
Wh...
What the heck?!
B-Brown?
Wh-What is going on here?
I don't get it!
This is Project Moon.
It's Project Moon!
What's Project Moon?!
Say goodbye!
It was just a dream.
Thank gosh...
I'm going back to sleep.
pirates
I am Captain Moon, king of the pirates
and explorer of the seven seas!
And I'm taking over as this ship's
captain immediately!
U-Understood!
You may have this ship, Captain Moon!
Hold it right there!
I'm the roughest and toughest
pirate on these seas,
Captain Cony!
And this ship is mine!
Oh, yeah?
No, this ship belongs to moi!
I'm the dazzling pirate
who can charm mermaids,
one with the sea breeze,
Captain James!
Oh, juby-julee!
That's me!
Is the pose necessary?!
I'm the captain!
No, I am!
As if! I'm captain here!
Oh no! The barrel's gonna blow!
Everyone duck!
Huh?
Who do you think you arr?
Wait, what?
You're Captain Brown?
This ship is yours?
Alright, hold on.
Don't tell me you all wanna be captain.
You bet! Show of hands,
who wants to be captain?
I do!
Me too!
Well, forget it!
None of you are more fit to be captain than me!
Oh yeah? How?
You see, the captain
is sort of like leader of the ship.
That's a real captain!
They must bare the lives
of their crew,
staying calm and collected,
sailing the seven seas with courage and wisdom.
In dire times,
they must sacrifice themself to protect the ship.
Which means a good captain
is a man who screams "reliable!"
Like who?
Like me.
Nah, you scream "weird" to me.
Shut it!
In this day and age, the only
good captains are the fashionale boys
who treat their hair as soon
as it's damaged by the sea breeze!
How does that help?!
Wh-What?
A captain has to be able
to ride a barrel?
That's useless!
A captain is the strongest
person on a ship!
Oh-ho. Are you challenging me?
Oh, but I'm both the prettiest
and the strongest here!
Oh boy, who's gonna command the ship?
Your ship will soon belong to me,
Captain Sally!
Fire!
Crew, look ahead!
Huh?
What is that?!
It's the greatest scourge on the seven seas,
Captain Sally!
Huh?!
This is no time to fight!
We must band together and fight
to protect our ship!
My standing as captain matters not to me
if I wish to defeat our enemy!
I'll work at the bottom
if I must!
What matters most
is that we protect our ship from the enemy!
What do you say?
You're completely right,
Captain Moon!
You really are most fit
to be captain!
Huh?
Yeah! We've been selfish this whole time!
You're the perfect captain!
Bravo!
Bravo, Captain!
Okay! I will negotiate with her!
Captain Sally!
Please listen to my pleas!
What are they?
I am Captain Moon,
the captain of this ship!
I care not what happens to me.
I care not if I work under you
for the rest of my days.
So, and I speak for my whole crew...
please help us!
This crew is like a family to me!
Oh, Captain!
How beautiful!
You're a captain, through-and-through!
I've never seen a captain
this brilliant!
Captain Moon, you may have my ship!
What?!
Please be everyone's captain!
Wow!
You're awesome,
Captain Moon!
Viva Captain Moon!
Huh?
What was that for?!
Hey, stop laughing at me!
Aah, sharks!
Help me!
Don't tell me...
No!
Another dream...
Moon!
They built a festival plaza
in the park,
and the others wanted to
run a fried noodle stand.
Wanna do it with us?
Fried noodles?
We'll get to have some
when we're done!
I'm in!
I decided to go with "Pirate Noodles"
to make it fun for the kids.
Pirate?
Please decide the manager
amongst yourselves.
Any benefits to being manager?
Well, if the stand is popular,
so is the manager.
Sounds good! I'll do it!
Not so fast.
I wanna be manager too!
The manager's gotta be beautiful!
Show of hands!
Who wants to be manager?
I do!
Me too!
Huh. This feels familiar.
Show of hands,
who wants to be captain?
I do!
Me too!
Manager... Captain...
It's just like my dream.
Aah, a cannonball?!
A-sore!
Be sure to make lots of
delicious fried noodles!
Aye-aye, sir!
Fried noodles, yum!
They're doing a fried noodle stand too?!
Oh, boy...
This is just like my dream too!
So if I do things
just like I did in the dream...
I'll become manager!
This is no time to fight!
We must band together and fight!
My standing as manager matters not to me
if I wish to defeat our enemy!
I'll work at the bottom
if I must!
What matters most
is that we protect our shop from the enemy!
What do you say?
Oh, okay.
That narrows it down to us three.
What?!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Yay! I'm manager!
James, Brown,
you two make the noodles!
Moon, you do the chores!
Whaaat?!
You said you'd work at the bottom.
I didn't really...
We better make some sales
and beat the other stand!
This isn't going well!
Wait, right!
There was more!
I just have to follow that.
H-Hold on.
I'll negotiate with the enemy.
Hey! Please listen to my pleas!
What are they?
I care not if I work at the bottom.
So please, stop inconveniencing my team
by selling your noodles right next to them!
My team members are like family to...me?
Don't ignore me!
You'll work at the bottom?
We'll leave the dishes to you, then!
Knock it off!
Why do I gotta do chores?!
You just said you would
work for us!
What about our employee?
He said he wanted to be ours.
He's ours!
No, he's ours!
Quit it! I've had it!
Why do I have to do your messy work?
I'm the perfect man
to be manager!
I don't wanna sell fried noodles otherwise.
Why do I gotta work for you?
We've got yummy fried noodles!
Our fried noodles are delicious!
It'll make you smile!
Here you go!
Coming right up!
Yummy, yummy fried noodles!
I don't want anything to do
with your fried noodles!
I wish I hadn't had
that stupid pirate dream!
No need to cry, Moon.
You can be manager.
Huh?
It's no fun without you.
You guys...
Alright, manager!
Give our noodles a taste!
Try ours too, manager!
Really?
It's no fun for us
without you either!
Th-Thank you guys!
Go on, give it a try!
What?!
Try ours too!
Wh-What the heck?!
Give it a try!
Huh? Another dream?
Thank gosh...
I need some black tea.
Sniff sniff... sniff?
Wh-What's a plate of fried noodles doing here?!
Give it a try!
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
I dreamt I was flying through the night sky
mahou no juutan ni notte
On a magic carpet
tondeku yozora no yume
And I just wanted you to see it
kimi ni mo
kimi ni mo misetakute
misetai
Oh, did I wake you? I'm so sorry
okoshichatta kana? gomen ne
I thought you sounded half-asleep
neboketa kotobatachi ni
And it made me swoon
nandaka
nandaka kyun to kita
kyun kyun
Just like the glittering scent of rose tea
kirameku kaori no roozu tii mitai ni
When my heart starts pounding, I lock up
dokidoki no sono shunkan
tojikomeru
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
Even though I could just type a <3 and send it to you
yubisaki haato wo nosete
tsutawattara ii no ni
It's hard to sum up the way I feel for you
kimi e no kono kimochi
hitokoto ja tarinai
It's like a millefeuille
egao mo namida mo zenbu
With all of my smiles and tears mixed in
tsumikasaneta mirufiiyu
I feel happy, I feel painful
ureshii setsunai itoshii
I feel longing — I'm in love
koishiteru
wreck
court
Next time on Line Town...
What do you do if you break something
important to your friend?
Well, they do say nothing lasts forever!
wreck
court
But don't worry—one thing that
won't break is your love!
Love does last forever!
So cherish it!