A-B-C-D-E-F-G
H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P
Q-R-S-T-U-V-W
X-Y and Z
Now you know your ABCs
Isn't it bizarre, the way we string together
letters from A to Z?
Whether it be out loud or by text,
let's find something to talk about!
How will the world end? What's for dinner?
Let's share those moments of laughter and tears
I decide what I like and hate
But that too is a barrier I can break down
Don't you see? Our words make us who we are
There's something I want to talk about with you
Just thinking about that gets me all giddy
Whether you're right next to me or not
You always brighten up my day
Of all the things you've spoken to me
I cherish every last word
It feels good to think about somebody
And it feels good to put that into words
small
Here comes Cony!
La-la-la-la-la!
La?
What'cha doing, mister?
Selling pendants!
Would you like one?
Oh wow! Super cute!
You see, these pendants come at a cost.
Well yeah, you're not just giving them away!
How else do you run a business?
Ah, that's not quite what I meant.
They're strange pendants, you see!
Really?
These stones hold mysterious powers!
Powers, you say?
Oh, uh-uh. I get it.
They're those "healing crystals."
Hate to break it to you,
but I don't buy into those magic charms.
Believe what you will, I won't force you.
But many customers indeed
have put this pendant on...
and had their wishes granted!
Nope. Not buying that.
I hear it's very good for losing weight.
Say what?
Many have worn this pendant,
and successfully lost weight!
Losing weight, eh?
You mean it?
Indeed! Who would've thought
it was as easy as wearing a silly pendant!
It just doesn't make any sense,
does it?
But this pendant just
happens to do the trick.
It's one heck of a mystery.
So cute!
This pendant really is cute!
I'll take it, mister!
Thank you for your patronage!
O-Oh, but don't get the wrong idea.
I don't need to lose weight at all!
I just want it because it's cute!
These random rocks I found stuck to cheap chains
are selling like nothing!
Now that's easy money.
Oh my!
It looks great!
I wish that I lose weight
and get slim!
Silly me. Even if it does help me diet,
it's not gonna take effect so quickly!
Urp...
Tip-toe...
Please don't...
What the heck?!
No way!
La-lala-lala!
Hey, Jessica!
Hi! What's up with you?
You look happy.
Oh-ho-ho! Do you notice anything
different about me today?
Oh! What a cute pendant!
Thanks! It really is cute!
But...
d'ya notice anything else?
I'm not sure...
Behold! I lost 4 pounds!
You did?
Yeah! After all these years, little ol' Cony
has finally lost some weight!
You know, I think your face
has gotten more petite too!
You really think so?
Yeah! Like it shrunk!
My, oh, my!
Have I actually gotten so pretty?
Y-Yeah, very!
On that note...
I thought I might treat myself
to some new clothes for getting slim!
So I'm heading into town.
Wanna come with, Jessica?
Sorry, I can't.
I was going to go meet Sally.
Uh, Jessica, have you gotten taller?
Huh?
You sure seem like you've grown.
Really?
I mean, you always have
a good figure,
but you look even more
slender today.
Oh, you flatter me.
No, I mean it!
Later!
Huh?
La-lala-lala!
There's the shop!
Now that I'm slim,
I can wear all sorts of clothes!
Here comes the cute clothes shop!
Oh?
Was the shop always that far away?
Hmm... Whatever.
I'll just have to run the way there!
Yeah, I can run all I want!
'Cause now I'm light as a feather!
What the heck?
What the?!
Why is my pendant super big?!
Huh?!
What was that?!
It was humongous!
What?! Is that you, Sally?
Hey, stop! Stop that!
Sally, stop!
I'm down here!
It's me, Cony!
Cony?
I thought I heard her voice.
Never mind.
S-Sally...
Wh-What in the world?
What the heck?
I-I get it.
The pendant didn't grow big...
I shrunk!!
Huh?
Brown, ya catch anything?
Huh? A white grasshopper, you say?
That sounds like a new species!
What a find, Brown!
That grasshopper's got some kick!
It's shaking up a storm!
I won't let you get away!
Gah! That's one weird grasshopper!
Who are you calling weird? You meanie!
Oh, that's just awful!
The grasshopper's talking to me!
I'm not a grasshopper!
What?!
You think it looks like Cony?
I don't look like Cony,
I am Cony!
It's me!
Dang, you're not kidding!
You scared us.
You think you're scared?
How did you get so small?
I wish I knew!
It all happened so suddenly!
You have to help me! Please!!
What are we supposed to do?
Man, you're useless.
You know, I've always looked down on you,
but now I actually am!
Hey!
I'm not gonna take this
from you, you short-sighted jerk!
Now, now, Cony,
you're a bit tiny
to be talking so high and mighty!
Say what?
Wh-What are you doing?
Hey, what the heck?!
I'mma boil you into a soup!
Don't do it!!
I'm only kidding.
Well, I'm not!
What's that?
She's like a cute little pet?
Is she now?
Here, wittle Cony!
Have a cucumber stem!
What am I, a rhino beetle?!
See? She's no scamp at all.
Guys, I know this is funny to you,
but this is really serious!
Please listen to me!
Huh?
It's like a theme park ride!
You want me to have that cake?
Oh wow! It's huge!
Man, I don't think I can fit this all!
Wait, I can't, I'm still on a diet...
Wait, my diet?
That's it! The pendant!
What's this about a pendant?
I wished to it to lose weight,
and it made me small instead!
So if I make another wish,
it should turn me back!
A magic pendant?
Who would want that?
There it is! That's the one!
Thank gosh!
I wish to go back to my normal size!
Not again!
Are you alright, Cony?!
Yeah... I forgot how small I was.
Thanks for looking out
for me, Brown...
Did you grab the pendant?
It broke!!
Now I'm gonna be small forever!
I'll never go back to normal!
Huh?
I'm big again!
I guess breaking the pendant
turned me back!
Thank gosh! I thought I'd have
to be small for the rest of my life!
Lame.
I wanted to toy with tiny Cony longer.
Other people aren't your toys.
I'm so glad I'm big again...
I was getting worried.
What a shock, though.
Didn't think it was actually
a magic pendant.
Cony! Moon! Brown!
N-No way!
You don't think instead
of turning me back...
...That it made us small too?
Whaaat?!
big
N-No way!
You don't think instead
of turning me back...
...That it made us small too?
No! I'm gigantic!
Seriously? Man, I'm dumbfounded.
You think you're dumbfounded?
How did you get so big?
If only I knew!
It all happened so suddenly.
James, did you happen to buy
a pendant from a weird old man?
A pendant, hmm?
A magic pendant that
grants your wishes?
Mister, that silly trick
won't work on me.
Believe what you will, I won't force you.
But many customers indeed
have put this pendant on and had their...
Je ne te crois!
I don't buy it!
I hear it's very good for your skin.
My skin, you say?
Indeed!
Those who put it on got their skin
silky smooth and glowing!
I'll take it!
Yeah, I did.
Do you have it?
Yeah.
That's it! That pendant
made you big!
It did?
Yeah, so don't worry!
Just smash it and you're good as normal!
Really? All I have to do is smash it?
Yeah! So do it!
Alright!
Hold on!
What?!
Moon, what's the big idea?
You're passing up on a big opportunity here!
How?
You turned into a Monster Man
and you're just gonna throw it away?
Don't call me that!
Why not? It's super cool!
Huh?
You look awesome, James!
Awesome?!
Yeah!
J-J-J-J-James
James, you're a big guy now
Th-Th-Th-Th-The biggest guy in the world
It's great to be big
Big is beautiful, yeah
I'm beautiful?!
Moon, what are you doing?
C'mon, if he breaks the pendant,
he'll go back to normal!
So why not play around with him
while he's still big?
Really?
Big is beautiful, eh?
You know it!
Why is Mt. Fuji so beautiful?
Because it is big!
I get it!
James, you are very beautiful
the way you are!
You're a World Heritage Site!
Beloved by all!
Even Hollywood's gonna want you!
Hollywood?!
Juby-julee!
Juby-juby!
You're a big star, James!
The biggest star in the world!
Juby-julee!
Everyone is screaming over me!
Man, it's not easy being famous!
Are they not screaming out of fear?
Moon, did you have to let
this go to James' head?
Oh, relax. We're having fun, aren't we?
Yeah. It's pretty exciting!
Alright guys, let me show you
something even more fun!
I'm a human ferris wheel!
Go!
U-Uh, what are you doing?
Go! It's a rollercoaster!
Free fall!
Juby-julee!
Having fun or what?
Y-Yeah...
Lots of fun...
What a pretty sunset.
It's so dreamy.
Wow! I've never seen
a sunset like this before!
Faraway places like this
are only a short walk away for James!
The sunset looks even smaller today.
What's that sound?
What the?
Sorry guys, I guess I'm hungry.
Juby.
Phew! All that fun made me starving!
I'm having an extra-large beef bowl!
Me too!
Count me in!
Huh?
James, even 100 extra-large bowls
won't fill you at that size.
Oh, right.
You'll have to turn back
before you eat!
There goes my big stardom.
Oh, well. Guess I'll go back
to being a normal-sized guy.
Just gotta crush this, right?
Juby-julee!
Wait, what?
I'm still big.
Cony, explain?
Didn't you say that would
make me small again?
That's strange. It worked for me.
Am I stuck like this?
Oh, no...
How many beef bowls do I need?
Let's do some math.
You're about 20 times
your original height,
and your volume is that cubed.
Kids, take note of this!
It's 20 times 20 times 20,
so you'll need 8,000 beef bowls
to fill your stomach.
Eight thousand?!
How much is that gonna cost?
Uhh, multiply it by 8,000...
A lot.
I'll never survive if I'm stuck like this!
Oh! I have some rice at home
I can give you!
And I have 10 bags of potato chips!
I've got some instant noodles!
Brown says he has
two dozen salmon tins!
Everyone gather up your food!
Yeah!
That's far from enough!
Besides, I can't expect you guys to feed me
8,000 servings of breakfast, lunch,
and dinner every single day!
I really appreciate the thought, guys.
But I can't make you do this.
I'll just...
have to fend for myself!
Juby-julee!
James!
That was a cool speech just there...
Have some priorities!
Cony, didn't you say smashing the pendant
would turn him back to normal?
Well yeah, I thought it would!
He said he'd fend for himself,
but what can he do?
He's helpless...
James!
Hey!
Mister!
Why, hello there!
How do we turn him back?
Huh? Turn who back?
What is it?
This is the guy who sold
those pendants!
Excuse me?
Is there an issue with my pendants?
Yeah! It made James gigantic,
and breaking the pendant didn't undo it,
and now he's missing!
I don't follow.
Tell us how those pendants
work, old man!
They don't do anything.
They're just made out of rocks
I found all over.
I'm sorry?
They're beautiful, aren't they?
Never seen rocks like 'em before.
And they made me a good profit.
They're not even magic?!
Magic? They're just regular ol' rocks.
Are you kidding?
How are we supposed to fix this?!
Again, fix what?
There they are.
I had a feeling.
Thank goodness.
Hey, what are you...?
These are our stomach medicines.
Much better.
We lost our medicine
and came looking for them.
Thanks for the help!
Goodbye!
Stomach medicine?!
So those rocks were from the aliens?
What happened to James, then?
Oh, right!
Hey, guys!
Look!
James!
You're back to normal? How?
We were worried sick!
I was just walking along,
and I randomly shrunk down!
Just like that?!
Yeah, I guess so!
None of this makes any sense!
Why did Cony turn small,
while James turned big?!
Why did destroying that pendant—
I mean, alien medicine,
turn Cony back,
but do nothing to James?!
Not to mention, why did he turn back to normal
after we got worried he wouldn't?!
Someone please clear this up for me!
Not like any of us know anything
about alien medicine.
Let's just be glad everything
is back to normal.
Yeah!
No! I need answers!
Those aliens sure love causing trouble.
Butt out!
Phew, I'm starved.
I need an extra-large beef bowl!
Me too!
What about your diet?
It's just for today.
You're having the salmon special?
What about you?
I think I'll have the regular beef bowl
with extra soup, s'il vous plaît.
You sure you don't want
the extra-large?
I like it better as it is!
You said it.
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
I dreamt I was flying through the night sky
mahou no juutan ni notte
On a magic carpet
tondeku yozora no yume
And I just wanted you to see it
kimi ni mo
kimi ni mo misetakute
misetai
Oh, did I wake you? I'm so sorry
okoshichatta kana? gomen ne
I thought you sounded half-asleep
neboketa kotobatachi ni
And it made me swoon
nandaka
nandaka kyun to kita
kyun kyun
Just like the glittering scent of rose tea
kirameku kaori no roozu tii mitai ni
When my heart starts pounding, I lock up
dokidoki no sono shunkan
tojikomeru
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
Even though I could just type a <3 and send it to you
yubisaki haato wo nosete
tsutawattara ii no ni
It's hard to sum up the way I feel for you
kimi e no kono kimochi
hitokoto ja tarinai
It's like a millefeuille
egao mo namida mo zenbu
With all of my smiles and tears mixed in
tsumikasaneta mirufiiyu
I feel happy, I feel painful
ureshii setsunai itoshii
I feel longing — I'm in love
koishiteru
robuddy
ice
Next time on Line Town...
How are you doing?
Summer vacation's coming to an end.
Are you rushing to finish your homework?
It happens, it happens.
robuddy
ice
If you start running out of time,
ask your mom and dad to help.
But for now, take a breather
with some shaved ice.