"Cap Revolution Bottleman DX: Side Story!"
People sure go nuts for Kurenai Haku
and Royal Gryphon DX.
No kidding. But you don't suppose
she'll be in that crowd too...?
She can come if she wants.
Not only does she have an Excitement Meter,
but we gave her another kind of bracelet.
You mean the one that uses vital sync technology
to pop out a restraining net
if her Excitement Meter
passes a certain treshhold?
Mhm. As long as those two things
are on her person,
there's no possible way Dr. Kaori could go mad!
Special Bottleman Exhibit Section
Kaori Excitement Rate
I got too close to the
C.C. Leon DX display
and broke the glass
Gwehehehe...!
R-Royal Gryphon DX is everything
I've ever dreamt of!
A wide, packed body unlike any Bottleman!
I got too close to the
C.C. Leon DX display
and broke the glass
I got too close to the
C.C. Leon DX display
and broke the glass
I got too close to the
C.C. Leon DX display
and broke the glass
I got too close to the
C.C. Leon DX display
and broke the glass
I got too close to the
C.C. Leon DX display
and broke the glass
I got too close to the
C.C. Leon DX display
and broke the glass
I got too close to the
C.C. Leon DX display
and broke the glass
I got too close to the
C.C. Leon DX display
and broke the glass
I got too close to the
C.C. Leon DX display
and broke the glass
I got too close to the
C.C. Leon DX display
and broke the glass
I got too close to the
C.C. Leon DX display
and broke the glass
I got too close to the
C.C. Leon DX display
and broke the glass
I got too close to the
C.C. Leon DX display
and broke the glass
I got too close to the
C.C. Leon DX display
and broke the glass
I got too close to the
C.C. Leon DX display
and broke the glass
I got too close to the
C.C. Leon DX display
and broke the glass
I got too close to the
C.C. Leon DX display
and broke the glass
I got too close to the
C.C. Leon DX display
and broke the glass
I got too close to the
C.C. Leon DX display
and broke the glass
I got too close to the
C.C. Leon DX display
and broke the glass
I got too close to the
C.C. Leon DX display
and broke the glass
I got too close to the
C.C. Leon DX display
and broke the glass
Kaori Excitement Rate
So jagged that it's just perfect!
Oh! Good to see you again!
I got too close to the
C.C. Leon DX display
and broke the glass
I'm the master Bottleman Engineer,
Dr. Kaori!
Kaori Excitement Rate
In this episode, I'm going to be giving
the full-view on Royal Gryphon DX...
I got too close to the
C.C. Leon DX display
and broke the glass
Ugh, can you shut up for a bit?
I got too close to the
C.C. Leon DX display
and broke the glass
Kaori Excitement Rate
I got too close to the
C.C. Leon DX display
and broke the glass
Kaori Excitement Rate
I got too close to the
C.C. Leon DX display
and broke the glass
Kaori Excitement Rate
I got too close to the
C.C. Leon DX display
and broke the glass
Kaori Excitement Rate
I got too close to the
C.C. Leon DX display
and broke the glass
Kaori Excitement Rate
I got too close to the
C.C. Leon DX display
and broke the glass
Kaori Excitement Rate
I got too close to the
C.C. Leon DX display
and broke the glass
Kaori Excitement Rate
I got too close to the
C.C. Leon DX display
and broke the glass
Kaori Excitement Rate
I got too close to the
C.C. Leon DX display
and broke the glass
Kaori Excitement Rate
I got too close to the
C.C. Leon DX display
and broke the glass
Kaori Excitement Rate
I got too close to the
C.C. Leon DX display
and broke the glass
We'll be doing some deep research on this guy's origins!
I got too close to the
C.C. Leon display
and broke the glass
Dr. Kaori's
BOTTLEMAN
Full-View!
— Royal Gryphon DX —
Deep Research!
Royal Gryphon DX
Two Bottlemen fused into one!
A reward for reaching the Bottle Stars!
Deep Research!
Royal Gryphon DX
Two Bottlemen fused into one!
A reward for reaching the Bottle Stars!
Deep Research!
Royal Gryphon DX
Two Bottlemen fused into one!
A reward for reaching the Bottle Stars!
Deep Research!
Royal Gryphon DX
Two Bottlemen fused into one!
A reward for reaching the Bottle Stars!
Deep Research!
Royal Gryphon DX
Two Bottlemen fused into one!
A reward for reaching the Bottle Stars!
Deep Research!
Royal Gryphon DX
Two Bottlemen fused into one!
A reward for reaching the Bottle Stars!
Deep Research!
Royal Gryphon DX
Two Bottlemen fused into one!
A reward for reaching the Bottle Stars!
Deep Research!
Royal Gryphon DX
Two Bottlemen fused into one!
A reward for reaching the Bottle Stars!
Royal Gryphon is unique for his ability
to fuse from two Bottlemen into one.
But do you know which one of these hatched first?
Deep Research!
Royal Gryphon DX
Two Bottlemen fused into one!
A reward for reaching the Bottle Stars!
Royal Gryphon, like C.C. Leon,
belongs to one of the Three Champions,
Clearly-a-Pug...
...I mean, Kurenai Haku,
and was a reward for him reaching the Bottle Stars.
Deep Research!
Royal Gryphon DX
Two Bottlemen fused into one!
A reward for reaching the Bottle Stars!
This base concept was actually proposed by Haku himself.
"Clearly, it has to be a fusion Bottleman.
"After all, every Bottle Battler dreams of fusion!
"How could someone on track to reach the Champions
like me not embody that concept?"
The researchers agreed to this,
but were quite troubled by it.
"A fusion of two Bottlemen? What a creative idea!
Haku is amazing!"
"But how is it supposed to fire caps?
"If the bullets were spherical, then it'd be
possible to combine the holding parts,
"but that wouldn't be possible with caps."
"Then have it shoot twice at once!"
Through many disputes like this,
they eventually came out with their first design!
Royal Gryphon's prototype!
The fused Bottleman Royal Gryphon,
designed for twice-in-one firing!
You can really see what made it into the final design!
But this form feels so innocent too!
However! When the researchers showed
this prototype to Haku,
they witnessed something shocking!
"What's this thing? 'Everyone dreams of fusion?'
What does that mean?"
"Whaaaat?!"
"I would rather it focus on control.
"Making sure every shot hits is more my kind of thing.
"Sorry about this, but do you mind
rethinking this from scratch?
"But no rush, take your time to think it out."
"He forgot everything that came out of his own mouth...
"It's like he's a different person."
"Not to mention, 'rethink it from scratch?'
"Doesn't he realize how demanding that is,
even if he says it with a smile?"
"People are like that! All well-mannered and nice
but they sure aren't smiling on the inside!"
"We only have so much budget to work with.
"For now, let's just take this prototype apart
and see what mileage we can get out of one side."
Through their grumbling, the researchers
finished yet another prototype!
R Greno DX!
Aaaaaaaa, I love this!
From the right-handed RG Grip,
to the excellent RG Grip Stabilizer,
to the RG Foot!
It's all so well put together to make shots
around one-handed control!
Any control-type Bottle Battler would be all over this thing!
Or so you'd think!
For this one only created further tragedy!
"WHAAT?! Since when was control in my artillerary?!
"I thought I told you to focus on speed!!"
"Why does he keep changing his mind
when we talk to him?
"And he's so wild this time too!"
"It's like he's a different person...
"But it's our job to make a Bottleman
that meets his demands.
"We have to do it."
"Guess we'll just rethink it from scratch again!"
"Not quite, there's still another side
from that fusion!
"Let's use that as a base and cut down the process."
And after all that blabbering,
they finally came out with...
L Milkaiser DX!
Squeeeeeeeee!!
This one's just as perfect!
It maintains stability thanks to the
LM Grip Stabilizer,
and with the left-handed LM Grip and LM Trigger,
it can make fast rapid shots!
Truly the best of both worlds!
There's no way he has any issue with it now!
Or so you'd think! Of course, at this point
the researchers had to stop and think.
"We've already had the table flipped on us twice..."
"And there's no saying there won't be a third time...
"Well, then...!!"
The researchers delved into production,
using up the rest of their energy.
They fused R Greno and L Milkaiser
and made it fire three-at-once
to prevent any more unreasonable demands,
with its middle shot being a vertical one.
And without further ado,
their completed supersized Bottleman...
Ta-dah! Royal Gryphon DX!
"This might actually be overdoing it..."
"Who cares, it is what it is!
"Let's just get this thing to Haku already...!"
"Eeek?!"
"We're sorry! We'll get back to work..."
"It's marvelous..."
"Huh?"
"It's marvelous! Marvelous! Just marvelous!"
"Oh, uh, thank you!"
"Is it good? Are we done...?"
This is it!!
That was the troubling tale
of wittle Royal Gryphon's birth!
Gwehehehehe...
Knowing its backstory just makes it even better...!
It's the way they made 1+1=3 that really does it!
I want to research that calculation so bad!!
D-Dr. Kaori?!
Gah!
What are you doing?! Where's your Excitement Meter?
What about the restraining net?!
Voilà! Blend Fusion!
Aaaaah!
What the heck?!
Hahaha...
Every engineer dreams of fusion!
Tune in next time!