"Cap Revolution Bottleman DX: Side Story!"
Too slow!
Your training does not stop
until you can run faster than a cap!
Aah!
Now, Ryo-kun!
Let us make this day bloom
like a beautiful flower!
The Private BMA Academy's Bottleman Club
This is the BMA Elite Academy.
It's a private academy that trains children of noble families
into the world's best Bottle Battlers.
Ever since our current headmaster was promoted
at the call of the Chairman,
Bottle Battler education has accelerated.
In this school is a Bottleman Club, an elite club
that only select people are allowed to join.
I'm one of its members, and Roland-senpai there
is very fond of me.
Beautiful moves must reside in a beautiful body...
First, the splits!
Tch...!
You're not doing so well, are you?
How about we train somehow else...?
Now, now!
If you can't even do this,
then you must not have enough beauty yet!
Roland-senpai... I can't take any more!
What was that gust...?
But I'm safe...
Goodness me, you've made a mess of the gym.
I know!
Clean up your mess!
With your Bottleman, of course!
Hocari Ryo... and Aquasports...!
They're terrifying!
What's the big idea?
Looks like I gave you too easy a task,
promising first-year.
I can't hear what he says here!
Clean your mess while you battle me!
Goodness, it's awful noisy!
Must be the farm team!
But nothing will stop us!
We'll do target shooting. Sound good?
You're kidding...!
Target shooting...?
That's Earth Roller's specialty!
And while cleaning? Aah...!
Hmph.
That's what happens when you let all those
fan letters get the best of you.
That's ridiculous...
Then how do you get more fan letters than me?
Tell me this instant!
It's... I...
Because they all...
...love you too much for it!
Your golden, lily-like hair...
Your hands, smooth like an olive...
They all love it!
But they can't work up the courage
to admit the weight of their love...!
And so... because of that...!
Thank you for making me realize something important.
Your blue hair like a ground cherry
is also so beautiful!
Roland-senpai!
Ryo-kun...!
I'll help you clean caps tomorrow.
Thank you!