You don't understand
a single thing about me.
You good-for-nothing friends.
P-Please, Miss Kuromi,
you have to stop!
Ever since Kuromi changed like this,
she's turned half the world to darkness!
Oni! Oni!
My powers are restored,
but without MM, I can't become Nico again!
Begone with all of you.
Oni!!
Hold it!
Huh?
Hey, guys.
Oni!
There's two of them?!
Hey, you! Stop muckin' up my world!
Tch. How'd you get out of the Dark World?
The word "impossible" is not in my diary!
Gah!
The saying goes "dictionary!"
Only the real Kuromi would
flub on a catchphrase like that!
Wow, Kuromi's just so cool!
You're getting along better than I did...
I get it now!
If you weren't here,
I wouldn't be so sad!
I'm gonna paint you in pure darkness!
I-I can't dodge that!
You came in with a cool line
and not a plan?!
Watch out!
Huh? We're saved?
I'll back you up from afar, Kuromi!
Wanna know who I am? Check out the first season!
What was that?
Alright. No other choice!
Take this!
Not if I get you first!
Universe!
Kuromi's keyword!
"Dark Kuromi's backstory!"
My backstory is worthless.