Kuromi and Nico rescued the villainess Kuromi,
but now they're competing for the name of true villainess?!
We shall compete...
...in infinity tempest crossover!
Y'mean ping pong?!
Rules: First to five wins!
The first to five points
is the villainess queen!
Villainess queen, eh?
I could take a liking to that!
Take this...!
Wait, what?
How terrible you are!
Say that again!!
Here I go!
You're literally no better!
Time out!
Now that's just dirty!
What could you mean?
I, Baku, am Miss Kuromi!
Take this!
Smash!
Nico, you gotta help me!
Remember, I can't interfere.
Oh, just shuddup!
Get 'im good, Nico!
This is for the mission...!
Huh?
Victory is mine!
I've become the villainess queen!
I'm sorry, Kuromi.
Wait.
Why were we fighting them?
Whatever. Looks like the me here is happy.
Universe!
Goodbye!
Kuromi's keyword!
"New Kuromi merch!"
New merch of me?
I wanna see what it is!