Meanwhile
We'd best not speak one word
about Halloween today.
Yes, sir.
Yessir.
How is Miss Kuromi?
Haven't heard from her.
Kuromi should be getting hungry soon.
I'll lure her out with my
special bavarian cream!
I've finished up the decorations
on her birthday cake too!
And just in case...
this scallion chocolate terrine
dessert should fix up her mood!
All you're doing is adding more food...
But it should work on Kuromi!
All ready!
She'll be here any moment!
Let's go!
Miss Kuromi!
Kuromi!
Sorry for all the confusion earlier!
It's fine!
After all, we're friends!
Oh, Kuromi! You're so considerate!
Then let's get your birthday party
back on track!
Birthday party?
What the heck?
I spend my birthdays by myself
eating cake that tastes like grass.
Who does this Kuromi think she is?
She's really mad at us!
I'm gonna go find where she is...
and trap her in the Dark World.
She's so much more mysterious
than usual!
She's tugging at my heartstrings!
Gureco, stop! Your magic's going crazy!
Hehehe, Kuromi...
We can't show this, we'll get banned...
Just you wait, Kuromi.
Kuromi's keyword!
"A prince on a white steed!"
A big bonus for me!!