Hey, Nico.
Yeah?
Y'know, when we were in that manga world,
Mhm?
something hit me.
What is it?
I've got...
Yeah?
a real talent for drawing!
You sure do!
I love drawing too!
Now slow down.
I love drawing!
Me too.
Excuse me?!
No, I do!
I do too!
Excuse me?!
No, me! No, me! No, me! No, me! No, me!
Me too! Me too! Me too! Me too! Me too!
Me too! Me too! Me too! Me too!
YEAH!
I said more than y—
AH-CHOO!!
lol.
lolol
That was one powerful sneeze!
You can spare me the compliment!
Hatchu!
Nico?
Your sneeze was contagious!
Say what?
They usually say that about yawns,
but sneezes are contagious too!
That's not...
You don't get to sneeze cuter than me!!
Oh, really?
Also...
it's kinda chilly in this warp gate.
It sure is.
I really wanna go home
and have some of Baku's
warm home cooking!
Mhm!
Like Baku's scallion pasta!
It's your favorite!
It is!
Yup.
Hm?
Wait, how do you know that?
What?
How do you know I like scallion pasta...?
Uh...
That's kinda...
creepy...
Wait, what?!
Are you like...
No-no-no! It's not what you think!
a huge stalker-fan of me?!
No, that's not it!
The other Kuromis like scallion pasta too!
That's where I picked it up!
Uh-huhhh...
Tell me, which Kuromis?
I can't, that would be a violation!
A violation, huh?
Glaaaaare...
I'm serious!
To name a few, 8-bit Kuromi,
samurai Kuromi, macho Kuromi...
I said too much!!
There's a macho me?!
Oh dear...
She's gotta be just as cute as me!
Mind if I take a peek?
Okay! I'll install a new feature on MM!
Uh, Nico, slow your roll...
The peeking feature works like this,
and to activate it...
Hang on. Earth to Nico!
Nope-nope-nope! I change my mind!
Huh?
It'll make the episode too complex!
What?
I feel like all this "multiverse"
and "Universe Patrol" talk
is making the show way too hard
for people to follow!
Don't worry about that!
Your cuteness makes up for all of it!
Oh!
Good point!
I really am that cute!
lolol