Huh?
It's Kuromi Base...
We made it!
Hey guys!
...Wait, what?
There's another me.
Maybe it's another world after all.
Darn, you got my hopes up.
Alright, let's get a move on.
Universe!
Huh?
Kuromi turned into a space-time portal!
I've been awaiting this moment.
It can't be...
Are you the Dark Kuromi?!
This is my world.
It is very dark and sorrowful.
In order to escape from this world,
I had to take your place.
Who knew you would end up here.
Hmm, yeah, what a predicament.
You can talk like that?!
You live a happier life
than any other Kuromi.
It's so unfair.
That ain't true!
My friends forgot my birthday!
At least you had friends
to forget about you.
You know what it's like here?
I tried to make a social media site from scratch,
but there's no one here, so I got no followers.
It hurt so bad, I made up 10,000 users,
made a mannequin and took a picture of it,
liked it from 10,000 accounts, and went trending!
What value do I even have?
Jeez, you're miserable...
So how about we trade lives?
#SWAPIFYTHEKUROMISProject
Huh? No way! I'm going home!
My world is mine and only mine!
Hold it!
Give my Mom and Dad back!
Kuromi's keyword!
"Nico's true identity!"
Who could you really be?