Wh-Where am I?
And when?
October 31st
I'm really back! Nico!
Happy birthday, Kuromi!
Happy birthday, Miss Kuromi!
D-Did you guys lose your memories?
Nope, we remember!
The whole world was in a real doozy!
But since we got to go back,
why not have your birthday party?
No more Halloween under our roof!
We're sorry for misleading you,
Miss Kuromi.
Uh... Hmph!
You don't think I'd get that angry, no?
Seriously though, I wonder what happened
to Nico and his parents?
Oni!
What's the matter, Koni?
Oni-oni!
Oh, yeah. Koni can draw the future.
So I really will see Nico again!
Yay, Nico!
Good for you, girl!
Are you holding your power in Kuromi's world?
Yeah, there's more I have to learn here!
Good for you.
Good to hear.
But your identity must remain a secret.
"Nico" will be back once I've grown,
so hang in there.
Y'know, I realized something
from my journey!
When I do my favorite things,
everyone else wants to join in!
So do the people around me!
Then the whole world starts following
their dreams and becoming happy!
Sounds like you learned a multitude
of things in the multiverse!
Be selfish! Be the person you wanna be!
That's the true spirit of Kuromifying the World!
#KUROMIfyTheWorldProject
I'm just minding my business
And I can't help the quirks
But like, what else am I supposed to do?
When people say something's weird
It's no weirder than the things you see everyday
Am I mad? Nah, I'm used to it
Oni-ni... Oni...
This is awesome!
Miss Kuromi, we have bavarian cream!
Say what?!
Huh?!
So good!
Oni!
Oni-oni-oni-oni...