Clack clack clack
Oh no!
I'm gonna be late!
I'm Kuromi! I attend Maiden's Academy!
Wrong place again!
Well, that's funny.
Something's wrong with MM.
Just forget it.
Let's tap and get this—
I love nothing more than...
I love nothing
more than
talking with
Otori!
Kuromi!
I think I twisted my ankle...
I'll carry you.
Are you sure?
I'm not supposed to, but yeah.
Thanks!
Let's go.
What's that?
Hey.
Want a ride?
Hey. Want a ride?
A prince on a white steed!
K-Kuromi, "Kuromi" went that way.
Hey there, little kitten.
Swoon!
Gasp!
It's you...
Every song I listen
to with you
is a love song.
Every song I listen to with you
I need you!!
Poor guy.
Why don't you
come home with me?
Senpai...
Poor guy. Why don't you come home with me?
Hubba-hubba! He's perfect!
This world's far too stimulating for you!
We've gotta get out of here fast!
Kuromi...
There's something I have to tell you.
What is it?
What could it be?
He's not talkin' to you!
Hah!
I gotta see the end!
What?!
Let's go!
You see,
I've always...
You see, I've always...
Ba-dump
Ba-dump!
had feelings...
Had feelings?!
BAM
...for an extra-large serving!
Bowl
Beef
...for an extra-large serving!
Beef bowls:
the next big flirting tactic?!
Beef bowl?!
Kuromi's keyword!
"The god of manga!"
I'm gonna draw a manga!