Ugh, where are we?
Huh? That's odd.
We're in a different world entirely.
What's the big idea?!
I swear, I followed the manual...
Do we have to tap the me
from this world to get out?
Don't worry. I'll get you home safe and sound.
Bold words, considering you've done
nothing right so far.
Kuromi!
What are you doing?
Hey, it's you, Baku!
Don't act so cocky, Kuromi!
Get cleaning!
I'm not cocky! You're cocky!
That's this world's Baku, not yours.
Who could you be?
Is that this world's me?
You bare a striking resemblance to me...
Hip hip hooray!
Alright, pal, put 'em up!
You look terrifying...
My engagement got broken off
And now I'm getting picked on
The Ballad of a Hapless,
Yet Beautiful Fair Maiden
In Count Baku's castle
This is all My Melody's fault
Is this song just her venting?
This world's Kuromi sure
lived through some hardships...
She drives me nuts
Though Count Baku's a big meanie too
Her concept seems familiar.
I hope I can break free from here someday
Is she... a villainess?!
I can't tap her yet...
I gotta save her first!
The villainess always gets
punished in the end!
I became a princess to save the villainess Kuromi!
It's a plan!
Say what?!
Kuromi's keyword!
"An evil look!"