Whew...
I'm so cute, even as a plush!
You sure are!
Personally, I really liked both
zombie Kuromi and villainess Kuromi!
Ugh, you made my heart skip a beat.
This is why I can't stand natural born hotties.
I want that plush of me so bad!
That's too bad. She turned into
the door between dimensions,
so we can't get her.
So you're saying...
Mhm.
if we had grabbed two,
I could'a taken one home!
Huh?
Alright! Back we go!
We can't!
Besides, we're not supposed to bring
things home with us anyways!
You meanie!!
Then again...
It was cramped in that crane machine,
so I can live.
Phew...
Also, y'know...
I'm starvin'!
Kuromi.
Do you smell something good?
F'real?!
Yeah.
Sniff sniff sniff...
You're right!
Is this smell...
takoyaki?!
It must be!
(Hits him)
AAAH!!
Nico. Nico!
Uhhhhh...
Are you hiding takoyaki in your sleeve?
The same takoyaki from episode 7?!
Shoot, I forgot!
You know that's bringing home
stuff from another world!
That's not allowed!
It's for research purposes, so it's okay!
Why are you defending yourself?
Managing delicious foods
across universes
is all in the work of Universe Patrol!
No fair!
Ah, Kuromi.
Is the hunger making you cranky?
'Course not!
Just gimme them!
Wait, no! Kuromi!
I need this, it's a research sample!
Aaah!
I lost my takoyaki
to the ends of spacetime...
Aw man...
S-S-Sorry, Nico...
Kuromi, look!
The scattered takoyaki
looks like a planet! Isn't it beautiful?
No food was wasted
in the making of this episode.