So you're Nico's parents?
You look just like him!
I am the top officer at Universe Patrol.
Dang, Nico's got it good.
I want to see Nico again...
Oh, we doing a flashback?
Don't let it run too long!
We visited the Dark World
to stop Dark Kuromi.
But she was more tricky than I thought,
and she stole my MM.
In order to get Nico out,
I quickly gave him my MM,
and he ran off with it.
Ever since then, we've been trapped here,
constantly looking for a way out.
I can't stop focusing on his fluffy 'stache...
I'm sorry, fluffy what?
Uh, forget that.
So this MM wasn't Nico's then?
Nico doesn't have one,
since he's an apprentice.
We don't want him running the risk
of interfering with other worlds.
Wait...
What?!
It's my MM!
Perfect.
We found this world's key.
Jeez, it really does look like me.
I'll tap it, so please return my MM.
Sweet! I'm on my way, guys!
Universe!
Wait!!
Whoo!
Come back!
Universe!
Tap!
Wait! Come back!
Universe! Universe!
Taaaap!
Universe!
Where are we? Huh?
Is that My Melody?
Kuromi's keyword!
Kawaii chaos!
Is this a different My Melody?