Watch with
the lights on and
at a distance
from the screen!
Watch TV with the lights on and
at a distance from the screen!
My name's Burton.
Our completed version of Ninja Gum
left me and Berecca as kids,
and now we have ninjas after us
for some reason.
We had no other choice but
to hide away inside the WNA Academy.
And that's where we met...
Van,
Lucy,
Emma,
and Kappei.
No way!
They're mass producing Ninja-Gum?!
What's going on?
We really need to get
our grown-up bodies back!
And the best way to do that is with
some ultra-nutritious smoothies!
Ugh, could you quit playing around?!
Maybe Baby, here we go! Something special just for us
Maybe Baby Lovin’ Beats Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, always makes my heart skip a beat
Maybe Baby
In this breathless city of the future
I invite you to take it all in
Accelerating at the speed of light
We'll change the world
Boomy Boomy Life
Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, here we go! Something special just for us
Maybe Baby Lovin’ Beats Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, always makes my heart skip a beat
Maybe Baby
Kappei of the Shinobi Village
Rise and shine!
Good morning!
Time to wake!
– Morning.
– G'morning.
It's morning?!
I'll take this, and this, and this!
I'm feelin' great!
Wanna grab some breakfast?
Do as you like...
Feel like getting breakfast?
You bet I do.
Whatcha doing?
Moisturizing.
You gotta start young or you'll
regret it by the time you hit twenty!
You're into hip-hop too?
Sounds like we've got lots in common.
I love punk, too.
Takes the stress right out of you.
I'm not 'bout to lose to you!
Neither am I!
Still at it, I see...
Oh!
Morning fellas. Where's Burton?
Still sleeping?
Huh?
You can either keep eating or answer, not both!
Still waiting for an answer here!
Burton finished up earlier
and headed off already.
He did?
There you are.
What are you doing out here?
Morning, Berecca.
Isn't it obvious?
Dunno if it's 'cause I don't stay up
late with research now that we're kids,
but I've been waking up extra early.
Yeah...?
Your morning smoothie is good to go.
It's full of protein and the whole
vitamin B group balanced just right
to help us grow.
This one should do it for sure.
Uh-huh, sure it will.
And what are we gonna do when it does?
We can't hang around the academy
as a couple of adults.
Think about it, though.
We've got Ninja-Gum. We can turn
back to kid form whenever we want.
Guess that's true.
We gotta hurry and get access
to the data at HQ.
Farewell now, young Burton...
Alright! Now we have 41 recipes
we know for sure don't work!
Forty-two by my count.
Let me start by congratulating you.
Today kicks off your first true day
as students of the academy.
You six will study under me, Bruce,
and Amy there behind you.
Now, a word about life here—
Are you a ninja, too?
Ninj-yeah.
Are you really strong?
Better shino-believe it.
So you can use ninjutsu?
I can use win-jutsu.
That's so cool!
I wanna learn to be like you!
You sure? Like that?
Different strokes for different folks.
Any other questions?
Are we allowed outside? After classes and stuff.
Of course you are.
You'll need to report on
where you're headed, though.
Anything else?
Do we get an allowance or something?
Around these parts,
you can buy just about anything
by flashing your academy ID.
Your purchases will be deducted from
your training allowances.
That's good news.
Any other questions?
Can we drop out of this place
if we feel like it?
Don't you worry.
You're not going to want to.
No other questions?
If not, then...
It's time for Ninjala battles!
Before we get to that,
we must first explain to you all
about just what role
we ninja play in the world today.
The WNA is home to a great number of ninja.
These ninja are dispatched to nations
and organizations with ties to the WNA.
There they handle a variety of missions.
Sometimes in the scorching tropics,
other times in frozen extremes.
Their missions are perilous,
but with ninja skill and fortitude,
they work in the shadows, hidden out of sight,
contributing to the advance of humankind.
Many of the world's peace treaties
and even agreements on framework
to combat global climate change
would never have been possible
without the help of us ninjas.
You could say that our world today
exists thanks to ninja support.
That's so cool!
So that's the sort of work my dad does.
Helping the world and hiding from the spotlight.
It's pretty awesome when you
lay it all out like that.
Sure is.
Devote yourselves to your training
and become great ninjas, young ones!
Yessir!
You can count on me!
Next up is Ninjala battle training.
About time!
I saw all of you in action during
the exhibition match.
I'll be honest, you've still got
lots to learn.
But with me you'll shino-be
your shino-best.
What...?
I can't wait!
Van and Kappei, start us off.
– 'Kay!
– Sure thing!
I hope you're ready.
To get beaten to a pulp, that is!
And I hope you're ready to
get sent flying!
The heck is this?!
What?!
That's a Corn Bat.
Ninja-Gum can turn into all sorts of
weapons, not just the IPPON Katana.
It can?
Cool! Lemme give it a try!
Great! I got me a hammer!
What else can it turn into?
How about a board?
Whoa!
Now there's a funny face!
A demon from Oedo!
And that's not all.
I'm a real genius, eh?
C'mon, then!
A sneaker!
That's Cerberus.
A hammer-type Gum Weapon.
Cerberus, huh? I think this is my jam!
Gimme your best shot!
Here goes!
Begin!
Go! Fight, fight!
Now's my chance!
Is that a shield?
I didn't know you could do that!
Oh, I'm just getting started!
What?!
Van, keep your distance!
Don't let him close in on you!
You're done for!
Whoops! Whiffed that one.
I'm not gonna lose that easy!
Not that...
Not that either!
That's more like it!
Mhmm.
It's all the same to me!
You won't get near me now!
Come on, bring it on!
Looks like we found a better fit for Van.
Eat this!
Ack!
Bwha?!
What?!
Wh-What just happened?
The Trick Ball can leave your
opponent temporarily helpless.
Now's my chance!
Oof! Agh! Cut it out!
Stop, I can't even move!
Gotcha now!
Gumchi!
Bwah!
What is that thing?
That's the little guy from yesterday!
Gumchi, Gumchi!
Gumchi! You're not supposed to be out here!
What's going on?
Well, so now that's where you went.
This little fellow is Gumchi.
My twin brother Genunsai in Oedo
left him here in Kappei's care.
Your twin? But then... No way!
My gramps runs a sword school in Iga Village.
Iga is famous for its ninjas,
so I've always loved 'em, but Gramps
told me there was no such thing.
I don't know any stinking ninjutsu!
But ninjutsu and sword skills are
pretty much the same, right?
Can you please just run a ninja dojo?
There's grant money in it for you.
Enough of this nonsense!
Leave me be! Go on, get!
We'll be back,
please just think it through.
You could at least join our
Requiem Festival this year.
Like I wanna help out at a festival
for a bunch of tourists!
You dilly-dallied on your way home,
didn't you, Kappei!
Give me 1,000 reps to make up for it!
Uh, sure thing, Gramps. I mean, master!
And bring in the laundry once you're done!
And get crackin' on dinner after that!
So Gramps, what was that
about the Reeky Bum Festival?
That's Requiem Festival, you dolt!
It's a festival we hold to
calm the souls of our Iga ancestors
and ask them to watch over us.
Yeah? So like, ninja ancestors, then?
Do they reek?
Absolutely not!
And there are no ninjas in Iga Village, okay?
That's just some story the people
'round here made up.
Now hush up and get back to your reps—
Pardon the intrusion.
And just who might you be?
I take it you are Master Genunsai.
That I am. Now who are you?
What the?!
Don't tell me, you're—
That's my Gramps you're threatening!
Little brat!
Ninpo, Flame Strike!
No way! Ninpo?!
Ninpo, Wind Blade!
Gramps!
I'll be fine.
It's only a scratch.
What was all that? Ninpo...?
Are you a ninja, Gramps?
No point in hiding it now, I suppose.
Our ancestors have long lived
in the lands of Iga.
But one day we began talking of this
shrine and ninja as stuff of legend,
hiding that we were ninja ourselves.
I knew ninja were real!
Huh?
What the heck is this thing?
Is it trying to talk?!
My guess is it's not something from earth.
Might well be an alien.
An alien?!
Is it friendly? It's not gonna bite, right?
You'll be fine.
So long as your heart is pure,
you have nothing to fear.
Gum!
Right?
Gumchi first appeared hundreds of years ago.
Some time after a massive meteorite
landed in Iga Village, it would seem.
Since then it has lived here.
Some called it a monster,
others feared it a ghost,
and people began to flee the village.
So the remaining tribe of Shinobi built a shrine,
hid away their techniques and powers,
and have protected the lands
for generations since.
Countless villains from far-off
lands tried time and again
to steal Gumchi away.
Those you faced were of the very same sort.
To think you hid it out in a place like this.
Time to hand it over.
Gummm!
Relentless, aren't you? What is the—
Gramps!
I'm not handing this little guy over
to the likes of you!
You'll have to fight your way through me!
Kappei, don't! Flee this place!
I'll keep the two of you safe!
Gummm!
Could it be...?
What?!
Gumchi, Gumchi!
So your name's Gumchi, huh?
Gum!
Alright, let's do this!
Well I'll be!
Ninpo, Flame Strike!
Kappei!
Whoa, that was awesome!
Gumchi, you're something else!
Coolchi, coolchi!
Take Gumchi with you and travel across the sea.
Seek out my twin brother, Genryusai.
Learn the true ways of the ninja.
If me and Gumchi are going overseas,
then what about you?
I'm staying right here.
What?
I can't just leave you here!
Kappei, the blood of the Shinobi
flows through you.
This day was destined to come.
The blood of the Shinobi... I'm a ninja...
Alright then, Gramps.
Gumchi, you and me
are headed for Komerika!
With you and some new Shinobi powers,
I feel ready to take on anything!
Whaddya say, Gumchi?
Yeahchi, yeahchi!
Devote yourself to the way, Kappei.
You can count on me, Gramps!
What a heartwarming tale...
You sound pretty tough!
If you're not a baddie,
then I guess that makes us friends!
Gumchi!
Mhmm.
Something wrong?
Nah, it's nothing.
These go off all night long, you know.
This is my favorite day
of the summer every year.
We have firework festivals
back in Oedo, too.
It's awesome. You can get shaved ice
and yakisoba and stuff, too.
You got that Bon-odori dance, right?
Always wanted to give it a try!
Yeah? I'll teach you how, then!
You're gonna teach her to dance? Fat chance!
Oh yeah?
What?
What-what?
What-who, now?
WNA Headquarters...
As Edison said,
never give up until you have just
what you've set out for.
Now it's do-or-die.
Ninja-like
Ninja!
Nin! Sinking underground with the sun
(Showtime! Our time! Da-dan-dan!)
Now! We seek our men along the thread
(Looking bright! Through the night! Ba-ban-ban!)
Just like the heavy winds (whoo-whoo!)
Just like the calm, quiet woods (ring-ring!)
Like the aliens primed to invade (meep-meep!)
Getting shot down like a crush (bump-bump!)
You only live once
Every encounter has its parting
Our world may burn in war with itself
But the Shinobi Night will protect it
In a flash of the glittering moonlight
We hear blades clashing around us
Through flames, through earth, our lives
They keep going, keep repeating
Life of a ninja! (Nin!)
Ninpo strike, to this day we're
just scraping our way thorugh the war
Until a day comes we can achieve glory
Until I reach your heart on the other side
Nin nin nin!
All sold out
Thank you!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
Concentrate and
succeed!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
“Now I shall take my leave... in smoke!”
Burton's Gum Weapon Lessons
Hey, Gumchi! How's it hanging?
Gumchi!
Today we're taking a look at this
Gum Weapon here!
SK8 Hammer
This is the SK8 Hammer.
It's a massive hammer made to look
like the wheels on a skateboard.
Gum-Gum!
It packs quite the punch, let me tell you.
SK8 Hammer
With it you can hop right into
a whole group of enemies!
Gum!
It's Gum Ninjutsu, Tenchi Muyo, can also
leave foes trapped in a pile of gum!
Now you're all ready
to score your own IPPON!
Gum!
Next Episode
Dear Gramps, I promise to train
hard at the academy. Love, Kappei.
That should do it, then.
Huh? Where are they off to this late?
Next time on Ninjala,
"Do-or-Die — Infiltrating WNA HQ!"
Do-or-Die — Infiltrating WNA HQ!
You better tune in!