Watch with
the lights on and
at a distance
from the screen!
Watch TV with the lights on and
at a distance from the screen!
After me and Berecca got turned
into kids by the Ninja-Gum,
we decided to join the WNA Academy.
There we met...
Van,
Lucy,
Emma,
Kappei,
and now Ron and Jane, too!
Wait, hang on a second!
Is that the same Ron that vanished
after he betrayed us?
No way, it can't be.
But if it is...
What are we gonna do?
Maybe Baby, here we go! Something special just for us
Maybe Baby Lovin’ Beats Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, always makes my heart skip a beat
Maybe Baby
In this breathless city of the future
I invite you to take it all in
Accelerating at the speed of light
We'll change the world
Boomy Boomy Life
Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, here we go! Something special just for us
Maybe Baby Lovin’ Beats Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, always makes my heart skip a beat
Maybe Baby
Not hungry?
I just can't make sense of it.
Ron and Jane seem to know
more about us than we imagined.
If they were really out to get us,
they had plenty of chances already.
That's the thing!
For some reason they've started
helping us instead...
Playing us two-faced, huh?
Not sure I like that.
I don't believe it!
What in the world are we looking at?
All we know for sure is that
no such lifeform exists on record.
But we may very well see more
of them in the future.
That's ridiculous!
We cannot rule out the possibility.
If our students are at risk,
we'd best call off all outdoor training.
I disagree.
The WNA Academy's goal is to train
skilled and competent ninjas.
Our curriculum will fall apart
if we allow these strange things to interfere.
You have a point.
I take it you have some sort of
plan in mind, then?
In addition to the watchful eyes
of our teachers,
we should bring in the Oniwabanshu
to step up our security.
Oh?
And should our students encounter
these creatures again,
we should send in a team
to capture them immediately.
Any thoughts?
An excellent idea, indeed.
Captured Ninja
Good mor-ninja, cadets!
Hope you're ready for some more
outdoor trai-ninja!
This follow-up training will be
even more practical than the last.
I call it: Cops Capture Robbers – The Game!
Not the most creative of names.
Two cops will chase down
and battle the six robbers.
The robbers get captured if
the cops either tag them
or land a hit with a Gum Weapon.
The game ends when all the robbers
get locked up in this cage.
The robbers can free their captured
friends using this key.
Hands up if you wanna be a cop!
Me, me, me!
And me!
Me too!
I'm gonna beat those robbers to a pulp!
That sounds like something
the bad guys would say...
Either way is fine with me.
Hmm, how are we going
to pick just two of you?
Oh, I know!
We could do a ladder lottery!
A ladder lottery...?
What's that?
Uhh, okay, basically...
We draw up ladders like this...
How is this a lottery?
How does this work again...?
You're kidding!
Rock, paper, scissors it is!
All right, ready?
Okay! Rock, paper...
Hey! What's that?
Huh?
All right!
Wha?!
I win!
Hey, that's cheating!
That doesn't count, right?
Tricking people is part of
the Shinobi way, you know.
Fine!
Two can play at this game!
Rock, paper—
What's one plus one?!
Two!
Wait, what the heck!
Why didn't you fall for that?
It was pretty obvious.
You're such a simpleton.
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot!
Wow! I won!
Now we have our cops,
fighting for justice!
They'll be facing off against our
evil, villainous robbers!
Listen up, baddies!
I'm gonna be taking you in!
I'd like to see you try!
Hey, now!
Your rampant evil stops here!
We're surrounded by roleplayers, huh?
You'll get two pieces of
Ninja Gum each.
Now then. Ready?
Start!
...After I say go!
Ready? Go!
What?!
Officer Emma, you head that way!
Roger!
Count me out of running around all day.
Better to preserve our energy
and bide our time.
It's the more mature strategy.
And a great one.
That voice...
Ack! Mosquitoes!
Oh man, and they already bit me twice!
Sounds like Burton and Berecca.
Hmm? Bwah!
How did you find us?!
How did she find us up there?
Huh?
There you are!
Can she hear us?!
Berecca! Maybe Emma has superhuman hearing!
She's chasing us with those sharp ears?
Shh!
Wanna know how sharp my ears are?
Huh...?
Gotcha, Berecca!
Burton, this is all your fault!
Sorry 'bout that!
Show yourselves, robbers!
Officer Kappei's gonna find you!
Who do you think that is?
Water-escape is a high-level technique.
What's that sound?
Oh!
There you are, robber!
You'll never catch me, copper!
Eat this!
Try and aim, next time!
Not the poop again!
Smell ya later!
No! Hey! Wait!
Kappei's really wasted his efforts, huh?
Hmph. Give me a break.
Ron! Put your hands up!
Freeze! You're under arrest!
Why do you look like that?
Hey, Ron! You need to
take this more seriously!
That voice!
Why'd you come outta hiding yourself?
Because you're not chasing me...
I'm hunting you!
It's always fun playing with you!
Say, Ron. This Ninja-Gum's something, huh?
Yup.
Bet it took some crazy tech to make these.
Mhmm.
I wonder how they did it.
Beats me. What do you think?
Answering questions with questions...
What a pain.
Resistance is futile!
Give up and come with me!
You're persistent!
We may be friends, but I can't let you off!
Well, I'm sorry to hear that.
Hey, since we're here,
can I just come out and ask?
What are you two trying to pull?
Hey! I'm comin' to save you guys!
Ugh, could you not?
What's that?
What the...?
What is this thing?
Look!
What are those?
We have an emergency! Everyone stay put!
Do not return to the cage!
Was that Bruce?
Is something wrong?
What happened?
What's going on?
Amy, get in touch with WNA HQ.
I'm heading down there.
Roger that.
Hup!
This is Amy,
WNA Headquarters, do you copy?
Hmm? Shown up again, have they?
Our students safety takes
top priority.
Send out the capture squad immediately.
Goodness me.
Gum Gum!
What's gotten into you, Gumchi?
Gum-Gumchi-chi, Gum-Gum!
Wait... Last time this happened...
was when the kids encountered
those strange lifeforms...
He told us to stay away!
Yeah, but "don't come back"
really means "come back fast," right?
I wouldn't be so sure!
Oh, you guys too?
I'm not just gonna sit around and wait!
Should'a known they wouldn't listen!
What the heck are these?
What are they attacking us for?
Take this!
Shoot!
That's enough!
Step back, Van.
Stay away from my students!
Mr. Bruce!
Teach!
I told you to stay back!
We can fight, too!
What?!
These things are dangerous!
Get back!
What do you think you're doing?
We just got orders from WNA headquarters.
All of you are to stand down
and wait somewhere safe!
What?!
The capture squad is en route.
We're taking those things in.
Orders from headquarters are
not to be disobeyed!
Understood?
Y-Yes, ma'am!
Then get going!
If you want a fight, I'm right here!
Teach!
Bruce, are you okay?
They're gone!
It's like they're ninjas, too!
Oh, no!
I'll take 'em down myself!
Don't! We have orders!
Hey, wait!
Leave our teachers alone!
Kappei! Van!
What are you doing?
This is dangerous! Get out of here!
We can't just stand by and watch!
Yeah!
Hey now, little gummie-boys,
try and catch us!
Emma?
Wha?!
Lucy!
Come on then, come get me!
How's that?
Nice work, Miss Jane!
Miss Jane!
What's this thing's deal?
It's dancing or something.
What's going on?
Hey, I think this is our chance!
All right, here goes!
You idiot!
Hah! That'll teach you to play
keep-away with me!
Burton!
Finally, the surface!
Kappei!
Got 'em!
Nice work, Kappei!
Heh!
You really showed them!
It's too early to celebrate!
Huh? Why?
The capture squad is coming here
to trap these things, right?
Shoot, I almost forgot!
Now's no time to worry about that.
If those other two come back at us...
Listen up! It's time to change our strategy.
We need to work together
and fight them one at a time.
We might be able to
capture them ourselves that way!
Right!
I'll make sure they can't get away!
Ron!
Nice assist, boys!
Miss Jane!
Walk the dog!
You're almost there! ...Huh?
Time for some payback!
Lucy, stop!
Time to crush you into mini gummies!
That's for thinking
you could mess with me.
Oh, no!
Hey!
That was a bit overboard!
This is bad, that means there's just...
Shoot!
Wait!
End of the line!
You're back?
That's the capture squad?
All of you, back away.
Ninpo, Spider's Web!
Ninpo, Glacial Freeze!
Are you kids all right?
Mr. Bruce!
Glad you're okay!
Huh? What's wrong?
Who are you...?
Oh...
C'mon, time to head back.
Ninja-like
Ninja!
Nin! Sinking underground with the sun
(Showtime! Our time! Da-dan-dan!)
Now! We seek our men along the thread
(Looking bright! Through the night! Ba-ban-ban!)
Just like the heavy winds (whoo-whoo!)
Just like the calm, quiet woods (ring-ring!)
Like the aliens primed to invade (meep-meep!)
Getting shot down like a crush (bump-bump!)
You only live once
Every encounter has its parting
Our world may burn in war with itself
But the Shinobi Night will protect it
In a flash of the glittering moonlight
We hear blades clashing around us
Through flames, through earth, our lives
They keep going, keep repeating
Life of a ninja! (Nin!)
Ninpo strike, to this day we're
just scraping our way thorugh the war
Until a day comes we can achieve glory
Until I reach your heart on the other side
Nin nin nin!
All sold out
Thank you!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
Concentrate and
succeed!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
“Now I shall take my leave... in smoke!”
Burton's Gum Weapon Lessons
Hey, Gumchi! How's it hanging?
Gum!
Today we're taking a look at this
Gum Weapon here!
The katana-type Drill Beast!
Drill Beast
Gum-mm!
It's a drill-shaped Gum Weapon
that can dig underground
and really mess with your foes.
Gum-mm, Gum-mm!
Drill Beast
Use Here and There to get in close
and give your opponents a real smack
with the Gum Ninjutsu, Punishing Blade!
Gum-m-m-m-mm!
Now you're all ready
to score your own IPPON!
Gum!
Next Episode
Those gooey little gummies
were so much fun to play with!
Huh? Is that Burton I see there?
Sure looks like he's
up to something secret.
Next time on Ninjala,
"Tailing Burton."
Tailing Burton
You won't get away!