Watch with
the lights on and
at a distance
from the screen!
Watch TV with the lights on and
at a distance from the screen!
After me and Berecca got turned
into kids by the Ninja-Gum,
we decided to join the WNA Academy.
There we met...
Van,
Lucy,
Emma,
Kappei,
and now Ron and Jane, too!
Wait, hang on a second!
Is that the same Ron that vanished
after he betrayed us?
No way, it can't be.
But if it is...
What are we gonna do?
Maybe Baby, here we go! Something special just for us
Maybe Baby Lovin’ Beats Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, always makes my heart skip a beat
Maybe Baby
In this breathless city of the future
I invite you to take it all in
Accelerating at the speed of light
We'll change the world
Boomy Boomy Life
Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, here we go! Something special just for us
Maybe Baby Lovin’ Beats Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, always makes my heart skip a beat
Maybe Baby
Hide and Seek with the Unknown
Today we've got more outdoor
training for you lot.
But today will be...
a round of hide and seek!
You don't really mean...
Isn't that a game for kids?
I guess you're all still little
pipsqueaks if you really think that.
Squeaky-squeak!
Listen here.
The name Shinobi means stealth.
Staying hidden and out of
sight is the essence of being a ninja.
Today's hide and seek is going to
drive this lesson home for you.
This here is a special stage
made just for this occasion.
This place looks deserted...
It was once a prosperous mining town.
But the mines dried up,
and everyone moved out years ago.
It's what you'd call a ghost town.
Th-There aren't really ghosts, right?
Of course not.
That's just what we call deserted towns.
No need to worry about disturbing
anyone here, so feel free to go all out!
Destroying a building or two
in battle will be no big deal.
We've got permission from
the academy already.
Now tell me, you all know how to
hide from your enemies, right?
Oh, by Gum Morphing!
Or we could use Gum Utsusemi.
Precisely.
You can change into just about
anything using Ninja-Gum.
Be sure to put its power to use.
But we can't do any of that
without Ninja-Gum.
Which is why we have two pieces
for each of you, today.
Two?
Huh?
Why?
I want you to use one piece
to wrestle with forming a weapon
suited for indirect attacks.
Meaning?
Well, I'm not talking figure-fours
and cobra twists, that's for sure.
Uh-huh...
What's he talking about?
He went from “wrestle” to
actual wrestling moves...
Too high-level for ya, huh?
We want you to use indirect attacks
that hit your targets from a distance.
From a distance, huh...
Sounds fun!
Now let's draw straws to see who's it!
All right! I'm it!
Hmph.
Okay, now while Van waits here
and counts to one hundred,
the rest of you need to go hide
somewhere in town!
This place really seems deserted.
Used to be some mining town, yeah?
Kinda gives me the creeps.
They said there weren't really
any ghosts here, but...
Hmm?
But I've heard rumors
that there definitely are.
What?!
Y-You don't mean...
Real ghosts?
No one knows for sure.
But something strange and unexplained.
Anyone who sees it faints,
so no one knows what it really looks like.
But there is definitely something.
And countless people have
lost their lives to it.
The whole mines running dry story
is just a cover-up.
What really happened is
everyone fled in fear.
S-Seriously?
You sure about that?
C-Cut it out, already!
Enough with the chitter chatter!
Once whoever is it calls out your name
you have to return here.
Now get hiding!
97, 98, 99, 100!
Okay!
Go out there and find 'em, Van!
There's a ghost out here somewhere?
Huh? What's the matter?
Oh, uhh, nothing...
I'm a ninja!
Gh-Ghosts can't scare m-m-me!
Good luck out there.
Where's everyone hiding?
Huh?
What the heck is this?
I see some...tempura?
Oh, it's a bowl of tempura soba!
But it's way too huge.
And this place is deserted, right?
Why's there a big hot bowl
of noodles here, then?
The only explanation is...
Show yourself!
Found you, Kappei!
Be more respectful of your food!
And I'll have you know that was
tanuki soba, okay?
Like I care!
Now go on and wait with the teachers!
Kappei's got no street smarts.
Course you're gonna get found there.
Best thing to do is hide up here.
Fixing up tea here
leaves my spirit calm as the
surface of a pond.
A clear and serene mind
is key to a perfect cup.
Gum-Gum!!
My, what's wrong, Gumchi?
Gum, Gum!
Settle down. Clear and serene, remember?
Gum, Gum, Gum, Gumchi-chi!
Gum, Gum...
This same thing happened once before,
didn't it?
What could this mean...?
This place is spooky...
Gh-Gh-Gh-Ghost!!
Come on, how long are we going
to look for a place to hide?
The best strategy in this situation is
to take the time to find a good spot.
It's simply the logical thing to do.
If we don't hide soon,
Van's going to come looking for us.
Don't worry, he won't get here that fast.
He probably won't find us here, right?
I wouldn't be so sure.
There's no way he can find all
seven of us in this town.
Wow, isn't this silverware lovely?
I bet it would clean up nice.
Don't let your guard down.
Huh?
That kid's smart and
full of energy, too.
Plus, we have more to worry about
than just Van.
Allen's thugs, you mean.
Thought it'd be harder to pull
anything if we slipped into the Academy.
But out in a secluded place like this...
Do you think our cover is blown already?
Not yet.
But it's only a matter of time.
We need to figure out what he's planning
and put a stop to it.
Mhmm.
What are you planning to do about them?
Burton and Berecca?
They're in the same sort of trouble, right?
Can't imagine they're not planning something
after having their research stolen.
They can worry about themselves.
Hmm?
We need to figure out how
we're gonna survive, first.
I'll go scout out back.
Maybe he's right.
Ron!
Ron! Are you okay?
I don't know, they came out of nowhere.
The Oniwabanshu?
No, but I couldn't quite make out who...
My Ninja-Gum is gone!
They picked it off me while I was down.
Your gum?
Looks like my leg's busted, too.
Can you walk?
Yeah, I'll be fine.
No you won't. We need to call for help.
They'll get you, too!
Don't worry about me.
I can fend for myself.
You better still be in one piece
when I get back!
Hide and seek is pretty boring...
Sure hope Van shows up sometime soon.
What?!
C'mon, we really need to hide soon
or else he's gonna find us!
No need to rush, planning this is key.
Fine, I'll go hide by myself, then. Hmph!
Berecca?
Good grief. Talk about a lack of
patience and inquisitiveness.
Berecca?!
Berecca?
What the heck are these things?
Berecca!
They ate the Ninja-Gum?
I'm next, am I?
Here! Have a snack!
Not hungry, huh?
Whatever, as long as they're after me,
I can keep them off Berecca.
Follow me!
Amy.
Hmm?
You know I don't like pumpkin.
At least try a bite, first.
Pumpkins are really nutritious.
I just can't.
Why not?
When I was still young...
my grandmother gave me this story book.
From that day on, the
Great Magical Pumpking was my hero.
The Great Magical Pumpking came to all
good girls and boys on Halloween
and helped them with whatever they needed.
I took every word in the book as true.
I called all my friends out to the pumpkin patch
But of course the Great Magical
Pumpking never showed.
And from that day on everyone called me a liar.
Uh-huh...
Sure is taking a while.
Hasn't he found anyone yet?
What are these things?
Are these the ghosts Lucy was talking about?
They kinda look like Gumchi...
Huh?!
Bring it on!
Wagh!
I've still found only one person...
Where is everyone?
Jane!
Burton?!
Berecca's in trouble.
Ron, too.
What are these things?
Your guess is as good as mine.
We need to get back to our teachers!
This way!
It's no use, we gotta hide!
I can't believe they got Ron.
It was an ambush, nothing he could do.
It's not like we knew these things were here!
But Ron's not like us,
he's already done ninja training.
Huh?
You didn't know?
Know what, exactly?
What's your deal, suddenly
transferring into the academy like that?
What do you mean? I'm just a girl
who wants to be a ninja someday.
Aren't you two the ones hiding something?
Nothing at all.
Really, now?
But you know...
I get the feeling we're dealing
with a similar sort of problem.
If you are in trouble...
Phase one!
Start off by understanding just
what problem you're dealing with.
Phase two!
Figure out how to solve said problem.
And finally, phase three...
Put that solution into effect, I imagine?
You're smarter than you look!
That's the logical way to go about
handling your troubles.
Logical, huh.
Were you an engineer, too?
Data management was more my thing.
You know, I think we might
actually get along.
Here they come!
This way!
Think this will hold them?
I wouldn't be sure.
Yikes!
They're going to break through the door!
– Phase one!
– Huh?
This door's about to break.
This is a storage freezer with no other exits.
We need to beat them before they make it in here.
Phase two... In order to solve this problem...
I want you to use one piece
to wrestle with forming a weapon
suited for indirect attacks.
An indirect attack!
Good idea!
We can use the Gum Weapon he mentioned!
That just leaves us with phase three!
Put it into effect!
I wish I could,
but those things stole my gum
on the way here.
Use your gum to make a weapon!
I'll give it a shot!
That's it!
Gum Ninjutsu! Piercing Mixer!
Take that!
Wow!
I'm not finished yet!
Sure is quiet out there now.
Think that got them?
Hmm...
Coast looks clear.
Awesome, it really worked!
Let's hurry back to the teachers!
Right with you.
We went out looking searching
because things were taking too long.
What in the world happened out there?
I'm just glad none of you
were seriously injured.
It's all because of Lucy
and her stories!
How is this my fault?!
I didn't really think there
was anything out there!
I was so scared!
So, what was it? What are these creatures?
I honestly couldn't tell you for sure.
It was some lifeform I've never seen before.
Hmm...
Sounds like I've got something
new to start researching.
Ninja-like
Ninja!
Nin! Sinking underground with the sun
(Showtime! Our time! Da-dan-dan!)
Now! We seek our men along the thread
(Looking bright! Through the night! Ba-ban-ban!)
Just like the heavy winds (whoo-whoo!)
Just like the calm, quiet woods (ring-ring!)
Like the aliens primed to invade (meep-meep!)
Getting shot down like a crush (bump-bump!)
You only live once
Every encounter has its parting
Our world may burn in war with itself
But the Shinobi Night will protect it
In a flash of the glittering moonlight
We hear blades clashing around us
Through flames, through earth, our lives
They keep going, keep repeating
Life of a ninja! (Nin!)
Ninpo strike, to this day we're
just scraping our way thorugh the war
Until a day comes we can achieve glory
Until I reach your heart on the other side
Nin nin nin!
All sold out
Thank you!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
Concentrate and
succeed!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
“Now I shall take my leave... in smoke!”
Burton's Gum Weapon Lessons
Hey, Gumchi! How's it hanging?
Gum-Gum!
Today we're taking a look at this
Gum Weapon here!
Scroll Blade — It's a scroll-shaped
katana-type weapon.
Scroll Blade
Gum-m-mm!
It offers a great offense-defense
balance and is easy to use.
M'chi!
Scroll Blade
And if you're ever up against someone
you can't see hiding behind a wall,
you can use the Piercing Mixer
Gum Ninjutsu to hit ‘em!
Gumcha'o!
Now you're all ready
to score your own IPPON!
Gum!
Next Episode
Those creatures definitely
looked a lot like Gumchi...
Forget that, though, next up it's
cops and robbers, and I'm the cop!
Man! I can't wait!
Next time on Ninjala,
“Captured Ninja.”
Captured Ninja
Promise you'll watch!