Watch with
the lights on and
at a distance
from the screen!
Watch TV with the lights on and
at a distance from the screen!
My name's Burton.
After me and Berecca got turned
into kids by the Ninja-Gum,
we decided to join the WNA Academy.
We're here disguised as students
while we figure out how to fix this,
but with Oniwabanshu assassins after us,
we're not getting anywhere!
Plus, now we're dealing with
these strange Space Ninjas.
What in the world are these things, Burton?!
I have no idea.
But we can't just let them run wild.
We've got to use our
Ninja-Gum to stop them!
Maybe Baby, here we go! Something special just for us
Maybe Baby Lovin’ Beats Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, always makes my heart skip a beat
Maybe Baby
In this breathless city of the future
I invite you to take it all in
Accelerating at the speed of light
We'll change the world
Boomy Boomy Life
Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, here we go! Something special just for us
Maybe Baby Lovin’ Beats Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, always makes my heart skip a beat
Maybe Baby
Leonard?
Seems he was a colleague
of Professor Sean's, hmm?
Yeah, he was there surveying
with him at the time of the accident.
Well, you may find what I'm about
to say hard to believe,
but a little bird has told me
Leonard is still alive.
But, if he is, then maybe
my father's still alive, too?
Again with the Space Ninjas?
How many do we need to exterminate?
There's no telling.
It seems there is no end to them.
How can they have such numbers?
I admit I'd much like to know how long
these fruitless battles will last.
And there lies our problem.
At present, there is too much we do not
yet understand about these creatures.
Director Allen is right.
We still have no grasp on their numbers
or where they have laid base.
Perhaps it's time we carried out
a full survey of these Space Ninjas.
We need to tail them and
discover how they operate.
Then we can wipe them out!
An excellent idea.
I'll issue a Ninja Mission post-haste.
Headed Home into the Sunset
Okay recruits, you understand
our mission, right?
'Course!
We're more ready than you think!
Good. Tell me what your orders are, then.
Huh?
Uhhh...
What were they, again?
The Extermination Squad is gonna
let the Space Ninja get away.
Then we're gonna trail it
and track down where they're hiding.
Yeah, that!
Good. But remember,
you only tail it for six hours.
Any longer than that and you pull out.
Everyone have their MakiPhones?
Yup!
Get in touch with us
as soon as anything goes down.
Guys, before we go...
What's wrong, Kappei?
Make sure your phones aren't phony!
R-Right...
Kappei, now's really not the time.
– It's getting away!
– Huh?!
Your mission starts now!
We're counting on you.
Roger!
That thing doesn't have a clue!
Maybe we thought
too much of these things.
I bet we could get in even closer!
Kappei, you can't!
That's even worse than not hiding at all.
That boy's getting an earful
when we get back.
What's going on?
– That one's mine!
– That thing's mine!
I'll head this way!
I'm gonna pulverize 'em!
We aren't supposed to engage!
Berecca, let's head this way!
Berecca...?
Stay outta my way!
I'm not about to lose to you!
Wait!
What now?
– It's gone.
– Huh?
This way, then.
Caltrops?!
What?! Is there a ninja at the wheel?
No!
Shoot, that thing got away.
Better let everyone know.
Ah! Look out!
Ow!
Who was that?!
– Shoot!
– Shh!
– What?
– That's not good!
Stop that!
Hey, wait a minute now!
Uh-oh...
Good, at least it still turns on.
You currently have 30% body fat.
– What?! No I don't!
– Detecting moderate obesity...
Wow, you hold your weight well—
– This thing's broken, okay?!
– You currently have 30% body fat.
There's no way! It's gotta be busted!
Stupid! Little! Lying! Phone!
See? Busted.
Yeah, because you just broke it.
Emma reporting. Sorry sir,
I let it slip away from me.
Right. I'll head back now.
Now then, which way's Eagle City...?
Talk about lame.
We let our MakiPhones get washed away.
What are we gonna do now?
I mean, we still got time,
but nothing to chase anymore.
Yeah...
Might as well get in some
fishing while we're here!
Really?
Shoot. How did we let it get away?
And how are we supposed to get back?
How do you want to head back?
We covered a lot of ground
coming out here.
I wonder what would be best.
Hmm?
Oh!
You want a ride out to Eagle City?
In your dreams!
Please, we're in a real hurry.
Nope. Ain't flying out that far.
All this corn's got me busy enough already.
Doesn't seem like the friendliest old man.
This isn't going to be easy.
You two still babblin' on?
Go on and scram already!
Hang on now,
do you even know who this is?
Should I?
Just look at her hair!
A hairstyle as unique and eccentric
as this should be proof enough.
She's the daughter of a big corporate exec!
You're dissing me, aren't you?
Just play along!
Bah! Execs, insects, don't matter.
I got my hands full enough.
You might want to reconsider.
Because her father runs a big food
business specializing in corn.
Isn't that right, now?
Huh? Ah-ha-ha-ha, yes it sure is.
W-We've got control of the
largest share in the market, I think.
Wait, the world market?!
And it's not only food.
They've got their eyes on using corn
as bio-fuel in the near future.
And they could really use a new
corn farmer to hop on board.
If you sign this whole field over,
you'd earn yourself a hefty
yearly salary off of it.
This all true, little lady?
Well, I could always ask Father.
My whole field, eh...?
Isn't this a bit much?
This is all on you, you know.
It's all for our mission.
And after that act you're an accomplice.
Hmm? What's the trouble?
N-No, nothing!
So, what do you say?
Oh, excuse me a moment.
Hello? Mhmm...
What? You found a nice cornfield
you think we can use?
What terrible timing,
seems another potential farmer has—
Fine, fine!
I'll fly you two out, just put in
a good word for me, quick!
Thank you so much!
You're too good at this, Jane.
There. Here's our chance.
Hey old man, hand over the truck!
We've been here forever without a single bite.
You just gotta relax. It's like I said.
The key to fishing is to keep
your mind clear and serene.
"Seer and..."
No, not "seer and queen,"
clear and serene.
Meaning?
Uh, well...
You just empty your mind and wait.
Okay, then. Clear and serene.
Clear and serene. Clear and serene!
Just know it's not as easy as it...
– Whoa!
– Seriously?
Sweet! This clear and serene
thing is awesome!
I guess that's a good start...
Look! Another! Hiyah!
Kappei, this serene stuff is great!
– Whoa! Another one!
– Told you so...
Where...am I?
Wait... What?
Here comes another. We can't let this one go.
We're melting out here, so let us in!
Lucy, do you understand
what's happening here?
Bye-bye!
Thank you!
We'll be in touch about your contract!
That was pretty mean, you know.
You two okay?
Did you find any leads
on the Space Ninja hideout?
We lost track of it, unfortunately.
Well, as long as you're all right.
Now mind explaining what
you're carrying there?
Some corn!
A present from our trip!
Man, that is good!
This next one's ready to go, too!
Whew! Heh, can't beat good fish!
Whose fish do you think these are?!
We really can't let this next one get away.
You there! Pull over, now!
Or maybe not.
What are they doing? Looks like fun!
Get off the road!
Let's have some fun!
Hiyah!
You there! Freeze!
Sheesh...
Judging by the direction of my shadow,
the academy must be...
This way.
It's going the wrong way,
but if I transfer again somewhere...
We oughta head back.
Let's take that bridge up there.
Sure.
Huh?
Hey, lucky us! If we catch this...
...it'll be a smooth ride home!
Huh?
Wh-What do we do now?!
I know!
– Huh?
– We use this!
R-Right!
Phew...
We made it.
Lucy!
Ron!
Lucy, what did you do this time?
I knew this would happen someday.
What trouble has our dear Lucy caused now?
She's really not a bad girl.
Actually, these two were a big help.
Huh?
What's going down here?
Burton sure is late.
Think he's okay?
What if he got caught by Space Ninjas?
Don't go and jinx it like that!
Burton...
Hello? Huh? Burton?!
Where the heck are you?!
Uhm...
Probably around
1,500 kilometers away, now.
How on earth did you get that far away?!
That's what I want to know...
Ninja-like
Ninja!
Nin! Sinking underground with the sun
(Showtime! Our time! Da-dan-dan!)
Now! We seek our men along the thread
(Looking bright! Through the night! Ba-ban-ban!)
Just like the heavy winds (whoo-whoo!)
Just like the calm, quiet woods (ring-ring!)
Like the aliens primed to invade (meep-meep!)
Getting shot down like a crush (bump-bump!)
You only live once
Every encounter has its parting
Our world may burn in war with itself
But the Shinobi Night will protect it
In a flash of the glittering moonlight
We hear blades clashing around us
Through flames, through earth, our lives
They keep going, keep repeating
Life of a ninja! (Nin!)
Ninpo strike, to this day we're
just scraping our way thorugh the war
Until a day comes we can achieve glory
Until I reach your heart on the other side
Nin nin nin!
All sold out
Thank you!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
Concentrate and
succeed!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
“Now I shall take my leave... in smoke!”
Burton's Gum Weapon Lessons
Hey, Gumchi! How's it hanging?
Gum!
Today we're taking a look at this
Gum Weapon here!
Drum Beat
The Drum Beat!
Gum!
It's a hammer-type weapon
shaped like a drum set.
Gumchi!
It uses sound waves to stop your
opponent, even from a distance.
Drum Beat
Wowchi!
And once you stop them with a
blast of its Echoing Scream,
you can sweep in for a
powerful hammer smash.
Whapowchi!
Now you're all ready
to score your own IPPON!
Gum!
Next Episode
You gotta have the worst
sense of direction, Burton!
Next time, we're all going on vacation!
What? The ghosts of the sea
are gonna steal our souls away?!
Seriously?!
Next time on Ninjala,
"Sea of Oranje."
Sea of Oranje
You better tune in!