Watch with
the lights on and
at a distance
from the screen!
Watch TV with the lights on and
at a distance from the screen!
My name's Burton.
After me and Berecca got turned
into kids by the Ninja-Gum,
we decided to join the WNA Academy.
We're here disguised as students
while we figure out how to fix this,
but with Oniwabanshu assassins after us,
we're not getting anywhere!
Plus, now we're dealing with
these strange Space Ninjas.
What in the world are these things, Burton?!
I have no idea.
But we can't just let them run wild.
We've got to use our
Ninja-Gum to stop them!
Maybe Baby, here we go! Something special just for us
Maybe Baby Lovin’ Beats Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, always makes my heart skip a beat
Maybe Baby
In this breathless city of the future
I invite you to take it all in
Accelerating at the speed of light
We'll change the world
Boomy Boomy Life
Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, here we go! Something special just for us
Maybe Baby Lovin’ Beats Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, always makes my heart skip a beat
Maybe Baby
You're kidding, right?
This isn't something I'd joke about.
We need to infiltrate HQ.
I figured this would happen sooner or later.
Ron and Jane's Infiltration Mission
My mission was to steal the Ninja-Gum
data once research was complete.
Yet I myself became an Oniwabanshu
target upon completion of that mission.
I found evidence that Allen is
colluding with President Harold,
and was saved by you when that
information put me in danger.
Our situation left us no choice
but to use Ninja-Gum.
We won't get anywhere by waiting.
I need your help.
I figured you would,
so I went ahead and made preparations.
When do we make our move?
Tonight.
Actually, the afternoon might work better.
Good thinking.
So, here's the situation.
Our mission this afternoon is to
scout out these aliens you call "Space Ninjas."
Uhh, sir? Ron and Jane aren't here.
They're both out sick today.
We'll run this mission without them!
They're "sick?"
Huh?
I want you all to prep your equipment
and report back here after lunch.
Yessir!
Sick, huh?
Ron still did his usual training routine
just fine this morning.
Hmm, something's up.
They're definitely planning something.
Oh, Rooon!
Heard you were sick so I came to see.
Mind if I come in?
Figured as much.
Oh, Burton, you really shouldn't.
Oh, but I'm just so worried
about my dear friend.
But Burton, that's no reason
to rummage through someone's stuff.
No, no, I'm just looking for a hint
as to where poor Ron went, is all.
Just looking out for my friend.
Ron!
I heard you weren't feeling well.
Yup, sure am sick.
I fixed up one of hose
omelets you love.
Thanks. Just leave it there.
If you aren't hungry,
you don't need to force yourself.
Get well soon!
Thank you...
Phew... Huh?
What am I even doing?!
What's the matter?
I'm an accomplice in his alibi now...
Huh?
What in the world is he up to?
Never knew he liked omelets...
Feels good to be back at it!
Like I said, we don't have detailed
sighting reports from around here,
but we can't let our guards down.
We might get through this whole mission
without even nabbing one.
Ugh, but where's the fun in that?
That's literally exactly what we should hope for.
If there was any report at all,
that must mean at least one's out here.
So are we still not allowed
to fight those things ourselves?
Duh! Get back to the chopper
as soon as you've got eyes.
We'll report to the extermination squad.
Lucy! No running off again like last time.
That's an order!
Hear that?
Yeah, yeah.
We can handle these Space Ninjas!
We've been training so hard!
Anyone who disobeys orders will eat
nothing but tofu for three days.
Seriously?
I'd get so sick of it!
Fine! Behave gingerly and I'll add in some ginger!
Ginger is nutritious and great for losing weight.
I'm not on a diet!
I actually love tofu.
You love the taste of nothing?
Guess a kid like you wouldn't understand.
– I've got grown-up tastes.
– Oh yeah?!
Okay, quiet down!
We'll be scouting out a
10km perimeter around the area.
Don't go traveling any further than that.
Burton, Lucy, and Kappei will take the east side.
Hmph!
Berecca, Van, and Emma will head west.
You have permission to use this gum
in a pinch, but only to escape.
Got that, Lucy?
Uh-huh...
Berecca and Burton will be in charge of comms.
I'll stay here, and if any Space Ninjas show up
I'll keep you all safe
until the extermination squad arrives.
Sure you can do that all alone?
Maybe I should stay to protect you.
Shut it and move out!
Location B. Hall three.
Okay!
Maybe I couldn't get into the server,
but security I can handle!
We're making good progress.
The real trouble is up ahead, though.
Wait for my signal.
Roger.
No sign, huh?
Hey! Space Ninjas! Show yourselves!
We're really better off
if they aren't around.
I got your Ninja-Gum right here!
Are you even listening?
– C'mon out!
– Here's some yummy gum!
Hard pass on three days of tofu.
Then just follow directions.
Yup. If we see anything, we take off running.
We're just gonna walk our way
through this whole mission, huh?
Hey! What are you chomping on that for?
I mean, we're on a mission, yeah? Hiyah!
Sure doesn't feel like it without a weapon in hand!
Can you not swing that around so close to us?
We were told not to let our guards down, right?
Doubt this is what he meant.
Never know when they might
get the jump on us.
– Like now!
– Huh? Bwha?!
Sir, we have contact!
Roger that!
Burton here.
What?! Understood!
The other team made contact.
What?
We need to retreat to the helicopter!
Berecca, behind you!
We gotta run!
Run where?!
Nice one!
What's our direction?
This is the way!
Aww man, they did?
Wish they showed up here.
I'm telling you, we're really better off if...
You just had to jinx us!
Well, now that they're here...
What? We're not supposed to
do anything but run!
We can use these for a getaway, right?
Lucy! Kappei! We need to get
back to the helicopter!
Ugh, you're such a drag!
Jane.
Here's where things really start.
Ready? Go!
3, 2, 1, zero!
Ron, are you okay?
Yup. Nicely done.
Well.
All in a days work for me, really.
Now find us that evidence.
Ron?
Well if it isn't little Ron.
What business does one of
our students have in here?
What?! Report your location!
We're currently...
– You currently have 16% body fat.
– No! Not that!
It'd be faster just to pulverize 'em.
I like tofu anyway.
Guys...
Let me guess,
that's Jane on the other end?
Thanks for leading Ron right to me.
They sniffed me out?
But my hacks are untraceable!
You still move like one of the Oniwabanshu.
But do you think you can beat me
in that puny little body?
Shame this has to happen here.
What are you and Harold trying to pull?
Hmm? Can't say I know what you mean.
You're clearly breaking the rules.
Where's your proof?
You wouldn't be here if there wasn't any.
Sounds like it'll be easy to cover up, then.
Are you trying to use Ninja-Gum
as part of some power grab?
Are you forming your own army?!
You know too much for your own good.
Chief Luke won't stand for this!
He won't be in charge for long now.
How's that useless old man going to stop me?
What do you mean?!
That man is incapable of anything but
researching the power of the Shinobi.
His good temperament holds him back!
Thinks he's better than us, does he?
Well then, it's time we
fight back with all we've got!
Wha?!
– Get ready.
– Got it.
Hold it!
What's the meaning of this?!
Sorry, sir, I'm on it!
Get these things offline!
They're not half bad at this.
You won't make it straight ahead. Turn left!
Nicely done.
– Jane.
– Huh?!
Heard you're feeling under the weather.
I brought you some of your favorite tiramisu!
Why now?!
Th-Thanks. Just leave it there!
Last time you said tiramisu should
have brandy in it, huh?
Did I say that...?
Jane!
There's no point in struggling!
But you're too young for brandy,
so I made you an extra special
one without any!
Get well soon!
Thank you...
Shoot! Shoot!
Director Allen.
Hmm?
Do we have an intruder?
We suspect it's just a system error
but are investigating now.
That sounds serious. Allow me to join you.
You're clear!
Seems like he made it out.
Ron?
I'm fine.
Heading back now.
Phew... I'm beat.
A hard day's work like that makes
me want to hit the bar for a drink.
Or two. Maybe three.
Hey, uhh, can you bring me
some wine too, please?
Great, now I have to
suffer three days of tofu!
Now's our chance!
No, it's not!
Now we run!
Are you all right?!
Bruce!
Is that...?
There's no sign that they've
re-emerged anywhere.
Of course. Our students are
all safe and... Hmm?
All safe and back here like ordered, right?
Sheesh...
Y'know, one of 'em looked
a lot like one from last time.
You thought so, too?
But like, a girl version.
It was ordering the other Space Ninjas around.
That might be another more intelligent version.
I'm beat...
Same...
What's Ron up to, skipping a mission like this?
Beats me, but he's definitely not sick.
I bet Jane isn't either.
Maybe I should pay a visit myself.
Jane.
Berecca?
You need something?
So, you really were sick?
Are you okay? What hurts?
Rggh, my head? And my wrists.
Your wrists?
No, never mind.
I figured you might be here.
Looks like I was spot on.
I helped you out, you know.
I'd say I deserve to get
clued in on what you're up to.
Helped out? With what?
I mean, it was... not the greatest move, but...
There's an omelet waiting for you
outside your door.
Make sure you thank the cafeteria lady.
Come on, still gonna play dumb?
What's wrong with your leg, then?
Just bumped it.
And this?
Just. Bumped. It.
Can you please answer me?
What would do this by "bumping" into it?
Allen's really up to no good, then.
We need to put a stop to his madness.
But we can't do it alone.
Ninja-like
Ninja!
Nin! Sinking underground with the sun
(Showtime! Our time! Da-dan-dan!)
Now! We seek our men along the thread
(Looking bright! Through the night! Ba-ban-ban!)
Just like the heavy winds (whoo-whoo!)
Just like the calm, quiet woods (ring-ring!)
Like the aliens primed to invade (meep-meep!)
Getting shot down like a crush (bump-bump!)
You only live once
Every encounter has its parting
Our world may burn in war with itself
But the Shinobi Night will protect it
In a flash of the glittering moonlight
We hear blades clashing around us
Through flames, through earth, our lives
They keep going, keep repeating
Life of a ninja! (Nin!)
Ninpo strike, to this day we're
just scraping our way thorugh the war
Until a day comes we can achieve glory
Until I reach your heart on the other side
Nin nin nin!
All sold out
Thank you!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
Concentrate and
succeed!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
“Now I shall take my leave... in smoke!”
Burton's Gum Weapon Lessons
Hey, Gumchi! How's it hanging?
Gum-Gum!
Today we're taking a look at this
Gum Weapon here!
Home Run Surfer
The surf-board shaped Home Run Surfer!
Gum-mm-Gum!
It's a board-type Gum Weapon
that can surf atop its own
super strong Overpowering Wave!
M'chi-chi!
Home Run Surfer
Plus, it can shoot its Gum Ghost
that goes right through terrain,
sending ghost-shaped gum
chasing down your opponents!
Creepchi!!
Now you're all ready
to score your own IPPON!
Gum!
Next Episode
We can't let Allen get away with this.
We need to hit him first chance we get!
Right, so our next Ninja Mission is...
No! It can't be!
Next time on Ninjala,
"Headed Home into the Sunset."
Headed Home into the Sunset
Lucy! You have to follow orders!