Watch with
the lights on and
at a distance
from the screen!
Watch TV with the lights on and
at a distance from the screen!
My name's Burton.
Our completed version of Ninja Gum
left me and Berecca as kids,
and now we have ninjas after us
for some reason.
We had no other choice but
to hide away inside the WNA Academy.
And that's where we met...
Van,
Lucy,
Emma,
and Kappei.
No way!
They're mass producing Ninja-Gum?!
What's going on?
We really need to get
our grown-up bodies back!
And the best way to do that is with
some ultra-nutritious smoothies!
Ugh, could you quit playing around?!
Maybe Baby, here we go! Something special just for us
Maybe Baby Lovin’ Beats Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, always makes my heart skip a beat
Maybe Baby
In this breathless city of the future
I invite you to take it all in
Accelerating at the speed of light
We'll change the world
Boomy Boomy Life
Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, here we go! Something special just for us
Maybe Baby Lovin’ Beats Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, always makes my heart skip a beat
Maybe Baby
Right, so these here are
your new add-in classmates.
Ron and Jane.
Ron...?
New Friends? — Ron & Jane
We have anything to worry about?
Course not. Faking data in the
academy's system is a piece of cake.
Right... Hmm?
Heya, new kids!
Huh?
I'm Kappei!
Nice to meet you.
Since you're new here,
I can help you however you need.
Feel free to ask me stuff!
Doubt you could teach anyone anything.
Since you don't know nothing yourself.
Oh, yeah?
If you think you do, then tell me:
Where is there a bird nest on the roof?
What? Of course I know that.
Oh, yeah? Let's hear it, then.
I mean, I've definitely seen it.
Why don't you answer me this?
Where are there a ton of ant hills?
Uh, 'course I know that...
Out where the principal is
secretly growing cherry tomatoes!
Yeah? Well, do you know where our
teacher Amy secretly grows pumpkins?
Pumpkins? Give me a break—
Even after I told her to lay off them...
Wait, so he's not lying?
Forget it, let's get started.
So this is Ninja Gum, huh?
Look!
This is how it works.
I was definitely faster.
Nuh-uh, I was at least half a second faster!
How, when I was a full second faster?
Actually, I was 10 seconds faster.
Turns out I was a whole hour faster, though.
I was a day, then!
Ten years!
A hundred years!
Then I was 10 thousand years faster!
Now, cut it out!
Eww, what is this?
Huh?
Don't sweat it, it's your first try.
You'll get the hang of it soon enough.
Guess it's not as easy as it looks.
I think I'm just gonna sit today out.
Oh! Looks like you're ready, though.
You're up first, Van.
'Kay!
Here goes!
Huh?
What?!
Hrmph!
Huh?
Still not used to these stubby arms and legs...
Nice dodge, man!
Get ready for this next one, though.
You'll never dodge this!
Agh!
Gotcha!
There's my chance!
Waaah!
You gotta be kidding me...
Must be embarrassing losing to a newbie!
I'll have a go next!
Guess that's no surprise.
Not bad for a newbie!
You won't get me next time, though!
You're free to head to lunch when you finish.
Can't go losing anymore to the new kid!
Definitely ate more than you today!
No way, I did for sure!
Huh?
We just can't win...
On the battlefield or in the cafeteria...
That kid's really something.
We were using the same weapon
and everything...
Never thought I'd meet anyone that strong.
I didn't stand a chance.
Delivery for Van.
Huh?
Delivery!
Thanks.
It's from Mom.
Dear Van, how are you?
I'm sure you're working hard.
We're always thinking of you.
That's definitely the same Ron, right?
Hmm, I dunno...
You saw how tough he was in his first battle.
Has the same sort of look, too.
But if that's the same Ron,
then that means he ate Ninja-Gum
just like we did, right?
Probably.
Just can't figure out why.
Why would he want to take kid form...
What if he's here to wipe us both out?!
I mean, I guess that's one way
to get closer to us.
Gimme a break...
Wait, but if he's a kid now,
does he knows how to turn back?
Would he tell us even if he did?
I just don't get it!
Wait, he wasn't alone, though.
Jane?
Seemed like they knew each other.
Think she's with the Oniwabanshu, too?
Maybe they just happened to be
add-ins at the same time.
Wait, though!
Huh?
Why even have add-in students
to begin with?
True.
Kind of a weird time of year for it.
Gah! None of this makes sense!
One things for sure, we better be careful.
Yeah...
C'mon, Mom.
I'm not some little kid anymore.
Sorry. Guess you didn't need all those toys.
Nah, it's okay. Thanks for all the stuff.
You sure?
Make sure you share with your friends!
Yeah...
How are you though? Everything okay?
You bet!
You should'a seen me in training today!
We got these new kids,
and I showed 'em the ropes.
Oh, wow! Sounds like you're working hard.
Yeah, so no need to worry, 'kay?
But uhh, how's Dad? He okay?
He's doing better each day.
No need to worry about us, either.
– Mom...
– Hmm?
I swear I'm gonna be a ninja
just like Dad someday.
Take care of yourself.
I will. Bye now.
Agh!
Hrngh... Yeowch...
Haste makes waste, you know.
Huh?
Master Genryusai!
Hey, is my dad really okay?
Mom said he's doing better, but...
Ah, so you've been in touch with
your dear mother?
Yeah, just now.
She's telling the truth.
His health is recovering.
That's good.
I'll be sure to send word
if I hear anything.
Okay, that's a promise, though!
Tell me now, what has you so worked up?
I just want to be stronger.
Didn't like losing to your new classmate, did you?
I never thought he'd be so strong.
You won't outmatch skills like that in just a day.
You need to be patient and
committed to your training.
Right. Thanks, Master.
You have strengths of your own, Van.
I–I do?!
I watched your match earlier.
You're agile and have quite the reflexes.
You've been keeping an eye on me?
Learn to concentrate.
Huh?
Watch your opponent's movement,
their breathing...
Learn to detect their actions.
And then...
And then?
Don't forget to take breaks.
Yessir!
Hi!
Hi.
What are you listening to?
Hip hop.
Hip hop? Cool!
I'm into hard rock, myself. Listen to much?
Not really...
No? I'll have t Nshare some good stuff.
The amazing drums pulse right through you.
Hits straight in the soul! It's amazing.
Right...
What a lovely fragrance!
What sort of shampoo do you use?
Dunno. Whatever was there.
Look at that silky smooth hair.
Makes me want to grow mine out.
We should head to the salon
together sometime!
Buh-bye now.
Let's chat again sometime.
That's good enough for some
first contact.
I'm not a fan of the tricks.
What choice do we have, now?
Can't hurt to have some friends
if things go south.
They're just kids.
We don't want to get them involved.
Does he have to be so cold?
– Chew this!
– What?
Hmm? Hey—Aah!
What was that all about? Huh...?
No way!
These ceilings sure are high...
Now where to begin.
Oh...
The food here looks great.
Yeah, it's pretty good.
See you later, then.
Later.
Something's definitely off with her.
Huh?
It's that unnatural smile.
Seems they haven't found me out yet.
Ahhh, what I would do for glass of wine!
How's this thing work?
What'cha got there?
Hmph! Huh?
Huh?
If you can't do it, just give it back.
Hang on, I can, I swear.
Give it back!
No!
Quit acting like some little kid!
Look who's talking!
Oops...
Ooo, a yo-yo! Takes me back.
Used to play with these all the time.
Huh?!
They're so fun! It's been a while.
No way!
Whoa!
How'd you do that?
Show us how!
Huh?
Oh, you wanna learn how to do this?
Yup!
How much do you wanna?
This much!
Even more for me! This much!
Even more than that for me!
As much as the whole academy!
As much as Eagle City!
– As much as Komerika!
– As the universe!
Yes, yes, okay.
Just this once, then.
Yippee!
Thanks, newbie!
Excuse me?
Whoops, I mean...
That's Miss Jane to you boys.
"Miss?"
Now line up.
Yes ma'am!
Stand up straight!
Good, now let's start with the basics.
Hooray!
Easy-peasy.
You all set?
Good to go.
No luck. This is levels beyond
hacking into the academy.
Pushing things further
would be dangerous.
Guess we need to be inside HQ.
Certainly won't have much luck here.
Night descends once again.
And like the great Edison said...
Wake at seven, sleep at eleven,
and you'll have 16 hours to...huh?
Hmm...
I know I should play it safe, but...
Ron.
You're...
really Ron, aren't you?
I introduced myself this morning.
That's not what I mean.
You like to tail people or something?
It's almost lights-out.
What are you doing up here?
Just getting a breath of fresh air.
Something wrong?
Nah, it's nothing.
Great! That's more like it.
And check this out!
You have strengths of your own, Van.
All right!
Okay folks, got your weapons ready?
Yessir!
Then let's get it going, and go get it!
Wanna play?
Sure!
I won't go easy on you, Miss Jane!
Fine by me.
Whoa! Shoulda seen that coming!
Woops...
Okay, something's definitely up!
Nope, just same as always...
Oh, yeah?
Like the great Edison always said...
Those who know success know it
doesn't come every time...
Gotcha!
Good grief...
This kid again.
Let's finish this.
Concentrate...
Detect his actions!
Ha-ha! Piece of cake!
I think I can do this, Dad!
Nice job!
Y'think?
Got a little careless
around the kid, did you?
Well, a kid he may be,
but I guess he's still a ninja.
Right? Won't hurt to make
friends like that, will it?
So this is how losing feels, hmm?
Good motivation to get stronger.
We're headed to camp for training today!
I've got the perfect place to
whip you into real ninja shape.
This is serious training,
but it'll be a walk in the park for you!
A walk?
I thought we were going camping?
Just give it your best....
Ninja-like
Ninja!
Nin! Sinking underground with the sun
(Showtime! Our time! Da-dan-dan!)
Now! We seek our men along the thread
(Looking bright! Through the night! Ba-ban-ban!)
Just like the heavy winds (whoo-whoo!)
Just like the calm, quiet woods (ring-ring!)
Like the aliens primed to invade (meep-meep!)
Getting shot down like a crush (bump-bump!)
You only live once
Every encounter has its parting
Our world may burn in war with itself
But the Shinobi Night will protect it
In a flash of the glittering moonlight
We hear blades clashing around us
Through flames, through earth, our lives
They keep going, keep repeating
Life of a ninja! (Nin!)
Ninpo strike, to this day we're
just scraping our way thorugh the war
Until a day comes we can achieve glory
Until I reach your heart on the other side
Nin nin nin!
All sold out
Thank you!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
Concentrate and
succeed!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
“Now I shall take my leave... in smoke!”
Burton's Gum Weapon Lessons
Hey, Gumchi! How's it hanging?
Gum-Gum!
Today we're taking a look at this
Gum Weapon here!
Corn Bat
Ta-da! It's the katana-type Corn Bat!
Gumchi...!
You think it looks tasty?
Don't let looks fool you, Gumchi!
Gum-mm!
Anyone wielding this can disappear
in an instant and sneak up on you!
Corn Bat
Watch out for that Stealth Attack!
Gummm!
It's Gum Ninjutsu, Dragon Lord,
will also hone in on its target!
Gum-Gum!
Now you're all ready
to score your own IPPON!
Gum!
Next Episode
Oh, Van and Kappei,
boys are so easy to control.
Next up we're training out in
the great outdoors, hmm?
Sounds dreadful.
Time to lather up the sunscreen.
Hellish Survival Mission
Next time on Ninjala,
"Hellish Survival Mission."
Hellish Survival Mission
You really shouldn't miss it.