Watch with
the lights on and
at a distance
from the screen!
Watch TV with the lights on and
at a distance from the screen!
After me and Berecca got turned
into kids by the Ninja-Gum,
we decided to join the WNA Academy.
There we met...
Van,
Lucy,
Emma,
Kappei,
and now Ron and Jane, too!
Wait, hang on a second!
Is that the same Ron that vanished
after he betrayed us?
No way, it can't be.
But if it is...
What are we gonna do?
Maybe Baby, here we go! Something special just for us
Maybe Baby Lovin’ Beats Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, always makes my heart skip a beat
Maybe Baby
In this breathless city of the future
I invite you to take it all in
Accelerating at the speed of light
We'll change the world
Boomy Boomy Life
Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, here we go! Something special just for us
Maybe Baby Lovin’ Beats Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, always makes my heart skip a beat
Maybe Baby
Face off!
Van! Kappei!
Huh?
Have you seen Burton?
No, why?
Haven't seen him.
No, huh? Thanks anyway.
Let's do this!
I'm way faster!
No, I am!
Burton? I haven't seen him.
Have you, Lucy?
Thanks anyway.
He's not even gonna make it
before it starts at this rate.
This lecture is gonna be great.
I know!
Maybe he forgot about it?
I doubt it though,
he was super excited for it.
Look, the famous physicist
Professor Bohm is holding an open lecture!
Let's sit in on it together!
Ron?
Haven't seen him.
Okay, thanks.
Okay, here goes!
You'll never beat me!
Ron? No, I haven't seen him.
How about you?
Something's definitely up.
I warned him about this.
Just because he saved us once
doesn't mean we can trust him!
I bet right about now they're...
You let your guard down.
Burton!
Did I do something?
Huh?
Burton! You're alive!
'Course I am!
Can you not jinx it like that, though?
Where the heck have you been?
Professor Bohm already started his lecture!
Professor Bohm...?
Oh, whoops! I completely forgot!
You what?!
That's today?! Ugh...
That's all he's gonna say...?
Something's definitely up with him lately.
Slips out every chance he gets.
And he never tells me where to, either.
Hmm?
Just out and about.
If he's not going to tell me,
I'll just have to find out myself!
Tailing Burton
All right then, let's see where you're off to.
Quit following me!
You're the one following me!
Huh?
Berecca!
What's the big idea?
Shh!
It's just Burton,
why are you being all sneaky?
Huh?
I just uhh, well...
You're tailing him?
Wha?!
Trying to figure out where he's off to?
That easy to guess, huh?
Lemme help, then!
It'll be fun, like we're spies or something!
You've got places to be though, right?
Nope. This idiot's just following me around.
You're the idiot following me!
No, you!
Time to face off!
Wait for us!
Hurry up, Berecca!
Can you please stop shouting
my name like that?!
Phew. Looks like he hasn't noticed us.
There he is!
Where?
Right over there.
Back there on this side.
By the Loco Soda guy.
Oh!
– See?
– There he is!
What do you think you're doing?!
Shut up already!
Seriously, you two!
We're sorry...
Berecca!
– Zoom!
– Swish!
– Woosh!
– Fwoosh!
Pitter-patter, pitter-patter...
Pitter...patter...
– Zoom!
– Swish!
Fwoosh!
– Swah!
– Fwah!
Wha?!
Pitter-patter, pitter-patter...
Sheesh...
He's ordered the same coffee
and chips he always does.
Huh?
Diff if fo good!
Doesn't really look like
he's up to anything secret.
He took a turn!
He's gone!
What? How?
Where'd he go?
He must have spotted us.
This is the purchase history
for Burton's WNA card.
He's been spending a small fortune as of late.
Do you have any idea why?
Nothing that comes to mind...
And you, Bruce?
No, nothing.
Maybe this is his only outlet to
blow off some serious stress?
Sir, can you leave this matter to me?
Very well.
Burton! All settled into the academy?
Huh? Uh, yes?
Great to hear.
Well, you know that
hardware store up ahead?
What hardware store?
Err, I mean...
What's your favorite thing
from the cafeteria?
Huh?
I'm a fan of deep-fried mochi, myself.
It's a dish from Oedo,
and the soy sauce it comes with
is more like joy sauce!
Umm...
Huh?
If you don't need anything, am I free to go?
What?! I mean, uhh...
Yeah, sorry to keep you.
Maybe we can chat again sometime.
Burton! My doors are always open for you!
A transmitter?
We won't lose him with this!
Woah, cool! Where'd you get that?!
I made it myself! I am a scientist, after all!
You're what?
Uhh... No I mean,
I made one in science class before.
You did?
Oh, it's just some school project?
We don't have class tomorrow,
so I'm sure he'll slip off somewhere.
I'll let you handle this part, Van.
Uhh, right...
Morning, Burton! Nice weather today, eh?
Right?
Signal's nice and strong.
We won't lose him now!
He stopped!
Here!
He's gone!
But his transmitter says...
Look!
Guess he noticed.
Must have been
when you slapped it on him!
More like when you turned it on!
We're leaving!
Phew...
Time to put this place together.
Master Genryusai!
Came to check in on things.
Certainly looks more like a laboratory now.
Yeah, and all thanks to you, Master.
If you hadn't stopped me back then...
Planning to sneak in again, are you?
Master Genryusai!
I take it you've got your reasons.
Unidentified lifeforms?
We captured one on our last training mission.
I was so excited at the thought
of having something new to study.
And once I heard they're researching
it down at headquarters...
I just couldn't sit still.
I'm still a scientist at heart,
and I still want to do research.
It's not just this new lifeform,
there's Ninja-Gum, too.
There's so much research I want to do!
Very well, then.
Follow me.
A secret door?!
Not the only one, either.
You have a target on your head.
This should double as a way to
stay out of trouble.
It doesn't see much use these days,
feel free to do your research here.
You mean it?!
I hardly recognize the place, now.
Took a lot to put it together.
But all I need now is some
special equipment.
I want to put a cage here for when
we catch another one of those things.
And here I'll set up an analyzer
and quantum computer.
Then I'll put all my
networking equipment over here.
And this whole area will be
for Ninja-Gum research.
For the time being,
I think I'll focus on why the gum
turns adults into kids.
And try and analyze these
new lifeforms on the side.
You'll enjoy both, I've no doubt.
But are you sure you can handle this all alone?
You mean without Berecca?
I'll bring her here eventually.
Just figure it'll be more fun
if I can surprise her when it's done.
If it's ever done...
Hmm?
I think I might have used
my card a bit too much.
Seems like the academy
has taken notice.
Oh, well, is that all?
Don't fret yourself over that. Here.
For me? Wow, thank you!
Put it on my card.
Huh?
Why give me a card that still
needs its balance paid off...
Hmm?
There.
In your secret lab?
No, I haven't been back since
we last spoke.
Well, somebody has.
Surely not. You and I are the
only two who know it exists.
I sure hope you're right.
Ah-ha!
This afternoon we'll be going over
and analyzing our
"Cops Capture Robbers" training.
Someone definitely broke in.
And if it was someone here...
factoring out Berecca, Van, and Kappei,
it's got to be one of those two...
But how did they find out
about it in the first place?
– Burton!
– Huh?
I think it's about time you
tell me where you keep going off to!
You might think this is some
fun game or something,
but I've been really worried about you!
Berecca...
I'll tell you when the time's right.
Fine. But promise me this.
That you won't get mixed up in trouble.
Not without me, at least.
Right. I promise.
We're not trailing him anymore?!
He's still hiding something though, right?
Turns out it's no big deal.
I pulled him aside and forced him to tell me,
and he said he was just calling his mom.
He was too embarrassed with everyone
around, so he went out for privacy.
So yeah! No more trailing! Thanks for the help!
You gonna stop?
Not a chance.
That's what I thought.
We'll figure out where he's sneaking off to!
Yeah!
He vanished again!
Go on and show yourself!
I swiped this to be ready.
Not gonna go down without a fight!
Here they come!
They're coming this way!
Who's there?!
What?
Goro?
It was you all along?
Is that...?
Now that that's settled,
I guess I can tell Berecca the truth.
She's gonna flip!
Who are you?!
Ron!
Leave 'em to me.
Ron! Ron!
Better you use it than me.
They're gonna kill us! Help!
We're gonna die!
They're trying to kill us!
– Who's killing what?
– Is everything okay?
– My goodness.
– What's going on?
– Someone call the police!
– What's the ruckus?
I don't wanna die!
You okay there, sonny?
My dad bought me this robot!
You can't have it!
Oh, it's just some kids.
You'll never get your hands on this!
Hang on, Ron.
There's something I want you to see.
This is...
That wasn't the only way in, either.
Feel free to pop in if you're ever in trouble.
But this is me and Berecca's secret lab.
Don't go telling anyone.
Burton...
We've searched everywhere!
Where did he go?
I need a break.
Same.
What the heck was that?!
Huh? Burton? Ron, too?!
Why are you here?
A lab?
Yeah. A secret one just for you and me.
Or at least, it was supposed to be.
But Kappei and Van found me...
Seriously...?
Nice place you found here!
Right?
Whenever any baddies are after us,
this place'll come in handy!
And you can see how that went...
So be it. But do not fail me again.
Don't tell me this Ron kid is...
Ninja-like
Ninja!
Nin! Sinking underground with the sun
(Showtime! Our time! Da-dan-dan!)
Now! We seek our men along the thread
(Looking bright! Through the night! Ba-ban-ban!)
Just like the heavy winds (whoo-whoo!)
Just like the calm, quiet woods (ring-ring!)
Like the aliens primed to invade (meep-meep!)
Getting shot down like a crush (bump-bump!)
You only live once
Every encounter has its parting
Our world may burn in war with itself
But the Shinobi Night will protect it
In a flash of the glittering moonlight
We hear blades clashing around us
Through flames, through earth, our lives
They keep going, keep repeating
Life of a ninja! (Nin!)
Ninpo strike, to this day we're
just scraping our way thorugh the war
Until a day comes we can achieve glory
Until I reach your heart on the other side
Nin nin nin!
All sold out
Thank you!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
Concentrate and
succeed!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
“Now I shall take my leave... in smoke!”
Burton's Gum Weapon Lessons
Hey, Gumchi! How's it hanging?
M'chi!
Today we're taking a look at this
Gum Weapon here!
The sneaker-shaped Cerberus!
Cerberus
Gum-Gum-mm!
Despite appearances, it can deploy an
amazing Full-Throttle Field.
This useful ability heals
both you and your allies.
Cerberus
Gum!
And it's a hammer-type weapon,
so it packs a serious punch!
Gum-mm!
Now you're all ready
to score your own IPPON!
Gum!
Next Episode
Heh-heh, my secret lair isn't
so secret anymore.
Hey! Please don't touch that!
Wait, it got away?!
Next time on Ninjala,
"Presenting... Space Ninjas!"
Presenting... Space Ninjas!
Be sure not to miss it!