Watch with
the lights on and
at a distance
from the screen!
Watch TV with the lights on and
at a distance from the screen!
My name's Burton.
I'm a ninja and an ace scientist at
the WNA, the World Ninja Association.
My research is on—
Hang on a minute, it's not
"your" research, it's our research!
Right, yeah. Sorry, Berecca.
Our team is tasked with the research
and development of Ninja-Gum.
What's Ninja-Gum, you ask?
It's an unbelievable item that draws
out a ninja's hidden strengths
granting them all sorts of
amazing new abilities!
And we finally perfected it!
But right as we did...
Our colleague Ron turned his sword on us!
To make things worse, the gum
turned the two of us into kids!
Look at us!
Now what are we supposed to do?
Maybe Baby, here we go! Something special just for us
Maybe Baby Lovin’ Beats Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, always makes my heart skip a beat
Maybe Baby
In this breathless city of the future
I invite you to take it all in
Accelerating at the speed of light
We'll change the world
Boomy Boomy Life
Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, here we go! Something special just for us
Maybe Baby Lovin’ Beats Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, always makes my heart skip a beat
Maybe Baby
There, hacked in.
Talk about an easy mission.
Oh? Well, this won't do...
To WNA headquarters, if you would.
A Long Day for Burton and Berecca
Never imagined we’d get cut off from our own lab.
Yeah, and as if losing access wasn't enough,
our tools and equipment are gone, too.
This is unbelievable.
Well, our Ninja-Gum research
was one of the WNA's top secret projects.
They probably wanted to put a lid
on it before anything leaked.
So what, someone had eyes on us this whole time?
That'd be my guess.
Not sure what we do now, though...
That's weird...
Marco's not picking up?
Nope...
We really need to figure out a way
to get ourselves back to normal.
It's getting late, though.
Pick things up again in the morning?
Sounds good to me.
All this has left me pooped.
My apologies for taking longer than expected.
Ninja-Gum. With this in our hands,
there's nothing left to stop us.
Except, those two I hear are still alive.
I'll continue my pursuit.
Keep an eye on 'em.
And one other one, too...
Huh? What the heck?
Quit that ruckus!
Ms. Peggy!
Wh-What's wrong with my lock?
And just who are you?
It's me, Burton!
The guy that lives here!
You trying to stir up trouble, boy?
Burton canceled his lease and moved out already.
And good riddance to him!
Got a bad feeling about this...
I knew it!
Berecca?
Dealt with the same thing at my place.
You too?
Lost access to my phone, too.
What?
My contract's canceled!
It's just one weird problem after the next.
But why?
Who's doing this?
That's it! Tomorrow, we head to WNA!
What?! But we aren't allowed in HQ...
Who cares about silly non-disclosure
whatevers at a time like this?
We're not gonna get anywhere
until we talk with Marco.
You've always been like this, huh?
And just what's that supposed to mean?!
I-I just mean you're always full of bright ideas.
Oh, whatever.
We've got more important problems
right now. Where are we gonna sleep?
Now, there's where I have a bright idea of my own!
Huh?
Whaddya think? Quite the view, eh?
You can look out over all of Eagle City from up here.
And for free!
I get we're broke and all, but do we
really have to spend the night out here?
It's not so bad.
We can rest safe knowing no one's
gonna bother us up here.
True.
All it's missing is a nice, comfy bed.
The city skyline before us
and the starlit skies above!
Add in the city sounds with all its... meows?
Wait, Goro?!
I was so worried about you!
His bell's gone...
Wonder where he lost it.
That was a gift from my dad, too...
Come on, we gotta go find it!
Nah, it's fine. I'm just glad Goro is safe.
He's sure been gone a while, huh?
I bet he's looking down on us
from somewhere way up above now.
He was one of the nicest guys I ever met.
And an outstanding researcher.
I joined WNA because I wanted
to be like him one day.
We'd never have perfected the Ninja-Gum
if it wasn't for your father's work.
That and a whole lot of luck, you mean.
Help!
Somebody, please!
Our boss is stuck in the slammer now
thanks to you and your big mouth!
You're gonna get the real
special treatment for this!
I'm sorry, this is all my fault.
You only did what was right.
Whadda you want, punk?
You'll be safe now!
Kappei, if you don't stay focused, I swear...!
Whoops, right!
Good grief...
What?!
Hey, don't look at me!
That same dream again...
Goro!
Goro! Sheesh, where did he go?
He'll show up again when he's ready.
Finally up I see.
Wow, are you okay? You're sweating bullets!
Yeah, it's nothing.
Dreaming of some long lost relative again?
Yup. The legendary Hattori Hanzo.
One of history's greatest ninjas.
Ready to get going?
Thanks for lending me some cash, Berecca.
Sure, but I thought we were
heading to WNA headquarters.
What are we doing out here buying groceries?
The great Thomas Edison once said—
"All effort is wasted effort without
good initial inspiration." See?
Now then, it's time for science!
Mind explaining what happened
to our plans to visit HQ?
I realized they had one critical flaw.
When our lab was locked down,
when we lost our apartments,
no one believed we were anything
but troublesome little kids.
Well, I mean, look at us.
Exactly. We won't get anywhere
until we've got our old bodies back.
Which is why we need to turn back
into adults before we visit HQ!
Wait, don't tell me...!
We managed to make that Ninja-Gum, right?
So I bet—no, I know we can make
something to counteract all this!
Growing up requires protein,
calcium, fiber, and vitamins.
And all that and more is packed in here,
in this all-in-one smoothie!
Test one, bottoms up!
Diwah no failurh, buh a firh
cafirh mehod whih doehn'h worh!
Uhhh, what?
Time to mix up our experimentation strategy!
What we really need to grow up is
a strong, healthy body!
Bring on the muscles!
And now that I'm all worn out...
my body is primed and ready
for these nutrients.
This is sure to work!
I had it all wrong.
What we really need are grown-up sensibilities.
Or so I thought, but what we need...
is this!
I think I’m gonna be sick...
Enough already!
I'm good as broke now thanks to you!
Guess it's time for our last resort.
And that is...?
Brute force.
We head straight for WNA headquarters!
You've got to be kidding me!
"Marco?"
Yup. Can you call him down for us?
He's our boss.
Yeowch!
He means our uncle! We're just here
with something he asked us to bring in.
Is that so? Just give me a moment, then.
I'm sorry, okay?
Sheesh...
Well, that's odd. There doesn't seem
to be anyone at WNA by that name.
What?!
Can you check again? He's in charge of
research with Burton and Berecca.
Are you sure you have the right names?
None of them are in our records.
Here we are again, no closer
to finding anything out.
I can't believe someone managed
to wipe all the data on us.
We're good as done for.
No place to live, no place to work.
And stuck as kids like this forever, maybe.
Yeowch!
Quit it with the sob story.
We gotta stay positive!
Okay, now you have me worried.
We’ve always been like this, huh?
Remember that trip we went on as kids?
You mean the time we got lost?
You looked fit to burst
into tears at any second.
F-Funny, I don't remember that...
Yo!
What are you kids doing 'round here?
What's it to ya? This is a free country.
Berecca...!
Wuzzat?
W-Well, we better get going...
Yeah, yeah.
Go on then, get.
But drop all your valuables first.
Listen, we've been stuck
sleeping outside, okay?
If anyone needs money here, it's us!
Oh yeah? You lookin' to mess, brat?
Oughta ask you the same!
Aaagh!
Let's get outta here!
That little twerp!
Right, uhhh...
This way!
How can you be sure?
Just got a hunch!
Do you really believe in something
as completely unscientific as that?!
Call it womanly intuition!
There they are!
We made it back home as kids, right?
See? This is why I don't
trust that sorta stuff!
Oh, can it!
We're dead meat!
Desperate times call for... Ta-da!
Oh, duh! Ninja-Gum!
Let's do this!
You got it!
Get 'em!
What's with this gunk?!
Playin' dirty now, are ya?
Shoot!
Are you kidding me?
How's she doing that?
Impressed yet?
Berecca, look out!
Now you're in for it!
My hero!
So you wanna play rough, eh?
Wow! Talk about cool!
What's with these kids?!
They ain't playing!
Let's get outta here!
So, that's what happened to them!
I bet these bad boys are gonna come in pretty handy.
Are you enjoying being stuck as kids like this?
We won't be able to use Ninja-Gum
like that once we're back to normal.
True.
But still, I'd rather have my regular body back.
Same.
Welp! We've still got loads of problems to sort out.
We'll figure something out, you'll see.
First things first, we need a place to sleep tonight.
Ugh, please tell me we're not camping outside again.
Another beautiful night out under the stars.
I am seriously not in the mood!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
Nin! Sinking underground with the sun
(Showtime! Our time! Da-dan-dan!)
Now! We seek our men along the thread
(Looking bright! Through the night! Ba-ban-ban!)
Just like the heavy winds (whoo-whoo!)
Just like the calm, quiet woods (ring-ring!)
Like the aliens primed to invade (meep-meep!)
Getting shot down like a crush (bump-bump!)
You only live once
Every encounter has its parting
Our world may burn in war with itself
But the Shinobi Night will protect it
In a flash of the glittering moonlight
We hear blades clashing around us
Through flames, through earth, our lives
They keep going, keep repeating
Life of a ninja! (Nin!)
Ninpo strike, to this day we're
just scraping our way thorugh the war
Until a day comes we can achieve glory
Until I reach your heart on the other side
Nin nin nin!
All sold out
Thank you!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
Concentrate and
succeed!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
“Now I shall take my leave... in smoke!”
Next Episode
Ugh, first we get stuck as kids,
then some hooligans pick a fight...
now we're stuck sleeping outside again?!
Huh? Where's that kid off to this late at night?
Next time on Ninjala,
"Awaken, Young Van!"
Awaken, Young Van!
Don't miss it!