The Azatoth Empire's reign spans
a myriad of stars and planets.
And now, they've got their
sights set on Planet Earth...
They told us to "watch our backs" around the cat,
but I'm not convinced.
Q
G
Ry
Researcher
Rel
Resx
Researcher
Resed
Reseag
Researcher
Researt
Researcf
Researcher
Researchz
H
P
Gk
Garmie Lou
Gah
Gard
Garmie Lou
Garmj
Garmiy
Garmie Lou
Garmib
Garmie W
Garmie Lp
Garmie LP
Garmie Lou
Garmie Los
Garnie Loa
Garmie Lou
What do you think?
Well... it's giving Liza trouble and
she's the most skilled member of the Research Team.
How can we be careful
if we don't even know what it looks like?
Q
G
Ry
Researcher
Rel
Resx
Researcher
Resed
Reseag
Researcher
Researt
Researcf
Researcher
Researchz
&
E
Ls
Luster Cole
Lum
Lusr
Luster Cole
Lustt
Lustev
Luster Cole
Lusten
Luster H
Luster Cf
Luster Cole
Luster Cox
Luster Colu
Luster Cole
Luster Colg
What a challenging mission this will be.
What an honor. I couldn't be happier.
Now then, let's get started.
a
ri
e
nai
Impossible...
ki
ka
ku
gai
Unprecedented...
ta
ma
ra
nai
Out of this world...
We run into each other on the catwalk
BLACK
HOLE
Your eyes suck me in like a black hole
tsun
tsun
da
You act so cold but flaunt your stuff
Why the hell is my heart racing?
They're saying it'll rain this afternoon
So maybe I should have an early lunch
ba
cchi
I see you gleaming in the sunlight
What an angel
I'll always be under your paw
My love for you warps the space-time continuum
You quickly become the center of my universe
do
kkun
ba
de
Ba-dump, ker-thump
I just can't take it anymore...
Forget fate or miracles
BANG
Us crossing paths was a big bang
Every star across the night sky is our miracle
I don't want my love to go to your head
I just want you to stay with me...
#3. No Surrender
Things aren't looking good, you two.
Is it because your allies are coming to Earth?
Two of my juniors from the Research Department.
Since they're your juniors,
I can't imagine they're that scary.
Yes, but... the problem is,
I'm afraid they might see a cat.
What's so bad about that?
Supposedly, when someone from
Liza's planet sees cats or other cute animals,
their hearts will explode
out of their chests!
Wow, that's one serious cat allergy...
For them, it's their first ever assignment.
It's a joyous occasion,
so I should congratulate them at least.
Maybe I should invite them over...
How thoughtful of you!
No wait, that's a terrible idea!
If they come over, they're gonna see Yozora!
They'll drop dead the second
they see his adorable sleeping face!
What's with the fish lips...?
Maybe it helps her lower her volume a bit...?
Then again, they're probably excited about it, too.
I'd feel terrible if I
flat-out refused to let them come over...
What do I—
Watch Yozora for me!
Huh?
Heya, Liza!
We figured we should come say hello first...
It's our first planetary
investigation after all!
Now, bring on the prai—
Get out!!
Huh?!
Don't just show up unannounced like that!
Warn someone first before you open a space-time
portal to their house! Where the hell are your manners?!
W-We just...
We really wanted to see you, that's all...
Yeah, well, this is Earth!
The front door exists for a reason!
C'mon, it's basic Earth etiquette!
Pot, meet kettle.
I bet all that commotion woke Yozora up...
I'm sorry for ruining your cozy nap, my sweetie—
He's still sound asleep!
Knock-knock!
The doors on Earth sure are flimsy!
I'm tempted to dropkick you
off this godforsaken planet!
Garmie was dying to see you, Liza.
There was nothing I could do to stop her...
And honestly, I missed you, too.
When you put it like that,
I can't really get mad at you...
That girl's got horns...
Is that an eye on his forehead...?
Not even Yozora could sleep through this much—
Are you kidding me?!
He's unwakeable!
This strange scent...
You're hiding the cat behind you, aren't you?!
Quit it, Garmie.
We have no visual documentation whatsoever...
Which lead us to believe you
were purposefully concealing it.
It must be dangerous to look at,
just like everyone's saying!
They say that anybody who sees one goes insane...
And that their voices can hypnotize people.
Master manipulators who
control Earth's society from the shadows...
A species superior to mankind.
The creatures known as... "cats"!
Holy crap, what is that monstrosity?!
Some of the details are off, but...
the resemblance is uncanny.
No way! That thing's a frickin' nightmare!
Please let us take care of this creature.
We'll destroy it.
Yeah, why not? Everyone keeps calling it a threat,
but it can't be that bad, right?
So we may as well see what
we're up against while we're here!
Show us the cat!
Nope. You'll die.
You don't trust us?
Don't underestimate us!
We're prepared to lay down
our lives for this investigation!
Shh, shut it or you'll waken the cat.
What is it, a demon?!
I knew it. Cats really are
savage, bloodthirsty creatures...
Something tells me it'd be
pointless to try and argue otherwise...
Earlier...
I felt a peculiar sense of uneasiness
as soon as I entered the room.
Almost as though my body was warning me...
"Don't go anywhere near that thing."
It almost feels like I'm choking...
And my eyes—
no... my whole body is itchy...
Wh-What's happening to me?!
H-Hey, Luster...?!
His symptoms sound a lot like... poison!
It can't be! Cats aren't poisonous!
Wh-Why is it... just me...?
Am I being attacked...?
Can it sense my hostility...?!
Kasumi! What the hell's going on?!
Um... If I had to guess...
He's probably allergic to cats.
And, uh... what does "allergic" mean?
Do aliens not know about allergies?!
It seems Luster has been defeated by a cat...
He hasn't even been gone that long!
After much deliberation, Garmie and Luster
ended up moving into the same apartment as Liza.
Luna
Lou
Cole
It's too...
cute?
Exactly. Cats are harmless creatures...
But they are unimaginably adorable.
So much so that I'm afraid you'll keel
over at the very sight of their fluffy bodies!
It's too soon.
You're still susceptible to their charms.
Which is why... you can't see them!
What the heck...
...are you even...
talking about?
Okay, why are you acting confused?
Seriously? Cats were actually
super cute this whole time?
Oh, I get it! You were keeping them
hidden 'cause you were too embarrassed
to let anyone see you acting all mushy
over a sweet little kitty-cat!
I'll just let Deputy Commander Amat know!
Did you listen to a single word I said?!
Creak-creak-creak-creak!
If you tell them the truth, everyone's going
to stop being careful and let their guard down!
You don't understand the
ramifications of their cuteness!
Reminder
Dinner time
Yozora's awake...
I need to feed him.
Catch you guys later!
DO NOT ENTER
Cat Inside
Well, it doesn't sound so bad...
Q-Quit it, Yozora!
DO NOT ENTER
Cat Inside
Don't eat that! I'm about to make your dinner!
DO NOT ENTER
Cat Inside
Get off! Let go of me!
DO NOT ENTER
Cat Inside
Knock it off, wouldja?! You can't sit in my lap to eat!
Just get down for a second!
How am I supposed to move?!
Stand back and—
My hand!! Wh-Why?!
I'm not food!! Please don't eat me!!
That's not the voice of someone
playing with a "harmless creature!"
DO NOT ENTER
Cat Inside
Oh crap!!
How cute!
Aw, he's so adorable!
Whoa... She was right. He's shockingly cute...
Wh-What...?
Good thing their hearts didn't explode, right?
Huh... I'm surprised.
It seems those two were much stronger than
I gave them credit for.
It gives me hope for the future.
Am I allowed to pick him up?!
Sure... so long as Yozora doesn't object.
His fur looks super-duper soft...
I've never seen anything like it...
Is that what you meant by "fluffy...?"
I want to savor it...
Fluffy!!
Watch out! You can't just pounce on him like that!
I know that... I really do...
But I can't control myself!
Not when he's so unbelievably fluffy-wuffy!
I have to squeeze him...
I can't contain my excitement!
Now's your chance to run...
Get him as far away as you can!
Or else, I...
Fluh... fluhhh...
Fluffy!!
Cut it out! Get ahold of yourself!
Remember: Everything in moderation!
Liza, pass me the cat.
L-Luster?!
Are you sure that's a good idea?
What about your "allergy" thing?
I'm perfectly fine.
Yeah, the blood says otherwise!
Even if my allergies worsen...
and even if the severe palpitations caused by
my elevated heart rate damage my internal organs...
It's all irrelevant in
the face of cats and their cuteness.
Nothing in this world is more important
than appreciating cats in all their glory...
Every moment spent not looking
at cats is absolutely meaningless!
Fluffy!! Fluffy!!
Cats... cats...
My life is worthless... Give me the cat!
I need to touch it!
Would you two take it down a notch?!
My brain short-circuited...
Looking at cats is dangerous...
Are you two alright?
Why isn't your video feed turned on?
Quit fooling around and turn it on!
Wha—?!
Amat.
Liza! What's going on down there?!
I can't go into specifics right now,
but let me just say this:
Don't mess with cats,
or you'll meet the same fate as them!
Maybe you should consider saying that
in a way that can't be misinterpreted...
Apparently, Kasumi's grandfather and her cousin
own pets that are completely different from cats.
Our mission is to—
...convince them to let us observe them...
R-Roger that...
A-Anyway, I gotta get Yozora to settle down
before we can leave, so go wait for me outside!
Wowie, cats aren't for the faint of heart, are they?
You said it... But we held ourselves together.
Perhaps we're starting to build up a tolerance to—
Good afternoon!
Fluffy!!
Cute animal detected! Lemme see it up clo—
Don't be... rude!!
I'm sorry if they scared you.
Are you hurt?
N-No...
We got cocky and careless...
We nearly got knocked unconscious...
No... It's my fault for not warning you
about dogs ahead of time.
It's called a... "dog"?
Alongside cats, they're very popular.
Hey, um, Liza? What happened to your face?
Oh, it's nothing.
G
Yozora was preventing me
from leaving as usual, when...
C'mon me, get it together!
It must've thrown him,
'cause he stopped crying after that.
Man, that sucks...
Um... Can I go now?
Still, showing up at a stranger's house and demanding
to see their pets? I hope we aren't imposing...
AZUMA
What kind of animals do they have? Dogs?
No. According to Kasumi—
Oh my... It appears the guests
Kasumi mentioned have arrived.
Ah, yes. She asked us to show them our adorable pets...
Then I suppose I'll have to show them my hamster.
%
B
KaZ
Kaz
Kasumi's Grandfather
Kasf
Kasumn
Kasumi's Grandfather
Kasumi;
Kausmi's E
Kasumi's E
Kasumi's Grandfather
Kasumi's Gy
Kasumi's Gru
Kasumi's Grandfather
Kasumi's Gra@
Kasumi's Granp
Kasumi's Grandfather
Kasumi's Grandfs
Kasumi's Grandfaw
Kasumi's Grandfather
Kasumi's Grandfathu
Kasumi's Grandfathex
Kasumi's Grandfather
S
&
I
Mf
Mitsuhiko Azuma
Miz
Mitse
Mitsuhiko Azuma
Mitsur
Mitsuhm
Mitsuhiko Azuma
Mitsuhib
Mitsuhiku
Mitsuhiko Azuma
Mitsuhiko D
Mitsuhiko Ap
Mitsuhiko Azuma
Mitsuhiko Azux
Mitsuhiko Azumh
Mitsuhiko Azuma
Hamsters are the cutest pets, after all...
Hedgehogs, on the other hand,
are super-mega-ultra adorable...
E
Kl
Kasumi's Cousin
Ka&
Kasx
Kasumi's Cousin
Kasua
Kasumt
Kasumi's Cousin
Kasumin
Kasumi'l
Kasumi's Cousin
Kasumi's M
Kasumi's Z
Kasumi's Cf
Kasumi's Cousin
Kasumi's Coi
Kasumi's Coue
Kasumi's Cousin
Kasumi's Cousp
Kasumi's Cousij
Kasumi's Cousin
D
A
Sx
Sasara Azuma
Sak
Sasn
Sasara Azuma
Sasaa
Sasas
Sasaro
Sasara Azuma
Sasara T
Sasara X
Sasara Am
Sasara Azuma
Sasara Azd
Sasara Azur
Sasara Azuma
Sasara Azuc
Sasara Azumy
Sasara Azuma
I ought to show them mine.
DUN DUN
DUH DUH DUN
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
Why, I didn't expect to meet real aliens.
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
SPACE CRACKERS
BLACK HOLE
JELLY
I just assumed she meant you were
a little on the strange side.
Sorry for scaring you like that.
Any friend of Kasumi's is welcome in this house.
You wanted to see our pets, is that correct?
Yes, please. We're on the hunt for cute animals,
even if they can't compare with cats.
Pardon?
Oh, I'd better warn her not to mention
her preference for cats...
"Can't compare with cats...?"
I-I'm sorry. I meant no offense...
It's okay! No offense taken.
Everyone has their favorites,
and animals are no exception!
People get defensive real quick,
especially when it comes to pets!
But it usually takes 'em a while to calm down again...
A-Again, my bad...
We'll go and get them, so wait right there!
It's my pleasure to introduce...
Mitsuro the hamster!
And Negimaru the hedgehog!
P-Preposterous!
What's with this level of tininess!
Having a compact size is a
crucial factor in terms of cuteness...
But this creature...
Its big, round eyes... Its soft fur...!
Its itty-bitty body contains astronomically
high levels of extremely concentrated cute...
I'm being sucked into...
an abyss of adorableness!
A black hole of cuteness!
A-And that one...
Impossible! How can it be so cute
when it's covered in quills?!
I want to cuddle with it, but it's made of knives!
No! Wait a minute...
There's more to its charm than
a simple "forbidden fruit" effect!
The delicate twitch of its nose makes its quills look
harmless, despite being designed to deter predators!
It's an inverse perspective... A reminder...
that cuteness is the most powerful weapon of all!
A sharp, piercing splendor...!
What's the matter with this girl...?
F-Forgive me...
I wasn't prepared to experience two
mind-blowingly adorable animals at once...
Don't worry about me...
I'll bounce back in no time.
Teensy-weensy fluffy!!
Spiky-wikey fluffy!!
I-It's sucking me in! I'm getting stabbed!
Teensy-weensy fluffy!! Spiky-wikey fluffy!!
Is this some kind of weird space disease...?
They're way more adorable than
I could have ever imagined...
I totally understand why you think
they make the cutest pets.
I must admit, it's nice to hear you say that.
I'm glad we could help you understand!
Still, Yozora obviously holds
the title of "World's Cutest Pet."
How dare you?!
Say it again, punk! See what happens!
Shuddup! I won't surrender to the likes of you!
My pwecious Yozora is the greatest
in the entire universe!
They're whisper-arguing so
they don't scare the animals...
Earthlings sure are passionate about their pets...
Now then... Shall we begin the battle?
Whoa, whoa, whoa...
I just finished my shift at the café.
I have no idea what's going on...
I shall prove, beyond a shadow of a doubt,
that I have the cutest pet!
And we're both willing to stake our pride on it!
There's only one rule!
No insulting your opponents' pets!
That goes without saying.
Duh, that's just basic respect!
So it's really just a big brag fest...
Fluffy!!
Allow me to show you how it's done.
How long are they going to keep up this gag?
Bow down before Yozora's exquisite beauty,
you filthy peasants!
This is the first time I've
ever left him home alone...
but I set up a camera for peace of mind!
Yozora!
"Is it her?! Is she home?!"
And he perks up at the sound of my voice!
"She's not here yet..."
And then he lays back down, disappointed!
He's a cat of many faces!
I wanna go home! I wanna
go home right now and snuggle him!
AAHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH
So precious!!
Fluffy!!
She's pretty good, isn't she?
Yeah...
The voice-over really ramped up
the "crazy pet parent" vibes.
She's a formidable opponent, for sure.
Feast your eyes, you uncultured swine,
on Negimaru's unparalleled charisma!
Are they all gonna do that...?
Your attention, please!
Ultimate Cutie-pie Orb Form, go!
I-I love Ultimate Cutie-pie Orb Form!
And when I rub this spot on her tummy...
Yeah...?!
Sh-She stretches out!
This is her Final Relaxation Form!
At first, she was a real fraidy-cat...
She spent all her time in Prickly Pear Mode!
But now,
she's completely unbothered by everything!
WASTED
A little too unbothered...
But don't the quills on her back dig into your skin?
Nope, not at all!
They do, don't they?
STAB
I mean, she's kind of poking me right now.
A-Are you alright?!
STAB
It doesn't hurt nearly as much as it used to.
It's how she shows her affection!
STAB
Like play-biting, except it's play-poking!
P-Poke me, too...!
Spiky-wikey!!
I believe it's my turn now.
Get crushed beneath the weight of
Mitsuro's sheer grandeur, you annoying brats!
Yeah, you lost me with that one...
Well? My darling Mitsuro is impressive, isn't he?
What?
Look right here.
H-He sits inside your pocket?!!
Mitsuro and I share a very strong bond.
He scampers around near me
when I let him out of his cage.
Tight spaces are his favorite.
He'll glady climb into my sleeves or pockets.
Squishy, squishy, squishy, squishy!!
Please! Walk all over me—
In other words,
the very definition of "inseparable"...
Precisely. Mitsuro might as well
be an extention of my own body!
Why are you on your knees all of a sudden?!
Because Mitsuro could get hurt
if he fell from a tall height!
What's that? Time to head home already?
Yikes, he turned himself into a pet pedicab...
Grandpa's going back to his cage,
so it's your turn, Kasumi.
I had a feeling I'd be forced to participate...
Prepare to be tortured by Masamune's electrifying charm,
you insignificant worms!
You don't sound all that upset...
Y'see, Masamune...
He's incredibly gentle and patient.
Whenever I'm feeling discouraged, he wraps his body
around me to try and calm me down.
Well, he likes to do that all the time.
Even when it's hot outside.
When I was little,
we had another golden retriever.
His name was Muramasa,
and I raised him from the day he was born.
He passed away when I was ten years old...
I had wanted to be like a big sister to him,
but Muramasa always did his best to cheer me up,
even at the end of his life.
That's when I realized,
"Oh. He was the one looking after me."
Later on, we welcomed Masamune into the family, and
I told myself I'd be the one doing the protecting this time.
Muramasa taught me that life is precious,
and I promised I'd never forget that...
That being said, I feel like
he's still watching over me to this day.
Stop... I wasn't prepared for a heartwarming story...
M-My bad...
Are your friends going to be alright?
They're a little woozy from
gorging on cuteness, that's all.
For a second there, I totally thought you
guys were gonna start throwing hands.
We're all winners, and that's fine by me.
Everyone loves their own pets the most,
regardless of what others might think.
I have the cutest pet in all the cosmos,
and nobody knows that better than me.
Good point. What you saw here today was
but a mere fraction of Mitsuro's magnificence.
The same goes for Negimaru!
Huh?
You have yet to gaze upon
the cutest tush in the world!
The legendary hamster heinie!
Don't forget the hedgehog booty!
"B-Booty"...?
Their butts! Look at their butts!
You can't leave until you look at their butts!
Oh my god, stop saying "butts"!
What the hell's wrong with you?!
wotchi wotchi are wa nanda? seimeitai no "se"!
Watch, watch, what's that I see? A lively lifeform!
saachi saachi moshikashite tomodachi ka?
Search, search, do you wanna be friends?
nyanboree nyanboree nyanboree nyanboree de
Myamboree! Myamboree! Myamboree! Myamboree! So...
moffii! moffii!
Fwuffy! Fwuffy!
nyanboree nyanboree nyanboree nyanboree de
Myamboree! Myamboree! Myamboree! Myamboree! So...
moffii! moffii!
Fwuffy! Fwuffy!
nyaa
Meow!
kawaii wa seigi sonja sonja aku to wa nan zo?
Cuteness is justice! So what are the evils standin' in its way?
urusai mama? kenka? shukudai? osouji?
Mom being naggy? Getting into fights? Homework? Cleaning?
kokoronai hitotachi ga afureteiru zo
There's a lotta cruel people out there
nakayoku shitekunakya muu muu da!
Better get along or you'll be a grumpypants!
chikyuu wa fushigi na toko de kaiseki taihen
Earth's a strange planet, and studying it's a pain
risou dake ja omanma taberenai ga
But just thinking about it won't put food on the table!
nishin geppo shikou sakugo
Through steady effort and trial and error
teinei ni tema hima kakeru no ga, otoshidokoro!
Give it a go and your hard work will pay off!
wotchi wotchi are wa nanda? seimeitai no "se"!
Watch, watch, what's that I see? A lively lifeform!
mikke mikke UTOPIA kamo?
I spy, I spy, a utopia?
doukaina?
There's no way, right?
nyanboree de waai! yatta ne nyanboree de uu!
Myamboree, hurray! Yippee! Myamboree, whoo!
muzukashii koto wa chotto oyasumi nanoda
We deserve a break after all that hard work
ashita mata ganbarou tte iettara OK!
As long as we promise we'll get back to it tomorrow, it's A-OK!
choi sawagi shichaou!
Let's have a party!
sore ga sunawachi heiwa tte yatsu janai?
That's what peace is all about, no?
iizo! moffi-ffii fuwafuwa ni
Alright! Fwuffy-ffy, dive right in
moffi-ffi tobikondara
Fwuffy-ffy, right into the fluff
ai tte yatsu ga wakari sou desu
And you'll start to know what love really means
totte oki no nukumori de
Lovingly conceal me
meromero ni tsutsundene moffii
In all that warmth of yours, so fwuffy
san, ni, ichi... kyou mo otsukaresama!
3, 2, 1... Good work today!
goronago chokomaka chochoi to goshujin
Catnapping nonstop, one second, Master
omimi wo haishaku, hidari kara nyaa
I need you for a sec, gimme your left ear-Meow!
nyanboree nyanboree nyanboree nyanboree de
Myamboree! Myamboree! Myamboree! Myamboree! So...
moffii! moffii!
Fwuffy! Fwuffy!
nyaa
Meow!
Azatoth's soldiers find themselves at the mercy of cats,
a species that cannot speak.
As her brethren teeter on the brink of insanity,
Liza works towards a surprising goal.
Next time, Episode 4: "Unknown."