The Azatoth Empire's reign spans
a myriad of stars and planets.
And now, they've got their
sights set on Planet Earth...
Seems like Garmie's super interested in bunnies.
She's going to the bunny café again today.
"Bunnies," huh... Are they really that cute?
Indeed. Their cuteness can only
be described as otherworldly.
Oh please, don't be so dramatic...
Behold, a rabbit.
It's meowgnificent!!
Bunnies don't say that, Fianna.
a
ri
e
nai
Impossible...
ki
ka
ku
gai
Unprecedented...
ta
ma
ra
nai
Out of this world...
We run into each other on the catwalk
BLACK
HOLE
Your eyes suck me in like a black hole
tsun
tsun
da
You act so cold but flaunt your stuff
Why the hell is my heart racing?
They're saying it'll rain this afternoon
So maybe I should have an early lunch
ba
cchi
I see you gleaming in the sunlight
What an angel
I'll always be under your paw
My love for you warps the space-time continuum
You quickly become the center of my universe
do
kkun
ba
de
Ba-dump, ker-thump
I just can't take it anymore...
Forget fate or miracles
BANG
Us crossing paths was a big bang
Every star across the night sky is our miracle
I don't want my love to go to your head
I just want you to stay with me...
#9. Outcast
Yeah, and check this out: Garmie mentioned
she's been thinking about adopting a bunny.
Adopting one...? There's no way!
That is not a real animal!
It's a dream! A hallucination!
Wake up, Liza!
No, you need to wake up! Listen to what I'm saying!
As Garmie's mentor, and as the resident expert
on raising Earth animals...
I need to be a proper role model for her.
I must become the ultimate pet owner,
one whose actions she can emulate and learn from!
This is so unfair! I want to meow around
with cute animals like everyone else!
Go home already, jeez!
I need to know what I'm doing wrong...
I'm not sure why, but I get the distinct feeling
that Yozora tries to keep his distance from me...
Mechayozora, too... The other day,
he told me I was acting creepy...
Meow!
Please refrain from coming any closer!
Huh?!
Why am I the only one with this problem...?
It sucks... I'm gonna cry!
You already are...
Well, I was about to play
with Yozora, so... wanna watch?
Maybe it'll be educational for you.
Yes, please...
Now, thou shall reveal thy secrets to me!
It's like she's losing braincells by the minute...
Alright... pull yourself together, Liza...
I've gotta improve my skills as a pet owner, Yozora!
And the first step is increasing
the amount of physical contact we share.
Hm... I noticed you didn't work
a cat pun into your sentence.
Was that a stylistic choice, or...?
If you don't shut it, I'm gonna kick you out.
Physical contact...
My attempts are usually thwarted by
Yozora's devastating cuteness...
But if I'm going to be a good role model for Fianna,
then I have to make a genuine effort to change.
C'mere, Yozora.
I'm sorry if I've been making you feel lonely.
C'mon, let me hug you. Come sit in my lap.
Omigosh! It's almost like
she's inviting someone to bed...!
My heart's pounding so hard, it's making me dizzy!
That's incredible, Liza!
Yozora looks totally calm and relaxed!
Liza...?!
My body's been paralyzed by
the devastating cuteness...
But I managed to pet him
for a whole minute this time!
That's a new record!
You're amazing, Liza! Absolutely amazing!
Well, I have had a lot of practice...
Practice...? That's it! Practice!
If I could just acclimate myself to it, then...
Okay, then. Wanna try playing with Yozora?
He's a pretty sociable cat, so he might let you...
Really...?!
Do you want to play with me~ow...?
Alright, on second thought, never mind.
Why not?! You're supposed to help me practice!
Do you want me to be awkward and creepy forever?!
What kind of a threat is that...?
Meow, if I wave this cat-tastic toy
ameowund, will he cattack it?
Uh, come again...?
Wait, why are you wearing cat ears all of a sudden?
To increase the chances of him liking me,
if only by a little!
H-Here, Yozora...!
Let's pawlay together!
C'meown, don't be shy!
Yozora...
Don't sit there and stare at me like,
"Am I meant to humor her?"
He's being pawfully cold...
He... He paid attention to me just meow!
Pretty considerate for a cat, aren't you?
H-He seemed kind of hesitant at first...
But that's how it goes, right? It's new to us both!
Y-Yeah, exactly!
Yozora's in "Relaxation Mode" right now!
I honestly don't even think he's in the mood to play...
Yozora...?!
Are you finding flaunting
your superiority enjoyable?
That wasn't my intention!
Still... I'm the only one Yozora shows affection to!
How am I not supposed to let that feed my ego?!
Hey, what the hell's that look for?!
Sorry, Fianna... I'm really, really sorry...
I'm not sure why, but I am extremely
pissed off right now!
Yozora the Cat
Yozora refuses to play
with me
Fianna
replied:
get rekt lololol
I'm not sure why, but I am extremely
pissed off right now!
Yozora the Cat
Yozora refuses to play
with me
Fianna
replied:
get rekt lololol
Yozora the Cat
Yozora refuses to play
with me
Fianna
replied:
get rekt lololol
Yozora refuses to play
Yozora the Cat
with me
Fianna
replied:
get rekt lololol
Yozora the Cat
Yozora refuses to play
with me
Fianna
replied:
get rekt lololol
Yozora refuses to play
Yozora the Cat
with me
Fianna
replied:
get rekt lololol
Yozora the Cat
Yozora refuses to play
with me
Fianna
replied:
get rekt lololol
Yozora the Cat
Yozora refuses to play
with me
Fianna
replied:
get rekt lololol
Yozora the Cat
Yozora refuses to play
with me
Fianna
replied:
get rekt lololol
Yozora the Cat
Yozora refuses to play
with me
Fianna
replied:
get rekt lololol
Yozora the Cat
Yozora refuses to play
with me
Fianna
replied:
get rekt lololol
Yozora the Cat
Yozora refuses to play
with me
Fianna
replied:
get rekt lololol
Yozora the Cat
Yozora refuses to play
with me
Fianna
replied:
get rekt lololol
Yozora refuses to play
Yozora the Cat
with me
Fianna
replied:
get rekt lololol
Yozora the Cat
Yozora refuses to play
with me
Fianna
replied:
get rekt lololol
Yozora the Cat
Yozora refuses to play
with me
Fianna
replied:
get rekt lololol
Yozora the Cat
Yozora refuses to play
with me
Fianna
replied:
get rekt lololol
Yozora the Cat
Yozora refuses to play
with me
Fianna
replied:
get rekt lololol
Yozora the Cat
Yozora refuses to play
with me
Fianna
replied:
get rekt lololol
Yozora the Cat
Yozora refuses to play
with me
Fianna
replied:
get rekt lololol
Yozora the Cat
Yozora refuses to play
with me
Fianna
replied:
get rekt lololol
Yozora the Cat
Yozora refuses to play
with me
Fianna
replied:
get rekt lololol
Yozora the Cat
Yozora refuses to play
with me
Fianna
replied:
get rekt lololol
Yozora the Cat
Yozora refuses to play
with me
Fianna
replied:
get rekt lololol
Yozora the Cat
Yozora refuses to play
with me
Fianna
replied:
get rekt lololol
Yozora the Cat
Yozora refuses to play
with me
Fianna
replied:
get rekt lololol
Yozora the Cat
Yozora refuses to play
with me
Fianna
replied:
get rekt lololol
Yozora the Cat
Yozora refuses to play
with me
Fianna
replied:
get rekt lololol
Yozora the Cat
Yozora refuses to play
with me
Fianna
replied:
get rekt lololol
Yozora the Cat
Yozora refuses to play
with me
Fianna
replied:
get rekt lololol
Yozora the Cat
Yozora refuses to play
with me
Fianna
replied:
get rekt lololol
Yozora the Cat
Yozora refuses to play
with me
Fianna
replied:
get rekt lololol
Yozora the Cat
Yozora refuses to play
with me
Fianna
replied:
get rekt lololol
Yozora the Cat
Yozora refuses to play
with me
Fianna
replied:
get rekt lololol
Yozora the Cat
Yozora refuses to play
with me
Fianna
replied:
get rekt lololol
Yozora the Cat
Yozora refuses to play
with me
Fianna
replied:
get rekt lololol
Yozora the Cat
Yozora refuses to play
with me
Fianna
replied:
get rekt lololol
Yozora the Cat
Yozora refuses to play
with me
Fianna
replied:
get rekt lololol
FIVE YEARS AGO
Don'tcha wanna come play with us?
I'm no good with group activities...
Can I sit here with you?
Huh?
Sure, but it's not going to be much fun.
Hey, you don't know that!
What?
You see things differently from everybody else,
which tells me you've got
your own unique brand of fun!
FAIRY
TAILS
Aw, look at them! Aren't they just adorable?!
Several of the bunnies living here at the shop
are available for adoption, too.
The little bunny with the floppy ears...
She hasn't moved from that one part of the room...
No... But the other bunnies seem
to be having a blast together...
The only one sitting in the corner,
without a friend in sight...
Seeing her like that makes me want
to give her some attention, you know?
This cutie seems to like hanging out by herself.
Even when I let her out of her cage,
she always finds a secluded spot to relax.
I guess you could call her skittish or shy,
but it's part of her charm, don'tcha think?
I can feel my maternal
instincts starting to kick in!
Whoa... That's weird...
It's almost like I'm looking at my past self...
"Adorable..."
"I want to give her attention..."
Is that what you were thinking
about me back then, Garmie...?
But I have to admit, your words were very touching...
Is something the matter, Luster?
No, everything's fine...
If you're happy, I'm happy.
Would you say she's your favorite?
Well... I definitely think she's cute...
Listen, Garmie.
If you're not sure whether she's the one, you're more
than welcome to think it over and come back later.
You don't have to decide right away.
He's got a point. Why don't you bring
your parent or guardian to the shop sometime?
Adopting a pet is a big commitment.
We ought to sit down and discuss it seriously.
My guardian...?
FAIRY
TAILS
DAYS LATER...
Guardian, reporting for duty.
Welcome. I am the manager
of Fairy Tails, Namikaze Samei.
Are you here about Garmie's pet?
Yup. Nice to meetcha.
Who the hell—?!
Relax, it's just my dad.
He only gets dressed up
like this for important meetings.
If I wore my usual outfit,
it might distract from the conversation.
Y'know, you might want to consider applying
that logic to your everyday life...
Did I miss something?
Unfortunately, I can't remain in
this form for long periods of time...
Why not?!
Now, let's get started!
"Heart-Pounding, Super Serious
Conversation Paradise," go!
His mask is already beginning to slip...
Facts About Bunny Rabbits
Diet: Grasses
Netherland dwarf
Now, let me ask you this...
In your opinion, Miss Liza,
Facts About Bunny Rabbits
Diet: Grasses
Netherland dwarf
Holland lop
can Garmie handle the responsibilities and
challenges involved in caring for a pet?
Netherland dwarf
Holland lop
Yeah, she can. I guarantee it.
The bunny over there...
She's the one you mentioned, right?
Does this means you've made up your mind?
To be honest, I'm still kind of worried...
I like her a lot right now,
but the other bunnies are cute, too...
And that's not even counting cats and dogs...
And hedgehogs, and hamsters...
So long as it's fluffy, I'd be happy with any of 'em!
'Cause when I see the fluffy,
I turn into an indiscriminate, feral fluff fiend!
You don't need to stress out about that!
Picking a pet can be tough.
I mean, they're all adorable!
It's okay if nothing stands out
about them when you first meet.
A-Are you sure...?
It doesn't have to be dramatic
or destiny or anything.
The longer you live together,
the more special your pet becomes.
At first, even Yozora was no
different from any other cat.
But as time went on, I began to see
his strong points and his charm.
And then one day, it hit me!
This cat...
He may very well be
the cutest animal in the universe!
Ah, to think that the world's most precious creature
would land on my doorstep...
Oh, so you're one of those pet parents...
Well... you wouldn't be able to say that if you had
any idea just how adorable my darling Momo is...
Oh, really...? Do you honestly believe she stands
a chance against Yozora's unfathomable cuteness?
Is there any particular animal that
you think is cute, Mr. Namikaze?
Personally, I shower my love
upon all cute animals equally.
Wow... You mean like acid rain?
Why acid rain...?
What do you think, Luster?
Huh?
We're gonna be living together
as a family from now on!
Do you think she's a good fit?
Or do you like a different one?
Oh, uh, well...
So long as you don't mind me being there.
I half-expected you to kick me out for
coughing and sneezing loudly all the time...
I'd never do something like that!
And we can battle your allergies along the way!
Fine by me. I don't know why,
but I feel like I can relate to her...
If we bring her home...
I have no doubt she'll be happy, too.
When you're an outcast, you enjoy being alone.
But still, having someone by your side
who accepts you for who you are...
It's like a ray of sunshine, warm and comforting...
I can't say for sure whether
she feels the same way, though...
That settles it.
We'd like this little cutie to join our family!
You can count on us to take care of her!
Yeah! I won't let my allergies get in the way!
These kids give me hope for the future!
Yeah... I think they're going to do just fine.
Alright, then.
Her life... is officially in your hands!
Now, class is in session!
Here's everything you'll need to know
about living with a bunny!
Let's get started!
Ensuring bunnies lead
comfortable and fulfilling lives...
it's the "Heart-Pounding Super Secret
Bunny-Wunny High School!"
I'll be quizzing you on this stuff later, got it?!
Facts About Bunny Rabbits
Netherland dwarf
Holland lop
Facts About Bunny Rabbits
Netherland dwarf
Holland lop
Facts About Bunny Rabbits
Netherland dwarf
Holland lop
Facts About Bunny Rabbits
Netherland dwarf
Holland lop
Facts About Bunny Rabbits
Netherland dwarf
Holland lop
Facts About Bunny Rabbits
Netherland dwarf
Holland lop
Facts About Bunny Rabbits
Netherland dwarf
Holland lop
Facts About Bunny Rabbits
Netherland dwarf
Holland lop
Facts About Bunny Rabbits
Netherland dwarf
Holland lop
Anyone who fails will not
be allowed to adopt a bunny!
B-But Professor Namikaze... we can't retain
any information if you distract us like that!
Overcoming that distraction is part of the test!
How does that help us take care of a bunny...?
{
CONGRATULATIONS!
}
You passed!!
Congratulations! You passed!
So that's what you meant by "eccentric..."
Eccentric, but a good person.
Well, I'm rooting for you.
And I'm here if you ever need help.
You should probably start thinking of a name.
I already picked out the perfect name!
"Hinata." Y'know, like "sunshine!"
Oh, I get it.
After Luster's clever little analogy from earlier.
Hey, don't say it like that! It's embarrassing...
It's nice to meet you, Hinata!
From now on, this is your new home, Hinata!
Ahh, she's drinking her water!
Oh, wow... She's so smart!
Be sure to give her some space until
she adjusts to her new environment, okay?
It's best not to take her out of
her cage for the first week or so.
Roger that!
I guess we'll have to adjust
to the new environment, too.
Yeah.
Oh, I know! We should take a video!
Then we can post it on YanTube.
I'm surprised, Garmie.
I didn't realize you were into that.
Of course!
I wanna share Hinata's cuteness with
everyone in the whole wide world!
Plus, it's gonna serve as proof...
...that bunnies are the most
precious animals in the universe!
ONE WEEK LATER
Are Garmie and Luster taking
good care of their little bunny pal?
Yup, they've been working hard with
the help of Namikaze and Sakihito.
I don't think we need to worry about them for now.
Except...
Garmie's completely and
utterly obsessed with bunnies now...
Well, of course she is. She's a proud new parent.
Is something bothering you?
At this rate, it's very possible that she might
challenge me and my love for cats someday...
And when she does,
I have no doubt she'll try to spread this idea of
"bunnies are cuter than cats" across the galaxy!
Bunnies are the most adorable
creatures in existence!
I can't just sit back and let that happen.
I'll have to take action. I must make the gloriousness
of cats known to the entire universe...
And by then, it'll be too late.
No one will be able to stop it...
A battle for cuteness supremacy will break out,
and every galaxy in outer space will get sucked into it!
No... The battle has already begun, I fear...
Uh-huh, whatever you say...
You want to learn how to shoot a video?
Yes! I've posted videos on YanTube before,
but no matter what I do, they don't turn out good...
We were hoping you'd teach us how you do it, Kaoru.
Well, I don't mind showing you how I film stuff,
but if you're looking for tips on
how to get views, I can't help you.
I'm guessing there's no quick
and easy shortcut for that...
Plus, given how chill and docile she is,
it might not make for very engaging content...
Why the heck not?! She's frickin' adorable!!
She's so YanTube-able, it's not even funny!!
Okay, sorry! Let's just start the filming part.
Today, we let Hinata out of her
cage for the first time!
Still feeling nervous, huh?
Aw, isn't she cute?
Who's a fluffy wittle bunny-wunny? You are!
Calm down!
Don't shove the camera in her face, Garmie!
Give her some—
Are you okay, Luster?!
I'm fine...
In fact, I want you to document
the state of pure bliss I'm in...
Why would anyone watch a video like that?!
Alright, I'mma head out. Good luck.
What?!
But we haven't even done anything yet!
Please, Kaoru...!
Nope, no way! This whole thing
is way above my paygrade!
But every single video I've posted so far has
gotten stuck in Single-Digit View Count Hell!
Well, what did you expect when
your videos look like garbage?!
I'm begging you!
C'mon, we even prepared
a little present to show our gratitude!
I don't want a present, so just let me go!
Hey there... Everything okay?
Huh?!
I invited Komachi over to hang out!
I figured that'd make you happy,
so... here's your present! Enjoy!
H-Huh...?
Q-Quit treating Kokage like
she's some sort of peace offering!
Still... I'd be lying if I said
I wasn't excited to see her...
He totally just said the quiet part out loud...!
She's really chill, isn't she?
We've been recording for quite some time now...
If I didn't know any better,
I'd have sworn it was a screenshot...
Maybe she's scared since
there's a lot of people around...
I guess that's our cue to—
No, she's just laid-back, that's all!
When we first opened up her cage...
she came hopping right out
without any hesitation or fear.
Even after you came over, Kaoru, she sat there
all calm like, "This has nothing to do with me..."
Let me go!
Please help us! Come on!
She lives life at her own pace!
We just have to let her do whatever she wants!
Look, she moved!
Well, when you put it that way,
she seems more dignified...
Alright, then we'll title the video: "The Bunny Who Won't
Budge on Her Very First Stroll Around the House."
How's that?
That's perfect!
Hinata doesn't need to change a thing.
Her mellow personality is part of her charm!
But I'm worried she won't get enough exercise...
Do you think she'll play with her toys once
she gets a bit more comfortable...?
What if we focus on that side of her?
Huh?
We can just leave the camera on the tripod for now.
We'll add subtitles and an audio track
on top of the footage.
You two are good at putting Hinata's charm into words,
so let's use that to our advantage.
Like a how-to video,
but for showing off Hinata's cuteness!
That way, instead of talking while filming,
we can have a relaxing, no-pressure chat.
You'll have to learn how to use editing software
and stuff, so it might get tricky...
Oh, it looks pretty self-explanatory.
They're geniuses when it comes
to everything except cute animals...
Hinata won't budge on her very first stroll around the house
In this clip, Hinata's wide awake!
She hadn't gone to bed yet.
If you look closely, she's moving ever-so-slowly.
Watching the footage back makes me kinda sleepy,
but it's kinda theraputic.
People watching this might get the impression
that she's a plush toy or something.
Her nose is the only part of her
that never stops twitching!
What if we film a close-up of her nose
and use a PIP effect?
Why would we need a PIP for that...?
Wh-Whoa... You talked nonstop for thirty minutes?
Actually, we talked for closer to an hour.
I barely said two words the entire time...
That's okay! Your soft-spoken personality
is part of your charm!
It's starting to get some likes.
We're happy with how it turned out!
And it's all thanks to Professor Kaoru!
I hope lots of people take the time to watch it!
If we show the world even just
a fraction of Hinata's cuteness,
then we'll be a little bit more like you! Right, Liza?
Huh? Oh, uh... sure.
We've gotta work hard, Luster!
Right!
"A battle for supremacy between bunnies and cats...?"
They're doing their best...
Just be happy for 'em, Liza.
What's your next video going to be?
So, our plan for the next one...
wotchi wotchi are wa nanda? seimeitai no "se"!
Watch, watch, what's that I see? A lively lifeform!
saachi saachi moshikashite tomodachi ka?
Search, search, do you wanna be friends?
nyanboree nyanboree nyanboree nyanboree de
Myamboree! Myamboree! Myamboree! Myamboree! So...
moffii! moffii!
Fwuffy! Fwuffy!
nyanboree nyanboree nyanboree nyanboree de
Myamboree! Myamboree! Myamboree! Myamboree! So...
moffii! moffii!
Fwuffy! Fwuffy!
nyaa
Meow!
kawaii wa seigi sonja sonja aku to wa nan zo?
Cuteness is justice! So what are the evils standin' in its way?
urusai mama? kenka? shukudai? osouji?
Mom being naggy? Getting into fights? Homework? Cleaning?
kokoronai hitotachi ga afureteiru zo
There's a lotta cruel people out there
nakayoku shitekunakya muu muu da!
Better get along or you'll be a grumpypants!
chikyuu wa fushigi na toko de kaiseki taihen
Earth's a strange planet, and studying it's a pain
risou dake ja omanma taberenai ga
But just thinking about it won't put food on the table!
nishin geppo shikou sakugo
Through steady effort and trial and error
teinei ni tema hima kakeru no ga, otoshidokoro!
Give it a go and your hard work will pay off!
wotchi wotchi are wa nanda? seimeitai no "se"!
Watch, watch, what's that I see? A lively lifeform!
mikke mikke UTOPIA kamo?
I spy, I spy, a utopia?
doukaina?
There's no way, right?
nyanboree de waai! yatta ne nyanboree de uu!
Myamboree, hurray! Yippee! Myamboree, whoo!
muzukashii koto wa chotto oyasumi nanoda
We deserve a break after all that hard work
ashita mata ganbarou tte iettara OK!
As long as we promise we'll get back to it tomorrow, it's A-OK!
choi sawagi shichaou!
Let's have a party!
sore ga sunawachi heiwa tte yatsu janai?
That's what peace is all about, no?
iizo! moffi-ffii fuwafuwa ni
Alright! Fwuffy-ffy, dive right in
moffi-ffi tobikondara
Fwuffy-ffy, right into the fluff
ai tte yatsu ga wakari sou desu
And you'll start to know what love really means
totte oki no nukumori de
Lovingly conceal me
meromero ni tsutsundene moffii
In all that warmth of yours, so fwuffy
san, ni, ichi... kyou mo otsukaresama!
3, 2, 1... Good work today!
goronago chokomaka chochoi to goshujin
Catnapping nonstop, one second, Master
omimi wo haishaku, hidari kara nyaa
I need you for a sec, gimme your left ear-Meow!
nyanboree nyanboree nyanboree nyanboree de
Myamboree! Myamboree! Myamboree! Myamboree! So...
moffii! moffii!
Fwuffy! Fwuffy!
nyaa
Meow!
A girl named Akaneko shares images
of a beautiful cat with the world.
Liza learns the secret to her success
and uncovers the ultimate technique.
Next time, Episode 10: "Trending."