Azatoth Empire, Thrale Research Vessel
Ship Bridge
Look, we may as well destroy this planet.
Their civilization is far too primitive.
Let's just deploy the ToxiCloud
and purge all its lifeforms.
Reduce it all to just minerals and water.
Slow down there, Liza.
Every planet has its own unique charms.
Cultures, ideologies, nature, history...
It may be hiding something
of use to us, after all.
M
S
Tp
Thrale Deputy Commander
Thrl
Thrac
Thrale Deputy Commander
Thrale X
Thrale Dk
Thrale Deputy Commander
Thrale Depn
Thrale Depuf
Thrale Deputy Commander
Thrale Deputy D
Thrale Deputy Coq
Thrale Deputy Commander
Thrale Deputy Commn
Thrale Deputy Commak
Thrale Deputy Commander
Thrale Deputy Commandj
B
K
Ad
Amat Roy
Ax
Amf
Amat Roy
Amr
Ama&
Amat Roy
Amay
Amat M
Amat T
Amat Re
Amat Roy
Amat Rz
Amat Roh
Amat Roy
Amat Roc
And out of all Azatoth's researchers,
you're the most astute.
It seems unremarkable from the outside, yes.
But that's exactly why we need your expertise.
Hy
Head Researcher
Her
Heaq
Head Researcher
Head R&
Head Rel
Head Researcher
Head Resx
Head Resed
Head Researcher
Head Reseag
Head Researcf
Head Researcher
Head Researchz
Head Researchep
Head Researcher
T
R
Lk
Liza Luna
Ln
Lih
Liza Luna
Lir
Lizi
Liza Luna
Liza G
Liza Z
Liza Lt
Liza Luna
Liza Lue
Liza Lud
Liza Lunr
Liza Luna
Liza Lun%
The Azatoth Empire's reign spans
a myriad of stars and planets.
And now, they've got their sights set on Planet Earth...
Something useful? Oh please, that's not possible.
This planet is a glorified trash heap.
The planet's lifeforms lack severely in intelligence,
indicative of a philistine civilization.
I can already tell it's the most
underdeveloped planet I've ever studied.
These people possess knowledge
that eludes my understanding?
Yeah, as if.
Ugh, this stinks...
I say we just activate the Supergravitron
and flatten the entire thing.
We're interested in what their cuisine is like.
Can you locate a suitable establishment?
Sure, whatever.
A café? They ought to have snacks.
Works for me.
Cat
Hello there! Welcome to the Nyanday Cat Café.
"Cat café?"
Cat... café. Cat...?
It's 500 yen for 30 minutes,
Cat... Cat...?
and extension prices are listed right over here.
Sure, no problem.
Okay then, please follow me.
Cat.
Cat...? Cat...
What in the world is a cat?
Please be careful when you enter the room
as they have a tendency to escape.
...iss?
Miss...?
Miss!
Um, I need to close the door
or the kitties will escape...
Is something wrong?
I-I...
Wh-What are...these...creatures?
Huh? Well, uh... Oh.
This little fellow is an
American Shorthair named Hajime.
A-And that's a...type of cat?
Y-Yes, it is...
Oh! Miss, did you perhaps mistake us for
a normal café when you walked in?
Just what the hell are these creatures?!
These cats...
Impossible... Impossible!
These creatures, they're just so...
Cute! They're way too cute!
Impossible! They're the most
spectacular organisms I've ever seen!
There's no way...! Just look at that shape!
Their soft tufts of fur, their physique!
Even the noises they make are cute!
My brain's gonna explode!!!
I've studied over 66 trillion species
of intergalactic lifeforms,
but these beings surpass them all in every way!
Manneloo
They make the top three universally adored creatures
look like the scrawlings of a kindergartener!
Manneloo
Dohftsus
Zoola
Here's the drink you ordered.
Th-Thanks.
T-The drink is about average...
I suspect the cuisine isn't
the main attraction of this establishment.
The customers come here for these creatures.
These cats.
If cats are this adorable,
then humans must surely worship them.
I must know more!
Um, you've been really nervous this entire time.
Are you perhaps afraid of cats?
No, it's just...
This is my first time.
Ah, visiting a cat café?
No. Meeting a cat.
Huh?
I know nothing about them.
Y'see, I'm not human.
O-Oh really...?
Th-Then that would make you an alien, right?
Wow! I've never met an alien in person before!
He's playing along 'cause he thinks I'm delusional...
Is he a pushover...?
Well, I don't mind that.
Approximately just how many
cats live on Planet Earth?
They must be a pretty rare species.
Around 100 in total? Or closer to 200?
If I recall correctly, there are
over ten million cats in Japan alone.
Ten million?!
And the number of domestic
cats increases every year.
I own one myself.
Domestic?!
Y-You can... keep them as pets?!
No way, he can't be serious...
Coming home to a cat in your house?!
What is this, some sort of fairyland?!
And they're all over the country?!
I wanna quit my job, blow off all my responsibilities,
and hang out with cats all day long!
How am I supposed to resist
that kind of temptation?!
What the hell's wrong with these Earthlings?!
They're very sweet!
They wander on over when they want attention
and then turn into big babies when you pet them.
Spoiled, aren't they?
You've gotta be kitten me...
They usually keep to themselves,
but they like to act silly sometimes.
Isn't that just the cutest thing?
But how? How can something so lovable exist?!
How cute!
When I was growing up...
All the things I was obsessed with...
Cute!
It's adorable!
M-Miss...?
Everything I've ever loved
pales in comparison to them...
The creatures on this planet... These cats...
From an evolutionary standpoint,
they're the ultimate species!
I-I mean, all animals are cute in their own ways...
You idiot!
My entire life has just
been flipped upside down!
M-Miss... I must ask you to lower your voice.
Otherwise the poor kitties will get scared...
Huh?!
S-Sorry! It was an accident...
I had no idea they were
such delicate creatures...
Had I known they feel stress...
I wish you told me earlier!
My apologies.
SHOOK
No, no... It's my own fault. I'm sorry...
How's it going, Liza?
Have ya found anything interesting yet?
N-Not really!
Is it okay for me to tell them
about these creatures...?
No, not yet... It's too dangerous.
Cats take cuteness to a whole 'nother level!
And the captain... He goes nuts over animals!
There, there. Aren't you just the cutest?
Are there any cute animals
at all, my dear Liza?
P
G
Td
Thrale Captain
Thx
Thre
Thrale Captain
Thraz
Thralq
Thrale Captain
Thrale V
Thrale Cw
Thrale Captain
Thrale Cj
Thrale Caz
Thrale Captain
Thrale Cap%
Thrale Captf
Thrale Captain
Thrale Captar
Thrale Captaib
Thrale Captain
X
Mo
Mikitty Fulpulring
Mir
Mikih
Mikitty Fulpulring
Mikitf
Mikittz
Mikitty Fulpulring
Mikitty Y
Mikitty Fug
Mikitty Fulpulring
Mikitty Fulw
Mikitty Fulpa
Mikitty Fulpulring
Mikitty Fulpue
Mikitty Fulpulm
Mikitty Fulpulring
Mikitty Fulpulrq
Mikitty Fulpulrih
Mikitty Fulpulring
Mikitty Fulpulrin&
N-N-Nope, none at all!
Trust me! There's absolutely none.
Then shall we deploy the ToxiCloud
and purge the planet of its lifeforms?
Hold on a sec! Not just yet!
What kind of tech is that? Could she really be an alien...?
But you just said—
I've only just started my investigation here!
Be patient, okay? I'm sure I'll find
something useful around here!
Bye for now!
Sorry for raising my voice again...
Are the cats alright?
Th-They're fine.
Wh-Why's it staring at me...?
What do I do...?!
I think he wants your attention.
Please feel free to pet him. He adores scratches.
See? Just like this.
Give...
Give
Give...?
me
a break
Give me a break!
me
a break
Just looking at it is making
my heart throb painfully!
If my heart gets any more excited,
I have no idea what will happen!
It's touching me...
It put its foot on me...
Oh, this is not good...
I've been backed into a corner...
What's with this softness,
this pleasant sensation...?
I've never felt anything like it!
This is it...
This is how I die!
C'mon, Hajime.
No murdering the customers.
Without its weight on my body, I feel empty inside...
Make up your mind...
Does it have something stuck
to the bottom of its foot?
It had a weird texture—
The bottom of his foot?
You mean his paw pad?
Its little feets are so precious!!!
MEOW~
M-Miss?!
I... can't take anymore...
It's just... too darn cute...!
a
ri
e
nai
Impossible...
ki
ka
ku
gai
Unprecedented...
ta
ma
ra
nai
Out of this world...
We run into each other on the catwalk
BLACK
HOLE
Your eyes suck me in like a black hole
tsun
tsun
da
You act so cold but flaunt your stuff
Why the hell is my heart racing?
They're saying it'll rain this afternoon
So maybe I should have an early lunch
ba
cchi
I see you gleaming in the sunlight
What an angel
I'll always be under your paw
My love for you warps the space-time continuum
You quickly become the center of my universe
do
kkun
ba
de
Ba-dump, ker-thump
I just can't take it anymore...
Forget fate or miracles
BANG
Us crossing paths was a big bang
Every star across the night sky is our miracle
I don't want my love to go to your head
I just want you to stay with me...
#1. Impossible
Cat
By the way,
an alien came into the café yesterday.
Y
H
Sr
Seiji Mukai
Sep
Seif
Seiji Mukai
Seiju
Seiji O
Seiji T
Seiji Mb
Seiji Mukai
Seiji Mud
Seiji Mukc
Seiji Mukai
Seiji Mukal
Seriously? That's surprising.
Never thought I'd hear good ol'
Stone-faced Mukai tell a joke.
J
Kp
Kasumi Yanagi
Ka@
Kasw
Kasumi Yanagi
Kasue
Kasumd
Kasumi Yanagi
Kasumi &
Kasumi K
Kasumi Yx
Kasumi Yanagi
Kasumi Yah
Kasumi Yans
Kasumi Yanagi
Kasumi Yanav
Kasumi Yanag!
Kasumi Yanagi
Look, I didn't believe it at first either.
But she used some sort
of strange communication device,
and she passed out when she saw Hajime's paw pad.
How come?
It was "too cute," apparently.
Cat
Oh, that's her right there.
What?
Wh-What the hell's with this creature?!
Why's it chasing after me?!
Because of this ball...? Is this what it's after?!
C-Come back, Mamehiko!
A creature that wags its fluffy tail
and runs after a toy?!
Oh, my god... It's...
so frickin' cute!
I-I'm so sorry! The leash slipped out of my hand!
Jeez, I can't believe you ran off like that...
He must've thought you were playing with him
since you picked up the ball.
What is that thing...?
It's, uh... called a "dog."
A dog!
Oh, not again... My heart can't
deal with this much excitement...
I need to sit down for a minute.
Sure, no problem...
CAT
DOG
Surrounded by cats on one side
and dogs on the other!
DOG
CAT
It's a nice problem to have, isn't it?
Wow, she might actually be an alien.
Her reaction is certainly out of this world!
Miss Alien, was that your first time meeting a dog?
Yeah...
And their cuteness could destroy
the space-time continuum...
Dogs are adorable, aren't they?
Up until recently, they outranked cats as
the number one most popular household pet.
Number one?! Over cats?!
It's the age-old argument of cats versus dogs.
Some people feel very strongly about
which one makes the better companion.
That makes sense...
Their furry little bodies are
instantly recognizable from afar...
And they're always full of energy!
Just looking at them puts a smile on my face!
Mamehiko!
And when they wag their tails?
Don't get me started on that!
Dogs are a completely different type of cute!
When dogs wag their tails,
it's usually a sign that they're happy!
What?!
Preposterous...
They wag their tails when they're happy?
Omigosh, they're way too precious...!
And they tend to bounce off the walls
when they're in the mood to play.
Y'know, I have a dog of my own.
Maybe it's my imagination, but I really
feel like we understand one another!
It's the whole "man's best friend" thing, I guess?
I find that having a cat in the house relaxes me.
Their independent nature is
a refreshing change of pace!
My dog comes running to the door when I get home.
Th-This is the Great Cats vs. Dogs Debate!
It's just the cutest thing!
My cat greets me at the door sometimes.
A multidimensional feud if ever there was one!
But the "sometimes" is key!
That's what makes it special!
Hey, Miss Alien. What's your name?
I'm Kasumi Yanagi.
It's Liza. Liza Luna.
Well then, Liza...
You want to learn more about dogs, right?
Huh?
If so, you should drop by my place!
I'll introduce you to my darling dog!
Huh?
Unless you get up close and personal,
you'll never truly appreciate how great dogs are!
You have to pet them and play with them!
A tempting offer,
but I don't know if my heart could take it...!
Dogs are great and everything...
But cats are just as cute!
Bah! What am I so afraid of anyway?
It's the perfect opportunity to study how these organisms live and get along with the Earthlings!
We haven't even scratched the surface yet!
Somebody's a sore loser...
You've got a point...
Alright then, I'll take you up on your offer.
Well, here we are!
Stay calm. There's no need to panic.
At this point,
there's nothing that could surprise me—
Masamune!
Were you waiting for me to get home?
What a sweet boy!
It's huge!!
Jeez, you scared me!
Wait... Hold on a minute!
Why's it so big?!
No one told me they could be that big!
And it's a completely different shape!
Are you sure it's a dog?!
He's a large breed known as a "golden retriever"!
G-Golden what...?
Now, now...
Don't be rude, Chiffon.
It's tiny!!
And she's a small breed known as a "toy poodle"!
Why are there a million different varieties?!
It's been several days since
you began your investigation...
I was told you had nothing
to report yesterday either.
Let me guess, you're going to tell me
their planet is insigificant.
And then, despite your insistence,
you'll find some kind of merit to it.
Whoa, slow down...
I appreciate how nauseatingly well you know me...
But we can't rush these things.
My work is a very delicate process...
I see. Well, the Azatoth army
has faith in you, as do I.
We're counting on you.
I'm not slacking off...
He probably thinks that
since I spend most of my time here.
But it's for research purposes, I swear...
Right...
I'm supposed to be working, yet I always
end up here instead... dying to see the cats...
What on earth am I doing?!
Move, stupid legs!
Get me out of this café and off to work!
Quit slacking on the job! I need to earn money!
Wooooork!
I know you're having a moment,
but could you do it more quietly?
Oh my god... If I keep thinking about cats,
I'm going to lose interest in everything else...
Every last brain cell taken over by cats...
Responsibilities
Cats... and dogs, too...
You were like a kid in a
candy store at my place yesterday!
Stop! Please, I'm begging you!
Don't be shy... Let your body do the talking...
If you hold out your hand and say, "Shake!"
he'll put his little paw right on top of it.
Y-You're lying! No animal could be that smart!
See? Masamune's waiting for you!
Sh-Shake...!
Aww, what a good boy!
He's the bestest boy!!
You guys are used to it,
so it probably seemed like an overreaction...
But from my perspective,
Earthlings are the weird ones!
How do you manage to stay calm around
something so cute and cuddly?!
Wait... Does this planet have other animals
on the same level as cats and dogs?
Hmm, let's see here...
We've got plenty of different species...
But in terms of pets,
cats and dogs are definitely the top two.
There aren't many others on the same level...
Phew...
I mean, rabbits are pretty cute.
Oh, and hamsters. They're small and adorable!
Ferrets also make great pets, don'tcha think?
Fer—?
I think hedgehogs are neat.
Hedge—?
Y'know, I'm kinda interested in degus...
Deg—?
What about birds? Like parakeets and cockatoos.
Bird—?
Oh, and owls.
Some people keep goldfish or tropical fish.
Gold—?
Reptiles are cool, too!
Rep—?
There are cute wild animals, too! Koalas,
capybaras, sea otters, penguins, red pandas and...
Holy moly, that's a lot...
This frickin' planet is messed up.
Let's take a trip to the zoo, Liza!
Are you trying to kill me?!
But researching Earth's animals
is a part of your job, right?
Well, I should probably
familiarize myself with them...
She's enjoying this, isn't she?
Okay, fine! Then show me some ugly animals first!
Wh-What...?
That might be easier said than done...
World Reference Guide
ANIMALS
Let's see...
Nope, gorillas fall into the "cute" category...
World Reference Guide
ANIMALS
Oh god, the one on the cover!!!
World Reference Guide
ANIMALS
She passed out again.
No way... There's just no way...
How can something so
monochromatic be so adorable...?
It doesn't exist, right?
Please tell me it's a mythical creature...
World Reference Guide
ANIMALS
It's called a "panda."
Endangered, yes. Mythical, no.
PENGUIN
Hedgehog
DEGU
FERRET
Gorilla
Capybara
PARAKEET
Cockatoo
RED PANDA
GOLDFISH
KOALA
Sorry for making you drag me out of the café...
Well, we can't exactly let you live in there...
Wow... I didn't accomplish anything
in terms of work today...
Y'see? That's why we oughtta go to the zoo!
You can see pandas in real life!
Er, I don't think I'm ready for that just—
Look.
Take me
home
There's a cat inside this box!
Someone must've dumped him.
What a cruel thing to do...
Is he alive?
Yeah... But he's in a pretty bad shape.
"Dumped"...? Some people abandon their animals?
Unfortunately...
I just don't understand
how someone could be so cruel!
Given his condition, I wouldn't be surprised if they never took care of him in the first place.
Irresponsible pet owners are the—
Is that so?
Stand back for a moment.
Scanning for organic lifeforms.
Take me
home
Diagnosis: severe malnutrition. Lifeform is unclassified.
Rehabilitation method is unknown.
How will you proceed?
Freeze time in the surrounding area
to preserve the lifeform.
Supply as much nourishment
from epithelial cells as possible.
Search brain waves, retinal afterimages,
and residual tissues for the original owner.
Data located.
Shut yer freakin' trap, wouldja?
I ain't got any grub for ya!
It's your cat, isn't it?
I don't care. It doesn't listen to anythin' I say!
Then dump it somewhere.
Black cats are eyesores anyway.
Good point.
I have pinpointed the location
of the individuals in question.
I want them to feel the pain they caused.
Rehabilitation status: complete.
So... is he going to be okay now?
I think so.
We should take him to
an emergency vet just in case.
Huh? Wh-What...?
Wait, what's going on?! Wh-Why's it doing that?!
I think he likes you.
What?!
He's probably grateful you saved his life.
I-I doubt it.
Even if it does like me,
that doesn't really change... anything...
What do you think about keeping him, Liza?
Huh? Keep it? Me?!
Nope, nope, not a chance!
I can't be around something so adorable 24/7!
I'm losing my mind over the fact that it likes me,
and you want me to bring it in with me?
When you meow at me with that sad little voice...
How the hell am I supposed to refuse?!
How unusual...
You're not one to call for an artillery strike.
Did you get into a fight with an Earthling?
Not really...
Well, I made sure your request was authorized.
Is the Earthside outpost sufficient?
Yeah... It's fine.
Then why isn't your camera turned on?
Eh, no reason...
Did something happen?
O-Of course not! Uh... I'm just getting changed!
Since when do you care about modesty?
My modesty is none of your business!
Hey, Liza?
I'm hearing a weird noise in the background...
A noise? I don't hear anything on my end.
Uh-oh, you're breaking up! I'll call you later!
What's wrong? You miss Liza?
Don't be ridiculous.
Everything will be fine!
She's an honest person deep down.
At the end of the day, Liza always gets the job done.
Yes, but that's not what worries me...
Something doesn't seem right. Specifically...
...this noise in her transmission audio.
As the Director of Telecommunications,
what do you think about this noise?
It's not interference...
And it doesn't sound artificial either.
An animal's cry, perhaps?
You're saying it's a language of some sort?
I don't know... I've never heard it before.
But listening to it gives me this...
prickly feeling in my chest.
Yes...
I feel strangely unsettled and
can't help but listen to it repeatedly.
According to Liza's report, animals on Planet Earth
possess somewhat peculiar characteristics...
Well... Let's hope nothing too
out of the ordinary happens...
I might be trapped in this room forever...!
wotchi wotchi are wa nanda? seimeitai no "se"!
Watch, watch, what's that I see? A lively lifeform!
saachi saachi moshikashite tomodachi ka?
Search, search, do you wanna be friends?
nyanboree nyanboree nyanboree nyanboree de
Myamboree! Myamboree! Myamboree! Myamboree! So...
moffii! moffii!
Fwuffy! Fwuffy!
nyanboree nyanboree nyanboree nyanboree de
Myamboree! Myamboree! Myamboree! Myamboree! So...
moffii! moffii!
Fwuffy! Fwuffy!
nyaa
Meow!
kawaii wa seigi sonja sonja aku to wa nan zo?
Cuteness is justice! Somethin' wrong with that?
urusai mama? kenka? shukudai? osouji?
Mom being naggy? Get into a fight? Homework? Cleaning?
kokoronai hitotachi ga afureteiru zo
There's a lotta cruel people out there
nakayoku shitekunakya muu muu da!
Better get along or you'll be a grumpypants!
chikyuu wa fushigi na toko de kaiseki taihen
Earth's a strange planet, and studying it's a pain
risou dake ja omanma taberenai ga
But just thinking about it won't put food on the table!
nishin geppo shikou sakugo
Through steady effort and trial and error
teinei ni tema hima kakeru no ga, otoshidokoro!
Give it a go and your hard work will pay off!
wotchi wotchi are wa nanda? seimeitai no "se"!
Watch, watch, what's that I see? A lively lifeform!
mikke mikke UTOPIA kamo?
I spy, I spy, a utopia?
doukaina?
There's no way, right?
nyanboree de waai! yatta ne nyanboree de uu!
Myamboree, hurray! Yippee! Myamboree, whoo!
muzukashii koto wa chotto oyasumi nanoda
We deserve a break after all that hard work
ashita mata ganbarou tte iettara OK!
As long as we promise we'll get back to it tomorrow, it's A-OK!
choi sawagi shichaou!
Let's have a party!
sore ga sunawachi heiwa tte yatsu janai?
That's what peace is all about, no?
iizo! moffi-ffii fuwafuwa ni
Alright! Fwuffy-ffy, dive right in
moffi-ffi tobikondara
Fwuffy-ffy, right into the fluff
ai tte yatsu ga wakari sou desu
And you'll start to know what love really means
totte oki no nukumori de
Lovingly conceal me
meromero ni tsutsundene moffii
In all that warmth of yours, so fwuffy
san, ni, ichi... kyou mo otsukaresama!
3, 2, 1... Good work today!
goronago chokomaka chochoi to goshujin
Catnapping nonstop, one second, Master
omimi wo haishaku, hidari kara nyaa
I need you for a sec, gimme your left ear-Meow!
nyanboree nyanboree nyanboree nyanboree de
Myamboree! Myamboree! Myamboree! Myamboree! So...
moffii! moffii!
Fwuffy! Fwuffy!
nyaa
Meow!
Liza, a researcher from outer space,
reluctantly decides to move in with a cat.
But in doing so,
she becomes the cat's lowly servant.
Next time, Episode 2: "Trapped."