The Azatoth Empire's reign spans
a myriad of stars and planets.
And now, they've got their
sights set on Planet Earth...
It happened in the middle of the night,
when most people were fast asleep in their beds...
I found myself tortured by an overwhelming urge.
And soon succumbed to it.
As Yozora opened his mouth for a yawn...
I stuck my finger inside!!
No, I've been captured!
The reason that cats yawn...
is to set a trap to capture their owners!
Owners... ners... ners...
Sounds like the happiest trap in the universe.
Wait, no, hold up.
I'm not finished telling the story yet.
Later, while I was taking a bath...
Yozora was in turmoil.
He clearly wanted to come next to me, but
his strong fear of water was fighting against that urge!
Scared
Wanna
go
Scared
Wanna
go
Scared
Wanna
go
Scared
Wanna
go
Scared
Wanna
go
Scared
Wanna
go
Scared
Wanna
go
Scared
Wanna
go
Scared
Wanna
go
Scared
Wanna
go
Scared
Wanna
go
Scared
Wanna
go
Scared
Wanna
go
Scared
Wanna
go
Scared
Wanna
go
Scared
Wanna
go
Scared
Wanna
go
Scared
Wanna
go
Scared
Wanna
go
Scared
Wanna
go
Scared
Wanna
go
Scared
Wanna
go
Scared
Wanna
go
Scared
Wanna
go
Scared
Wanna
go
Scared
Wanna
go
Scared
Wanna
go
Scared
Wanna
go
Scared
Wanna
go
Scared
Wanna
go
Scared
Wanna
go
Scared
Wanna
go
Scared
Wanna
go
Scared
Wanna
go
Scared
Wanna
go
Scared
Wanna
go
Scared
Wanna
go
Scared
Wanna
go
Scared
Wanna
go
Scared
Wanna go
It was the very first time that Yozora
managed to come close to the bathtub.
What's up, Yozora?
Aw jeez! This little guy loves me way too much!
But then...
What Yozora did next was simply unbelievable...
Don't, Yozora!
That's dirty and not good for you!
And then, it finally hit me.
The reason he intentionally
drank the bath water...
The bath water that I was soaking in...
Could it be because our bodies produce
an extract that cats find especially delicious?
They're desperate to get a taste for it and that's why
they always lick us and drink bath water, yeah?
Well, that's an interesting idea...
Anyway, here's what I plan to report back.
"Cats are fond of human extract and feast upon it."
No way!
That's totally going to give them the wrong idea!
Besides, you don't have any
real basis for that theory, right?
And the scrutiny begins...
a
ri
e
nai
Impossible...
ki
ka
ku
gai
Unprecedented...
ta
ma
ra
nai
Out of this world...
We run into each other on the catwalk
BLACK
HOLE
Your eyes suck me in like a black hole
tsun
tsun
da
You act so cold but flaunt your stuff
Why the hell is my heart racing?
They're saying it'll rain this afternoon
So maybe I should have an early lunch
ba
cchi
I see you gleaming in the sunlight
What an angel
I'll always be under your paw
My love for you warps the space-time continuum
You quickly become the center of my universe
do
kkun
ba
de
Ba-dump, ker-thump
I just can't take it anymore...
Forget fate or miracles
BANG
Us crossing paths was a big bang
Every star across the night sky is our miracle
I don't want my love to go to your head
I just want you to stay with me...
#6. Capyballama
So, without further ado...
Let's give Yozora a bath!
Woo!
A bath, huh?
Are you sure it's okay? I'm kinda worried.
Well, we can't help it if he puts up a big fuss.
But cats with long hair need
to be bathed every once in a while.
Even multiple times a year.
Is there a reason you're worried?
Well, you know how cats are.
Sometimes they turn all loose
and supple almost like a liquid.
Which is why I can't help but feel like they might
dissolve into nothing if you put them in water.
I understood you at first,
but you totally lost me in the latter half.
Times when they're almost like a liquid?
I totally get it!
Huh?!
Right?
That's what led to my hypothesis
on cats being afraid of water.
And I've already reported that
back to the mothership.
I told you to check with me
before you report anything!
Crazy to think that cats were actually a liquid.
But how can a liquid be a living creature?
Perhaps it's a liquid with a high viscosity that
allows it to be both fluid and shape-changing.
They apparently dissolve if you put them in water.
But how can you explain such a mechanism?
Per the information in Liza's report, there is a researcher
on Earth who proved that cats are, in fact, liquid,
and apparently won an award in physics for their work.
It was called the "Ig Nobel Prize"
or something to that effect.
Fianna.
Do you also think that cats are a liquid?
I would have to agree. The possibility seems very high,
considering how flexible and soft they are.
I guess there's no room for doubt if you say so.
This is only leading to more questions than answers,
but knowing that water is their weakness is very helpful.
Let's wait for Liza to report back with more information.
A cat's fur isn't designed to repel water
and doesn't dry easily.
That's the reason they hate water so much.
Oh, that explains it!
Welp, guess I gotta amend my report.
Apparently, cats don't like water
because of their body hair. See ya.
But how the hell does a liquid grow hair?!
What about the cat at your place, Komachi?
Does it not do well with bathing?
Yep. My little Maru really hates the bath.
Why hello there, Maru!
I figured that since she came into the bath
by herself, it was okay to give her a little wash.
Argh! Why?!
But she gave me a good smack
after I sprayed her with water.
Why do you sound so happy about it?
I'm gonna try asking some more people.
Do I ever bathe Iroha?
Not exactly, but I have washed
her feet when they've gotten dirty.
She didn't seem especially afraid of the water.
Doesn't seem to be afraid of the water?
I'm betting curiosity got the better of her.
She slapped the water in the wash bowl around,
and then slowly dipped her feet in all by herself.
What is this stuff?
"What is this stuff?"
Is what the expression on her face
said when she looked at me!
How adowwible!
I'm pretty sure that Emmers enjoys taking a bath.
Hold up, "Emmers?"
Let me send you a picture.
Oh wow, she looks like an elegant lady
and an old man at the same time.
I guess the bottom line is
that all cats react differently.
Okay then.
Let's see how Yozora likes it.
Equipment check!
Shampoo!
Towel!
Dryer!
Form up!
The Yozora
Bathing Squad
Form up!
The Yozora
Bathing Squad
Form up!
The Yozora
Bathing Squad
Form up!
The Yozora
Bathing Squad
Form up!
The Yozora
Bathing Squad
Form up!
The Yozora
Bathing Squad
Form up!
The Yozora
Bathing Squad
Form up! The Yozora Bathing Squad!
Form up!
The Yozora
Bathing Squad
Form up!
The Yozora
Bathing Squad
Form up!
The Yozora
Bathing Squad
Form up!
The Yozora
Bathing Squad
And also,
a stretcher for when I inevitably collapse!
You gotta be kidding! I think I'm gonna bail.
Break up!
Form up!
Please don't leave, I need you.
Just calm down, Liza.
Yozora's all fidgety because
he can tell you're stressed out.
Wh-What is it?
He just latched on to you
like he was pleading for help!
So cuuuuuuute!
I give up!
You can't just give up before we even get started!
Never give up!
This girl is beyond hopeless.
Guess it's up to us.
C'mon, Komachi, let's get started.
Roger that.
I'm going to wet you down now, Yozora.
What kind of face is he making?!
I guess he doesn't like it.
He's trying to get away!
Yozora, calm down! Shucks, you cutie pie!
But you know,
he's not making that much of a fuss about it.
His owner's making a bigger fuss than he is.
Since Liza mentioned he came close to
the bath when she was in it,
maybe he feels at ease when they're together.
All right! Let's just wash them together!
O-Okay, go for it!
Come on, don't just give orders!
You have to help wash him, too!
Oh, right.
Can't say I've ever seen someone
bathe a cat like this before...
Sh-Shampoo, please.
Here comes the shampoo, Yozora.
Just hang on a little longer.
Gosh, he's being really well-behaved.
Huh?
But he's been crawling all over me the whole time!
That's relatively calm as far as cats go.
He must feel safe when he's clinging on to you.
Y-You think?
It's time to rinse him off now.
Be extra careful that you don't spray
any water directly on Yozora's face, okay?
Uh, could you be more considerate
of my face too, please?!
Move down a little, Yozora! I can't see anything!
Argh! My hair! He's biting my hair!
Go down! Lower! You gotta get those suds off him!
Down!
To the left!
Stop directing me!
Yozora's not a piñata!
Looks like Yozora's mostly stopped squirming.
He must have gotten used to it, huh?
Pardon me, sir! Please don't use
my face as a relaxation spot!
Get down! Mooooooooove!
Ugh...
I gotta say, bathing cats is a real struggle...
You did great.
Nah, I didn't do much.
The real hard worker was Yozo...
ra?
He's dissolving!!
Oh, thank God. He's back to normal.
No duh.
I guess he doesn't have
any problem with the dryer, huh?
A lot of cats hate it, though.
The loud noise bothers them.
Is that so?
This little guy must be used to a lot of noise.
Probably because his owner is so darn loud.
Gosh, do you think I should start
wearing a mouth gag all the time?
That would just make him more scared of you!
All done.
You're so clean now, Yozora!
Thanks for hanging in there.
I think you deserve a treat.
And thanks to both of you, too.
You were a huge help.
Sure thing.
It was a lot easier than I figured it'd be.
You guys are always saving my butt.
I want to show my appreciation.
Is there anything that
I could get or do for you two?
I can grant just about any wish
imaginable by using my powers.
I know! I want you to help me give Maru a bath!
Yeah, do the same for me and Masamune.
Aw jeez, that's more of a chore
than eradicating all of humanity.
Well then, I'll help you out.
But you don't want anything else?
Not even to travel somewhere?
A trip, huh...
Oh! Why don't we go to a hot springs?
Hot springs? If you want. Are you sure that's all?
Oh yeah! That sounds great!
Yeah, except not a normal one.
This time I suggest...
we go to a capybara hot springs!
A capy-what?
Great idea! Capybaras are the best!
I know, right?
What are they? Another cute animal?!
I can't wait!
Hup.
Is this it?
We're really here!
That was like something out of a sci-fi movie!
Well, we can pretty much go anywhere
as long as I know what the coordinates are.
So, what is this place?
It's the Izu Shaboten Zoo!
Izu Shaboten Zoo
This place is the pioneer
of the capybara open-bath!
Interesting.
Since it's a zoo, there must be
a number of earth animals I can see here.
However,
today's target is none other than the capybara!
Time to go take a look!
And see what bathing capybaras are all about!
Yo! Three adults, stat!
Um, ma'am?!
Wh-What do you think you're doing?
It's dangerous to be walking
around with a blindfold on...
T
V
Are you filming a video for YanTube or something?
Staff
So
Sr
Staff
Stx
Stp
Staff
Staw
Stae
Staff
Stafh
Stafl
Staff
F
T
Co
Chiharu Kumadori
Chz
Chihf
Chiharu Kumadori
Chihas
Chihark
Chiharu Kumadori
Chiharu B
Chiharu Kd
Chiharu Kumadori
Chiharu Kumc
Chiharu Kumar
Chiharu Kumadori
Chiharu Kumadh
Chiharu Kumado&
Chiharu Kumadori
Chiharu Kumadory
I heard this place is home to many cute animals.
But my target for today is only the capybara.
And without this on, I would definitely
collapse before I reach them!
Wh-What should I do?
I don't get the sense she's just goofing around...
Okay, come on. Let's go.
W-Wait! Don't pull me!
So, Liza, you gave up on the blindfold after all?
Yeah.
I didn't want to cause any problems
for the staff or other customers.
What's that?! What's going on?!
They're like a couple
going through a haunted house...
They have llamas here! Look!
Llamas? What are those like?!
Are they cute?! They must be!
I personally think llamas are adorable.
C'mon, Liza.
Just take a look for yourself.
Hold on! Stop!
They always have this silly blank stare that's so cute.
Wow! They have Patagonian maras over here!
Oh boy, what now?! More cuteness? Are they cute?
Like two peas in a pod...
Attention all guests, the zoo's open-air capybara bath
is scheduled to start soon at 1:30 PM.
Fennec Ranch
Did you hear that, Kasumi? We gotta hurry!
All right.
Omigosh! Fennec foxes! How precious!
Totally!
Fennec?! I dunno what that is!
Save it for another time!
She can't walk if you shake her like that.
Argh! I'm about to leave your sorry butt behind!
Please no! Don't leave me alone in
the middle of a bunch of cute animals!
Izu Saboten Zoo
The Original Open-Air Capybara Bath
Hello everyone and thank you
for visiting the Izu Saboten Zoo today.
Yikes, there's already a huge crowd.
It was such a desperate struggle just to get here.
But now I can't see anything...
Now then,
allow me to introduce you to our capybaras.
This one here is the eldest son of the family...
Would it be causing too much trouble for us
to teleport straight to the front row?
Yeah, we're definitely not doing that.
Oh! The crowd has thinned out a little!
Let's head for the front.
Such a calming sight.
It heals the soul!
So these... are capybaras?
All right. I guess you could call them... cute?
It's kinda weird. What's up with their faces?
It's as if they're in some kind of trance.
Watching them like this puts me
in such a strange mood...
Everything's slowing down, almost like
the flow of time itself is taking it easy.
Just watching these creatures is enough to relax my
whole body as if I'm soaking in the tub along with them.
It's so calming. So refreshing. So cute.
All of these sensations...
are slowly seeping through down to my core...
Liza...
Earth to Liza!
She snapped out of it.
Whew, that's a relief.
Guess I was totally spaced out...
Are you okay? You looked like
you were dreaming or something.
Yeah, I was having a good soak.
Inside the hot springs known as "capybaras."
You make less and less sense every day, I swear.
CAPYBARA TREATS
Look at 'em go!
How cute!
What should we do next?
Do you wanna check out some other animals?
I guess so...
Get a hold of yourself, girl.
Don't let the capybaras overtake you.
Uh, it's too late for that. I'm pretty sure my brain is now
filled to the brim with capybaras.
Your face is even starting to look like one, too...
Since we came all the way here,
I'm willing to try looking at one more animal!
U-Uh, okay. You go girl... I guess?
I've already accomplished our main goal
of seeing the capybaras,
which means it's okay for me to collapse whenever!
Hold on.
If you collapse on us before we get home,
it's gonna make getting back really difficult...
Oh yeah. Can we teleport if you get knocked out?
I'm afraid not.
Which means we'd have to take the train home...
This says it takes a 30 minute bus ride
just to get to the nearest station.
And it takes over 3 hours to get back.
Not to mention, you'll have
to carry my unconscious body!
Are you up to the challenge, ladies?!
Absolutely not!
If you pass out, we're leaving you behind!
Okay then, should we just go home?
Ugh, but that's a waste.
Attention all guests, the interactive feeding time
at the red panda exhibit is about to begin.
Red pandas?! I'll give it a try.
No, hold up! Red pandas would be insta-kills for you!
We're going to look at the red pandas by ourselves!
Just crouch down and wait around here, okay?!
I gotta crouch down and wait?
Phooey. Why do I gotta wait for them
down on the ground like this?
I mean, I know it's risky for me to catch sight
of any of the cute animals around here.
But like, come on! I've made
a little progress on that front lately.
The capybaras didn't pose a problem, right?
All right.
Fennec Ranch
I personally think llamas are adorable.
C'mon, Liza. Just take a look for yourself.
Hold on! Stop!
Oh, it's that girl...
The one from earlier who has the
unusual condition of passing out
whenever she sees animals that are extra cute.
What a relief. She seems to have made it back okay.
Hello, miss! Do you like llamas?
I happen to love llamas myself!
They're a member of the camelid family
with the silliest face!
And that lazy gaze of theirs.
Whenever they stare at me
with those mysterious eyes,
I feel like they're drawing me into a universe
that lies within their pupils...
Those red pandas were just adorable!
Right?
Oh, hey. Is that Liza?
Have you ever experienced that sensation?
Of the llama universe?
Ah, that explains the indescribable feeling
that washed over me when I looked at the llamas.
I was experiencing their universe, huh?
What the heck are those two talking about?
U-Um, Liza?
Hey. Welcome back, you two.
You feeling okay, Liza?
Your face looks almost
exactly like a llama right now.
The cuteness of llamas is very
difficult to describe in words.
So this llama-loving staff member
was just helping explain them to me.
It's the first time someone
has shared the same sentiment.
Did you know? The reason that llamas
have faces that seem so mysterious to us
is because you can see the universe in their eyes.
Oh, God. I don't understand
a word either of them is saying.
C'mon, Liza. It's time to go.
To the universe?
To go home!
Please come again!
Can you use your teleporter?
Yeah, uh...
Wait. How does thing work again?
It wasn't just her face!
She's gone full head empty!
She's been totally overtaken by the llamas...
What should we do? Ditch her?
She might snap out of it with time.
And since we're all the way in Izu,
we might as well wait
until Liza recovers by going to...
Oh, yeah!
How is it, Liza? You back to your senses?
Yep, I'm all good.
Seeing all those capybaras bathing
made me want to hit up a hot springs, too.
For sure.
This trip was supposed to be how I paid you guys back,
but I just caused more problems for you.
Or so I thought. But it wasn't so bad, huh?
Well, I had a good time despite all the crazy stuff.
I'm willing to put up with this level of trouble, no sweat.
We're friends, after all!
It's more fun than troublesome, but mostly
because of how out-of-this-world things with you get.
Oh, yeah?
Cool, so can we go home now?
I can't help but worry about Yozora.
Let us enjoy the hot springs a little more!
I dunno how much more I can stand.
wotchi wotchi are wa nanda? seimeitai no "se"!
Watch, watch, what's that I see? A lively lifeform!
saachi saachi moshikashite tomodachi ka?
Search, search, do you wanna be friends?
nyanboree nyanboree nyanboree nyanboree de
Myamboree! Myamboree! Myamboree! Myamboree! So...
moffii! moffii!
Fwuffy! Fwuffy!
nyanboree nyanboree nyanboree nyanboree de
Myamboree! Myamboree! Myamboree! Myamboree! So...
moffii! moffii!
Fwuffy! Fwuffy!
nyaa
Meow!
kawaii wa seigi sonja sonja aku to wa nan zo?
Cuteness is justice! So what are the evils standin' in its way?
urusai mama? kenka? shukudai? osouji?
Mom being naggy? Getting into fights? Homework? Cleaning?
kokoronai hitotachi ga afureteiru zo
There's a lotta cruel people out there
nakayoku shitekunakya muu muu da!
Better get along or you'll be a grumpypants!
chikyuu wa fushigi na toko de kaiseki taihen
Earth's a strange planet, and studying it's a pain
risou dake ja omanma taberenai ga
But just thinking about it won't put food on the table!
nishin geppo shikou sakugo
Through steady effort and trial and error
teinei ni tema hima kakeru no ga, otoshidokoro!
Give it a go and your hard work will pay off!
wotchi wotchi are wa nanda? seimeitai no "se"!
Watch, watch, what's that I see? A lively lifeform!
mikke mikke UTOPIA kamo?
I spy, I spy, a utopia?
doukaina?
There's no way, right?
nyanboree de waai! yatta ne nyanboree de uu!
Myamboree, hurray! Yippee! Myamboree, whoo!
muzukashii koto wa chotto oyasumi nanoda
We deserve a break after all that hard work
ashita mata ganbarou tte iettara OK!
As long as we promise we'll get back to it tomorrow, it's A-OK!
choi sawagi shichaou!
Let's have a party!
sore ga sunawachi heiwa tte yatsu janai?
That's what peace is all about, no?
iizo! moffi-ffii fuwafuwa ni
Alright! Fwuffy-ffy, dive right in
moffi-ffi tobikondara
Fwuffy-ffy, right into the fluff
ai tte yatsu ga wakari sou desu
And you'll start to know what love really means
totte oki no nukumori de
Lovingly conceal me
meromero ni tsutsundene moffii
In all that warmth of yours, so fwuffy
san, ni, ichi... kyou mo otsukaresama!
3, 2, 1... Good work today!
goronago chokomaka chochoi to goshujin
Catnapping nonstop, one second, Master
omimi wo haishaku, hidari kara nyaa
I need you for a sec, gimme your left ear-Meow!
nyanboree nyanboree nyanboree nyanboree de
Myamboree! Myamboree! Myamboree! Myamboree! So...
moffii! moffii!
Fwuffy! Fwuffy!
nyaa
Meow!
Liza receives an order to return.
Faced with the prospect of being torn away from
Yozora and her friends, what future will she choose?
Next time, episode 7: "Return to Base."