Currently, Japan's food self-sufficiency rate
*On a calorie basis in 2021
is merely 38%!
Is there even a future for a country
which cannot feed half of its population?
Of course not!!
In Hokkaido, the food warehouse of Japan,
a manga artist worked day after day
in the trenches to save our people from famine!
And they call her...
Arakawa the Farmer!!
NOBLE
FARMER
My name is Arakawa Hiromu.
Manga artist
Before I became a manga artist,
I spent 7 years farming in Hokkaido.
My mother and father are both fully-blooded farmers,
with bloodlines of farming pioneers
in Hokkaido.
Would you say that farming is tough work?
Editor for Shinshokan
To an extent, yes. It's a lot of physical labor,
and you're working all year long.
But the sound of "This is delicious!"
from our kind patrons keeps us going.
Although...
Uh, doesn't milk make you fat?
I'll pass.
Ew, why would I eat vegetables?
Check it, I just tossed my trash into that field.
*PLEASE do not throw your trash away in paddy fields.
Whenever I hear stuff like that,
I think about cutting off the food supply
and lettin' 'em starve to death!!
Y'know, as you do.
Your eyes tell a different story.
Because of that, my family runs
a dairy farm and a field crop.
Arakawa Farm
We mainly sell milk and potatoes.
I'll be telling you about the milk this time.
Head 1
Milk
Arakawa
Farm
After I started aspiring to be a manga artist,
my parents would send me milk to drink every week.
Pasteurized
and packed
Arakawa
Farm
When one day...
Hey, Pops.
Is it just me or does the milk taste weird?
Ezo
Approx.
Kanto
Ezo
Approx.
Kanto
Eeyup, government mandated
a change to the drinking water.
Ezo
Approx.
Kanto
Ezo
Approx.
Kanto
Ezo
Approx.
Kanto
Arakawa Hiromu's father
Approx.
Kanto
It reeks of bleaching powder,
so the cows are on strike.
There's a direct correlation between
the taste of the water and deliciousness of the milk.
It's been tasting real strong...
Arakawa Hiromu's
mother
Should we cut back on the corn feed?
Arakawa Hiromu's
mother
Corn feed is rich in protein, etc. and very nutricious
Milk is a barometer of our cows' physical state.
The taste of everything we consume
falls on their condition.
Does the taste of milk really change
that much based on their condition?
Why don't you see-slash-taste for yourself?
How the Taste of Milk Changes
(For Arakawa Farm)
How the taste of milk changes!
How the Taste of Milk Changes
(For Arakawa Farm)
From December to April!
December to April
Changes in the Taste of Milk at Arakawa Farm
Wow, so sweet!
The cows don't drink too much water in the winter,
so our dairy gets much thicker.
From May to June!
May to June
Changes in the Taste of Milk at Arakawa Farm
It's so much smoother.
That's because they've started grass grazing.
From July to September!
July to September
Changes in the Taste of Milk at Arakawa Farm
It's kinda bland...
They've started drinking more water because of the heat,
which dilutes our dairy.
From October to November!
October to November
Changes in the Taste of Milk at Arakawa Farm
It's gotten sweeter again!
It's a much more comfortable season,
so the cows are in better shape.
I never knew milk was so nuanced.
As you've seen, milk has a variety of different tastes,
though milk consumption in Japan has staggered
in recent years, partly due to the impact of Coronavirus.
Agricultural
Cooperative
My deepest apologies.
Agricultural
Cooperative
We have too much milk in stock,
can you please reduce production?
Agricultural
Cooperative
There it is!!
Agricultural
Cooperative
A production restraint put on us
due to staggered milk consumption.
Production Restraint
This is important for improving supply-and-demand,
but we sometimes have to discard milk.
How many years has it been
since we had to dump milk?
It is what it is.
Heartbreak is inevitable in the life of a farmer.
It always hurts to watch as the milk flows
out from its tank to the sewage plant.
There's no way we can carry
this conversation on milk alone.
Well, there's more where that came from.
But there's only one thing left I must say.
Go on!
If they can't have water,
let them drink milk!
When did you get so noble?!
Bless milk!
Praise be milk!
Milk shall save our world!
Go drink some milk, okay?
Milk Marketing Anime: Fin!
What's trivial depends on how you look at it
Let's make our future, golden as a wheat field,
Dance and sway
"Good to see you again," "Welcome home,"
How I want to greet you and sing innocently
May the joy of self-sufficiency
Spread even further