CAP REVOLUTION
Boosting off with the force of a pinched hose nozzle
hoosu no saki wo tsumanda you na ikioi de hajike rocket start
haji
ke
roc
ket
start
Ready Cap!
Rea
Ready Cap! (Ready Cap!)
dy
Cap!
Bottle Battle Go!
Bot
Bottle Battle Go! (Bottle Battle Go!)
shuwatto soukai saikou na kibun aidea shidai de meccha tanoshii days
shuwa
Feels great to be fizzed full'a energy
Our days packed with all the fun we can envision
kibun
ccha
tano
shii
days
Ready Cap! (Ready Cap!)
Ready Cap!
Rea
dy
Cap!
Bottle Battle Go!
Bot
Bottle Battle Go! (Bottle Battle Go!)
Cast
Coga Cota
Hinata Mina
Hocari Ryo
KENN
Akaushi Tsubasa
Kimura Subaru
Hakase Kaori
Sekine Akira
Up Nana
Matsui Eriko
Hocari Suezo
Kuroda Takuya
Hocari Io
Hayami Show
Saida Mitsuya
Igarashi Hiromi
Kinjishi Leo
Hiyama Nobuyuki
Ebarata Ayata
Fujiwara Natsumi
Zan Santa
Iwasaki Ryota
Black Suit 1
Iwakawa Takugo
Black Suit 2
Okada Yuki
Spectator
Kondo Hironori
All you need is one push of the thumb
chippoke na oyayubi hitotsu de
To spur you towards your goals
senaka wo osu koto datte dekiru yo
senaka
wo
osu
koto
da
tte
de
kiru
yo
Written by
Yamamoto Kazuyoshi
Storyboarded by
Kanazawa Hiromitsu
Directed by
Miyoshi Nao
Assistant Chief A.D.
Mori Kazue
Animation Director
J.W.Kim
B.S.Lee
S.Kim
Y.M.Lee
Assistant Animation Directors
Iwabuchi Yasuhiro
Murai Keita
Action Animation Directors
Tamura Ryota
Kato Haruna
Give your 100%! Splash Volcano!
zenshin zenrei! Splash Volcano!
zen
shin
rei!
Splash
Vol
ca
no!
Key Animation
Cleanup Animation
It was ever since I reached out for that small light
garakuta ya gomi ni umoreteru chiisa na hikari wo
gara
kuta
ya
gomi
ni
umore
teru
chii
sa
na
hikari
wo
boku ga te ni shita ano toki kara
boku
That shone from within the landfill
ga
te
ni
shita
I found something I can get sucked into
muchuu ni nareru koto ima mitsuketa yo
muchuu
ni
nareru
koto
My heart started racing before I had time to think
atama yori saki ni kokoro ga hashiri-dashita
atama
yori
saki
ni
kokoro
ga
hashiri-
dashita
gamushara ni tobi-dashita yume no michinori no
gamushara
I'm on the road to my dream I impulsively jumped out towards
ni
tobi-
dashita
yume
no
michi
ri
no
saki de matteruze MY SUPER HERO
Waiting for you at the end, my super hero
SUPER
HERO
Master!
Ayata!
This is great!
Let's have our rematch here!
I'm not here to battle!
There's something I must ask of you!
Huh? What is it?
Hocari Ryo's in trouble!
The President will tell you everything!
What happened to him?
And by the President, you mean his father, right?
Hello?
Coga Cota.
I request your assistance.
It appears a problem has risen
from our research facility.
Ryo has gone berserk
and has concealed his location.
What?!
Ryo's gone berserk?
Ryo is not in normal condition right now.
We must make haste and find him.
Not only for him, but for the fate of the BMA.
Please.
So I just have to find Ryo?
Got it. I guess I'll scour the field for him.
If you can, please.
Ebarata Ayata will assist you there.
Ijuin Shiman and Asue Roland
are also assisting in this search.
What in the world?!
What happened here?
Ayata, no signs of Ryo over here yet.
Any updates there?
Huh? Ayata?
Ayata, you there?
Did the vending machine break?
Ayata? Do you read me?
What's wrong?
Over there!
Is everything okay? Update me!
Ayata!
The BMA-authorized Bottle Battler Ranking is as follows.
Bottle Battlers start at Normal Rank.
Above them is Bronze, then Silver and Gold.
The top 10 are the Bottle Stars.
Above them are the Three Champions,
who can then take on the Bottle King.
Who will be the next to claim the king's throne?
Bring It, Whuh! Tansatan DX
Ebarata Ayata too...?
Are they okay?
Thankfully, yes.
Though unfortunately as for Ryo...
It seems like he's escaped onto the field.
We'll continue our search there.
We're partway through the Bottle Royale!
Let's go back over some highlights!
Tsubasa and Leo've got everyone shook
Their long battle keeping us hooked
The amazing rookie Cota loses the race
And Santa's got victory all over his face
But Cota hangs on and stays on track
Now's his chance to turn the tables back!
Bhah, what?!
He wasn't disqualified?!
The second round is about to begin!
Let's see just who will take the win!
This is Suezo, waiting for 'em cheer caps
Taking this chance of mine to rap
Cap?!
Now we will return to the battle.
Can't find Hocari Ryo...
And I can't get in touch with Ayata...
What happened to him?
Mehh-rry Christmas!
Coga Cota, ya think ya can
pull the rug on me, eh?
Zan Santa?!
Wait, you actually remembered my name?!
Thank you so much, man!
Anyways, Coga Cota! Ya must think you're so clever,
pretending I beat ya and running off!
Now hold on just a sec, uhh, Sanpei!
I wasn't try'na do any of that!
It's Santa!
You literally just got it!
We're going to battle for real this time, all-out!
I told you, I'm totally down for this!
Just not right now, I'm bus—
What was that?
Mitsuya!
If Cota of all people is rejecting a battle,
surely there's a good reason for it.
So...
For now, you can battle me—
Saida Mitsuya—and my Arrowcider!
Thanks, Mitsuya!
I'm truly sorry, Zan Santa!
I'll explain later when I have time!
Let's battle again some other time!
Hey, wait! Come back!
He's gone...
Well, then...
I'll just have to battle you!
Any friend of Coga Cota has to be crazy strong!
Saitama Mitsuo!
That's Saida Mitsuya to you!
Let's do this! Bring it on, Sazanga Kyuta!
It's Zan Santa!
You're doing that
on purpose!
So are you...
Earlier in the Champion showdown,
Kinjishi Leo began his ongoing attacks.
And Akaushi Tsubasa's
got his feet glued to the ground!
What's his goal here?
If he's trying to rush the time limit,
he won't win either...
I didn't think his ten-shots
would be able to hold me down...
It's time I start fighting back!
Aha, at last! Akaushi Tsubasa
has fired for the trap switches!
If you don't want to be devoured,
you begin hunting for yourself...
Is that what you're doing, Tsubasa?
I like it! Charge at me with your horns,
and I'll face them with my fangs!
Alongside the fiery Champion showdown,
the battle over here is raging!
Watch what I can do!
Submehh-rge!
There was a switch there?!
Tansatan is good at firing at low targets!
Not to mention the momentum
from the wing and foot rollers...
So powerful...
You've got a real good partner there!
But you can't top my sharpshooting!
He sure has a good grip on his Bottleman...
Must've gotten a lot of practice.
He sure knows the ins and outs of his Bottleman...
Must've done a lot of research.
He's just like me.
This battle ain't as showy as the Champions...
But they're like one in the same in wisdom and strength,
which adds a whole layer of passion!
Phew, no kidding!
I'm so glad I got to witness a battle like this!
Hey, Zan Santa!
It's time we put an end to this!
I was 'bout to say the same thing!
Cider Impact!
Mehh-rry Christmas!
I'll get this victory gift-wrapped!
Boost Cyclone!
H-He got me!!
It's over!
Zan Santa's admirable shot
has taken out Saida Mitsuya!
Mehh-be it's silly coming from me,
but that was a good game, right?
I've never had a battle bring out
so much of Tansatan's potential before.
Same here.
I feel like I'm starting to
get the hang of using Arrowcider!
After such a heated battle,
the two share a firm handshake.
And the audience is flooding them with cheer caps...
Caps!!
Gimme caps too!!
Shut up!
Caps!
Apologies for the disturbance!
Now, back to the coverage...
What was that?
What the?
What's going on?
Here you go.
Now then.
Time to get to work.
Huh... This bridge...
Whaaat?!
I-It wasn't me!
I swear, I didn't do anything this time...
Are you alright?
Hocari Ryo?
Uh, hey!
What's wrong with you?
Destroy Bottle Battling!
One moment, please.
Hocari Ryo just showed up on camera, but the drone...
Oh! We've gotten footage from a different drone!
Destroy Bottle Battling!
What happened to him...?
Ryo, come on...
What's up with you...?
Stop! Where are you going?
R-Right, I need to alert Io...
It's very noisy up there...
Destroy Bottle Battling!
Destroy!!
What the heck?
How can you do all this with caps?!
Cota!
Io! It's real bad!
We have to stop him!
Thank you for tracking down Ryo.
But your job ends here.
If anyone must stop him...
it is my duty.
Next Time
The Burst?! Snap Out of It, Hocari Ryo!
I'm Zan Santa!
Did y'all see that?!
Me and Tansatan's a-mehh-zing
performance!
Huh?! Who are you calling
a minor character?!
Get fizzed up again next week!