Cast
Coga Cota
Hinata Mina
Hocari Ryo
KENN
Hayari Ponta / Citrus
Otsuka Takeo
Akaushi Tsubasa
Kimura Subaru
Usami Seimei
Nara Toru
Up Nana
Matsui Eriko
Hocari Machiko
Karasawa Jun
Saida Mitsuya
Igarashi Hiromi
Mizuno Iroha
Shibuya Ayano
Kinjishi Leo
Hiyama Nobuyuki
Kurenai Haku
Kakihara Tetsuya
Zan Santa
Iwasaki Ryota
Narrator
Iwakawa Takugo
Written by
Koyama Makoto
Storyboarded by
Yoshida Tooru
Directed by
Tamano Takahiro
Chief Assistant A.D.
Mori Kazue
Animation Director
Momoyo
Assistant Animation Director
Iwabuchi Yasuhiro
Action Animation Directors
Tamura Ryota
Kato Haruna
Key Animation
Cleanup Animation
feel.
Toriyama Maiko
Saito Kaori
Snow Light Staff
Matsushita Tomomi
Hocari Machiko, daughter of
BMA's Chairman Hocari Suezo,
announced a new organization—B-DACT.
And in lieu of BMA's Bottle King Citrus' absence,
Kinjishi Leo was crowned B-DACT's Bottle King.
They then challenged BMA to a Special Bottle Royale
to claim rights to its management.
Who will control the company?
And what will this make of the future of Bottle Battlers?
Yo! Yo! Round 1's got us all
on the edge of our seats,
It's about time we make the victor concrete!
A certain duo teams up, who would've guessed!
Taking on a Champion, giving him their very best!
When Cota Cota sends himself out,
Boy, would I like to know what that's about!
All of a sudden, Kinjishi Leo bursts!
Beats Akaushi Tsubasa, gives him his worst!
And he's greeted on the scene by Hocari Ryo!
Where this battle will go, nobody knows!
And who are you?
I challenge you, Kinjishi Leo!
Blow, Cap Storm! Leo vs. Ryo!
Just knowing that I was in your shoes once...
It feels so shameful.
The burst gives me the power
to devour everything in my path!
I'm sure you know what that's like!
Of course I do!
That's why I have to stop you!
If that's what you want...
Give me your worst!
I'm gonna eat you...
I'm gonna devour you!!
Is that... Leo?
Strange...
I really thought Cota would get it.
I'm here for you, your majesty.
We won't need someone of his caliber.
Cota is necessary for the kind of
Bottle Battling I'm seeking.
Can I ask you a favor, Kurenai Haku?
For what do I owe you the pleasure?
My business here is done for today.
Do you mind cleaning up?
At your service.
Holy cap! Kurenai Haku is bulldozing through the battlers!
He's unstoppable! Unbeatable! Flawless!
The Bottle Royale has taken an unexpected twist
ever since Bottle King Citrus showed up!
Unbelievable...
Do you even realize how long it took
to plan this through?
I'm gonna eat you, Hocari Ryo!
Going face-to-face with the burst
reminds me of what it feels like...
But this power is wrong!
Apologies for interrupting.
You guys!
So you've come, Citrus.
Prepare to be eaten!
That's quite arrogant, Leo.
You're in the presence of a king.
I'm the Bottle King here!
Alas, you are a mere impostor.
Triple Impact!
Whoa-ho-ho-ho!
Hocari Ryo and the Champion Kinjishi Leo
have been disqualified at the same time!
These two are the only Bottle Battlers remaining...!
Sir Citrus and I are not aligned with BMA nor B-DACT.
We have decided to form a new team.
Excuse me?!
I would've been happy if Cota were with me.
But you can join if you want.
Uhh...
They're forming a third team out of the blue...?
There's no way, right?
Hocari Suezo has given his approval!
Dang it, you're so infuriating!
And with that, "Team Citrus" has bounced
straight up to the top of the ranking!
Hey!
What is the meaning of this?!
Coga Cota!
Off we go!
Huh?
While everyone's still crazed
about that shocking first round,
the second round is underway today
and the hype for it is even higher!
Team Citrus is currently up at the top!
Many Bottle Battlers have shown approval
for Bottle King Citrus' ideals,
all of them transferring teams
one after the other!
Man, it's so surreal to be on the same team as Citrus!
You're out of your league, mehh-n!
I'm gonna get Citrus to acknowledge me
and become famehhs!
Your motive is too corrupt!
What's that? I can't hear you,
you're just a side character.
Look who's talking!
They get along so well...
Now for some news that'll knock your socks off!
Looks like one of BMA's core members, Coga Cota,
and one of the Champions, Akaushi Tsubasa,
are entirely absent from Round 2!
Thanks to this, BMA is at
an overwhelming disadvantage!
Ryo, are you sure about this?
Yes. We don't get to choose our means.
Time to kick this round off!
Ready Cap...
Bottle Battle...
Go!
There he is!
Kinjishi Leo!
Come here to get eaten?
Rapid Beast Omnistrike!
Screw Quintet!
Hound Strike!
I'll make sure I eat you on this next...
Whoa-ho!
Team Citrus has secured a boatload of points!
Want to join forces with us?
What?!
I don't think it's safe to let Citrus do as he pleases.
Even you won't last forever like this.
Teaming up with a bunch of weaklings?
What do you take me for?
How about you judge whether I'm
a "weakling" or not after a Bottle Battle?
Alright.
Holy cap! Hocari Ryo and Kinjishi Leo
are plunging into a duel!
Leo, you can't go battling Ryo right now!
We'll be playing a special version of Gunman 5—
with thirty targets, a.k.a. Gunman 30.
Both camps have thirty caps lined up,
far more than usual.
Whoever knocks down more targets
in under three minutes wins.
My kind of challenge.
He's challenging Kinjishi Leo
on rapid-firing?!
You sure are bold, rich boy...
I'll keep watch.
I won't let anyone interfere.
Ready Cap...
Bottle Battle...
Go!
Screw Quintet!
Rapid Beast Omnistrike!
Feel like giving up yet, Hocari Ryo?!
The game's only just begun.
Let's do this, Aquasports!
Leo's five points ahead...
Was it really that bad to face him head-on?
One minute's passed.
Here it comes...
I feel the burst!
Stop surrendering yourself
to the corruption, Kinjishi Leo!
Corruption?
All that matters is it makes me stronger!
Why should someone who made it all the way
to the Champions have to rely on that strength?
Shut it!
I know you still have some pride
as a Bottle Battler left in you!
Now Leo's only four points ahead...
Ryo's catching up!
One minute left!
I know how it feels.
To get overtaken by power, for my feelings
as a Bottle Battler to get corrupted...
More than anything, Leo...
you're deserting your Bottleman!
What?
Ever since then, I made a vow to Aquasports.
One that we would Bottle Battle together!
You added a magazine?!
Rest in peace on my caps.
Screw Requiem!
Eat him up, C.C. Leon!
Rapid Beast Omnistrike!
With a lead of just one target,
the victor of this grand duel...
is Hocari Ryo!!
And get this!
Kurenai Haku magnificently shot a DX Target,
putting an end to the second round of
the fateful Tri-Match!
Like we promised, you'll be fighting alongside us.
Okay.
But once Citrus is down,
I'll devour you.
Do whatever you want.
Good job, Ryo.
Thanks.
Hot dog!
Though, uh...
Are you sure you wanna be out here?
Yeah.
I've quit Bottle Battling anyways.
Oh, I see.
Wait...
For real?!
Next Time
The Raging Bull Stops
This is Coga Cota!
You're quitting Bottle Battling?!
Hold on...
You're joking, right?
Tsubasa, if you're joking, just tell me!
Get fizzed up again next week!