ResQ!!
Res
Q!!
When days come where I can't seem
to focus on anything (Everyday Everyday)
zenzen nani mo te ni tsukanai you na hibi ni
zen
nani
(E-Everyday E-E-E-Everyday)
(E-
Every
day
E-
Every
day)
You strike first?! Attacking me with your gaze
sensei kougeki!? kimi no shisen de ichigeki
sen
Cast
Coga Cota
Hinata Mina
Hocari Ryo
KENN
Hayari Ponta / Citrus
Otsuka Takeo
Akaushi Tsubasa
Kimura Subaru
Hakase Kaori
Sekine Akira
Usami Seimei
Nara Toru
Up Nana
Matsui Eriko
Hocari Suezo
Kuroda Takaya
Hocari Io
Hayami Show
Hocari Machiko
Karasawa Jun
Hocari Eri
Nagasawa Miki
Saida Mitsuya
Igarashi Hiromi
Mizuno Iroha
Shibuya Ayano
Kinjishi Leo
Hiyama Nobuyuki
Kurenai Haku
Kakihara Tetsuya
Asue Roland
Toki Shunichi
Ijuin Shiman
Umehara Yuichiro
Ebarata Ayata
Fujiwara Natsumi
Zan Santa
Iwasaki Ryota
Professor Ludbeer
Takahashi Shinya
Black Suit 1
Iwakawa Takugo
Black Suit 2
Endo Hiroyuki
sei
kou
geki!?
kimi
no
shisen
de
ichi
geki
And it's got me totally off-balance
kuratte kara chokuritsu funou de
choku
ritsu
fu
nou
de
Written by
Yamamoto Kazuyoshi
Storyboarded by
Kawasaki Itsuro
Directed by
Tamano Takahiro
Assistant Chief A.D.
Mori Kazue
Animation Director
Masuda Shunsuke
Assistant Animation Directors
Iwabuchi Yasuhiro
Murai Keita
Action Animation Directors
Tamura Ryota
Iwabuchi Yasuhiro
I can't keep waving it off, no no
furafura shiteru dake ja No! No!
fura
Isn't it about time I told you?
sorosoro tsutaenakya ja nai no?
soro
tsu
ta
Key Animation
Masuda Shunsuke
Ikemori Emi
Konishi Mio
Yoshida Toru
Ishimori Ai
Murakami Mayu
Ninomiya Takeshi
Tamura Ryota
Murai Keita
Cleanup Animation
R.I.C
Shadow Media
But when I'm standing in front of you
demo kimi no me no mae ni tattara
tara
I can't stop my heart from pounding
out of my chest (Ugh, I give up...)
dokudoku kizamu kodou osaerannai no
doku
kiza
mu
kodou
(Aa mou dame...)
dakara Help me! Help me!
da
So please help me! Help me! I try to call out
kara
Help
me!
tte sakebitai demo
Help me! Help me! But nothing comes out, no-no-no
Help me! Help me!
Help
me!
koe ni dase Na Na Na nai
koe
ni
dase
Na
nai
uta nara sha la la♪
uta
I can sing, sha-la-la
nara
sha
la
la♪
But my words just do-do-don't work
They stop right at the exit!
kotoba wa naze da? Da Da me nanda deguchi de Stop!
Stop!
But to me, to me
demo betsu ni! betsu ni!
de
mo
betsu
ni!
No one else will be as special to me
as you are, no-no-no
kimi ja nai hito wa toku
betsu ni! betsu ni!
betsu
ni!
naru wake ja Na Na Na nai
If I could just be bold and say "I love you"
hora omoikitte "kimi ga suki" tte
ho
ra
omoi
It would be so easy
But I can't, so please come to my ResQ!!
dekitara sorya kantan da yo na
deki
tara
sorya
dekinai kara onegai ResQ!!
Soar freely, you two.
But remember,
the Bottle Battle ends
once the caps stop flying.
A Bottle Royale over the fate of the world
is getting underway!
Will Coga Cota and Hocari Ryo
save humanity from this crisis?!
Please, we ask, do not use social media
during this Bottle Battle!
No photography either!
We deeply apologize for interrupting your battle.
Forget it. Just explain.
Okay.
The Final Mission! Caps Save the Earth
Let's go.
Oh, uh, yeah!
Oh, it opened!
We were certain back then
that Ryo had managed to cut off the AI.
But just before that, it copied all of its data
and escaped onto the network.
The AI swam through the network sea,
infiltrating a number of criminal organization computers,
before settling in one spot.
The facility of a mysterious organization
which was conducting inhumane research until recently.
We have ten minutes.
After that, the whole building will be scanned
and our plan will fail.
Got it, got it.
The AI hijacked their computer,
and began preparing to launch
a massive electromagnetic pulse attack.
Electro...what now?
An attack that will render electronic devices
across a wide range unusable.
If he gets away with it,
human civilization relying on tech will crumble,
and we'll regress to the middle ages.
But why did you pick us?
There are three components
to making this plan work.
1. We need brilliant Bottle Battlers.
Bullseye!
Well, no one but Bottle Battlers
would make it through this.
True that!
2. We need a pair of two boys or girls.
I'm guessing we shouldn't touch those?
Nope. They seem to be devices
set up to prevent adults from breaking in.
We can get through
as long as we bend over!
3. Of those two, one of them has to be a Hocari.
How come?
The facility was owned by the Hocari family
before those scoundrels settled in.
Thanks to my research, we know that
the security system from before still functions!
You can use it to get into the facility!
I see, so we were being tested.
What do you mean?
That whole Bottle Royale was just a test
to see who was fit for this plan.
Aw, what? I hate tests.
But why is the AI doing all this?
Isn't it supposed to assist humanity?
We don't know right now.
But we have a guess.
He's afraid of the power humans have.
The strange, enormous power
of our emotions.
Here it comes!
Alright, I've got this!
This is the target we assume is in the last room...
Blastboss!
If you break the armor on both sides,
then hit both hitpoints inside at the same time,
it should terminate.
Got it. So Ryo and I
just have to hit it at the same time?
Kaori, bring it out.
Gladly, Miss Machiko!
These are the metal caps
I developed specially for this plan!
These caps are equipped with a special type of metal!
With the power these caps have,
you should be able to stop Blastboss easy!
If all goes well, it'll get glitched!
I helped out with it too!
You got it?
I also...
Glitched how?
It'll short-circuit!
Let's do this!
So this is the final boss, huh?
Looks like it!
Start by taking out its armor on both sides!
Got it!
Alright, next mission.
Good ol' co-op play, right?
I'm getting fizzy!
Let's shoot on the count of three!
Ready?
Yeah!
One!
Two!
Three!
Dangit!
Don't worry, let's try again!
I messed up...
Don't sweat it!
I miss like that all the time!
Never thought you'd be the one encouraging me.
Uh-oh, we only have one minute.
Are you kidding? Darn it...
We're not going down!
No use in getting frustrated.
We'll just have to keep going until time's up!
Yeah.
Are we sure we don't have the other option?
What other option?
Bottle Battling with the AI.
You know we can't do that.
We're already this deep in.
I see...
But he was thinking of humanity all this time.
You mean we maybe could've been friends?
Perhaps.
AI is made by humans!
It's all up to how its controlled,
both AI and human emotions alike!
You've got that right!
This is our last shot.
Are you afraid?
Nope, I'm all fizzed up!
I like to hear that.
Let's go!
Yeah!
Holy cap, what is that?!
There's some sort of golden aura
around Coga Cota and Hocari Ryo!
The monitor isn't broken!
It's Sparkling Nova!
The rare change of form that spawns
when a Bottle Battler and Bottleman
are fully synchronized in their enjoyment...
I can't believe I'm seeing it with my own eyes...
What a wonderful time we were born in...
That goes for everyone.
Sparkling Requiem!
Let's go!
Splash Volcano Nova!
We did it!
Fizz yeah!
Blastboss has been stopped in its tracks!
Coga Cota and Hocari Ryo
have just saved the world!
Crud! Cota, run for it!
They didn't say anything about this!
Cota!!
Ryo! Cota!
Tell me this isn't happening...
I-It can't be...
Cota and Ryo are okay, right?!
That's what we're gonna find out!
We're coming with!
Let us know if there's any way we can help!
I'm his best buddy toooo!
He has to be okay.
I said I'd treat him to crab hot pot
when the battle was over.
Don't make plans like that!
No running in the halls...
but we must hurry.
Hey, Cota! We're coming for you!
You better not die!!
Shut up! I'm gonna eat you!
I can see them!
C-Cota! Ryo!
Where are they? Are they okay?
No...
What do I do...?
This is all my fault...
Yeah, it is your fault.
If I had never put Origin in his locker,
none of this would've happened...
Huh? What are you talkin' about?
It's your fault we're stuck with
these two Bottle Battling idiots.
Even at a time like this...!
You're just amazing, Ryo, Cota!
Boosting off with the force of a pinched hose nozzle
Fizz yeah, I win!
Are we finally tied?
Ready Cap! (Ready Cap!)
Not just yet! Let's go again!
Bottle Battle Go! (Bottle Battle Go!)
Hehe, you're persistent!
Feels great to be fizzed full'a energy
Our days packed with all the fun we can envision
You almost died, and yet you keep going.
Bull-hull-hull! Wonderful!
This is what a true Bottle Battler is like!
Ready Cap! (Ready Cap!)
Woo-hoo! Crazy!
Bottle Battle Go! (Bottle Battle Go!)
I was worried about you...
All you need is one push of the thumb
I gotta make more crazy caps next!
Let me join!
To spur you towards your goals
Lemme savor the memory
with an autograph!
Give me a hand print!
Give your 100%! Splash Volcano!
I want a handshake!
You two are even more beautiful
than candy crabs!
It was ever since I reached out for that small light
I'll be your referee!
And I'll do commentary!
That shone from within the landfill
Who knows where we'd be now
if I had never restored Colamaru when he was broken.
I found something I can get sucked into
Oh, yeah.
Thanks for fixing him, Kaori.
My heart started racing before I had time to think
He's in tip-top shape!
But if I hadn't been sent the data back then...
I'm on the road to my dream I impulsively jumped out towards
That's right. Back then,
I made the right judgment!
Waiting for you at the end, my super hero
I was the one who hacked into Origin's data
and sent it to you!
You did not!
I did too!!
None of us know who you are,
but thanks, Mister!
Wait, you don't know him?
Do you?
More or less...
Anyways.
That's 125 wins, 125 losses.
Whoever wins the next battle
becomes Bottle King!
You'll also get my specialty rice ball!
Sounds good.
Let's go!
Thank you for watching!