Cap Revolution BOTTLEMAN DX
Boosting off with the force of a pinched hose nozzle
hoosu no saki wo tsumanda you na ikioi de hajike rocket start
haji
ke
roc
ket
start
Ready Cap!
Rea
Ready Cap! (Ready Cap!)
dy
Cap!
Bottle Battle Go!
Bot
Bottle Battle Go! (Bottle Battle Go!)
shuwatto soukai saikou na kibun aidea shidai de meccha tanoshii days
shuwa
Feels great to be fizzed full'a energy
Our days packed with all the fun we can envision
kibun
ccha
tano
shii
days
Ready Cap! (Ready Cap!)
Ready Cap!
Rea
dy
Cap!
Bottle Battle Go!
Bot
Bottle Battle Go! (Bottle Battle Go!)
All you need is one push of the thumb
chippoke na oyayubi hitotsu de
To spur you towards your goals
senaka wo osu koto datte dekiru yo
senaka
wo
osu
koto
da
tte
de
kiru
yo
Give your 100%! Splash Volcano!
zenshin zenrei! Splash Volcano!
zen
shin
rei!
Splash
Vol
ca
no!
garakuta ya gomi ni umoreteru chiisa na hikari wo
gara
It was ever since I reached out for that small light
kuta
ya
gomi
ni
umore
teru
chii
sa
na
hikari
wo
boku ga te ni shita ano toki kara
boku
That shone from within the landfill
ga
te
ni
shita
I found something I can get sucked into
muchuu ni nareru koto ima mitsuketa yo
muchuu
ni
nareru
koto
My heart started racing before I had time to think
atama yori saki ni kokoro ga hashiri-dashita
atama
yori
saki
ni
kokoro
ga
hashiri-
dashita
gamushara ni tobi-dashita yume no michinori no
gamushara
I'm on the road to my dream I impulsively jumped out towards
ni
tobi-
dashita
yume
no
michi
ri
no
saki de matteruze MY SUPER HERO
Waiting for you at the end, my super hero
SUPER
HERO
The BMA-authorized Bottle Battler Ranking is as follows.
Bottle Battlers start at Normal Rank.
Above them is Bronze, then Silver and Gold.
The top 10 are the Bottle Stars.
Above them are the Three Champions,
who can then take on the Bottle King.
Who will be the next to claim the king's throne?
Fizzed to Life! Colamaru DX
The next challenge is everyone's favorite Bottle Royale!
Everyone is your opponent!
Rack up your points by shooting targets
with caps while dodging obstacles!
Our crowd favorite Bottle Battler is...!
Asue Roland!
He's grabbing points from the get-go
with his hallmark precision shots!
Aw, nuts. I missed him.
Roland gets all the points!
Dang it, where did that come from?
Only one person can shoot from that far away...!
Usami Seimei's sniped his targets!
Both players disqualified!
Whoa, nice one!
Usami Seimei's the coolest!
So this is "Origin?"
Piece of cake.
Emergency. An intruder has been
spotted in the top-level area.
I repeat.
Intruder!
An intruder has been spotted in the top-level area.
Get back here!
Wait!
–One of you, go that way!
–Yes, sir!
What a bunch of pests...
Destroy Bottle Battling.
And recreate it.
Didn't think someone else infiltrated here too.
Plan B in case of emergency, Agent Ryo.
Please hand over Origin.
I'm the one handing it over.
Failure...
...isn't an option.
Catch...
...and release!
Fizz yeah! I made it!
That was amazing, Cota!
Oh, Ponta! The heck did you go?
Sorry, dude. Got lost.
Ponta...
I know, I'm supposed to be the older one here.
A field?
I see...
–There you are!
–End of the road, pal!
Hold it, not that way!
Your hands sure are strong.
You would make such a great Bottle Battler, Cota.
That again?
I already told ya. Fame sounds like a chore to me.
It's such a waste, bro.
You're probably one of the most talented people
this world's seen in the past 10... no, 50 years!
Cota, watch out!
Now you've done it.
Holy cap! Hold on to those bottles!
The time-out flag is in the air!
It gives you courage!
Drink this bad boy and come face me!
It vaporizes Akaushi Tsubasa's sweat away!
Red-Hot Soda: Energy Brave!
Now on sale!
It's gonna be that expensive to repair?
There's no way I can pay this!
Just be glad that's all we're billing you for.
How many caps am I gonna have to pick up to pay this off?
Sorry about this, Cota...
This is all my fault.
Don't sweat it.
Besides, I shouldn't have spaced out.
Huh? What's this thing?
A Bottleman?
Wow, Cota! Didn't know you had a Bottleman.
It's not mine...
W-What the?
Cola...maru?
Do you... want me to be a Bottle Battler?
Maybe they want you to use him
to pay off your debt.
Dang it, where is he?
Ryo?!
Yes?
What's all the ruckus about?
What's that?
Is it a bird? Is it a plane?
No, it's...!
Trembull-trembull-trembull-trembull...!!
Akaushi Tsubasa!
One of the Three Champions in the Bottle Stars!
The raging bull from hell, Akaushi Tsubasa,
has made a surprise entrance!
Holy cap! We've got an even bigger surprise...!
It's Hocari Ryo!
Absent this season so far,
the Blue-Dragon Rapid Fire Prince, Hocari Ryo,
has made an unexpected appearance!
Ryo?!
Ryo!
What's my boy doing there?
Caps!
The game is back on!
Put a cap in it!!
If you can find and destroy the Deluxe Target on the map,
you'll obtain a load of points and win the game!
But to destroy it, you'll need a heap of brute force!
Power-types have the upper hand!
That's a normal target.
Aim very carefully then shoot!
Like this?
Not quite.
No way you can shoot it like that.
I know!
How 'bout this?
Where on earth did you learn that?
Trembull! If you've got the courage,
come face me, Hocari Ryo!
He never changes.
There's no use running, Hocari Ryo.
A cap...?
It can't be...
There we go, see! You learn quick, Cota!
Lookin' strong!
I missed the target...
But I feel the power fizzing inside me!
It's bubbling!
Huh?
Burst!
Gaze at the power of a charging bull!
Dang it, I missed!
His line-driven cap...
It's riding the power of Tsubasa's cap...!
And it's heading towards the target!
No way...
Keep going! You can make it!
Next Time
Swift Rapid-Fire! Aquasports DX
I'm Coga Cota!
If I keep this up, my debt's as good as paid!
Return Origin to me.
Who are you? Eh, forget it.
Bottle Battle Go!
Get fizzed up again next week!