Cuuuuute!! So cuuuuute!!
Cute wittle kitty!!
He's so cuuuuute!!
Cute, cute, cute!!
Are these "cats" really that cute...?
I'm so happy he likes me!! Cuteeeee!!
Honestly, I still find it
difficult to believe, but...
Gah!! I love you, cute wittle kitty!!
Over here, Your Mewjesty...!
Judging by the reactions of those who've come into
contact with one, perhaps they're telling the truth...
Yes, but if I'm not mistaken, they've encountered
plenty of cute animals in the past, haven't they?
C-Captain...!
In my opinion, my darling Gee is
the cutest animal in all the cosmos.
And regardless of how adorable these Earth animals are,
they pale in comparison to Gee.
I cannot watch as my crew falls
to Earth animals any longer.
Go forth now, and
bring the Earthlings to me at once!
a
ri
e
nai
Impossible...
ki
ka
ku
gai
Unprecedented...
ta
ma
ra
nai
Out of this world...
We run into each other on the catwalk
BLACK
HOLE
Your eyes suck me in like a black hole
tsun
tsun
da
You act so cold but flaunt your stuff
Why the hell is my heart racing?
They're saying it'll rain this afternoon
So maybe I should have an early lunch
ba
cchi
I see you gleaming in the sunlight
What an angel
I'll always be under your paw
My love for you warps the space-time continuum
You quickly become the center of my universe
do
kkun
ba
de
Ba-dump, ker-thump
I just can't take it anymore...
Forget fate or miracles
BANG
Us crossing paths was a big bang
Every star across the night sky is our miracle
I don't want my love to go to your head
I just want you to stay with me...
#12. Too Cute
Cat
Hello there. Welcome to Nyanday Cat Café!
Oh. Hey, Liza.
S'up?
Everyone's waiting in the back.
'Kay.
Sorry I'm late.
Thanks for inviting us!
"An alien friend in need is an alien friend indeed!"
Sure thing.
What's the matter with Akaneko?
She's... a little nervous.
Wait, we're going to space? Like, for real?
'Kay, let's head out!
Run by our director of Biological Research,
Nhapat Nehemo...
The Great Intergalactic Wildlife Refuge,
located aboard the Thrale Interstellar Research Vessel!
Whoa, awesome!
There's tons of weird creatures here!
What's this little guy called?
A dohftsus.
They're a species of dragon.
Try not to provoke them.
They're fire-breathers.
They breathe fire?!
Sounds dangerous...
Yeah, I know...
They end up burning their
mouths with their own fire...
What a sad way to live...
What about these?
Tomtails!
They're pack animals with a tendency
to stick close to their fellow brethren.
Nayunata, marine organisms
that love to sunbathe.
Mokoro, living tofu that entices
other organisms to eat them.
And finally, zoola. No one knows what they are,
what their biology is, nor where they came from.
We're not even sure if they're animals.
They're very bizarre creatures.
It's kind of surreal...
Is it... cute?
I'm not sure...
Whaddya think? Of outer space animals.
They're a little too alien.
My brain's struggling to process it...
Like, my first instinct is to be like,
"What are these things?"
Oh, gotcha.
What about you, Akaneko?
Holy crap, I'm in space... Oh my god...
Am I dreaming right now...?
I guess the animals are the least of her worries...
Hey, Liza! Liza!
Huh?
What about this guy? I like his cute little outfit!
No, no! He's no animal! He runs the refuge!
So long as you're enjoying yourselves,
that's all that matters.
The captain has instructed me to ensure that you,
as Liza's friends, feel welcome.
Yeah, it's great!
I love all the cute-sual animals ya got here!
You're pretty cute-sual yourself,
like a mascot!
P-Pardon me? "Cute-sual?" "Like a mascot?"
Cute in a casual way!
Don't hit him with the technical jargon.
You'll confuse him.
Hm, I see... What an intriguing concept...
I'd be curious to learn more about Earthlings
and their perspective in regards to "cuteness."
Let's have a chat, shall we?
'Kay, then let's take a stroll around the zoo, Nhappy!
"Nhappy?!"
Giving him a nickname like
that is awfully presumptuous!
Sh-She's right! You're making me blush!
Well, don't look so happy about it...
Sasara's pretty comfortable around humans
and non-humans alike, isn't she?
She's fearless like Liza,
but in a totally different way...
This is a pernila.
They're awkward and ungainly creatures.
They require constant supervision, or else
they'll immediately run into a wall or fall over.
Pernila
So they're klutzes! Which makes them "klute!"
"Klute..."
That must mean you find
their clumsiness charming!
How wonderful!
So what other kinds of animals are—
PETTING
ZOO
Gee
What is that...?
Oh, actually, it was the captain
who invited you here today.
And this was his true motive...
That's your captain?!
Regardless of how adorable these Earth animals are,
they pale in comparison to Gee.
Once the Earthling children see him,
they're bound to go absolutely nuts for him.
Yes, but there's a possibility
that they'll think he's hideous.
What?!
If they dare say such a thing,
I'll blow their planet to smithereens!
But Captain...!
Well, knowing them, they probably
wouldn't say anything that mean...
but you should be prepared
for backlash just in case.
No, that won't be necessary.
Gee is too adorable for that.
Now hurry up and bring
the Earthlings to me at once!
Fidget
So, long story short, he's waiting
there to see your reactions.
Fidget
Sorry our captain's a pain in the ass...
SQUELCH
When he's feeding,
his stripes turn into polka dots.
And that's some sort of charm...?
He's, um... very interesting!
H-How unique!
And wow, what an unusual color!
You're not just saying that
to make me feel better, are you?
Please, feel free to be honest.
"Oh, he's precious!" and the like.
Yup, a major pain in the ass...
I think he's...
totally cugly!
BANG
WHAM
"Cug...?"
What is that supposed to mean?! Explain yourself!
Cugly! So ugly that it's cute!
How does "ugly and cute" make any sense?!
Ugly things are, by definition, ugly.
They aren't cute! You're just mocking my darling
Gee in a roundabout way, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
You certainly are! You're patronizing my poor Gee!
You fiendish Earthling...!
I told you, I'm not!
DUN
Then what is this "cugly" you speak of?
Explain it in a way that I can understand!
DUN
And if you fail to do so,
today is the day that Planet Earth perishes!
DUN
Please don't let that be
the reason Earth gets destroyed!
DUN
Ah... I'm sorry if I offended
you or anything like that...
Well, uh... An apology goes a long way...
But I wasn't mocking him!
Looking at him made my heart flutter!
'Cause he's ugly and cute.
Y'see, he's not just cute...
He's got an inexplicable charm about him
that no one else has!
So ugly that it's cute — what's not to get?
Cute trumps ugly, one hundred percent of the time!
And so long as that charm is there,
then even the ugly parts become cute!
PETTING
ZOO
Gee
That's what makes it cugly!
Instead of denying how I feel,
I choose to follow my heart!
Is it cute or is it ugly?
Perhaps it's not so black and white...
An eagerness to attempt to find beauty
in something that is otherwise unpleasant...
Her pursuit of and appreciation for
all things cute is far more profound than ours!
Is Miss Sasara a scholar who specializes
in cuteness or something along those lines...?
Nope, she's just an average
middle-schooler who fears nothing.
"Cugly," eh?
Perhaps it isn't such a bad concept after all...
I'm used to it 'cause I have a hedgehog as a pet.
The spines on her back hurt and they're kinda ugly,
but she's super adorable!
Spines on its back?! Is it a monster?!
Just look at that smile.
He'll probably need to go potty soon.
Earthlings have fascinating ideas,
don't they, Liza?
I wonder if it's because their animals are so cute...
Yes, but not all Earthlings are like them.
I've suddenly developed
a strong interest in Earth animals.
Oh, I know! Why don't we all go
and visit an Earth zoo next?
Whoa, hold your horses, Captain!
These are the same animals that were cute enough
to knock me on my ass! You get that, right?!
Don't worry about me.
After all, I've got my darling Gee.
So long as their cuteness doesn't exceed his,
I'll be perfectly fine.
This won't end well...
Catch ya in the second half!
Let me welcome you to today's
destination: Adventure World!
What's this?
Will the rest of your friends
not be joining us?
Yeah, they passed 'cause
they knew how this was gonna go...
So that's why I brought along a replacement!
I'm Mukai...
Hey, uh, I don't wanna be here either. Can I go?
Don't make me do this by myself! Please?!
There's no need to fret, Miss Kasumi.
We'll be on our best behavior
so as to not disturb the other Earthlings.
Right, everyone?
TA-DA
S-So this is an Earth zoo...!
Where all of the cutest animals hang out!
Is everyone mentally prepared for this?!
Yeah!
This is gonna be a pain in the ass...
I can smell it.
Are you sure about coming with us?
If you pass out, I'm not helping you.
I won't hesitate to walk away!
I-I'll do my absolute best not to lose my cool!
'Cause we wanna see the Earth animals, too!
I couldn't care less about animals and the like.
I am simply a chaperone.
You look pretty excited to me...
Just relax, you two.
I've prepared a contingency plan.
Everyone's wearing one of these necklaces...
"emergency separation devices," so to speak.
If one of us sees a cute animal and starts to freak out,
that person will be immediately teleported to the ship.
It's only going to be me
and Mukai left in the end, isn't it?
I'm not sure how many of us can survive...
I guess these Earth animals are
a force to be reckoned with...
Interesting...
Now, let's get moving! And brace yourselves!
Our first stop is...
the pandas!
They're...
so cuuuute!!
At least survive past the first animal!
I'm afraid it's too late for me...
M-Mithra!!
Kinda feels like we're
supposed to say "rest in peace..."
It was just too much for poor, delicate Mithra...
The captain's already in trouble, too...
No wonder...
It's his first time seeing an Earth animal.
So these are Earth animals...
"They're going to keel over
from the cuteness," she said...
I assumed it was some sort of joke...
This level of cute shouldn't be possible!
If anything, I'm surprised the floor
isn't littered with corpses...
Have I no choice but to surrender?
Will they force me to admit
that Gee is hideously disgusting?!
I refuse!
Gee is the cutest animal in the universe,
and I will stand by that statement!
My darling Gee, please...
lend me your strength!!
He managed to recover?!
Gee is... adorable...
Gee is... number one...!
Wow, you really love your pet... No doubt about it...
You guys okay?
Yeah... just barely.
Oh please... What are you all so worked up over?
Uh, your legs are shaking...
I dunno how many more exhibits we'll make it to.
Everyone seems close to their limit...
I wanna see more cute animals right meow!!
Again with that bit...?
It seems we've circled back to the entrance gate.
This works out well.
Let's take a little break, shall we?
Sure.
I think we're safe now. For one thing,
we saw a real panda and lived to tell the tale.
Why don't we buy some
souvenirs for everyone on the ship?
What's going on...?
"Welcome Room...?"
What's in here...?
Oh my god, this creature...
Does it exist solely to
transcend the limits of cuteness...?
Its face, its fur... down to
the last detail... it's precious!
Stop!!
How can such a creature exist?!
The way it twitches and flaps its wings...
I-I can hardly believe it's real!
The way it waggles its butt,
its slappy feet as it walks...
I'm going to explode!
Don't send me back until I get to hug
its fluffy little body! No...!
Fine! Nothing else matters anymore!
I'll retire from the army and live here instead—!
I can't sense Fianna and
Shamil's presence anymore...
I'm losing all my friends, one after the next...
Maybe we weren't prepared for this after all...!
Liza... Please calm down.
You're not safe either.
The better question is,
how the hell are you still here?
These Earth animals are staggeringly
adorable, aren't they?
If Earthlings were to see my darling Gee,
I doubt they'd have a positive reaction.
Nevertheless...
I still believe Gee is the cutest of them all!
You're incredible, Captain!
A paragon of pet ownership!
Even now, Gee is number one in my...
N-Number one... in... my...
In my heart!!
H-Hang in there! Don't give up, Captain!
This confirms my suspicion that there are
delusional pet owners in outer space, too...
And honestly, I respect that.
Y-You understand, don't you, Mukai?!
U-Um... Do you mind...?
Pets are pets, and other animals are other animals.
You can appreciate both at the same time...
Yeah, I think we should probably call it a day...
Too much more of this and
the captain might go beast mode...
Plus, we might be attracting
a little too much attention...
I heard they vanished into thin air!
Man, that dude's huge...
Is he a bodybuilder...?
Speaking of which, where did Luster and Garmie go?
Are they okay?
Those two ran on ahead of us quite a while ago.
So big!
And white!
Whoa!
They were pretty flustered at first, too...
But they calmed down after a quick break.
They're doing just fine.
Those two get stronger and stronger every day.
Savoring the beauty and wonder
of wild animals with all their little hearts...
Ah, such childlike innocence...
Well, that is the whole point of a zoo...
I think I grew out of that
kind of innocence a while back...
Liza, Liza!
Oh, speak of the devil.
They've got these cute
animals with really long noses!
Look at this one! It's cute, and it's got a long neck!
Their ears are enormous, too!
How'd they even get that big?!
Their spots are adorable...!
Oh, and this one's got horns just like Garmie!
Wow, they're ginormous and adorable...
How can one animal make my heart beat so fast...?
It reminds me of the innocent
excitement I felt as a child...
It's called an elephant! Cute!
This one's a giraffe! Cute!
It's like they're suddenly kids again...
Cute!
Animals are fun!
Why would it teleport me back here?!
Because you must've been freaking out
in one way or another...
But I was looking at the elephants!
Let's all go see the giraffes, as a team!
That's an official order!
Even the captain couldn't handle it...
And you're telling me that Earthlings are somehow able
to live on that planet without losing their minds...?
No! Send me back to Earth!
Launch the Thrale! Full speed ahead!
Cat
Going over our war against
the unprecedented "too cute" threat...
I believe your decision to minimize the amount of
information you shared with us was correct, Liza.
Oh, Nhapat...!
H-Huh?
I try as hard as I can...
I wasn't sure what to do, though!
Everyone was gonna go nuts!
I know... You've been through a lot...
Uh-huh...
I mean, Liza loses her mind over cute animals, too...
But we're also guilty of it,
so we can't really say anything...
Be that as it may, our survey of
Planet Earth has reached a standstill.
Even our highest-ranking soldiers
were unable to succeed...
Then mentally preparing yourselves would
be the most important step, right?
But preparing ourselves how, exactly?
We'll simply have to think of something and try it out.
The Department of Biological Research
will help in any way we can.
Rest assured that we,
the 16th Squadron, shall rise again.
Us, too!
We'll do our best to hang in there!
That includes me and Mithra, of course.
You can count on us!
Y-You guys...!
Thanks!
I believe in you, my crew.
You can overcome this.
Please proceed with the survey...
Head Researcher Liza Luna.
Sure. Leave it to me!
I bet there are tons more adorable animals
on Earth just waiting to be discovered...
So let's get out there and find 'em!
For the future of the universe!
wotchi wotchi are wa nanda? seimeitai no "se"!
Watch, watch, what's that I see? A lively lifeform!
saachi saachi moshikashite tomodachi ka?
Search, search, do you wanna be friends?
nyanboree nyanboree nyanboree nyanboree de
Myamboree! Myamboree! Myamboree! Myamboree! So...
moffii! moffii!
Fwuffy! Fwuffy!
nyanboree nyanboree nyanboree nyanboree de
Myamboree! Myamboree! Myamboree! Myamboree! So...
moffii! moffii!
Fwuffy! Fwuffy!
nyaa
Meow!
kawaii wa seigi sonja sonja aku to wa nan zo?
Cuteness is justice! So what are the evils standin' in its way?
urusai mama? kenka? shukudai? osouji?
Mom being naggy? Getting into fights? Homework? Cleaning?
kokoronai hitotachi ga afureteiru zo
There's a lotta cruel people out there
nakayoku shitekunakya muu muu da!
Better get along or you'll be a grumpypants!
chikyuu wa fushigi na toko de kaiseki taihen
Earth's a strange planet, and studying it's a pain
risou dake ja omanma taberenai ga
But just thinking about it won't put food on the table!
nishin geppo shikou sakugo
Through steady effort and trial and error
teinei ni tema hima kakeru no ga, otoshidokoro!
Give it a go and your hard work will pay off!
wotchi wotchi are wa nanda? seimeitai no "se"!
Watch, watch, what's that I see? A lively lifeform!
mikke mikke UTOPIA kamo?
I spy, I spy, a utopia?
doukaina?
There's no way, right?
nyanboree de waai! yatta ne nyanboree de uu!
Myamboree, hurray! Yippee! Myamboree, whoo!
muzukashii koto wa chotto oyasumi nanoda
We deserve a break after all that hard work
ashita mata ganbarou tte iettara OK!
As long as we promise we'll get back to it tomorrow, it's A-OK!
choi sawagi shichaou!
Let's have a party!
sore ga sunawachi heiwa tte yatsu janai?
That's what peace is all about, no?
iizo! moffi-ffii fuwafuwa ni
Alright! Fwuffy-ffy, dive right in
moffi-ffi tobikondara
Fwuffy-ffy, right into the fluff
ai tte yatsu ga wakari sou desu
And you'll start to know what love really means
totte oki no nukumori de
Lovingly conceal me
meromero ni tsutsundene moffii
In all that warmth of yours, so fwuffy
san, ni, ichi... kyou mo otsukaresama!
3, 2, 1... Good work today!
goronago chokomaka chochoi to goshujin
Catnapping nonstop, one second, Master
omimi wo haishaku, hidari kara nyaa
I need you for a sec, gimme your left ear-Meow!
nyanboree nyanboree nyanboree nyanboree de
Myamboree! Myamboree! Myamboree! Myamboree! So...
moffii! moffii!
Fwuffy! Fwuffy!
nyaa
Meow!
I'm home!
Jeez, I feel like I've been
all over the galaxy today...
You must've been lonely, huh? I'm sorry...
My research is taking a lot
longer than I expected it to...
but when I'm with you, time seems to fly by.
And yet I'm still not used to
how frickin' precious you are.
Yozora... thanks for always sticking by my side.
Y-You're just way too cute!