The Azatoth Empire's reign spans
a myriad of stars and planets.
And now, they've got their
sights set on Planet Earth...
No matter how many times I see it,
I'm blown away by this design.
Earthlings have impeccable taste,
that's for sure.
Certainly makes you want to sit down and
chat with the original creator, doesn't it?
a
ri
e
nai
Impossible...
ki
ka
ku
gai
Unprecedented...
ta
ma
ra
nai
Out of this world...
We run into each other on the catwalk
BLACK
HOLE
Your eyes suck me in like a black hole
tsun
tsun
da
You act so cold but flaunt your stuff
Why the hell is my heart racing?
They're saying it'll rain this afternoon
So maybe I should have an early lunch
ba
cchi
I see you gleaming in the sunlight
What an angel
I'll always be under your paw
My love for you warps the space-time continuum
You quickly become the center of my universe
do
kkun
ba
de
Ba-dump, ker-thump
I just can't take it anymore...
Forget fate or miracles
BANG
Us crossing paths was a big bang
Every star across the night sky is our miracle
I don't want my love to go to your head
I just want you to stay with me...
#11. Warriors
Why does Mechayozora have the same
pattern on the underside of his foot...?
Perhaps this design isn't an
Earthling creation after all...
The underside of a cat's foot... A cat's footprint...
That means this design must be...!
The shirt of a human who
was crushed by a giant cat!
Um... then what about this outfit Liza gave me...?
It's covered in cat footprints!
A distinctive pattern such as this...
It must be a symbol that
cats use to brand their slaves!
I see... So these are the garments of a slave...
Uh, I don't think it's quite as morbid
as you're making it out to be...
It's placed underneath the foot...
Could its purpose be to reduce
strain on their feet?
There you go! I'm pretty sure that's what they're for!
But what if they extend like tentacles,
and they use them to capture prey?!
Or maybe even to deposit their eggs!
Liza, the conversation is increasingly
taking a turn for the strange.
Perhaps they leave behind
a painful stinging sensation!
Or they tear into your stomach
and release larvae!
Can't you stop them?
Listen up.
The fleshy areas on the bottom of their feet are called
"paw pads," and they're used for gripping their prey.
Hold on, is that really the best
way for you to phrase it?
I knew it! They are tentacles!
See? You've given them the
wrong end of the stick again!
And the T-shirt isn't part of a slave uniform...
I mean, people who like to wear that kind of stuff are
usually the ones whose entire lives revolve around cats...
So depending on how you look at it...
I guess they kind of are their slaves in a way...?
Stop overthinking yourself and
just tell them that they're wrong!
Why must you insist on saying misleading things
that are only gonna make the situation worse?!
Darn it, this is frustrating!
Forget it!
Let me go there and explain it all myself!
This is Kasumi Yanagi, from Planet Earth.
She was kind enough to volunteer
to sit in on our meeting.
Good to have you, Kasumi.
I didn't think they'd actually invite me...
Guess I'll introduce you to
the members who're here today.
Leader of the 16th Squadron, Shamil.
Hello.
Second-in-Command, Gaim.
Our newest recruit, Mithra.
Hiya!
Director of Biological Research, Nhapat.
Thank you very much for coming.
And this is the voice you always hear on my
transmissions, Deputy Commander Amat.
I'm Amat, Deputy Commander of the Thrale Research
Vessel, 4th Interstellar Research Squadron.
Nice to meet you.
Now then... We've asked you here
for a very specific reason.
We'd like for you to teach us about
the creatures known as "cats."
"Teach you...?"
There's nothing to teach. Cats are just cute.
And there's nothing scary about 'em either.
She spilled the beans!
And she was so blunt about it!
I get it...
Your pithiness is meant to signify an iron will,
along with a refusal to yield to the likes of cats.
No, no. It's not that serious.
We are aware that cats appear
friendly from the outside.
But if they were merely "cute"...
I doubt Liza and Fianna would
have such strong reactions.
Huh?
Opening portals to Earth...
Meow, meow!
...and leaping in while shrieking...
C'mon, there's a good kitty!
Following Mechayozora around with a strange rod,
crawling on all fours...
He saw everything...!
People don't start foaming at the mouth at the sight
of something that's merely "cute."
Then, there's that design...
Indeed, it's quite charming.
But something about it makes me uneasy.
What is this sensation in my chest...?
I feel it poisoning my mind...
I can only assume it's a method
of brainwashing perpetrated by cats!
You're right... It must be poisoning our minds!
Your face looks like a tomato...
Yes, but Miss Kasumi's mind does
not appear to be adversely affected at all.
Good point.
I had imagined that the
Earthling population would have
Earthlings
a lifeless look in their eyes
when being controlled by cats.
Earthlings
She must have undergone training
to withstand the brainwashing.
Perhaps she possesses the power to resist them.
Like I said, cats are just ordinary animals that—
She does wield a certain amount of power...
After all, she's a dog person.
If you bring that up now,
you're only going to confuse them more!
"Dog person?!"
What is a "dog person?!"
Don't get all bent out of shape!
Am I, like, invisible to these guys or something?!
A war between cats and dogs
has raged on for many years now...
Are these dogs allied with humans?
Dogs are just ordinary animals, too!
My precious family!
Cats, who aim to dominate humanity...
and dogs, who aim to coexist with humanity...
It's not that kind of argument!
And Kasumi is a soldier
who fights alongside dogs...!
In other words, the Resistance!
Which means they're the warriors who fight
to liberate mankind from the tyrranical cat overlords!
I'm telling you, you're wrong!!
What's the matter with all of you?!
How are you gonna invite me to outer space
and then not listen to a word I say?!
You're absolutely right... That was rude of us.
My apologies.
Then please, won't you educate us?
What is it that the
Mankind Liberation Army does, exactly?
That is a delusion, and I refuse to entertain it!
Do you think we ought to meet a dog in person?
In order to better understand the situation?
U-Um, I don't think that's a good idea right now...
If they all lose their minds at the same time
like me and Fianna, we're screwed!
I'll make it happen one of these days,
so just be patient.
Is it because we offended Kasumi...?
If she has that much influence...
she really must be a key player in the Liberation Army.
Do you think she's their princess?!
Either that or their commander...
That's it, I'm showing them a picture of Masamune...
Woah, woah, woah! Don't do it, Kasumi!!
Huh?
Mithra, what's wrong?
Fianna...
Mechayozora's blocking the hallway...
I-Is it safe? He won't hurt me, will he...?
You're not a big fan of him, are you?
No... It's just that I never know what Mechayozora
wants or what he's gonna do next...
He walks around with this air of pride...
Like he's superior or something.
I think it has to do with the look on his face, honestly...
Like, "I could get away with murder..."
Well, of course he could... He's adorable.
If only you saw a real cat!
I know you'd change your mind!
Cats are so cruel... It's as though they enjoy
tormenting people just for the sake of it!
It's like they think of humans
as nothing more than playthings!
For such cute creatures,
they sure are awful, aren't they?
Yeah, I wish cats would treat me like a plaything!
They won't even give me the time of day!
You want Mithra to meet Yozora...?
If Mithra were to see a real cat,
I'm sure she'd come around!
Anyone who sees Yozora is
bound to fall under his spell!
Good point... I think so, too.
C'mon... Let's at least give it a try.
We can turn Mithra to the dark side...
Yes...
If we experiment with
someone averse to cats first,
rather than showing him to someone
who's weak to their charm...
it could work.
Has it already been three
years since you and I met...?
We were enemies at first, weren't we?
Why are you bringing up memories from the past?
I'm about to show you a cat, so don't die on me, alright?
"Die?!"
What you lack in intelligence, you make up for in spirit.
I know you'll make it back home...
Wait, back home from where?!
Where are you taking me?!
Relax, Mithra...
It's only scary at first, I promise...
You'll start to feel the pleasure soon enough...
You're about to enter into a whole new world...!
What, are you gonna drug me?!
N-No, something isn't right!
Liza, Fianna...
The cats are controlling you, aren't they?!
You're already slaves to the—
Wh-What's this...?
Huh? What is this...
sil...kiness...?
Is that... a cat?
The very being that drove level-headed Liza
and kind-hearted Fianna to the brink of insanity...
What has it done to them...? I won't stand for this...
Cute... So cute...
I have to save my friends.
How can something... be so cute?!
That noise!
Oh my god, it's frickin' adorable!
No, wait! It doesn't matter how cute it is!
This thing poses a threat to our lives!
But it's so damn precious!
The cuteness is suffocating...
I can't take it anymore...
It's too cute!!
M-Mithra...?
Are you okay?
Yeah. Everything makes sense now.
You weren't being controlled by cats.
You became His Mewjesty's slaves...
of your own free will, didn't you?!
"H...His Mewjesty"?
I can't believe it...
I actually touched His Mewjesty!
That was my first time...
I'll never wash this hand again!
The cuteness worked a little too well...
Be careful! If you jump from that height,
you might get hurt!
Please, use me as your step stool!
It seems Mithra has fallen victim
to the cats' brainwashing...
Yes... It's a tragedy...
I refuse to stand by and watch them
destroy our subordinates!
From this point on, us Azatoth soldiers
are officially at war with cats!
Now, let's go... To Earth!
Shamil and the others have begun preparing to invade
Planet Earth in order to exact revenge against cats.
I know they're skilled fighters
with long military careers, but...
Even so, I'm worried about them.
Kasumi! Please, have the
Mankind Liberation Army help them!
Oh, are we still doing that?
But what the hell does he want me to do...?
You're the one who showed Mithra a cat.
What, am I supposed to team up with
your soldier buddies and beat you senseless?
Don't go giving them any ideas...
We heard the whole thing!
Wh-What?!
Y-You four...?!
What are you guys doing here?
Garmie told me all about it, Liza...
When you introduce your alien pals to Earth animals,
you make it a point to show 'em cats, don'tcha?
As if they're the epitome of
cute Earth animals or something...
Seems like you're trying to plant
the seeds of bias in their heads!
It's unfair! It's always cats with you!
Yeah, what she said!
Alright, so, let me guess...
You want me to introduce them to your pets, too?
Damn straight!
My darling Mamehiko is cute
on an intergalactic level, too!
You sure, Grandpa?
We may be watching the downfall
of mankind in real time!
I can't think of a better way to go
than being killed by cuteness...
Hm, might not be a bad idea.
I've always opted to show off my beloved Yozora...
but instead of throwing them in
the deep end with the ultimate pet,
maybe I should start with the slightly
inferior ones to ease them into it...
The hell's that supposed to mean?!
They're not inferior!
Everyone knows Negimaru
is the strongest of 'em all!
No, Mamehiko is!
You really should've expected
to get beat up for that, Liza...
These cats have done something to drive Liza,
our most talented researcher, mad...
Which is why we're sending
the best of the best this time!
Then we shall lead the charge!
L
X
Dy
Doma Jalander
Dod
Domb
Doma Jalander
Doma U
Doma E
Doma Jp
Doma Jalander
Doma Jf
Doma Jav
Doma Jalander
Doma Jalu
Doma Jalaz
Doma Jalander
Doma Jalaw
Doma Jalan&
Doma Jalander
Doma Jalandg
Doma Jalanden
Doma Jalander
"Best of the best"? You're making me blush...
F
Eu
Erma Annes
Eh
Ere
Erma Annes
Ern
Ermt
Erma Annes
Ermx
Erma B
Erma Annes
Erma R
Erma Av
Erma Annes
Erma Ank
Erma Anl
Erma Annu
Erma Annes
Erma Anns
Erma Annep
Erma Annes
Erma Anneh
Just sit back and relax, Commander.
G
Lz
Lenny Ein
Lh
Lei
Lenny Ein
Lez
Lenu
Lenny Ein
Lenx
Lennd
Lenny Ein
Lennr
Lenny P
Lenny Ein
Lenny M
Lenny Eq
Lenny Ein
Lenny Ek
Lenny Eid
Lenny Ein
Lenny Eij
It'll all be over in no time.
In the name of the 16th Squadron,
we shall fulfill our duty.
S
V
Kw
Kaya Garda
Kg
Kan
Kaya Garda
Kab
Kayz
Kaya Garda
Kaya M
Kaya L
Kaya Gk
Kaya Garda
Kaya Gj
Kaya Gas
Kaya Garda
Kaya Gar%
Kaya Garp
Kaya Gardx
Kaya Garda
Kaya Gardv
G
Bs
Battra Swunk
Baj
Ban
Batf
Battra Swunk
Batty
Battc
Battrv
Battra Swunk
Battra E
Battra J
Battra Sr
Battra Swunk
Battra Swo
Battra Swy
Battra Swue
Battra Swunk
Battra Swunb
So we're dealin' with a real pain in the ass, eh?
Battra Swund
Battra Swunk
Now, let the invasion of Planet Earth begin!
Yessir!
Okay, so why are you a part of this, Mukai?
Well, I guess...
I just can't sit back and let Yozora
take all the glory as "the perfect cat," y'know?
A team of five, eh?
I take it you are Kasumi of the
Mankind Liberation Army.
And you must be her comrades-in-arms.
Your help is greatly appreciated.
Ah... They've got quite the
intimidating exterior, don't they?
Those are the faces of brave, experienced warriors...
ones who've seen much bloodshed.
Well, we know they're terrible judges of character...
Each of these special agents has
the power to bring a planet to its knees...
And with their abilities combined,
there exists no greater force in the universe.
I-It's adorable!!
What the hell is this creature?!!
Impossible!! This can't be...!!
This planet is a nightmare!!
Oh my gosh, they're... they're pwecious!
What the hell happened out there?!
Commander... it was a massacre...
There were more... than just cats...
Cats aren't... the planet's only... anomaly...
I mean, the cats were cute, but...
Every animal on Planet Earth...
Is... impossibly...
So ador—
"Ador...?"
They couldn't handle it, could they?
There's more than just cats?!
Are you telling me there are other animals
that pose the same level of risk as cats?!
Send as many soldiers as you like.
The number of casualties is only going to increase.
You're probably the only one
who could actually survive...
Shamil Naga, Strongest Hero in the Cosmos.
You wanna know more about cats?
Come and see for yourself.
Most Popular
Reaction Rankings
Mitsuro
Emily
Momo
Mamehiko
Negimaru
Welcome... to Planet Earth.
So that is a cat... I see.
The organism with a perfect physical form,
unparalleled in its magnificence...
And? Is this creature supposed to impress me?
Wha—?! He's... totally unfazed?!
It's mildly appealing at best, wouldn't you say?
Uh... Don't get me wrong.
I don't think it's cute or anything.
A proud warrior like myself would
never be concerned with frivolous thoughts
such as whether or not something is "cute..."
If cats aren't dangerous,
then there's no need to vanquish them.
I'm leaving.
Wha—? Already?
W-Wait a second, Shamil...
You really don't care at all?
Now that an adorable cat is
staring you in the face?
What exactly did you expect, Liza?
The same sort of disgraceful
display that Fianna put on?
Okay, then explain why your
legs are wobbling like that.
Oh please... I'm not shaking at all!
You totally are!
He's so cute that it's making you weak in the knees!
I-I can hardly breathe...
Earth's atmosphere must not agree with me...
You've got butterflies in your stomach! Admit it!
I know nothing of these so-called butterflies!
A warrior such as I?! Absolutely not!
Besides, that creature isn't
cute in the slightest!
It's ugly... hideous...
Gotta hug it...! No, it's disgusting...!
This man's got some insane pride...
and unshakable willpower!
A hero through and through!
However...
I know you're bluffing, but you've got a lotta nerve
calling my beloved Yozora ugly!
And I know for a fact that you're screaming
internally about how damn precious he is!
How dare you! You mean to rich... ridicule me?!
I ham... I am not putting on an ash...
an act, you hear me?!
You can't even talk! Sit down right now!
You're not leaving! Not until Yozora's excruciating
cuteness has you writhing in pain on this floor!
How's Shamil holding up?
It looks like... he's playing with the cat right now.
If you insist, then I suppose
one game wouldn't hurt...
The feather toy isn't for the faint of heart...
So don't cry if he decides to ignore you.
Of course one such as I wouldn't cry!!
I am a man!!
He's losing brain cells!
This is absurd...
What could possibly happen when I wave this—
Lucky you, Shamil... He's actually playing with—
Did you suck a lemon or something?!
Ooh, and he's standing on your lap!
Okay, now you look like you're full of helium!
Does this not qualify
as "disgraceful behavior" to you?!
What's going on down there?!
Can you turn on your video feed?!
You probably don't wanna see this...
Huh...?
Wh-Who's that...?
C-Commander...?
Is he... facing off against the cat?!
I'm surprised he's still conscious...
That's our commander for you!
They're impressed by him right now...?
You see? I made it out completely unscathed.
I don't see what the big deal is with cats.
Fine... I admit defeat.
Now then... I suppose it's time to head home...
Would you mind giving me a few moments alone?
Oh, and cover your eyes and ears as well, please.
Sure... No problem.
Cuuuuute!! So cuuuuute!!
Cute wittle kitty!!
He's so cuuuuute!!
Cute, cute, cute!!
I'm so happy he likes me!!
Cuteeeee!!
Commander Shamil...!
Wh-What does he mean, "likes him?"
Gah!! I love you, cute wittle kitty!!
He makes it sound like a pet...
There's nothing to teach. Cats are just cute.
So frickin' cute!!
No... Was she right...?
How the hell can something even be so cute?!!
Cats don't derive power from
brainwashing their victims...?
I don't understand!! It just doesn't make sense!!
Could it really be that they're just... that cute?
Cute wittle baby itty-bitty kitty!!
Meow!! Meow!!
Oh gosh!! Oh my gosh!!
So unbelievably cute that they bewitch everyone in
their presence and force them into submission...?
Cute!! Cute!! Cute!!
So cuuuute!!
wotchi wotchi are wa nanda? seimeitai no "se"!
Watch, watch, what's that I see? A lively lifeform!
saachi saachi moshikashite tomodachi ka?
Search, search, do you wanna be friends?
nyanboree nyanboree nyanboree nyanboree de
Myamboree! Myamboree! Myamboree! Myamboree! So...
moffii! moffii!
Fwuffy! Fwuffy!
nyanboree nyanboree nyanboree nyanboree de
Myamboree! Myamboree! Myamboree! Myamboree! So...
moffii! moffii!
Fwuffy! Fwuffy!
nyaa
Meow!
kawaii wa seigi sonja sonja aku to wa nan zo?
Cuteness is justice! So what are the evils standin' in its way?
urusai mama? kenka? shukudai? osouji?
Mom being naggy? Getting into fights? Homework? Cleaning?
kokoronai hitotachi ga afureteiru zo
There's a lotta cruel people out there
nakayoku shitekunakya muu muu da!
Better get along or you'll be a grumpypants!
chikyuu wa fushigi na toko de kaiseki taihen
Earth's a strange planet, and studying it's a pain
risou dake ja omanma taberenai ga
But just thinking about it won't put food on the table!
nishin geppo shikou sakugo
Through steady effort and trial and error
teinei ni tema hima kakeru no ga, otoshidokoro!
Give it a go and your hard work will pay off!
wotchi wotchi are wa nanda? seimeitai no "se"!
Watch, watch, what's that I see? A lively lifeform!
mikke mikke UTOPIA kamo?
I spy, I spy, a utopia?
doukaina?
There's no way, right?
nyanboree de waai! yatta ne nyanboree de uu!
Myamboree, hurray! Yippee! Myamboree, whoo!
muzukashii koto wa chotto oyasumi nanoda
We deserve a break after all that hard work
ashita mata ganbarou tte iettara OK!
As long as we promise we'll get back to it tomorrow, it's A-OK!
choi sawagi shichaou!
Let's have a party!
sore ga sunawachi heiwa tte yatsu janai?
That's what peace is all about, no?
iizo! moffi-ffii fuwafuwa ni
Alright! Fwuffy-ffy, dive right in
moffi-ffi tobikondara
Fwuffy-ffy, right into the fluff
ai tte yatsu ga wakari sou desu
And you'll start to know what love really means
totte oki no nukumori de
Lovingly conceal me
meromero ni tsutsundene moffii
In all that warmth of yours, so fwuffy
san, ni, ichi... kyou mo otsukaresama!
3, 2, 1... Good work today!
goronago chokomaka chochoi to goshujin
Catnapping nonstop, one second, Master
omimi wo haishaku, hidari kara nyaa
I need you for a sec, gimme your left ear-Meow!
nyanboree nyanboree nyanboree nyanboree de
Myamboree! Myamboree! Myamboree! Myamboree! So...
moffii! moffii!
Fwuffy! Fwuffy!
nyaa
Meow!
Humans are summoned onto the spaceship,
and its captains land on Earth.
Two worlds of cuteness... are about to collide.
Next time, Episode 12: "Too Cute."