The recent Bottle Battles
and the AI stuff...
Perhaps those wouldn't have happened
if I had just opened up to you from the start.
Whatever could you mean?
Open or not, I believe in you
and would follow you regardless.
That will never change.
That's why, when you sent me
the coordinates during the battle...
Could it be...?
Sir Citrus?!
So you're planning to
make an entrance soon, are you, sir?
I understand.
I shall fill the time until then.
I'm here!
What the?!
Sorry. Stole your job, didn't I?
I wanted you to be the first to know.
Plus, I had to give back the Bottleman
you lent me.
Couldn't get into your element without it, anyways.
I couldn't imagine you switching
to B-DACT's side, though.
I'm terribly sorry for all the trouble I have caused.
It's okay. Besides, I've been worried about you too.
Ever since I went undercover,
you stopped appearing in Bottle Battles.
Kurenai Haku appears to be
absent from this Bottle Royale as well.
Many are wondering
why he's been gone so long.
My... I can't believe you've been
thinking of me this whole time...
I understood how you felt back then...
I don't think I can go any further
if I don't apologize.
I'm really sorry.
And thank you for believing in me
no matter what.
Hey.
Want to make rice balls together?
Yes!
...so from here onwards,
I will be retiring from Bottle Battling.
Additionally, at his own heavy desire,
Citrus has given up the title of Bottle King.
Therefore, he will battle going forward
simply as a Bottle Battler.
Does this mean that battles will continue
without a Bottle King?
No. In line with the BMA's new regulations,
the management has nominated
a provisional Bottle King.
Who is it? Who did you nominate?!
The new Bottle King is...
Whuh?!
Cota, you're...
...the Bottle King?!
First I'm hearing about this!
Now, calm down, Cota!
Hayari Ponta Returns
Let's all chill and eat rice balls together.
I have black tea to top it off!
Citrus?!
He brought Kurenai Haku with him?!
Sorry for bottling up so much.
I think I really do
want to be here with all of you!
If that's okay...
Are you crazy? No matter what happens,
you're still Ponta, dude!
We missed you, Ponta!
Thanks, everyone!
Whuh, now then...
Haku, can I get your autograph?
There should be some room on the left!
Ponta, feel free to sign "Citrus" there too!
Can you not act like that here?
Ponta's been through a lot, you know?!
I know, but I can't help it!
Any boy would do this when he meets his idol!
This isn't the time for that!
Maybe some other time!
How about we battle then, Ponta?
Your match will be Bowling.
Three rounds, thirty seconds each.
Does that sound good?
Heck yeah it does!
So be it, then!
I've got this in the bag!
Hm? What's up?
Just thinking, I made the right call
letting Origin into your hands.
Oh, okay.
Wait...
What?!
That concludes Round 1!
It's a draw!
Ponta, keep going! Tell us more!
What did you mean by that?!
Well, here's the thing.
Origin was frozen in research,
and I was afraid B-DACT would get their hands on it,
so I used the ID from when I was experimented on
to get access to the research facility.
I managed to get Origin back from Agent Ryo,
but the security was too tight to get Origin outside.
So for the time being,
I decided to hide it in the locker room.
So you're the one who put him in my locker?
Not quite. I put it in my locker!
You just opened the wrong one by mistake!
Huh?
Huuuh?!
Before I could get it back,
you connected with Origin,
and made him Colamaru.
A Bottleman?
Wow, Cota! Didn't know you had a Bottleman.
It's not mine...
Cola...maru?
So that's what happened!
Yeah, I didn't see it coming.
It sure gave me a scare!
Why didn't you lock your locker...?
Seriously...
Mr. Ryo!
We recieved word from the hospital.
Miss Eri has regained consciousness...
She has?!
You're really on top of this!
I gotta get back into the game!
You think so?
So, like I was saying before...
Yeah?
I'm still glad that you got Colamaru out of Origin.
When that happened,
I was in a cold sweat on the inside.
I thought I might've gotten you involved
in something disastrous.
So I tried to keep you safe in secret.
But...
the more I battled with others,
got blasted away by traps,
and ate with others...
I started to get it.
Ponta, gimme another!
I started to get the meaning of enjoying
Bottle Battles and everyday life.
That concludes Round 2.
Evidently, it's another draw.
And the more I saw you, I would think...
"He's going to change Bottle Battling.
I just know it."
Change Bottle Battling?
You're going to make a world
where everyone will enjoy Bottle Battling a lot more.
That's why...
when B-DACT started forcing vital sync onto everyone,
I just couldn't take it anymore.
I had to be Citrus again and put a stop to it.
And then...
I was not expecting you, Citrus.
It's time for a change of plans.
I will adopt you as an external device.
So you're planning to make use of my body?
Alright. Do it.
It'll be more convenient for me anyways.
Intent of statement unclear.
Requesting explanation.
I'm going to take you over
and use you back.
If you think you stand a chance,
then come at me!
And you know the rest.
I lost to the AI and made everyone suffer.
All because I went too far.
Oh, you're here, boy!
Why are you here?
Ryo! This man has been assisting with Eri's treatment.
It's the AI! It went through the medical system
and interfered with her consciousness!
Now everything should be fine!
I removed the effect the AI had on her!
Is that so, Professor?
Let's go over this calmly over here!
Oh, but the AI is still active,
it hasn't been shut off!
Move along, now.
Your mother's fine now.
You can talk to her normally now,
and can visit her whenever you want.
Hey, cut it! I'm not done talking!
Thank you very much.
I'm listening, take your time!
Absolutely not!!
Come in.
Ryo?!
M-Mom...
True, a lot happened before,
but none of that is your fault!
Yeah! Don't blame yourself for all that!
We're just glad you made it out in one piece!
Thanks, guys.
You're always there to help me when I need it.
Let's get the final round going!
Well then...
Splash Volcano Energy!
I think I can do it too now...
I can battle just like Cota...
ResQ!!
Square More in action?!
Quatro Impact!
When days come where I can't seem
to focus on anything (Everyday Everyday)
You strike first?! Attacking me with your gaze
And it's got me totally off-balance
I can't keep waving it off, no no
That concludes the final round.
Isn't it about time I told you?
10–8, game Ponta.
Thanks to the points from this round,
But when I'm standing in front of you
Ponta wins the battle!
I can't stop my heart from pounding
out of my chest (Ugh, I give up...)
That was so awesome, dude!
So please help me! Help me! I try to call out
That was great, Ponta!
I felt the fizz!
Help me! Help me! But nothing comes out, no-no-no
Thanks! So did I!
I can sing, sha-la-la
But my words just do-do-don't work
They stop right at the exit!
It's so much easier to go all-in
when you're having fun!
I better be off now.
But to me, to me
You're already leaving?
No one else will be as special to me
as you are, no-no-no
Yeah, just a bit busy today.
There you are!
If I could just be bold and say "I love you"
Coga Cota!
I knew you'd be here, Master!
It would be so easy
But I can't, so please come to my ResQ!!
Huh?
What's going on?
Master Cota! Congratulations on
becoming Bottle King!
Tell us, how do you feel?
What is it, Cota?
Sorry, I think I oughta get going first!
Take care!
You had a dream?
Yeah. There was this little imp in it.
The kid would run around a lot,
and I would try to catch him,
telling him off for doing bad things.
Like tag or hide and seek.
What happened to him?
He just disappeared at one point.
That's when I woke up.
But...
Mom, I have to apologize to you.
For what?
I got too into Bottle Battling...
If it weren't for that,
then you wouldn't have collapsed...
What are you talking about?
That's just poor timing is all.
No one's fault, now, is it?
You're still the same as ever, Ryo.
You're like a bottle cap.
Huh?
A cap's purpose is to stay firm
and keep the contents of the bottle inside.
But...
the best caps...
are the ones that soar freely.
How do you...?
Mom?
That kid from my dream...
I can't help but feel like
he's not done making mischief yet...
You'll be in the next Bottle Royale, won't you?
Tell us, are you excited for your
first battle on defense?
I dunno, man!
Cota!
Master!
Ryo, do something!
Ryo!!
Next Time
All Hands on Deck! The Bottle King Scramble!
This is Hocari Ryo.
Being the new President of BMA
will be no easy task.
I'll still be the Chairman!
Actually, I'm the new President.
Get fizzed up again next week!