Whaaat?!
Halloween, Halloween!
October 31st, 10:31
It may be Halloween for everyone else,
but it's got nothing to do with me!
'Cuz today...
is my birthday!
Gotta set out the cake and drinks.
What the heck?!
What are you huffing about?
Have a snack!
Yo, Baku!
Why are you decorating
for Halloween?
I have your cake right here, Miss Kuromi.
Today's a big day!
I knew you'd get it, Gureco!
I got you the perfect costume!
But I couldn't decide what was best,
so I bought quite a few.
That's way more than "a few..."
I can't believe you guys...
Why are you getting into the Halloween spirit?!
You know today's my birthday!
Oni...
"Miss Kuromi's Birthday Plan!
(And Halloween Celebration)"
They're unbelievable.
All they care about is Halloween.
Kuromi's Truth Bombs
What happened to celebrating my birthday?
I feel so stupid for getting my hopes up.
This world stinks...
I hate it so much!
What the?
Kuromi's keyword!
"A mysterious dashing prince."
What's a prince doing in a zombie world?
Could it be...?