Kuromi, let's move!
Absolutely, my prince!
Is he taking me on a date?
Onwards!
Wait, what?
Alright! Alright! Alright!
C'mon!
Why are you making me pull you?
So fast! Look at you go!
Who are you anyways?!
I'm Nico.
I've come on Universe Patrol duties
to assist you.
Universe Patrol For Dummies!
Universe Patrol For Dummies:
Bite-Sized Cartoon Version.
Bite-Sized Cartoon Version
There are many different worlds
born from different variations.
This is called the "multiverse."
Multi
verse
It is the job of the Universe Patrol
to oversee the multiverse.
The end.
The End
I can't even see the screen!
Oh, whoops.
It seems like a space-time orifice
opened up in your world,
and brought you to this one.
Okay, I guess...
This seems like a heavy plot
for a bite-sized show.
But I take it those aren't
actually my friends, then.
Wait...
I left my vent account wide open...!
I have to get back home
before they see!
Nico, do something about them!
Universe Patrol isn't supposed to interfere
with any worlds.
Man, you're totally useless!!
But I know how you can get out of here.
We just have to find the you
from this world.
Huh? The me from this universe?
Thanks for comin'!
Kuromi's keyword!
"Scallion cola!"
Oh, the one I drank before.
It tasted pretty good.