These fan-made subtitles are not for sale, rent or any profit whatsoever.
Please support official  Snack World anime releases in your home country.
See lumpstud.tumblr.com for certain translation notes.
This is Snack World, the hallowed
ground of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam and
people have handy smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
...And my name's Chup.
My village was burnt down by the evil
land-destroying merchant, Vinegar Khan,
and I've embarked on a journey
to get my revenge 1000-fold!
The tickets to King Oyster City, where
Vinegar is, cost 20 million gillan.
So I'm on an adventure searching for
big treasure to make loads of cash!
[Chup humming theme song]
Alright, let's go on another big adventure today!
I can't be bothered, I'm way too hungry...
Ep. 12: The Prince That Became a Goblin
Well, what's for lunch?
Hmm...
[Ping]
Oh, it's from the king!
What now, more summons from Princess Melora?
What if she wants me to be the photographer for her next photo album?
Right, Mayone?
Don't you know by now? She's just gonna give us another pathetic request, mind you.
"My Melora's in series trunb e."
"My Melora's insseris trnbb;e! Grt herw ayoncw!!"
"Gurt heraw ayoncaw."
Uh. What exactly does that say, Chup?
Not sure...
Let me see.
"My Melora's in series trunb e,"
"Gurt heraw ayoncaw..." that didn't help!!
Now...
It sounds like the king was typing that in a hurry.
I sure hope nothing really bad's going down at the castle.
At any rate, let's get a move on!
Princess Melora! It's me, Chup!
Huh?
Good, you're here, Chup!
Oh, Minister Crouton!
"Minister?" Did you get promoted?
Didn't you hear the news of his replacement?
Awesome, you're risin' on up!
Nah, I'm just serving as a substitute for Minister Gastank in his absence.
Though Gastank's disappearance was our fault, wasn't it...?
- Hm? What did you say?
N-nothing!
Thing is, some stuff has been going down since I took post.
What happened? Is the king okay? What about Melora?
The king heard some tough news and broke down in shock.
Tough news?
Oh, there you are, Chup!
Your majesty, what's going on?
Chup... My Melora, at this rate, she's....
she's...on the brink of death.
Whaaaat? It can't be!!
Basically...
[Melora moaning]
Melora, are you okay?!
She's under medical examination. I'm afraid we cannot let you pass even if you're the king.
Daddy...
Melora!
I'll go check in on her.
Sir, how's the princess looking?
[Melora moaning]
She just overate.
I can't eat any more...
[Sighs]
Sir, I'd like to talk about our marriage arrangements.
Guh, this isn't really the place to talk about that.
Excuse me, what?
You heard me. We're getting married!
What's with that?
He's going to marry me!
What are you talking about? It's me!
It'll be me!
[Both] Me!
Hold it, enough. Cut it out, you two!
As a matter of fact, my parents have decided who I'm marrying.
What?!
Then you have to cancel it now!
The wedding is next week, it's too late.
Huh?
IT'S TOO LAAAATE!!
It's...too late?!
T-t-t-too late?!
Waaah...how awful!!
- Your majesty!!
This is unfair!!
I-i-it can't be good if the nurses are crying!!
Your majesty!
I've done all that I can. Girls, wait!!
Even the doctor threw in the towel!
Meeeloooraaa...
- Your majesty!!
That's what happened!
Oh no, Princess Melora...
Right now, the princess is resting,
unaware of her own fate... [Sniffles]
Princess Melora~!! What on earth am I to do?!
Isn't there any way we can save her?
There is but one way to save Melora.
Huh?!
Far up north from French Toaster
are the Macaroni Mountains.
Taking down the Monster at the summit will reward you with Eternal Life.
Gob-san, do you need to go to the little goblin's room?
- He's just trembling in fear.
I've heard some rumors about that.
The Monster at the top is a big shot that can burn through anything in its path - Phoenix.
Wha- You're actually wetting yourself??
But Minister Crouton, what is the Eternal Life?
Eh? Er, it's like, uh...
Yeah, he totes doesn't know.
He is still new to the minister thing.
[Clears throat] Moving on. Phoenix is a very formidable foe.
Our most elite forces went up against it for Melora and they were destroyed.
Chup, d'ya think we're up to the task?
It's like my grandmother once said!
Where there's a will, there's a way. Where you lose weight, you get more mates. If you have a good face!
Where there's a will, there's a way.
Where you lose weight,
you get more mates.
If you have a good face.
Where there's a will, there's a way.
Where you lose weight,
you get more mates.
If you have a good face.
-Tome
Eeegh! I'm sure someone out there likes this face!!
I'll go, your majesty!
For real, Chup?
But Phoenix is a Monster covered
head-to-toe in burning flame...
Can we really take it on...?
I burn with passion for Princess Melora!
I'm fully, flawlessly, filled with fury!!
Our equipment might get burnt though.
Huh, burnt?! That won't do...
We're doomed.
There's no need to worry. Minister, bring them out.
Your majesty, what are these?
Don't hold back, open them!
However, one of them is empty, so you'll be testing your luck.
I see! So we need luck to beat Phoenix, right?
It ain't empty! It's actually a grand
prize...their own Mimic, hehehehe!
Well then, Chup.
Hm, which one do I begin with...
This one, over here! Come get your prize!
This one! Yo, sweet!
Oink!
Gosh darn it!! But there's still another chance...
Ooh, what a rare prize!
That beauty is a sure and steady
masterpiece dear to the royal family.
The Clan Crystal Sword!
Those are ridiculously priced at weapon shops!
Ai'ght, next treasure chest...
I know which one I'll pick and it's...you!
This one!
Hoohoo, it's finally time! Come open it uuup!
Yeah, this one!
Grr, why'd you change your mind so quickly, you brat?!
You guys hear something just now?
Mm-mm.
I didn't hear anything. You're probably just hearing things cuz you're old.
Fellas, you don't think it was a Mimic, right?
Hoooo...
Let's just open this up. Yah!
Wow, check out the length on this thing! Sweeeet!
That's a rare item too! It's the Clan Metal Lance that goes with the shield!
King, you didn't have to!
I'd spare anything for my Melora's sake.
Quest
Get the Eternal Life
[All shouting]
We can use that to attack without being burnt by its flame!!
Thank you, your majesty!
DANGIT! Now I'm left with having to jump out and attack...
Looks like there's no need for this empty box now.
Understood, I'll pass it down to the incinerator underground.
Underground? Incinerator?
[Gasp]
I have a message of encouragement!!
My website is mimictreasurechest.com...!!
Mountain Range of the Dead: Macaroni Mountains
Urrrgh, what's with this mountain...?
It feels like it's sucking the life outta me...
Huh?
You brats dare disturb these mountains?!
[Trembling]
Wh-wh-who's there?!
I'm the reaper sent from the underworld...
R-r-reaper?!
If you wish to climb this mountain, you must give up...
your precious lifespan!
WHAAT?!
Just which one of you should I pick~...
You! The old geezer.
Eh, me?!
I'll be taking your lifespan!
[Yelps]
Here we go, yaaah!!
It's sucking the lifespan out of Gob-san!!
Gob-san!
Ugh...it seems my adventure may be coming to an end...
Save Melora...
Gob-san!
I'm sure you can...
Don't die on us!!
That's all I...ask of you...huh?
Hahaha...I only took, like, 5 hours off your life, haha.
Only 5 hours? So that means Gob-san is perfectly fine??
Of course not, 5 hours is a big deal for the elderly!
Give me back my 5 hours this instant!
Hm? Isn't something fishy about this reaper?
I can hear its voice coming from over there.
Ah? Oh, no, they fraught me!!
You're the reaper?
And that voice before was your's?
You can't say I didn't put my afterlife into it.
Death-kun
I'm a reaper in training.
Thanks to my practice, I can suck up a whole *5 hours* from lifespans now!
5 hours is cute...
But if you take any more I'm gonna wipe you out.
Aah, I'll guide you to the mountain's summit!
Great! I'll register your snack.
Gob-san, we ain't making memories here.
Haha. Just climed a mountain.
[Pants]
Here we are!
It's sweltering...
Oh?
It's Phoenix!!
Phoenix
Seems like it just woke up!
[Roaring]
[Screaming]
This is where we part! You guys take care of your lives, okay?
Seriously?!
Tch...come at us, Phoenix!
Clan Metal Lance!
Clan Crystal Shield!
I'm gonna deus ex machina you and get that Eternal Life!
[Roaring]
How's that?!
Nice, it repelled!
Of course! The king's recommendation holds up!
Take this!
Treasure Chest Super-Lucky Charge!
It dodged it!
Ah!
- You got 'em!
Gob-san, finish him!
Get a taste of this! My strongest spell...
[All clamoring]
Oink, oink?
Huh? I'm not burning up...where are we?
Don't tell me we're...?
Did we die from the flames?
No way...I just know I remember this place. Hm?
Older brother!
What is it?
There's something I need to talk to you about.
Oh my, that gentleman! What a hottie!
I remember!
Remember what?
That hottie was me in the past!
What? That's some leap.
Did the flames get to your head or something?
No, really! It actually was me!
So, where does that make us, then?
We must have ended up in a world of my memories.
Hear me out.
This is the "illusion" trick the Phoenix uses!
Huh, illusion?
It allows you to see the illusion of
the hidden holes in your heart.
You can tell, because they can't see us.
Wha?
However, it moves the way I thought it would...
Hello, hello, can you see me?
Gob-san, you telling us you used to be this guy?
I don't believe you.
You gotta show us proof you were really this prince.
Hmm...oh yeah!
This guy is my younger brother!
After the king, my father, stepped down,
We vowed to build a fine kingdom while supporting each other.
Again with the tall tales?
Father will be stepping down this time next year.
You will take his place as king and manage this kingdom.
Please stick by my side when that happens.
Of course. With that, I bid you farewell.
Big brother...no. Next king.
It is true!
[Gasps]
Pardon me for my rudeness all this time, Gob-san...
No, Prince Gob.
Haha, no need to change. Gob-san's fine.
Okay, so hypothetically if I'm wrong and you actually were a prince,
what led to you becoming such an ugly goblin anyhow?
Don't call me ugly!
[Everyone gasps]
- What's happening?!
Huh? Where are we?
We must be in a different memory.
Oh, there's a Gob-san over there!
[Goblin struggling]
Did you get caught in this trap?
This is the part where I became a Goblin.
How?
Well, watch and see!
This place is full of traps. It's best
you steer clear of the village.
T-thank you very much.
You're free now, free to play, eat, and sleep whenever you like.
Without the unseemly power struggles.
Sir...
Power struggles?
Gob-san, did you...hate being a prince?
I wish I could live a life of freedom like you.
You do? Oh, here's something to show my gratitude...
I might be able to fulfill your wish with this swap gem.
For real?
Please do.
At your request.
That gem will break if it's used one more time.
Take good care of it, prince.
I can't thank you enough.
And so, I stopped living my strict prince
life and began living as a free goblin.
And we all lived happily ever after.
Mayone, do you believe him now?
Yeah! You're very reserved, Gob-san.
You shoulda told us about this stuff ages ago.
Sorry.
But wait.
What about the goblin, does he
later cause trouble in the castle?
Oh yeah!
[Everyone screaming]
- This again?!
Get back here!
- We were just here!
- Oh, prince!
[Prince chuckling]
- Oh, no, haha!
This is hard to watch.
Aw. So much for the high-class prince, now
they're stuck with the sleazy goblin.
Oink...
What's with him lately...is it stress from taking on the throne?
Anyway...the time has come at last to execute the plan.
Ah, just when I need you.
I found this super movie in the castle town earlier.
You can borrow it, but it's valuable, so don't forget to give it back!
[Gasp] It's glowing!
Ugh, what now?
[Questioning gasps]
Oh, it's the prince and his younger brother!
Are they going hunting together?
Hmm? Don't tell me...
Older brother, it sure has been a while since we've hunted alone.
I won't give up today!
Hahaha...indeed.
Now, hold on. There's no prey here, no need to be hasty.
Oh, but there is prey. Older brother...it is you!!
WHAAAAA?
[Prince gasps]
Because my older brother died due to unforeseen circumstances while hunting...
I will take his place as king!
Why, you little piece of... How dare you?!
He only wanted to take the throne!
Why such a dramatic twist?!
[Prince groans]
Hm?
- A fire!!
He must be starting a fire to erase the evidence!
W...what happened to you?! Speak to me!!
Prince, this is the end for me.
Since you were targeted at a time like this...
I know it was my wish to swap our bodies, but, I can't do this to you.
We'll use this.
P-prince...
I've had months to enjoy my freedom.
I'm satifised with it.
P-prince...
Now you're back in your original body, as a healthy goblin.
Prince!!
Did he just wet himself...?
In such an otherwise serious moment too...
That's Gob-san alright...
Wait, hold on now!
What is it?
[Screaming]
We're back...?
Mayone, what is it that caught your eye?
If my deduction is correct...
The prince helped a trapped Goblin in the forest.
He said he wanted to have some ounce of freedom, and his wish was fulfilled.
The Goblin used magic to swap bodies and become the prince.
Yeah, and?
The brother took his life trying to take the throne,
and on his deathbed, the real prince came back and swapped again.
This turned the Goblin back to normal.
Which means...
The prince was a prince from the beginning,
and that Goblin was Gob-san!
Hoho, and in summary?
You are not a prince, Gob-san!
Just a Goblin who was momentarily a prince!
That is correct! ...What?
The prince was acting crude in the castle because you were inside of him, right?
Gob-san, why did you lie to us?
Hmph. I did not lie one bit! A temporary prince is still a prince, you hear?
I'll scold you later.
Watch out!!
[Gasping]
- What the?
[Screeching]
This time, you can't run.
Him...
He must've gotten here through Phoenix's power...
Do you remember me?
Did you forget you owe me a huge loan?
Gob-san!
[War cry]
[Groans]
Hmph.
That porn movie I rented back then!
Gimme back "A Prince Could Never Play Tricks!"
"A tidy and beautiful maid is in the prince's bedroom..."
"A Prince Could Never Play Tricks"
What?
A porn...
- ...Movie?
[Gulp]
Did you throw it away?!
Did you throw away "A Prince Could Never Play Tricks!"?!
No, I just don't have it with me. It's somewhere in the castle.
Thank goodness. Hear that, guys? It's alright!
Phoenix, can you do your illusion trick so I can go back and get my por-
Not in a million years.
There's no need to use the trick just for that.
I don't understand how the Phoenix's trick would even help...
Anyways, let's take down this illusion!
Take this! Super Princess Melora Eternal Life Stab!
[Screeching]
[Screaming]
konbini de kuda wo maku ukiyo wo samayou wakoudo yo
All you youngsters loitering about your lives,
shrouding the convenience stores
omaera wa genjitsu ni torinokosaresugi andeddo
You’re like undead who have left behind reality
itsumade son na koto kurikaesu no o-tsu-ka-re
How long are you going to keep doing this?
Don't you get tired of this same old routine?
hashiridase yo ENDLESS ROAD
Run forth through the endless road
koetemiroyo BORDERLINE
Go on past that borderline
sekai wa mugen ni hirogaru kouya
The world is an endless, limitless wilderness
omae no dokyou wo tameshiteiru
Where you can put your courage to the test
sumafo nankaja kensaku dekinai
It’s not something you can search for on your smartphone
sekai wa mugen ni hirogaru PARADISE
The world is an endless, limitless paradise
omaera wa giragira no
Soon you'll come to life taking in the blazing sun
taiyou kuratte ikiteiru
Raws
Translation/Typesetting/Timing
ED Karaoke
QC/Review
Raws
Translation/Typesetting/Timing
ED Karaoke
QC/Review
AnimeLand (BSJ)
Lumpstud
Noroino Hanako
NeSubs
(Specter Subs)
AnimeLand (BSJ)
Lumpstud
Noroino Hanako
NeSubs
(Specter Subs)
[Sigh] That thing burned me all over...
Don't you guys agree that the Phoenix's fantasy trick is just downright dirty?
Trying to show you your mental wounds so you'll give up on fighting...
Didn't do much to Gob-san though.
Gob-san?
Are you getting all sad by yourself thinking about how the prince died?
Oh, yeah. We have to report to the king.
Huh? My fairypon's gone!
What?!
- Aha, gotcha!!
"A Prince Could Never Play Tricks!"
"A Prince Could Never Play Tricks"
"A tidy and beautiful maid is in the prince's bedroom..."
"Purchase"
A video-sharing site? Is that all you care about?!
Agh, you better not be tryin' to buy somethin' lewd!
Take my money!
"A Prince Could Never Play Tricks"
"A tidy and beautiful maid is in the prince's bedroom..."
"Purchase"
No way!
He could really use a lesson from a real prince...
Hellooo? Any bit of prince left in there?!
Let me buy it!!
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone!
What are you teaching us about today?
"Mountain Range of the Dead: Macaroni Mountains"
Today's about the Macaroni Mountains.
The Macaroni Mountains are a dungeon covered top-to-bottom in snow.
Because a lot of the monsters you'll find are undead or demons,
it's often called the Mountain Range of the Dead.
Heheh. No matter what kind of enemy...
I'll be able to fully, flawlessly defeat them. ...Probably!
Next Time
Our next contender against the strong Phoenix is...wait, Butako?!
We get to remember my fateful encounter with her thanks to its fantasy trick.
Next time: "I'll Buy Butako!"
I'll Buy Butako
Alright, it's time for a big adventure!