This is Snack World, the hallowed
ground of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam and
people have handy smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
...And my name's Chup.
My village was burnt down by the evil
land-destroying merchant, Vinegar Khan,
and I've embarked on a journey
to get my revenge 1000-fold!
The tickets to King Oyster City, where
Vinegar is, cost 20 million gillan.
So I'm on an adventure searching for
big treasure to make loads of cash!
[Chup humming theme song]
Alright, let's go on another big adventure today!
Ep. 11: The Sirens' Life-Risking Love
We're getting close to Siren's Garden.
Chup, hold on. It's great we're getting a move on, but,
have you been thinking of a plan to beat the Siren Sisters?
Yeah!
- For real?
It's like my grandmother said!
The one who knows most goes tip-tap-tip-tap-tip!
The one who knows most
goes tip-tap-tip-tap-tip.
-Tome
Ooh!
That guy definitely never thinks.
Those wonderful words fill me with energy!
Tip-tap-tip-tap-tip!
Huh?
Really...?
Tip-tap-tip-tap-tip!
- Oink!
- Tip-tap-tip-tap-tip!
[Mayone sighs]
Tip-tap-tip-tap-tip!
- Tip-tap-tip-tap-tip!
Mayone, you too! Tip-tip-ti--
[Boys groaning]
- Oink...oink...oink...
You guys are idiots...
[Singing]
- Huh?
The fog's getting thicker!
There they are!
Who are you two?!
I am Si.
And I am Ren.
Together, we're...
♪ Siren Sisters~!
So you're the Siren Sist--aagh!
Enough of that already!
Hm?
- Again?
♪ Are you guys back for more~?
That's right, we're back! And we're here for that love potion!
You need to shape up!
Constantly going after folks who don't want to see you.
Huh?
You brats should...
- think fast and...
♪ Head on home~
♪ But we don't wanna.
What the?
[Mayone sighs]
Hm? By any chance, is there any one you would want to see?
Of course! How about it, Siren Sisters?
Huh? Uh, well...
By chance, there is.
By chance, there isn't.
♪ Cha-cha, cha-cha-cha
So which is it?
♪ Cha-cha, chance there is, there is, cha-cha
♪ Cha-chance there isn't, there isn't, cha-cha
♪ Hey!
Chup, cut it out!
♪ Cut'i, Chup, cut-cha
♪ Cut-cha, cut-cha, cha-cha-cha
♪ Cut-cha (cut-cha), cut-cha (cut-cha)
[Sigh]
♪ Cut-cha, cut-cha, cha-cha-cha-cha-cha!
♪ Cut-cha (oink!), cut-cha (oink!)
♪ Cut-cha, cut-cha, cha-cha-cha!
♪ Cha...
- Huh?
[Screaming]
Saw that one coming...
Oink...
That was some funky rhythm!
Should we consider picking up beatboxing?
What's beatboxing?
Beatboxing, or voice percussion,
is mimicking percussion instruments with your mouth.
What?
Can we go back to what were talking about before?!
Who's the guy you want to see, Siren Sisters?
Do you want to hear?
Do you really want to hear?
Fine, we'll tell you.
[Beatboxing]
Huh? Beatboxing off the bat?
♪ This here is our, this is us sisters'
♪ Story of our undying love
[Beatboxing]
Oh, what on earth did they just start?
♪ Oh yeah, this is...
Deep, deep, thick and deep,
♪ Word!
[Beatboxing]
♪ Oh, yeah!
♪ Yeah, it's even deeper than fog, what makes it...
♪ Love~
After talking with them for a while, we've figured it out!
Oh, what did you figure out?
Where's that power spot...?
What are you doing, Princess Melora?
She's dowsing.
Dowsing?
That's right, with L-shaped poles.
People use it to find underground water and lost items.
I've heard about that.
You can track down all sorts of hidden things.
Huh.
Okay, so Princess, what are you looking for?
I'm searching for power spots to boost my charm as a princess.
I've found a pimple you've been hiding!
Uh...
And it's an ugly one.
Why, you...!
Calm down, Mayone. Nothing to get worked up over.
That's right, it's okay to get rejected!
Don't worry about it.
Why is it okay for me to be rejected?!
Moving on...
Do you have any updates on the Siren Sisters?
Oh, right!
Despite the sisters being evil towards humans,
there was actually a hidden truth.
[Gastank shudders]
- What kind of truth?
It's... ohh...
"Ohh?"
Hm? It seems like you've got something hidden here.
What is it?
- Oh, my...
"Oh, my?"
[Giggling]
Forget it, I'll tell you.
Well, well? Come on and tell us!
Who's the guy you want to see?
A man, it's gotta be a man! Must
be why they quit being idols.
Why are the genies so riled up?
Don't you have a girl's night to get to or something?
A girl's night...?
- Well?
Is it a man? Spill it!
That's right.
[All laughing]
- I knew it!
But Ms. Snow White told me they had
to part ways with their boyfriend.
No, we didn't part ways.
One day, he just stopped talking to us for some reason.
We've been waiting day after day...
For him to come back...
But...
♪ He never came again~
[Sobbing]
Since then, we've been here in the forest, where we first met.
And we believe we'll meet again.
And so we keep on singing!
What a compelling love!
I understand!
We'll go look for your boyfriend and bring him back here!
For real?
That's our Chup! Speaking it like a handsome man!
Eheee!
Your backside's very manly and adorable too!
Yo, that's not fair! I wanna be aloof too!
'Kay then, me first!
[Genies being weird]
That's how it went down.
They promised to hand over the love
potion if we bring them their boyfriend.
And, this boyfriend is...?
Someone living in French Toaster!
It looks like something's hidden here!
[Gastank quivering]
With that, we'll fully, flawlessly figure out
who the Siren Sisters' boyfriend is!
I'm counting on you, Chup!
[Gastank quivering]
This is a picture taken by the paparazzi.
"Hechima Kikou"
But we can't make out their boyfriend's
face in this. Let's try searching for...
Get back here!!
- Huh?
Grr...
You can run, Penne!!
He looks like it!
- Huh?!
This time I really mean I'll never forgive you!!
Oi, wait, Tartar!
Tartar, tell us! Are you the Siren Sisters' boyfriend?
Huh?!
- Heh.
That's right, he's the Siren Sisters' boyfriend!
What?! Penne, you little...
We hit jackpot, guys!
Tartar was actually the Siren Sisters' boyfriend!
Chup, Tartar and the guy in the pic don't look a thing alike.
Huh?
Ugh! Why do you always get in my way?!
Why? Just as I thought we could get off easy.
Life's not easy with these things.
Lots of folks live here in French Toaster.
Finding just one man of many is a Herculean task.
It's like trying to find a lone sock in a pile of unfolded laundry.
That's difficult!
I just buy all the same socks in advance.
That's a good idea!
What are we talking about?
Excuse me.
Hm?
- Oink?
Behind you.
Oh, Minister. What's the problem?
Not a problem, more of a...little inquiry for you.
What is it? Advice of some sort?
You can probably tell, but we're a bit busy at the moment.
Y'know, looking for the Siren Sisters' lover.
The thing is, the whole lover thing, a, a little, advice...
What? Do you like someone out of your league?
'Cuz I can introduce you to some love masters I know.
Hey! Do you don't suppose these "love masters"
knows anything we don't about the Siren Sisters' boyfriend?
Of course, let's go see them!
This is Romeo and Juliet's matchmaking agency.
O Romeo! Wherefore art thou Romeo?
Juliet, t's because I loveth thee.
Guh, so close. Can't you get a room?
Even the wind cannot breaketh our love apart.
Hello, consultors here! Look over here!
Oh, Gob-san! Apologies!
Alas, we haven't hath found a mistress
interested in dating thee yet.
Hold on a moment! We're not here for me today.
So, Gob-san's a registered member here, isn't he?
Thought so.
[Clears throat]
Alright, Minister! Go on and ask for their advice.
Uh, no thanks, I'm not so...sure about...
Occupation: Minister. 50's, Male. Calm yet elegant appearance.
It sayeth he mumbles at the end of his words!
Sounds good!
Quick registration!
O, Romeo! Wherefore doth thy fingers moveth so fast?
Juliet, t's because I loveth thee.
They better not be planning on doing this all the time.
Good now, bid us what's on thy mind.
Huh?! No, it's just, I...
Alright! If Minister won't do it, I will!
Oh, right! Let's ask about the Siren Sisters' boyfriend first!
- I want to get married to Princess Melora!!
How do I go about that?!
We're not here to get consultation for your love!!
Ow...oww...
O Romeo!
Juliet!
That's enough of that!
- Romeo...
- Juliet!
This is a test of our love!
Ohh...
- These two, I swear...
Well then, putting a pin in the Minister for later. How about it?
You haven't heard the rumor about
the Siren Sisters' boyfriend, no?
I has't not, but I can feel his love!
That gent's still in this town, and very close by.
Close by?
C'rrect! His love is beside us!
Love beside thee!
Close!
Love!
- You sure are close...
- Don't you realize how close you are?!
Love!
- You never came to me!!
Love! Love!
- Love! Love!
[Gastank mumbling]
Shut up with the love!!
Hm, what's wrong, Minister?
Love...love is...love is so awful!! [Sobbing]
Now, now, Minister. Calm down a bit and tell us the problem.
The truth is, the Siren Sisters'
boyfriend you've been looking for is...
It's me!
Mhm, I understand...
WHAAAT?!
It was sometime just before I joined the royal palace.
[Sigh] Smells like nature!
I went and took a walk in the forest,
when I encountered the Siren Sisters.
It was love at first sight.
You mean both sisters at once...?
Yes...
What a score!
Whoo-whoo!
It was the beginning of a nightmare.
Si and Ren started fighting over who's boyfriend I'd be.
No, no, you're just making yourself sound good.
Bragging about the idea of women liking you.
What a score!
Whoo-whoo!
And that was the beginning of Season 2 of the nightmare.
Why are you talking about it like an ongoing foreign drama?
Sirens are Monsters that suck the life out of men.
In other words, anyone that became their boyfriend
had the life sucked right out of their bodies.
That's to say, the Siren Sisters' love
can and will be the death of you.
[All groaning]
What a...well...what a sore.
Because of them, 12 men have
become mummies so far.
And I...I...I don't want to become the 13th!!
It's different from the love story I imagined...
Those sisters are just plain awful...
What ever should we do...
- Everyone, listen up!
Love troubles...can only beest settl'd with love!
Settled with love?
Forsooth! Thee shouldst showeth those
folk where the line is drawn on love!
The line drawn on love?
We, in the name of love mast'rs,
shall writeth a spare break up lett'r.
You mean it?
Ay!
Good for you, Minister! Now you don't have to die!
With that letter, you can put an end to
your relationship with the Sisters!
Thank you, my life is in your hands.
Aren't you glad, Minister?
That letter's a foolproof way to break up with them!
Yes!
Eek!
Did you guys hear that?
The Siren Sisters must have caught another
man and are violently taking care of him...
What?!
Yes!!
- To the rescue!
Chup!
[Shrieks of pleasure]
Uh, Master Panpan?
Come on, now! I can't hear you!
Candle
[Panpan shrieking]
- Come on!
[Shrieking]
- How's...
- ...This?
Is he going to try dodging it...?
He's taking it to the heart...
Quit movin' around, you little geek!
I'm no geek! I'm a serious super geek!
I don't care!!
Hah! Master, here!
Psssh...
You did it!
I'm gonna open that treasure chest!
I've got this covered!
[Shutter clicks]
What will it be~?
Hurray, it's a Sarria Arrow from Peffany!
Ooh, if it's a bow, I gotta have it!
But Peffany's for me!
You've got some good whippin'!
Oh, you're pretty good at getting beaten!
Candle...
Panpan...
Candle!
Panpan!
Candle!!
Panpan!!
Cand...err??
Oh no, my hand slipped! It's still going, oh dear!
[Both screaming]
Ugh...we really got caught up in their twisted love.
[Singing]
[Gastank gasps]
This singing must be...
I am Si.
And I am Ren.
Together, we're...
♪ Siren Sisters~
[Quivering]
Siren Sisters, we've brought your boyfriend!
♪ Ta-da~
[Gasps, shrieks]
[Gasping] Too close!
You really are our beloved one.
♪ For sure~!
Alright...
- Then...
[Gasps]
Time to take your life!
Minister, the letter!
Right!
Listen to me, Si, Ren. This is how I feel!
Hm?
Get a life, you...ugly...women.
GET A LIFE, YOU
UGLY WOMEN!!
Romeo and Juliet sure left a detail or two out there...
What was that?
What...was...that?!
[Quivering]
Apologize to them, Minister!
Do it, hurry up!!
[Quivering]
[Shouting]
[Crying]
I called you ugly women. Ya hear me, you ugly women?!
Huh?
Wuh...?
[Grumbling]
How impudent of you to attempt romance with humans,
with that otherworldly face of yours!
[Groaning]
[Mayone quivering]
- Minister?
Go find a man at a monster mixer party instead!
And chat him up all you want!
[Grumbling]
Earth to Minister?
Why, you...Stalker Sisters!!
Oink-oink...
T-to the Minister's bravery...salute!!
[Shout]
Farewell, Minister!
Oink?
- Huh?
To talk to us like that...
...It really takes some guts.
♪ Now we love you even more!
- Guh, you're kidding!
♪ Now nothing can keep us apart!
W-wait a minute!!
[Singing]
Um, hello? I think there's been some kind of mistake!
Hello? Wait!
There sure is some twisted love in this forest.
Oh, Chup! They didn't give us the love potion!
Ah, you're right! Hey, Siren Sisters!!
Please give over the love potion!!
We did it! We got the love potion!
Quest
Get the Love Potion
So, what do we do about the Minister?
Hm...uhhh...
Good luck out there!!
Thank you, Chup!
Of course, anything for you, Princess Melora!
[Humming]
So who do you think Princess
Melora's gonna use the potion on?
That, I still don't understand.
It has to be me!
Yeah, no.
Then, is it me?
How about me?
No, it's totally me!
No it's nooot!
- That's just silly!
That's enough!!
[Humming]
Uh, what's that?!
Princess Melora's pet earthworm!
[Humming]
That woman's using the love potion on the earthworm!!
[Earthworm mumbling]
Wonderful, it works!
Now every living thing in the castle is madly in love with me!
That's Melora for you! Doesn't
overlook even the smallest lovers!
That's some woman!
Just like the forest, this place really is full of...twisted love.
konbini de kuda wo maku ukiyo wo samayou wakoudo yo
All you youngsters loitering about your lives,
shrouding the convenience stores
omaera wa genjitsu ni torinokosaresugi andeddo
You’re like undead who have left behind reality
itsumade son na koto kurikaesu no o-tsu-ka-re
How long are you going to keep doing this?
Don't you get tired of this same old routine?
hashiridase yo ENDLESS ROAD
Run forth through the endless road
koetemiroyo BORDERLINE
Go on past that borderline
sekai wa mugen ni hirogaru kouya
The world is an endless, limitless wilderness
omae no dokyou wo tameshiteiru
Where you can put your courage to the test
sumafo nankaja kensaku dekinai
It’s not something you can search for on your smartphone
sekai wa mugen ni hirogaru PARADISE
The world is an endless, limitless paradise
omaera wa giragira no
Soon you'll come to life taking in the blazing sun
taiyou kuratte ikiteiru
Raws
Translation/Typesetting/Timing
ED Karaoke
QC/Review
Special Thanks
Raws
Translation/Typesetting/Timing
ED Karaoke
QC/Review
Special Thanks
AnimeLand (BSJ)
Lumpstud
Noroino Hanako
NeSubs
(Specter Subs)
https://lingojam.com/EnglishtoShakespearean
AnimeLand (BSJ)
Lumpstud
Noroino Hanako
NeSubs
(Specter Subs)
https://lingojam.com/EnglishtoShakespearean
I-I somehow got away...
[Cackling]
Serves you right! Don't come back,
UGLY WOMEN!! ...Huh?
♪ We told you nothing could keep us apart~
- NOOOO!!
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone!
What are you teaching us about today?
Today's about the Sirens' Garden.
"Sirens' Garden"
Sirens' Garden is in the middle of a forest
a small distance away from French Toaster.
There's always a thick fog, said to confuse adventurers.
Just getting there is hard to begin with.
I got there thanks to the Master!
Panpan didn't know anything though!!
What do you see in that guy...?
Next Time
Guys, Gob-san might be a disgusting, lewd, common old man.
But in reality, he does have a shocking past hidden from us.
Next time, "The Prince That Became a Goblin!"
The Prince That Became a Goblin
Alright, it's time for a big adventure!