This is Snack World, the hallowed ground
of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam
and people have handy smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
And my name's Chup!
My village was burnt down by
the evil land-destroying merchant Vinegar Khan,
so I've embarked on a journey
to get my revenge 1000-fold!
At last, my journey has brought me
close to Vinegar.
In order to defeat him, I will overcome
any impossible mission that comes my way!
Alright, let's go on another big adventure today!
Episode 30: A Sighting of the Legendary Darefalcon!
Are you here for a tour?
Our apologies, but you'll have to call or go online
to make a reservation.
Tours start at 300,000 gillan...
Sir Laozi, please let us resume our training!
We're ready, sir!
Don't be in such a hurry.
Seconds, please.
At once!
My tea.
Why are you eating all by yourself...?
Mind making yourselves useful
and cleaning up the temple?
You can eat after.
We'll have your cleaning done in a jiffy!
What a ruckus.
What's going on?
Oh, no...
Asura!
He took out every one of them!
Are they taking a nap?
Yeah, no...
Also, is it just me, or does he look kinda pissed off?
Mayone, go apologize.
Why me?!
What else could it be?
Honestly, even I thought that was overkill.
What was I supposed to...
Mayone.
Ugh, I can't believe this...
H-Hey, Asura...
I'm sorry for how I acted before.
But come on, it only happened
because you fell for me!
Ow...
Are you okay?!
That can't be him.
What do you mean?
What's all this noise about?
Princess Melora!!
What's gotten into him?
What's happening?
I can sense an evil aura
coming from him.
I believe someone has taken control of him.
It can't be... Is it...?
Vinegar?!
Vinegar Khan.
Three strong energy reactions
are nearing Dragon Shaolin Temple.
This is gonna be fun to watch.
Your wish...
...is our command!
Ta-dah!
Bludo!
Redra!
Gregon!
And together...
One, two...!
We're the Dragon Brothers!
Yes, we did it!
Awesome!
It sounds lame when you go "one, two" out loud!
Wait, for real?
Yeah, it did feel a bit cheap.
Well, how else do we stay in sync?!
You don't have to worry about it that much...
Never mind. No one gets away
with invading our turf!
You're picking the wrong fight.
Why are we the only ones talking?!
Hah, you getting cold feet?
Alright, I'll go first.
You're just a small fry to me.
What's wrong?
Uh-oh!
He's gone to the dark side!
How did you get him on your side?
You won't get me that easily...!
Hey, what happened?!
Uh-oh, he's gone to the dark side too!
Dang it! But I won't go down as easily...
Wouldn't have killed you to observe...
They've all turned evil, just like that!
Mayone, go with Melora.
Got it.
Princess!
What's going on...?
Just come with me!
I see we're doing this 4-on-4!
Pepperon, Gob-san!
Huh?
You've got this, Chup!
We'll root for you from back here!
Good luck!
Do we even stand a chance?
Rice with seaweed is irresistible!
Sir Laozi, it's an emergency!
Oh, how bad could it be?
I'll deal with it when I'm done.
You'll deal with it now!
You can't savor your meals forever.
Dettonic Sword!
Dettonic Sword.
So strong...
This isn't looking good for us!
Chup, use your Snacks
to call in a strong fighter!
Good idea!
Mountain Gorilla!
Beast!
Now that's a strong fighter!
When did Chup get his Snack?
Nothing escapes Chup!
Mountain Gorilla, take them down!
You got it!
This is hopeless...
Clearly, those muscles
are just for show.
Wait, what?!
I worked up a good sweat.
Ow, hot!!
I'm on fire!!
A forest fire!!
We'll have to do this ourselves.
They're looking real powerful, though...
Oh, joy.
I suppose I'm needed.
Sir Laozi!
So powerful...
You go, Sir Laozi!
What's wrong, Sir Laozi?
Power-induced stomachache...
My word!
His butt's getting all wiggly!
P-Perhaps my homemade seaweed went bad...
Apologies for the interruption. Snack World will be back momentarily.
Be right back
Are you okay...?
I hope Sir Laozi's alright...
Asura. Go look for the Dragon Heart.
Shoot!
Dang it...
Time to go all out!
We'll back you up, Chup!
There's no chance we'll beat them!
I should've eaten whatever I could
before I die...
That's it!
What is it, Vinsant?
Pepperon, get over here!
You too, Gorilla!
Chup, Mayone, Gob-san,
buy us time!
What do you mean?
Go on, buy us time!
Just me?
Get out there!
Alright!
Take this, my ultimate spe—
You're useless!
Do something, Chup!
Uhh... I just need to buy more time, right?
Fairjii!
A soul, a ghost, a spirit!
My name is Fairjii.
Fairjii!
Hm? Have we met?
Yeah, in the woods!
Oh, indeed we have!
Fairjii, we need you to buy time
with your elderly wisdom!
Hmm... Sure thing.
Really? Thank you!
Aye.
Listen to my tale!
You can't just make them sit and listen!
Fairjii's
Tale
Once upon a time, long long ago...
Fairjii's
Tale
Wow, he won them over in an instant!
A man dropped his axe into a pond.
Oh, it's The Honest Woodcutter!
His axe was a no-brand,
extending 25cm.
It had a very good grip on the handle.
He was very sad to lose it.
When suddenly...
The pond went blub-blub, blub-blub...
Blub-blub-blub,
blub-blub-blub...
Speed up, I wanna see the rest!
He's stalling for time, dummy!
The End
Point is, he got to keep all the axes for himself.
Why is it over already?!
Take care!
Wait, don't go!
Is all hope lost?
You idiot!
Banana peels?
O-Oh, no!
What's going on?
Oh, relax. They're just peels.
Gregon!
Redra!
Success!
Dangit, now we can't move!
But neither can they!
What the?!
What is he doing?!
Look at those acrobatics!
Show them the result of your training!
Take this, hah!
Rolling Banana Slip Attack!
H-How are you attacking us like that?!
Tch, you're making this a real pain!
Agh, he was so close!
This smell is making me hungry!
What in the world?!
You go, Vinsant!
Beyond-the-Construction-Point Attack!!
Heck yeah!
Way to go!
You've grown from your training, too!
Looks like the dragons are out of the way.
Heh, thanks for the show.
Good job.
Asura...
If it's not inside the temple,
clearly, one of you has it.
Listen, Chup.
If we work together,
we can take him down.
Got it.
Hmph. Clone art!
What?!
I forgot he could use that!
Mayone, do your thing!
What? No way, no how!
It's like my grandmother said!
"Three breads are tastier than one!"
Three breads are tastier than one.
-Tome
Now, that's something I can get behind.
Good luck, Mayone!
Aw, man.
Fine, I'll do it...
What?!
There's even more!
I can do this as much as like.
Now we're evenly-matched.
We'll send you all to the afterlife!
I'm starving...
I could go for a chocolate parfait.
Me too!
Something seems... off.
Those other three clones
seem kinda rough.
They're acting like idiots.
It takes an idiot to know one!
Oh, so you admit it, then?
Little idiot!
No fighting!
Idiots!
Of course! His intellect got split into six!
Not to mention...
He has biases!
So his clones might be weak, too!
We might stand a chance!
Oh, no!
Sir Laozi hasn't come back from the restroom...
P-P-P...
Princess Melora!
You're so beautiful!
They've fallen head over heels...
Vinegar's spell seems to have been
split apart and weakened too.
Princess, please go out with me!
No, go out with me!
No, me!
No, how 'bout me?
Boys, stop fighting.
Quit crying!
Nice, they're arguing!
Chup, now's your chance!
Uh, Chup?
Hold it right there!
How dare you...
try and win the princess's heart!
Really, Chup?!
Oh, no! They united against us!
Ugh, come on!
What's going on here?
Just stay back, Melora!
Welp, I have an appointment at the gym.
My word!!
Asura art!
We're done for.
We have to fight!
Chup!
Dang it...
Hand over the Dragon Heart.
Do it, or I kill every monk in this temple!
It's over.
We'll have to destroy the Dragon Heart.
But then we can't become Dragon Knights!
We can't meet Darefalcon!
All that...
and we can't get back on Vinegar!!
We have no other option!
We can't let them resurrect Scardon.
Hand it over.
Don't!!
What the?!
Dang it!
Let's give chase!
Alright!
This light...
What just happened?
Who might you be?!
I am known as Darefalcon.
Darefalcon
A spirit with dragon powers.
Huh?!
That's Holy Dragon Darefalcon?!
I thought he was an actual dragon!
Give me the Dragon Heart, or you're dead!
Wait, what?
What were we doing?
Lord Darefalcon!
Why, you...
Awesome!
You cheeky little...
What's going on?
Dang it. No other choice...
Final Ninja Art...
Disappear!
He ran away!
Are you all...
the ones who bestowed me
with the Dragon Heart
and re-awakened my power?
What do you desire?
Please gift me the power of the Dragon Knight!
Oh, me too!
Do you intend to become Dragon Knights
so you can get revenge on Vinegar Khan?
Yes!
Ever so naïve.
Do you know why there isn't
a single Dragon Knight at this temple?
It's proof of how difficult
the path of the Dragon Knight is.
You're not wrong about that.
But that's not why.
Do you know?
Show your respect!
Because Vinegar is a Dragon Knight.
However, he made a pact with the darkness,
granting him mighty powers.
That's to say, he's the ultimate
Dark Dragon Knight.
He's no simple greedy fat man.
Before trying to take over the continent
with his despicable arms tradings,
he was a monk here at Dragon Shaolin Temple.
The temple had to defeat him
to settle this matter.
Many such Dragon Knights were dispatched
in order to vanquish Vinegar.
But not one came back from the fight.
Why is that the case?
He's found their mental weak spots
and pulled them into the darkness.
Those he won over
became his dragon servants.
That explains why there's so many dragons near him...
On the nose.
So how do we defeat him?
The power to overcome the darkness' temptation...
That of a pure mind.
Just like what Sir Laozi mentioned...
That is something we dragons do not possess.
You have to acquire it for yourselves.
On the path towards being a Dragon Knight,
I can only lead you.
I understand.
Then I ask you please lead us
to becoming Dragon Knights!
You seem confident.
Alright, then.
I shall make Dragon Knights out of you!
shobokure gao no mobukyara domo ga
On and on these tired old NPCs
iiwake shinagara aruiteru
Keep walking around excusing themselves
itsumo miteiru michisugara
As I took the same old path again
mita koto mo nai wakuwaku wo mita
I found the thrill I've sought for my whole life
itsumade shibonda mama nano
Just how long will I keep drooping around like this?
minikui ahiru no mama nano
How long will I stay an ugly duckling?
ima no reberu wa ichi dakedo
I'm still only level one
ima ni mitero yo sono uchi JUMP UP
But watch me, soon I'll jump up
saikin no wakai mon wa tte
"Why, kids these days..."
toshiyori domo ga boyai teru kedo
...Our old boomers grumble and complain
soro soro omei henjou da
But it's not too late to clear my name
iya ga ou ni mo mattanashi daze
I might not like it, but I can't wait any longer
ketsu no ana kara jetto funsha daaa
I gotta blast free from my cowardly shell!!
ore wa itsuka hana ni naru
Give me time and I'll bloom like a flower
sora ni nobiru hana ni naru
A flower spread out to the sky
kimi ni todoku hana ni naru
The flower that reaches you
We shall begin tomorrow morning at 6:00.
Begin what exactly?
Your Dragon Knight...
training!
What?!
We don't just get our powers, like, "poof"?
I'm afraid it won't be that convenient.
Then what was that light all about?
Just my own little performance.
Are you kidding...?
Ugh, more training...
But I'll grant you three meals and snacks.
We get snacks?
I'm going to present you
with the ultimate choice.
Gulp...
What do you want for dinner tomorrow:
Japanese or Western?
Make your choice!
You can't just spring this on us!
I'll take Japane—
I didn't ask you.
Does the Japanese dish
come with hot spring eggs?
Yes. And the Western dish
comes with a spongy omelet.
Spongy...
Can we wait to see how we feel in the morning?
No can do. I need time to prepare.
No! I wanted to pick once I see it!
Okay! Just give me one minute to decide!
This is certainly a pure response
to an imminent threat.
They could became dragon servants...
The power to overcome the darkness' temptation...
That of a pure mind.
They might just manage.
Now, choose!
We pick...
both!
Pick one!!
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone!
What are you teaching us about today?
Today's lesson is on the Dragon Heart!
Dragon Heart
The Dragon Heart is a crystal
embedded with the spirit of a dragon.
It's needed to resurrect
the evil overlord Scardon.
It can awaken the power of
the Dragon Knight too!
Basically, whoever has the Dragon Heart
has the upper hand in battle!
I'm gonna be a Dragon Knight!
Next Time
I gotta defeat strong guys
all over the world!
And my first opponent is...
Mr. Carbonara?!
Next time: "The Test of the
Dragon Knight—Come at Me, Tough Guy!"
The Test of the Dragon Knight—Come at Me, Tough Guy!
Alright, time for a big adventure!