These fan-made subtitles are not for sale, rent or any profit whatsoever.
Please support official  Snack World anime releases in your home country.
See lumpstud.tumblr.com for Genie song explanation and other notes.
Snack World, the hallowed ground
of dreams and adventures.
A world full of dragons, smartphones,
and convenience stores.
It's a pretty cool place!
But like any world, it has a villain.
Vinegar Khan.
He is an evil merchant who has taken
everything from our young hero, Chup.
And so, the boy embarks on a
reckless journey for revenge!
What perils await him?
The answer lies in his...destiny.
Come on, I don't wanna!
Get up, Chup, let's go!
No, I don't wanna give up!
Chup, we don't stand a chance against Medusa.
Ep. 4: The Genies of the Lamp Debut!
We took her on three times and failed, we can't do it!
Let's just go to the king
and tell him "we give up."
But...if we do that...
What, you can't do it? Why, you can't be
serious, you'd have to be totally done with!
You're totally done with!
Tch...we can't. For the sake of the peace in this world, we absolutely cannot give up here!
You just don't want the princess to hate you.
Guh.
Ugh, aren't you gonna say anything, Gob-san?
Sorry...I don't feel very good right now.
Aah! There's a snake biting Gob-san's head!
[Gob-san screaming]
Isn't that a snake Medusa sent flying?!
[Gob-san yelping]
Is it still biting him?
I didn't even notice.
Wouldn't it be awful if it were poisonous?
Oi, anyone, I'm begging you, take it off of me!
Ah- right, Pepperon!
N-not happening.
I'm not the person to touch a snake with my bare hands.
Ulp...looks like we have to give up.
Don't give up so easily!
Uhh, for now, why don't we take him to the infirmary?
Huh? I hate the infirmary.
Who asked you?
Oh, I'm sure there's a nursery close by.
Not the "nursery," the "infirmary."
He's not even a baby!
Oh, I get it now.
Aah! Gob-saaan!
[Spooky laughter]
Good news: it's not poisonous.
Thank goodness, Gob-san!
I can't trust anyone...I'm all alone...
I'm going to die bearing my loneliness...
Ahaha...he's sulking...
Hmm...hm?
Hm! I've figured out Medusa's weakness.
- Huh?!
- Really?!
Medusa is weak to light.
It's possible you can fight her off with a strong light.
Is that true?!
Thanks, Mr. Carbonara! This time,
we'll fully, flawlessly flatten her!
Chup!
You should ask for a weapon.
You're right. Are there any weapons that emit strong light?
And no counterfeits this time, please!
Hm...strong light...there might be?
I'll give you all the money I have for it!
[Gasps]
Hee...Pinocchio! We have company!
Service Level F.
Meh... 'sup.
Grr...
They're splurging today.
Changed to Service Level B.
Welcome in! I will prepare some tea.
Oh, that's right, Chup.
How about this Laser Beam Gun?
Laser?
Does it glow?
Nope, it's broken and doesn't glow, but this is good!
It sure looks cool!
[Laughing]
It's no good if it doesn't glow.
Hm? Well, what about this rice cooker?
Does it glow?
It doesn't glow, but it fully cooks rice.
What's the point if it doesn't glow?!
Have some tea.
Where does that come from?!
And why's there only three cups?!
Well, this doesn't glow, but it's still good.
It's useless, Mr. Carbonara's just being greedy.
[Chup sighs]
Things that glow...things that glow...
Excuse me.
You wouldn't happen to sell anything with a strong glow?
- How about that?
- Hm?
It's a shining lamp passed down from ancient times.
A lamp?
Does it glow?
Of course, you fool.
Ooh! You think this'll work?
How much does it...
- Huh?
- Hm?
She vanished...
How are we supposed to make it glow?
Maybe we need to light it up with fire!
Can Mayone's magic be used for the fire?
Is that what you think magic is?!
Hm...perhaps someone out there will sell a lighter?
Oink-oink!
Oh, you can erupt flames, right, Butako?
Oink!
Alright, light this up, then!
Oiiiiii!
Hot, hot, ow, ow!!
- Huh?
- Oink?
It burns! It buuurns!
Ugh, that was awful!
That scorched!
My skin's all dry!
Come on, that's hot!
What were you thinking?
You can just rub it to summon us!
- Uhh..
- Who are you?
We're the singing, dancing trio, the genie band--
"The Genies!"
The Genies
Ooh, sexy~!
G-genies?
Are all genies like this?
That's wicked cool!
Oh, why, aren't you cute. What's your name?
It's Chup!
Oh, dear, that sounds quite dirty...
How cute...I love a small child like this!
Dear, Chup's [redacted] isn't that small.
What, no! I'm talking about his spine!
You nut, I think Chup's [redacted], his [redacted]...
Yuck, what are you saying?
You animal!
[Genies laughing]
Uh, hello?
Yes?
We didn't mean to summon you...
We just wanted to make the lamp glow...
Humph! Now that you've summoned the genies,
I'll make one of your wishes come true.
I'll fulfill one as well.
I'll grant one too!
- Huh?!
- By that, you mean...
We can make three wishes in total?
Then, first off...
I wish for one cow's worth of filet steak...
That and cream of corn soup...
Uhh..I wish-
Wait just a minute!
We need to consider this a little more carefully!
Hm, she's right!
I wish I could take a bath with Princess Melo-ow!
Oink...oi...
Listen to me!
Huh? What?
I have no memory of the last 10 seconds.
So, what do you want?
Err, is it alright for us to have three wishes for each of us?
What a shameless girl you are.
All of you are a group!
So that's three in all for you. Try to come to an agreement.
Hm...besides Butako, that's three wishes for four of us.
It's not enough.
You don't have any wishes, right, Gob-san?
You're just assuming that!
Hey, do you think we could ask them to level us up?
Or maybe just ask them to defeat Medusa?
No, as you'd expect from that...
Alright, I'll test it out by telling them my wish.
What?
Genies, this is our first wish.
I wish I could have bushy hair on my head like I'm in my 20's!
Huh?!
Oooh, sexy~!
Ohh, this body, this shine, it's genuine!
Why, this hairstyle brings me back to my youth!
Ah- what the...what's this blood thirst about?
Gob-san, what'd you just do?
We never let you get a head start.
It doesn't even suit you at all!
At your age, that afro just looks ridiculous!
What do you mean it doesn't suit
me? My hair's naturally curly...
It's no use. Sorry, genie, please turn my head back to normal!
Mmmm, sexy~!
Hmph. Is this better?!
Well, that's now two wishes granted.
What?!
What would you like to do with your last wish?
Hold on, we just wasted those wishes!
We need to think about this one carefully!
You can't say that!
Whether you cry or laugh, you've got one left.
While we wait, our special skill is our sexy dance!
One, two...
One, two, three, four!
We're the best!
saikou yo!
O-N-E-E onee
The magnificent!
idai naru!
O-N-E-E onee
We're the best!
saikou yo!
O-N-E-E-O-N-E-E
Uh...no, your dancing is okay, but my wish...
I wish you'd stop dancing already!
Ooh, sexy!
Your third wish has been granted.
Farewell! Ooh, sexy~!
W...wait, hold on, why?!
They must have taken "I wish you'd
stop dancing" as your last wish.
What the heck, this is the worst!
My fillet steak...
My bath with Princess Melora...
Oink...
Hm...
I guess they're not coming out...
Of course they won't, they already took our wishes.
Besides, why are we in the desert again?!
It's a shortcut, no complaining.
Chup, have you figured out how to light the lamp?
Oh, right, I have to try and light it up.
Ugh, you're impossible!
Chup, can we just go back?
If we can't light the lamp, won't we fail miserably if we go to Medusa?
Oh, I've got an idea!
What is it?
We need someone else to rub the lamp,
then the genies will come out.
That's our Chup, what a good idea!
Then we'll ask them how to make the lamp glow.
I get it!
The genies will know!
My grandmother once said:
Rice cake comes from a rice cake shop,
Rice cake comes from a rice cake shop, bread from a bakery,
bread comes from a bakery,
the rest can be found at
the rest can be found at a convenience store!
a convenience store.
-Tome
Yeah, they must have the perfect product lineup!
The heck are you guys saying?!
It would've been easier for me to just ask "who?"
but who else would even be in a place like...
- Let's ask that person over there!
Huh?
Excuse me!
Hold it, Chup, that's a monster!
Uh...what?
I'm fairly certain that one is Yeti!
Yeti
Why would it be in a hot desert like this...?
Alright then, take this! Instant victory!
So scawy, so scawy...
[Gulps]
What's wrong?
Ah...I dunno, it's kinda cute.
So scawy...I cawght a cold...
Don't fall for it! It'll spew out an absolute-zero blizzard!
It's a brutal monster that freezes over cities!
- [Yeti quivers]
- Hmm...
Okay, Mayone! You can handle this!
Eh, why me?
Eat this, monster! Uh-...
[Shivering]
What happened?
Something doesn't feel right about beating her up, as the girl...
Would my popularity plummet...?
What are you gettin' worked up about?
[Shivering]
Here it comes! It's going to spew a blizzard!
Tch...
Ah-choo!
Heh...heheh...
It's so precious...
Probably best we leave it be, right?
Nuh-uh, you can't just let a monster loose! Absolutely not!
But what else can we do...?
Hm...mmm...I can't see...
Where is it?
This isn't watermelon splitting...
This seems a bit cruel to me...
More to the left!
- [Quivering]
- To the left?
No, that's not left!!
How careless.
I'm an evil demon disguised a cute monster.
Time to take your life!
[Gasps] Chup!
What is it? Ah-
Aaaaaah!
Oink-oink!
What was that voice?
He has no idea after all that.
It's really a terrifying monster.
Hmm?
A treasure chest!
Ooh! An axe from Qloris!
You can have it, Pepperon!
Huh, you mean it?
Yeah, I think it's more suitable for you than me.
I've finally gotten a new weapon of my own...
Huh?
Are you okay?
I wanna go home...
Oh, okay. Rub this lamp, then!
This'll help you get home!
Reawwy?
Rub, rub...
Sweet!
Ooh, sexy!
Oh, it's you, Chup!
Must be fate we meet again!
About that, we need you to fulfill Yeti's wish.
Please!
Ugh, you black-hearted little brat.
Pay us some mind, Chup.
You animal...
W-what's gowwing on?
Did you hear that "gowwing?"
What a sly character...
You animal...
Well, since it called you out, why don't you take its wish?
It wants to go home.
Where's your home?
It's a vewy cold place faw up nowth.
North would be that way, huh.
Hmm, alright, we'll take your wish.
To your cold home.
So cwude!
Bye!!
Was there really no better way to do that?
Was that good for you?
Later, Chup!
Slow down!
Can I have the wishes Yeti had left over?
Weeeeell, bit of a greedy plan...
Since when were you a greedy kid, Chup?!
You animal!
Please! Would it be okay if I just asked for one?
Nuh-uh! Rules are rules.
That's right. No way.
Unless you want to hang out, of course.
Right, hanging out would be good with us!
That'd be great!
Hahaha... sure, great.
If that's what I need to do, I'll hang out with you!
Oh, excellent!
One, two...
One, two, three, four!
We're the best!
saikou yo!
O-N-E-E onee
The magnificent!
idai naru!
O-N-E-E onee
We're the best!
saikou yo!
Would you stop dancing?!
Ooh, sexy!
Your wish has been granted.
Welp, later!
I'll keep your promise to hang out!
The exact same mistake!!
Oink...
What do I do now... Huh?
- Oh?
- What's up, Chup?
I figured out how the lamp works!
[Gasps]
- Really?
This time we'll be able to fully,
flawlessly flatten her! Maybe!
[Vinegar Khan laughing]
They're quite the disobedient few.
Pepperon, just go swing your axe!
I can already feel myself giving up...
Ugh... Chup, will you- huh?
[Hissing]
Chup, where's your sword?
[Clamoring]
Chup, take out the Crystal Sword!
No, Chup's preserving his stamina.
"Preserving?"
Medusa, my grandma once said:
There's no night that sheds no light, and a lid that sheds no light should be cooled off!
There's no night
that sheds no light,
and a lid that
sheds no light
should be cooled off.
-Tome
Yeah! If you can't open a jam lid,
just cool it off with hot water and it pops right off.
Realize the power of a glowing lamp!
Attached plug, lock-on!
Say what?
So it was an electric device?
Buttery!
Machine! Machine!
Grumble-grumble! I was in the middle of eating!!
Let me borrow your nose.
Wha...[snorts]
- Oh!!
- It lit up!
Take this, Medusa!
[Growling]
Nice, it's working!
Chup, keep doing that and corner her!
Way to go!
[Genies clamoring]
Hot, hot, hot!!
Come ooon...
We'll get burnt to a crisp...
Well, aren't you a nuisance.
They came out again...
The Genies...
Why'd you have to burn us up like that?
You animal. Hmph.
[Squeals]
Grr, ow-ow... what was that for?!
Err...come on, guys, do something!
What'cha lashing at us for?
Picking a fight with us?
Mmm?
[Hissing]
Aah! What on earth is that?
That really is an animal!
Just take charge and do something!
But we already granted your wishes!
That doesn't matter, do something!
Oh!
They have quite the unexpected combat ability!
Looks like we'll be doing you a favor after all!
Time for our final techniques!
One, two...
One, two, three, four!
We're the best!
saikou yo!
O-N-E-E onee
The magnificent!
idai naru!
O-N-E-E onee
Dancing at a time like this?
What are they trying to accomplish?
We're the best!
saikou yo!
Oh, maybe...you know how snake charmers use music to make snakes dance?
O-N-E-E-O-N-E-E
Oh, you mean those fellas who play those flutes?
Well, I’ve heard of snake charming before.
Guys, look!
Medusa's looking eager to dance!
Ain't that swell?
Let's go around one more time!
Dance dance power evolution!
O-N-E-E onee
The magnificent!
idai naru!
O-N-E-E onee
Please let this work...
It's a bit strange to expect a Boss to dance...
Hm? Look, look!
We're the best!
saikou yo!
O-N-E-E-O-N-E-E
She's dancing!
Perfect! We'll have her keep dancing until she tires!
Ooh, sexy!
Wait, why'd you stop?
You're such a whiny girl.
She's worn out.
Take a look, see?
Ooh! She's tied up!
She can't emit petrification rays like that!
Now's the time, Chup!
While she's weak!
Aim for the little shiny spot on the top of her head!
Shiny...oh!
It's shining!
Alright, let's deliver one final blow!
Crystal Sword!
Crystal Sword.
This ends here!
Take this! Deathblow: Aiming-for-the-Shiny-Spot Slash!
Still on the cheap half-baked move names!
[Gasping]
Hurrah!
You did it, Chup!
Quest
"Vanquish Medusa"
We got the Purple Eye!
Good job, Chup!
Mission complete!
- Oink!
- [Sobs] It took so long...
Purple Eye Obtained!
Whoo! Chup's the best!
konbini de kuda wo maku ukiyo wo samayou wakoudo yo
All you youngsters loitering about your lives,
shrouding the convenience stores
omaera wa genjitsu ni torinokosaresugi andeddo
You’re like undead who have left behind reality
itsumade son na koto kurikaesu no o-tsu-ka-re
How long are you going to keep doing this?
Don't you get tired of this same old routine?
hashiridase yo ENDLESS ROAD
Run forth through the endless road
koetemiroyo BORDERLINE
Go on past that borderline
sekai wa mugen ni hirogaru kouya
The world is an endless, limitless wilderness
omae no dokyou wo tameshiteiru
Where you can put your courage to the test
sumafo nankaja kensaku dekinai
It’s not something you can search for on your smartphone
sekai wa mugen ni hirogaru PARADISE
The world is an endless, limitless paradise
omaera wa giragira no
Soon you'll come to life taking in the blazing sun
taiyou kuratte ikiteiru
Raws
Translation/Typesetting/Timing
ED Karaoke
QC/Review
Raws
Translation/Typesetting/Timing
ED Karaoke
QC/Review
AnimeLand (BSJ)
Lumpstud
Noroino Hanako
NeSubs
AnimeLand (BSJ)
Lumpstud
Noroino Hanako
NeSubs
Well done, Chup!
Princess Melora, for you!
- No thanks.
- Huh?!
Things like the Purple Eye are so out now.
You could say, it's not very exciting anymore.
To be honest, I guess it feels done with?
It's done with!
Chup!
Chup's been turned to stone!
So, daddy, that aside, I have a request~.
Hm? What is it? Another item of your desire?
Oh, you really know me, daddy!
In that case, then, Chu...huh?
Hey, where are you folks going?
We, uh, remembered we have
things to do and people to see.
Goodbye!
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone!
What are you teaching us about today?
"Qloris"
Today's about Qloris!
Qloris, one of the popular brands, the most popular in the continent,
is responsible for a number of products.
Since they're mass-produced in tons of factories,
they're high-performance, yet very cheap.
Oh, I own a sword and shield from Qloris.
Since they commonly use simple designs,
they make great casual equipment.
The secret to their popularity!
Next Time
Just when we thought we barely defeated Medusa,
now it's a kraken?
In order to protect Melora's beautiful skin,
I must get my hands on the Ultimate Moisturizing Cream!
Next time: The Desert Kraken!
The Desert Kraken
Alright! It's time for a big adventure!