This is Snack World, the hallowed ground
of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam
and people have handy smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
And my name's Chup!
My village was burnt down by
the evil land-destroying merchant Vinegar Khan,
so I've embarked on a journey
to get my revenge 1000-fold!
At last, my journey has brought me
close to Vinegar.
In order to defeat him, I will overcome
any impossible mission that comes my way!
Alright, let's go on another big adventure today!
Episode 24: The Genies Murder Mystery—Gob-san's the Killer?!
I know who ate my cake without asking...
It was you, Pepperon!
H-How could you tell?
I'm gonna guess it's
the frosting all over your face.
Hey!
Mr. Fishburger gave me that cake...
I'm sorry.
What's all the playing detective for?
Don't you remember?
We need to solve more mysteries
in order to get us all
into Vinegar Palace!
1 case solved,
1 person.
If you all want to go,
you'll have to solve more cases.
We've solved one mystery,
so there's three more to go!
But big-time crimes
don't just happen every day!
We'll work out a different plan tomorrow.
But it's getting late, so I'm heading to bed.
Huh? Where's Gob-san?
He's drinking down in the lobby.
Probably trying to get Bunnilla
to keep him company.
He's hopeless.
Man... Today was terrible...
Bunnilla, my sweet...
Bunnilla?!
Did you want to drink with me?
Oh my, somebody pinch me!
I knew you'd come around eventually!
I never thought you'd come to me
of your own accord!
Were you embarrassed to confess your love
in front of company?
What is it? Are you shy?
My word!!
Gob-san!
Gob-san!!
Gob-san!! Wake up!
Oh, shoot. Did I sleep here all night?
Gob-san, what did you do?!
W-What in the world?!
I can't believe you!
I-I didn't do this, I swear!
Good morning!
Oh, heeey, Chup!
I wonder what miracle
brought us together here!
H-He's dead?!
No way!
Who did it?
Who killed him?!
Pipe down, Genies!
Pipe down? Are you insane?
Don't you realize how bad this is?!
Ow-ow-ow-ow...
Don't you?
Well, don't you?
Cut it out!
What the heck...?
Top of the morning!
Inspector Chilipepper!
Officer!
There's a murder!
Arrest him immediately!
What on earth?!
Whoever did this, come forward!
Was it you?!
N-No! It wasn't!
You liar! What's that you're holding?
Uh, that— It's not mine!
What do you think, Chup?
You don't got a lot going for yourself, buddy.
Outsiders aren't allowed in the hotel at night,
so there's really no one else it could be...
I swear, it wasn't me!
Don't lie, we know it was you!
You little beast!
R-Right! I can back myself up,
I have an alibi!
You do?
Last night, I was drinking with Bunnilla.
Huh?
Oh, really?
We were drinking for ages,
and then I just passed out.
Ask her, she'll vouch for me!
Bunnilla, did you actually drink
with Gob-san last night?
P-Please help me, my sweet!
Everyone suspects me!
Can't help you.
W-What? Why?!
I knew it.
Gob-san, you're such a bad liar.
I-I swear!
You're coming with me.
Hold it right there!
Gob-san may be dumb,
perverted and revolting,
maybe his face is gross
and his jokes are awful,
maybe his farts stink,
and his breath too,
and maybe he's just some old dude
who follows me around...
That's enough!
But Gob-san would never
kill an innocent person!
I know he wouldn't!
My savior...
You're right! Besides, Gob-san
is too big of a chicken to do that.
He's just a weak, worthless old man!
Could you dial back the insults...?
I understand.
Then I'l leave it to you all
to solve this mystery!
So, can you? Well?
Yeah, can you?
I have to!
It's like my grandmother once said!
The die has been cast...
by the tiger!
The die has been cast
by the tiger.
-Tome
Tigers are really strong!
What does this have to do
with anything...?
Alright, Chup!
Solve this mystery for us!
Thinking time, start!
One, two!
One, two, three, four!
This feels great!
O-N-E-E, homo!
Quiet, please.
I'm trying to concentrate.
Our dance routine feels so off
with just two of us.
Once we figure out who did it,
we're so gonna give it to them!
Hey, so, we'd like to hear more
about last night.
Were you actually there with Gob-san...?
For the millionth time,
I can't help you.
Yeah, I can't really imagine
you two working out.
What's all the fuss about?
Haven't you heard?
There was a death in your lobby!
Hngh?! When?
I didn't study for it at all!
Not a test! A death!
Babaocai?
That isn't even close! That's bonkers!
B-Bok choy?
Ugh, forget it.
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
I didn't do it!!
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
Habanero Murder Case
Suspect A
Gob-san
I'll give you thirty minutes, no more.
Gob-san, are you really telling the truth?
I swear, I was with Bunnilla
the whole time!
You have to believe me!
Then why isn't Bunnilla backing you up?
I don't know...
Did you make her mad yesterday?
Make her mad...?
How old are you, Bunnilla?
You're not married, no?
What do you love the most about me?
Wait, don't tell me—is it my body?
By the way,
what color are your panties today?
Yuck!
Like you're putting on a show
of sexual harrassment!
I might've gotten a bit carried away.
No wonder she isn't vouching for you.
Pepperon, try to get Bunnilla to tell the truth.
You can count on me!
While he does that,
Chup, can you figure out who really did it?
Who really did it...
Hey, Mr. Yon.
Who was in the hotel last night?
Let me see...
Me, you guys, and Bunnilla.
And those genies.
Come to think of it,
why are you here, Genies?
I rubbed this vase,
and they popped out.
Ooh, sexy!
Hello, welcome!
Oh, hello!
A vase? What about your lamp?
We do more than lamps, darling!
There's holes calling for us all over the world!
You know how there's a bunch of exits
in the subway? It's just like that!
Is that how it works?
They said they could grant me three wishes,
so I assigned each of them to cleanup.
What a waste of wishes.
You better not be saying one of us did it!
Why, you little pussycat!
We were in the same room
all day yesterday!
He was only apart from us
because his snoring is so loud!
Yeah!
So you both have alibis.
Then who could it be...?
Oh, right! There was one more
person lodging here.
Who was it?!
It had to have been them!
Oui, oui, one moment...
Do you mean me?!
Mountain Gorilla
Yes! Thanks for staying here,
Mountain Gorilla!
My, what fine muscles you have!
Such a beautiful inverted triangle!
Such a big, bulging chest!
Such bulging biceps...
Go, Muscle Mountain!
I got it!
Last night, he was clinging
onto those muscles like you are now...
I love your muscles!
Such a huge chest!
Oh, I love your muscles!
I love them, I do!
He got so clingy...
...Mountain Gorilla got mad
and killed him!
That's how it happened!
I could see that!
He always had a thing
for macho-gorillas!
So...?
The killer was... Mountain Gori—
That's ridiculous!
I don't need a bow and arrow to kill!
I have my own two well-trained arms!
So cool!
That makes sense...
Last night, I spent my time training outdoors!
I only just got back!
My alibi is flawless!
My, and so are your muscles!
You look totally perfect!
Go, Muscle Mountain!
Take a look!
Hold the phone!
Look at this guy's muscles!
I love this mountain!
Why are you competing...?
Hold on, lemme get a closer look!
Lord, you are smoking!
Here it comes! Muscle fever!
Muscle Carnival!
I wanna have a taste
of all sorts of muscles
Keep it coming,
that muscle à la carte
Bend your arms,
flex those lady-killer biceps
Brachialis!
Open your belly,
split it into six, that six-pack
Rectus abdominis!
Muscles lookin' super hunky
(Super hunky)
Touchin' makes me feel so funky
(Feeling funky)
Running, squatting, jumping
Dancing, grabbing, dangling
Keep it coming,
that muscle à la carte
Muscle Carnival!
I can tell you this: those muscles don't lie!
He's innocent!
I see...
Welp, seems like it really is him...
I told you, it wasn't me!
Oh, right.
There was one other guest
who came in late at night.
Interesting. What were they like?
Oui, oui. One moment.
I would never do such a thing!
Master Panpan!
Why were you here?!
I got lost delivering a pizza
and ended up staying here.
Oh, I see!
You got an alibi?
No way someone that flabby
would have an alibi!
Well, do you?
Last night, I was in my room listening to
AKZ48's All-Night Throbbing Hood.
AKZ48's All-Night...?
Throbbing Hood!
I wouldn't have let myself
miss a single second of it!
They never miss a beat,
just as usual.
Master, your alibi stands true!
Just like that?
Master, I don't know what to do anymore...
Don't whine!
Listen carefully to the voices in the room.
Yessir!
Listen to the voices in the room...
What did you hear?
Sounds like someone got hurt...
Chup, I got us a lead!
She was in her room?
That's what it sounds like.
Is this true?
Why, yes!
Yesterday, we were playing cards in her room!
Huh?!
Yikes, I lost again!
Come on, one more time!
Had to have lasted around 8 hours.
Doesn't that get boring...?
So this means Gob-san was lying to us?
Sure sounds like it.
Aw, come on!
Bunnilla, don't you remember?
You kissed me yesterday!
As if.
Gob-san, stop lying through your teeth!
I mean it!
Looks like we're starting
to narrow things down.
Alright, Chup! Spill the beans!
Give us the answer!
One!
Two!
One, two, three, four!
This feels great!
O-N-E-E, homo!
Now!
The killer is Gob—
Wait a minute!
Some small, black creature
just flew by!
Hm, a cockroach?!
Oui, oui, I'll take care of it!
Eep!
Aren't you...
Clone?!
Don't tell me you're behind this?
Oh, I think I've got it, Chup!
Maybe Gob-san was telling the truth!
Huh?!
But Bunnilla was in her room
all night last night!
Don't you remember what Clone does?
Oh, right! Clone changes people's appearances!
Yeah. So, I presume,
whoever did it used Clone
to take the form of Bunnilla.
And then they made contact with Gob-san
in order to direct suspicion towards him.
I get it! Clone's the accomplice!
That makes sense!
So who's the actual killer, then?
I don't know...
Oh, Mr. Yon! What's that?
AKAMI: "I'm Graduating from AKZ!"
Declaration brings tears to fans' eyes
It's today's sports magazine.
I see!
I've fully, flawlessly solved this mystery!
Have you? Well, who is it?
That would be...
Get back here, Clone!
Tell us who sent you!
Really, Mayone?
You're ruining my moment here!
W-What the?
Go away!
I...don't know him... I swear!
Panpan...?
I dunno, seems awful attached to you.
Shoo, go away!
Kurosuke! Go away!
Kurosuke?
You named it?
Crud!
I don't suppose...
Nonsense! I'm an idol of the woods!
I'm so sorry, Master...
The killer was...
you, Master Panpan!
My word!
What?!
Are you certain, Chup?
T-That's nonsense! I have an alibi!
I was up all-night listening to
AKZ48's All-Night Throbbing Hood...
No... You were doing no such thing.
Wh... Where's your proof?
Master, you said something earlier.
"They never miss a beat,
just as usual."
Y-Yeah, so what?
Last night...
...was definitely not "just as usual!"
Huh?
AKAMI: "I'm Graduating from AKZ!"
Declaration brings tears to fans' eyes
Say what?!
Akami graduated?!
Says she announced it on
All-Night Throbbing Hood last night.
Nonsense!
You were on such a good roll,
why would you graduate now?!
Actually, I guess it makes sense
in order to train their younger members...
I guess that means their new song
"Ripe Grandmother" is her last one...
But I should've heard about this
on the radio first!!
Right, Kurosuke?
Crud, noooo!
There goes your alibi.
King Oyster Penitentiary
is cold and frightening.
Fairy Crystal Sword!
Downloading Fairy Electronics.
Fairy Crystal Sword.
Master, time to face the music!
Why did you do it?!
Why did you kill him?!
You little beast!!
I-I wasn't planning to!
Last night, I went to the reception
to borrow a radio...
This is so freaky...
Feels like a ghost is gonna pop out.
So dark... So scary...
Don't stand behind me!
What do I do, what do I do...?
Bunnilla, my sweet...
So that's when you thought
to pose as Bunnilla and pin it on Gob-san.
Yeah. The whole thing was put together
by me and my pet Kurosuke.
So the one who kissed me last night...
My word!
Yes, that was me.
Apologies for the interruption. Snack World will be back momentarily.
Be right back
Say goodnight, Master!
Don't move, or I rip the pig's nose straight off!
You really don't know
when to give up, do you?
Dang it...
Butako's nose is her greatest feature!
What the?!
Good going, you!
Come with us,
we'll give you plenty of spankings!
Master, thanks for everything.
You still look up to that guy?
Stop it! Put me down!
What are you doing?!
I'm both excited and terrified...
What the heck?!
shobokure gao no mobukyara domo ga
On and on these tired old NPCs
iiwake shinagara aruiteru
Keep walking around excusing themselves
itsumo miteiru michisugara
As I took the same old path again
mita koto mo nai wakuwaku wo mita
I found the thrill I've sought for my whole life
itsumade shibonda mama nano
Just how long will I keep drooping around like this?
minikui ahiru no mama nano
How long will I stay an ugly duckling?
ima no reberu wa ichi dakedo
I'm still only level one
ima ni mitero yo sono uchi JUMP UP
But watch me, soon I'll jump up
saikin no wakai mon wa tte
"Why, kids these days..."
toshiyori domo ga boyai teru kedo
...Our old boomers grumble and complain
soro soro omei henjou da
But it's not too late to clear my name
iya ga ou ni mo mattanashi daze
I might not like it, but I can't wait any longer
ketsu no ana kara jetto funsha daaa
I gotta blast free from my cowardly shell!!
ore wa itsuka hana ni naru
Give me time and I'll bloom like a flower
sora ni nobiru hana ni naru
A flower spread out to the sky
kimi ni todoku hana ni naru
The flower that reaches you
Well done, you all!
That makes two mysteries solved!
Can't wait to work with you again!
I was getting worried there...
Oh boy, what do we do?
Huh?
What happened to Panpan?
He got away!
He jumped from the window
and scurried!
He got away?!
It's me! A criminal is on the loose!
I want a BOLO on this immediately!
Please catch him!
My, I slept like a log.
Looks like you solved it.
Whaaat?!
You're alive?!
Yeah! I was trying to teach him a lesson
by playing dead,
then I fell asleep on the spot!
I thought something was off!
After all, genies don't die!
You got that right!
My b, y'all!
You little beast!
It's about time.
How's Scardon's resurrection going?
It's been a bit of a challenge...
I hope you can wait just a bit longer.
Boooring.
Hurry it along,
or I'll drown you in the bunker.
You can't catch me!
I'll keep running!
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone!
What are you teaching us about today?
Phantom
Today's lesson is on Phantom!
Phantom is a brand of
magical equipment
often encountered deep in dungeons!
It was first sold by a merchant
on a mail order show,
and it exploded among temptresses!
Now, grown-ups tired of normal fashion
have picked up on it from word-of-mouth!
Vinsant seems to use Phantom a lot!
Next Time
Bad news! Mayone's been kidnapped!
What do we do?!
Well, for now, let's look for her replacement!
A Day Without Mayone
Next time:
"A Day Without Mayone!"
Alright, it's time
for a big adventure!