These fan-made subtitles are not for sale, rent or any profit whatsoever.
Please support official  Snack World anime releases in your home country.
See lumpstud.tumblr.com for certain translation notes.
This is Snack World, the hallowed
ground of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam and
people have smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
...And my name's Chup.
My village was burnt down by the evil
land-destroying merchant, Vinegar Khan,
and I've embarked on a journey
to get my revenge 1000-fold!
The tickets to King Oyster City, where
Vinegar is, cost 20 million gillan.
So I'm on an adventure searching for
big treasure to make loads of cash!
[Chup humming theme song]
Alright, let's go on another big adventure today!
Mayone, Mayone!
Ep. 9: Snow White's Deep Zone
[Mayone mumbles]
Wh-who are you?
So, you've saved me again, huh?
Heh, and you're still in a bit of a daze it looks.
Fair enough, I'll wake you with a kiss...
[Smooching]
[Grunts]
[Mayone gasps]
- The heck!!
- What was that about?!
- Hm?
- Oink!
Where are we?
Uh-huh, I'm awake...
- Huh?
- [Cinderella giggles]
Oh, that's right!
We were being tooled with by the Siren Sisters...
Did that gentleman come and save us again?
Gentleman?
Huh? Come on, Chup, you didn't
seriously forget about him, right?
[Ringtone sound]
Oh, it's the king!
"King"
"On it!"
"Today"
"So, you've lost again..."
"Get over here so
we can strategize!!"
"So, you've lost again... get over
here so we can strategize!!" he says.
You really think we'll actually come up with a plan? No way.
We've got no odds against foes with tricks like that!
Hm...they did end up slicing Gob-san in half...
But that was you who cut him...
I'd rather you keep your body in check
before you hack off any more limbs!
Hmm...though...
- [Ringtone sound]
- Oh!
I-it's a text from Princess Melora!
Mwah!
"Princess Melora"
"Today"
"Chup, come quick~"
Ka-booooom!!
Ahaah, I got a text directly from Melora!
It's like my grandmother said!
Correctness is victory! Croquettes are side meals!
Correctness is
victory.
Croquettes
are side meals.
-Tome
Ooh, I'm getting a cravin' for both of those!
Oh, Chup, I beg of you! Please fetch
me that love potion when you can~
She's acting even more sexy today.
I'm so jealous of that yoga ball.
Princess! You have no need for a love potion.
Because all this time, I've always...
- L-la-lo...
- Ooh, is Chup about to confess?!
...la...lacked clothes!!
What on earth did you just blurt out?!
I think I just forgot about...about...huh?
[Melora moaning]
[Chup giggling]
What a little rodent...
Say, daddy, can you tell them?
Well, just like that, I entrust you'll be able
to obtain that potion without fail!
Don't you have any advice on how we
can take down the Siren Sisters?
Hm, in that case, you should pay a visit to Snow White.
Snow White? Who's that?
Huh? Right, she's an advisor of the forest
who's known for her fortune telling.
Advisor of the forest?
Where can we find her?
Snow White is in the forest's...uhh...
right around here!
Gee, barely giving any hints, huh?
Yeesh...this place is so creepy...
Hmm...where are we?
So you did get us lost!!
It's times like this I wish Master Panpan were here!
You still trust that guy?!
- [All shrieking]
- There's something theeere!!
They're bears!! They're a group of bears!!
We gotta play dead quick...
Oh, please! Get a hold of yourselves!
Who are you calling bears?
You kids've gotta be pullin' our strings!
- They're hunting us...
- [Mayone, Butako crying]
I am dead!
I'm a dead body too!! A dead body that can't feel pain!!
But we're not bears!
No need to be rude!
How long are you gonna hide?
- Huh? Aren't you guys...?
- Hm?
That's right!
We're the singing, dancing,
magical band of three: The Genies!
Ooh, sexy!
- Ooh!
- Oh, so it was just you guys!
Now, Chup, wasn't that just harsh?
You left us behind at Snake Tempura Temple back then!
You animal!
Uh...haha! I guess I was so happy when we beat Medusa and got the Purple Eye, I...
That's okay, but that was awful of you!
Huh, what was?
[Genie sobbing]
We got called again by someone near a river.
Like this.
Hm?
But the man who called us out was astonished!
Then he dropped the lamp into the river!!
We've been searching for the lamp ever since!
So, if you come across it, call us!
Got it! For now, I'll just register your snack.
- Ooh, sexy!
- [Shutter click]
Can I ask you guys something?
Sure, what?
We'll listen to anything!
Anything but our weight and three sizes.
Do you know where we can find Snow White?
Unfortunately, no...
Maybe try asking the locals?
Who would we even call a "local..."
Yeah, in a forest like this?
- Hm?
- ♪ Hey-ho, hey-ho, off to command we go ♪
-  ♪ The cutesy little Kinokos, oh, how they love their jobs ♪
- Hm, what's that?
Well, that was peculiar.
I thought they'd be around here, but...
Hey, look, look over there!
Oh my~, the elegant Kinokos!
Even their mushroom caps are magnificent!
Ahh, when you say it like that, it's like you mean [censored]!
That's not fair, your mind's so dirty [censored] is all that's in there!
You animal!
Agh, I'm at my limit! Let's just eat already!!
This is bad!! Everyone run!!
[Kinokos screaming]
[Kinoko gasps]
That mushroom is standing!! Ah, dear, what did I just say...
What is this? We can't have you
enjoying talking to yourself!
You animal!
Chup! Stop getting distracted and focus on the Monsters!
What, now?
We gotta go after them now! Chop chop, get a move on!
[Chup yells]
- Yikes...
- Oink...
Oyyy...
Goodness, they're pure white!
And the most desirable rear...
I want it for myself!
Aah! Stop, don't strip me!
Chup!
Chup, wait for us!
[Panting] I can't take anymore...
Just run around a bit and you'll feel better.
Where are the Genies?
They went to look for their lamp on their own.
We should keep looking for Snow White.
But we don't even know where we are...
Maybe if Chup hadn't recklessly run off...
I did not run!
I merely scurried off on foot so they couldn't catch me!
That's just fancy talk for running!
- Oink!
- Huh?
"Snow White and the Seven Kinokos"
"Teacher" "Touchy"
"Sprayer" "Angry"
"Slacky" "Carefree"
Look at the nameplate!
Huh? This must be Snow White's house!
Those of you waiting for Lord Snow White's fortune telling.
Our princess has just fallen into slumber.
We hope to see you all visit again.
Tsk. What the heck?
We've waited so long!
"Front of the Line"
[Kinokos gasp]
Are you kids after the princess?!
Kinoko
No, of course not! You must be, umm...
Grumpy, right?
I-if you have no business, we want you to head back...
Hah, and you're Bashful!
Haha, all seven of them have their own unique traits.
That's enough. Scram, won't you?
Huh, are you also Grumpy?
- [Sneeze]
- Oh, you're Sneezy!
Who's Sneezy now?
What, you're Grumpy too?
Isn't that quite a lot of Grumpys?
Moving on, we need to speak with Snow White!
If you want to see her so badly...
you'll have to get through us first!
[Gulps] We have no choice, we must fight these Monsters!
Don't let your guard down. They may
be small, but there's still seven.
They outnumber us!
Take this, our first strike!!
[War cry]
Huh...?
Oh?
- Uhh...
- Oink...
[Gasping]
[Wailing]
Uhh...
Mmm...
Ugh...
[Crying continues]
Don't cry!!
I'm too sad not to!!
Lookie, a treasure chest!
- Huh?!
- That was a win for us?!
They're just a bunch of crybabies!
Time for a peek...
Ooh!
A Holiday Cat Shield! This is perfect!
Huh, how?
Don't you know?
It's fully soundproof, so you can
block out all noise in front of you!
Really?
Now the Siren Sisters can't get into our heads!
Hehe, sweet!
Hey, since we won, does this mean
we can talk with Snow White?
No can do.
What, why?
The princess has just fallen into slumber.
She probably won't wake for another 5 years.
Huh, five years?!
We can't wait that long...
Isn't there a way to wake her up?
Well, there is one way - she needs a kiss from a prince.
[All gasp] A kiss?!
A...a kiss with the princess...
It's been told she'll awaken with one.
Err...sorry, but there's not even one of us that can
be called anything remotely close to a "prince..."
You can make this kiss count...there's nothing to lose!
- Perhaps our greatest challenge...
- Oink...
As I'm sure you all know, I was a prince
that got turned into this by magic.
You sure seem motivated!!
I'll take this on.
I mean, I'm the closest to a prince in this room.
I feel like the main hero!
W-why, you rats just shamelessly...
Fair enough, follow me.
Alright!
Chup, how stingy...
This is the princess' bedroom.
I can't wait...!
[Loud snoring]
Snow White
Come on, prince! Give her one hot kiss!
Get smoochin'!
Tch...I've been so foolish...
A real prince would never say he's like a prince.
I'm unfit for the title of a prince!!
Yet another runaway, huh?
It's like they're hit with whiplash when they see her.
I think a real prince would be someone like Pepperon!
Why are you like this now?
Oh, so you think I should kiss her instead?
I told you, I used to be a prince...
Of course I do! Go for it, Pepperon!
I'm right on it! Excuse me, haha.
[Pepperon humming]
Goodness, why are you so excited?
But I was a prince before!!
- [Knocking on door]
- Huh?
I forgot!
The closest prince we have in here is
obviously the former prince Gob-san!
What?!
Hmph, took you long enough, huh?
After all, you're just not used to my royal grace.
Pepperon, we should help this prince kiss the princess!
Good idea!
What are you two doing...?
Just go with it.
Which way, which way, which way, chop chop, right along.
[Loud snoring]
[Chup laughing]
[Gob-san straining]
[Whimpering] N......noooooooo!!
[Smooching]
[Snow White snoring]
[Gob-san whimpering]
Looks like Gob-san's kiss was a failure.
Yeah, he wasn't anything like a prince at all.
Isn't there anyhow else we can get this done quick?
After all, wouldn't the first guy be the most fit to the task?
Mhm.
Nuh-uh-uh! I'm not doing it, no way, no how!
Calm down!
If it's come to this, we'll have to ask the Mirror of Truth!
- Huh?
- Mirror of Truth?
Mirror, mirror, as you loom,
who's the most fitting prince in this room?
That would have to be Chup.
It's lying!! That mirror only speaks lies!!
No, that mirror only says truths.
Tch...agh! You mirror!!
- Chup, what are you-?!
- Hyah!
- [Glass shattering]
- [All clamor]
Pepperon, we're gonna have to use force!
No way! Don't you dare!
Chup, I must do my job!
Hmph!
Crystal Sword!
Crystal Sword.
Don't come closer or I'll slash!
Bringing out weaponry at a time like this?
Chup, if you can't pull this off, we can't find
out the weakness of them Siren Sisters!
I- I know, but...
If you wanted weaknesses, you coulda
just asked the Mirror of Truth.
HUH?!
See, you reap what you sow. Go on and kiss her!
No way in hell!
[Both grumbling]
Oh, Chup, I just realized!
- Clone!
- Huh?
Summon Clone, and ask it to turn someone else into you!
Mayone, that's genius!
Come out, Clone!
A soul, a ghost, a spirit!
[Clone laughing]
[Gob-san catching breath]
Clone, I need you to turn Gob-san into me!
[Clone laughing]
Huh? Huuuuh?!
- Alright, Pepperon!
- I'm on it!
W-what the? [Whimpering]
N-nooooooo!!
[Smooching]
[Snow White snoring]
[Gob-san whimpering]
That didn't work either...
I guess if it's not really Chup in flesh and blood, it won't work.
Oh, I think I've got it!
Ugh, I give up. Let's just figure something else out.
Huh?!
Princess Melora?!
So, Chup? Ya think you could kiss her now?
Guh, my pleasure! Hehe, this is gonna be great...!
[Chup wheezing]
Woah, Chup, calm yourself!
Chup, your face is all red.
[Moaning]
Mmm, I'm out.
Chup's innocent heart is making my heart pound too!
♪ Hey-ho, hey-ho, joining voices as one ♪
Coming through, pardon us.
It's dinnertime for the princess.
- Huh?
- But isn't she asleep?
- I'm starvin'...
- Huh?!
I'm havin' a bit of that soy sauce...
- [Startled gasp]
- She talked!
The princess grows an appetite when
she's early into her slumber.
Hey, uhh...can you hear my voice?
What is it?
- Ooh!
- Oink!
- Great!
We'll have to ask her stuff before she's done eating!
So, we're here to learn the Siren Sisters' weakness...
Hm? Oh, those scandalous women...
Those two used to be idol stars in the spirit world.
But when they became popular out of the gate...
they came to a sudden halt in activity.
Their dear love was exposed in magazines.
"Corrupt Idols"
"Siren Sisters: Boyfriends Discovered!!"
But it wasn't because of those scandals,
but because they gave these men too much.
As reality suggests, they just gave
up on chasing their dreams.
Really?
In the end, they broke up with those
men, and now they're retaliating.
The rumor is, as you see, they mess around
with you by making everything confusing.
Another, please.
So, then, how do we beat them?
Consider trying getting them to follow
their dreams again, maybe?
Thank you for the meal!
Wait up! How do we encourage them?
Sing to get them to sing.
[Snoring]
So that's what we do?
What do you mean?
It's like my grandmother says!
An eye for an eye and a toothpick for a tooth!
An eye for an eye,
and a toothpick
for a tooth!
An eye for an eye,
and a toothpick
for a tooth!
-Tome
Of course!
I always get food stuck in my teeth after I eat!
So that's what we do!
What is it we're doing?!
What's that? You want us to teach you a song?
We want to improve our singing so we can
present our message to the Siren Sisters!
So we'd like you to make a song if you can.
Well, even if we do... [Door opening] huh?
- I've got this!
- Commander!
"Commander's" no good. Call me "chairman!"
- Huh?
- "Chairman?"
As once-was chairman of a
world-famous musical company,
I was called the song-teaching demon.
T-that's one heck of a job title...
I can put together a composition
too! If you'd like me to, that is?
- Yes, please, Chairman!
- W-whaaat?
♪ Hey-ho, hey-ho, off to command we go ♪
♪ The cutesy little Kinokos, oh, how they love their jobs ♪
♪ Hey-ho, hey-ho... ♪
Just the motive I thought!!
[Mayone quivers]
[Gob-san poorly singing scales]
Several days later...
[Pepperon poorly singing scales]
[Chup poorly singing scales]
[Mayone skillfully singing scales]
Alright, Mayone's a pass, but the rest of you
are going to be training the night away!
Yessir, Chairman!
You're really okay with that...?
- Good work, all of you.
- Hm?
Let's take some time off and have a tea break.
Wait a minute, isn't that...?!
It is, The Genies' lamp!
Heheh, it was drifting through the river, so I picked it up.
[Gasp] Hey, Chup!
Oh, right! Let's ask them for help!
[Sirens singing]
Ooh, we really can't hear them at all!
Thank goodness for the soundproof shield!
Now we don't have to worry about them confusing us!
I am Si.
And I am Ren.
Together, we're...
♪ Siren Sisters~ ♪
Tch...so you're the Siren Sisters!!
You know them! This is our second encounter!!
Back again?
You really are...
♪ Such persistent kids ♪
Hey, Chup, do you really think this song will work?
We haven't really improved it yet...
Let's wait until the Genies get...here.
You shouldn't give up on your dreams
yume wo akirametara dame sa~
Wha, Chup? Huh?!
You should smile and laugh when you feel down~
kujike souna toki koso warae~
Dream about the smashing success you will be someday
itsuka no seikou wo yumemite~
Huh, Pepperon and Gob-san too?! What?!
With that, now's the time you sing with a big smile
sousa ima koso, egao de utae~
They've all gotten better!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
We'll join in!
One, two...
One, two, three, four!
If you keep on believing in your dreams
yume wo shinji tsuzukete ireba,
supottoraito wa kanarzu ataru
You'll always steal the spotlight for sure
- Wow...they've really gone all out.
- Oink!
Then when you let your radiance out and let it shine (and look forwards!)
sono toki kagayaki hanateru you ni mae wo muite
Use all your full power and...
itsumo zenryoku de
Come on, sing a song! Sing one together (happily!)
saa utae koe wo awasete (genki ni)
It's the Kinokos!
Come on, sing a song! Get stretching your lungs (pleasently!)
saa utae mune wo hatte (tanoshigeni)
Have faith in tomorrow, and in your hopes and dreams
ashita wo shinjiru sono omoi koso
That's your passport to the future!
mirai-e no pasupouto
Everyone's here!
What's going on? It's not like this is
the last episode, right?! [Crying]
konbini de kuda wo maku ukiyo wo samayou wakoudo yo
All you youngsters loitering about your lives,
shrouding the convenience stores
omaera wa genjitsu ni torinokosaresugi andeddo
You’re like undead who have left behind reality
itsumade son na koto kurikaesu no o-tsu-ka-re
How long are you going to keep doing this?
Don't you get tired of this same old routine?
hashiridase yo ENDLESS ROAD
Run forth through the endless road
koetemiroyo BORDERLINE
Go on past that borderline
sekai wa mugen ni hirogaru kouya
The world is an endless, limitless wilderness
omae no dokyou wo tameshiteiru
Where you can put your courage to the test
sumafo nankaja kensaku dekinai
It’s not something you can search for on your smartphone
sekai wa mugen ni hirogaru PARADISE
The world is an endless, limitless paradise
omaera wa giragira no
Soon you'll come to life taking in the blazing sun
taiyou kuratte ikiteiru
Raws
Translation/Typesetting/Timing
ED Karaoke
QC/Review
Raws
Translation/Typesetting/Timing
ED Karaoke
QC/Review
AnimeLand (TX)
Lumpstud
Noroino Hanako
NeSubs
AnimeLand (TX)
Lumpstud
Noroino Hanako
NeSubs
- The fog cleared up!
- Oink!
Do you think your song touched their hearts deeply?
Welp, we'll be around!
Thanks for helping us find our lamp!
Thanks to you too, Genies!
Ooh, sexy!
Hehe.
You lot can be on your way now.
You did a great job!
Oh, right! We have to get the love potion!
Ah, you're right!
So? Did we heal the wound in your hearts?
- Wait...what?
- Huh?
Ungh...
H-huh? Why do you look mad?
Trying to counter us with a song? That's not funny.
Besides, our song, on the other hand...
♪ Is much better to listen to ♪
S-should we be worried they're singing back at us...?
Grr...how could Snow White--?!
That's wrong! Your singing may have been
good, but the song was still awful!
Chairman!
Nah, I think you're going a bit overboard...
♪ This very song of mine... ♪
Haaaaaaah!
Whyyyy?!
[All shrieking]
Way to read the room!!
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone! What are you teaching us about today?
We're talking about Flying Cat today!
"Flying Cat"
Because of its refined design, Flying Cat
is a popular brand with young folks.
The Striped Sword 2 that Chup has is a
Flying Cat item that you can't easily buy.
It's proof of my unbreakable heart with Commander Cinderella!
But it did break very easily...
Next Time
It's a battle of idols of the past and idols of the now!
The popular idol group AKZ48 is gonna take them down!
Next time: New Gen Idols AKZ48!
New Gen Idols AKZ48
Alright, it's time for a big adventure!