This is Snack World, the hallowed ground
of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam
and people have handy smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
And my name's Chup!
My village was burnt down by
the evil land-destroying merchant Vinegar Khan,
so I've embarked on a journey
to get my revenge 1000-fold!
The final battle is here at last!
He's going down!
Alright, let's go on another big adventure today!
It's been too long since I've used my powers.
Episode 37: The Battle Continues! Chup Cries Out!
Cut it out! What are you doing?!
Chup, Vinsant! Are you guys okay?
Stop it!!
His Dragon Knight awakened!
You beat me to the punch.
I'll back you up, Chup.
Good luck.
A-Am I...?
So you've become Dragon Knights, eh?
Well, that certainly makes things
much easier for me.
Explain yourself!
Wave of Darkness!
That darkness is born from your soul:
your grudges, jealousy, envy...
Things that Dragon Knights are not immune to.
There it is!
I spy a deep jealousy
inside of you!
Vinsant!!
He turned Vinsant into a dragon!
Indeed. Vinegar can do that...
...as a Dark Dragon Knight!
Go on, Vinsant.
Show these heroes to their graves!
Snap out of it, Vinsant!
He's controlling you!
You grew wings and a tail
and you have this weird look in your eyes!
Well, yeah, he turned into a dragon!
Wake up, Vinsant!
I have a feeling that isn't our Vinsant anymore!
He probably doesn't understand us at all!
Vinsant...
I can't get close to him!
Pepperon, stay back!
This is my fight!
Perhaps I should let the trash
take its fellow trash out!
Vinsant!
Haven't we stuck together this whole time?
We ate melonpan cookies together,
and did a whole bunch'a other stuff too!
Why is that the only thing you remember?
Looks like I'll have to show no mercy!
C'mon, Pinocchio!
Huh? What? Where am I?
That's what you call no mercy?
Pinocchio, take a good look!
Whut?
Best day ever, whoo!
Did you have to pull that move
during such a grim moment?
But it worked for him!
Keep it up, Chup!
There's more where that came from!
Genies!
Ooh, sexy!
We made it, Chup!
What's happening?
Oh, look at you in that little outfit!
So adorable!
Listen up, guys!
No way!
Chup does not have a small *****!
It just hasn't gone through metamorphosis!
It's more like an ****worm if you ask me!
Good lord! An ****worm?
That's so dirty!
I just pictured it getting ****!
You beast!
Guys, I need you to fight against him!
My only wish for today
is that you suppress him!
Hmm, I don't really wanna,
but if you insist!
After all, it's what you wished for!
We'll do it just for you!
Let's do this!
Genies...
Hip Push!
How is a dumb attack like that
supposed to do anything?!
It worked?!
Good going! Next up...
Master Panpan!
Don't stand behind... YEOWCH!
And Candoll!
Hmph! I'll stand wherever I please!
So you do, huh?
Yeowch!
You female dog!
I'm not even a woman!
YEOWCH!
You may as well be!
Nothing you're saying is appropriate!!
Candoll! Master Panpan!
I need you to weaken him!
Excuse me?
You think you can summon me...
I stress,
you think you can summon me
to do your dirty work?
I'm begging you, Master Panpan!
Got it, you can count on me!
Candoll! Go on, do your thing!
I'm on it!
YEOWCH!
How is it, dragon I've never met before?
Are you feeling it?
Why would he?!
Oh come on, he is?
Now's my chance!
I can't...
We can't lose here!
We'll beat Vinegar!
We'll beat him hard!
It can't be!
He's using the ultimate Dragon Knight technique,
Flying Lightning Bolt Slash!
Yeah, I doubt it.
Special attack!
What Happened to Our
Melonpan Cookie Friendship Slash!!
See?
Now that's good!
Even as a Dragon Knight,
he's got good move naming!
Not bad. Not bad at all.
Vinegar, I'm gonna defeat you!
100%! Even if I die in the process!
I swore it to my mom, to my grandmother,
and to Princess Melora!
You've got guts, kid.
Dang it!
Vinsant!
Are you alright?
I thought you'd be stuck
as a dragon forever!
I mean, you were pretty cool
as a dragon too.
Wh-What's gotten into you, Vinsant?
Come on, go back to nor...mal...
Did you really think it'd be that easy
to break my spell?
Once you've fallen to the vine-side,
there is no escape.
My word!
No!
Chup!
Huh? Princess Melora?
Chup, did you really die?
Did I?
Yep, dead as a doornail.
Damn it, and I was so close
to beating Vinegar!
Even if I die, I was supposed
to defeat him!
Say, Chup.
Was beating Vinegar
all that you lived for?
Huh?
Then why not just accept death?
What?!
It doesn't really matter to me if
Vinegar lives or not.
If the only reason you're alive
is for something as silly as beating him,
you may as well be a zombie.
But I came this far to get my revenge!
Revenge, I see.
So you're fighting on behalf
of those that died?
Then look on the bright side,
now you get to visit them!
But I...
No buts, no cuts, no coconuts!
"I'll defeat him even if I die doing so"
is lame, you know why?
'Cuz you can't defeat him if you're dead!
Melora...
Chup! You're not supposed to die winning.
You want to honor your village?
Survive, rise from rock bottom,
and grab ahold of the future,
give it new hope!
You're not after a rare item,
you're after a rare future!
Huh?
Hehe, silly.
Chup! Dinner's almost ready!
Why don't you go wait with your grandma?
Okay!
Grandma, let's play!
Want to thumb wrestle with me, Chup?
Sure! I won't go easy on you!
Let's go!
I declare a thumb war!
Almost got you!
Gotcha!
One, two, three!
Game set! Grandma wins!
Man, you always win!
Do I? Are you sure you're not
just a little weakling?
Oh come on! You're a grown-up
and I'm a kid!
Are you saying grown-ups are stronger,
and kids are weaker?
I'm just an old lady!
Yeah, I guess...
But my point is, you only won
because you're the grown-up!
It's no fair!
How's this, Chup?
Your loss had nothing to do
with your age.
Huh?
You lost because you went into it thinking,
"It's no fair I'm up against someone older than me!
Of course I would lose!"
Do you get it?
Huh?
Yeah... Now that you mention it.
Listen here, Chup.
Going into a battle prepared to lose
makes you even less than a weakling—
a wimpy little plankton turd!
Really?!
Chup, if you continue to believe
that you can win,
then you will win eventually!
You will most certainly win!
You'll fully, flawlessly win!
Got it!
Wh-What the?
Grandma... I don't know why...
but I just... I can't stop crying!
What do you think you're doing?!
Doing that to his corpse
is just cruel!
What?! He's already dead?!
Is he not?
Just look at him!
That's a bona fide dead body!
Did you really think you had a chance?
Some shameless trash you are to come at me
when you know you can't win.
This is what happens.
Worcester, clean up these scraps!
Yes, sir!
It's like... my grandmother said!
Going into a battle prepared to lose
makes you even less than a weakling—
a wimpy little plankton turd!
Whoa! Chup came back to life!
What's that aura coming from him?
And I'm no plankton turd!
I... I'm...
Could it be?
Has he surpassed the Dragon Knight
and become the legendary Duke Dragoon?
Even I had no idea that stage really existed...
With all due respect, Darefalcon...
I think Chup...
has a different idea.
I'm Chup, the Super Great Dragon Knight!
What?
Told ya.
Chup never changes!
It's like my grandmother said!
I can win!
I will win, fully, flawlessly!
I can win. I will win,
fully, flawlessly.
As long as I believe in myself,
I will come out on top.
I can win. I will win,
fully, flawlessly.
As long as I believe in myself,
I will come out on top.
I will come out on top!
-Tome
Oh, but I'm afraid vigor alone
won't be enough to defeat me.
My goal isn't something as simple
as taking you down.
My real goal is not a rare item,
but a rare future full of hope!
What is he saying?
Did he get hit in the head real bad?
Is that the price for coming back to life?
My head is perfectly fine.
I'm being fully, flawlessly honest.
Come at me, Vinegar!
Right, Vinsant. Keep serving me!
My word! He's taking them both on at once!
Is that really the same Chup?
He's rocking it!
What the?!
Did I just...?
That was awesome, buddy!
He seems more shocked than us.
You're the only one left, Vinegar!
Right, I was told about that.
The stage above being a Dragon Knight,
the eukaryotic awakening, Duke Dragoon...
Even so, I made a pact with the darkness
and raised my power to its limits!
You don't stand one chance.
What's happening?
Vinegeres
Is that the thing they usually do here,
where the final boss gets a second form?!
He looks awful scary like that!
No matter how stubborn the foe,
I will win!
I'm gonna defeat you,
save the world, and save Melora!
You're nothing but a feeble little table scrap.
What makes you think you can defeat
the great Vinegar Khan?
If you ask me, you're no stronger
than a little shrimp!
Dang it...
Chup, you're not alone! You have us!
We're your friends, aren't we?
Vinsant!
Looks like I caused you a lot of trouble.
Allow me to redeem myself!
Trouble? Nah! You made me stronger!
I can see. Now, how about we
clean up this mess?
Hold it!
We won't let you guys
hog this cool moment for yourselves!
I'm a pretty good mage, if I do say so myself.
Yeah! I wanna show y'all the fruits of my training!
This is the perfect time
to use my ultimate spell!
You guys!
Alright, Vinegar! You better
fully, flawlessly watch out!
Send all the people you want,
it won't change anything!
I'll erase all of you!
Go, Chup! Now!
Vinsant!
I won't let you lay a finger on Chup!
Me neither!
Thanks, guys!
I've got this! Just watch, Butako!
Come at me, Vinegar!
It's like my grandmother...
No, it's like my beloved
Princess Melora said!
Grab
Grab ahold of that rare future!
a
Grab
hold
a
Grab
hold
a
of
hold
a
of
hold
that
of
rare
that
fu
rare
ture.
fu
Love, Melora
ture.
You better prepare!
My ultimate spell: Maximum Descent Meteor!
Huh?! Your ultimate spell
is a real thing?
Now, Chup!
Use the meteor's fire
with your sword!
Got it!
Here I come, Vinegar!
I Don't Really Get What "Rare Future"
Means, But It Sounds So Cool Slash!
You little shrimps are actually
besting me...?
That's ridiculous... It can't be...
We're no shrimps!
And that's offensive to shrimp!
No need to take it so literally.
Oh, but you don't get it.
Without me, the world's economy
will collapse.
Soon you will recognize
the grave crime you have committed.
Crime?
That's rich talk, coming from you!
Yeah!
You don't get it at all.
So be it. After all, the world will soon...
fall into the Vinehman Financial Crisis!
What happened to him?
He paid the consequences
for his pact with the darkness.
I-Is it over?
It looks that way.
Yeah.
We did it!!
The sun is rising in King Oyster City...
That explosion earlier must have
taken out the Solar Compression Generator Sol-Eater.
Adrian!!
Who's Adrian?
Huh? It's Mr. Carbonara's chicken, no?
Why did you mention her?
Heh, just felt like it.
So that didn't mean anything?!
That's our Chup!
Sure is.
shobokure gao no mobukyara domo ga
On and on these tired old NPCs
iiwake shinagara aruiteru
Keep walking around excusing themselves
itsumo miteiru michisugara
As I took the same old path again
mita koto mo nai wakuwaku wo mita
I found the thrill I've sought for my whole life
itsumade shibonda mama nano
Just how long will I keep drooping around like this?
minikui ahiru no mama nano
How long will I stay an ugly duckling?
ima no reberu wa ichi dakedo
I'm still only level one
ima ni mitero yo sono uchi JUMP UP
But watch me, soon I'll jump up
saikin no wakai mon wa tte
"Why, kids these days..."
toshiyori domo ga boyai teru kedo
...Our old boomers grumble and complain
soro soro omei henjou da
But it's not too late to clear my name
iya ga ou ni mo mattanashi daze
I might not like it, but I can't wait any longer
ketsu no ana kara jetto funsha daaa
I gotta blast free from my cowardly shell!!
ore wa itsuka hana ni naru
Give me time and I'll bloom like a flower
sora ni nobiru hana ni naru
A flower spread out to the sky
kimi ni todoku hana ni naru
The flower that reaches you
It can't be...
Huh? What's up?
This isn't the real Dragon Heart!
It's a fake!
Huh?!
Does that mean...?
This is bad.
We might have just made a terrible mistake.
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone!
What are you teaching us about today?
Today's lesson is on
Dragon Knight evolution!
Dragon Knight Evolution
Dragon Knight is a title given to people
who endure hard training to gain mighty powers,
but there's a stage above it
called Duke Dragoon!
It's an evolution past the point
of being a Dragon Knight!
Incorrect! It's actually
the Super Great Dragon Knight!
That name is just like you, Chup...
Next Time
We finally beat Vinegar!
I gotta go tell Princess Melora!
Wait, what? Something's off about our town.
And Vinsant's about to go
through some terrible trials!
Next time: "Vinsant Puts Up a Brave Fight."
Vinsant Puts Up a Brave Fight
Alright, it's time for a big adventure!