This is Snack World, the hallowed
ground of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam and
people have handy smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
...And my name's Chup.
My village was burnt down by the evil
land-destroying merchant, Vinegar Khan,
and I've embarked on a journey
to get my revenge 1000-fold!
The tickets to King Oyster City, where
Vinegar is, cost 20 million gillan.
So I'm on an adventure searching for
big treasure to make loads of cash!
[Chup humming theme song]
Alright, let's go on another big adventure today!
Ep. 14: Little Weakling Pepperon
Hnnn...mmm... I can't take any more of this...
Is...is the princess hanging in there?
As you can see, she's still suffering.
Princess Melora...
This is impossible!
Wh...what the? She's eating fruit...?
Princess, more of the fruits you requested came in.
This is impossible!
Just like I thought, she's just overeating...
Melora doesn't seem to be recovering any time soon...
For lunch today, she was given one cup of udon and left behind half of it.
Half of it?!
Well yeah, 'cuz she's clearly going down on those fruits.
I cannot afford any more delays on this. Sir, bring out you-know-what.
Hmph. Requesting you-know-what.
He's certaintly gotten used to the role...
Hm?
Please equip this as you wish.
It is the strongest class weapon in my inventory.
[Both gasp]
What could it be this time...?
Ooh, yet another Clanarine item!
It must be the Clan Crystal Axe!
Oho!
You can wield the axe, Pepperon!
Eh, is that alright with you?
Yeah!
- Oooh!
I'm begging you, please beat the Phoenix this time!
Come on! Fellas, you just leave this one to me!
You trying to kill me?!
Use my axe and SLASH, use my axe and SLASH!
Pepperon seems jolly today!
He sure does love his axes!
Hey, can I say something?
Hm?
- What's up, Mayone?
I...still think...we're gonna lose today!
Huh?!
- Why are your hopes so low?!
Yeah, why?! Pepperon seems very enthusiastic about it!
I can already read today's outcome.
What do you mean by "read" the outcome?! This isn't some sort of comic!
Mayone, what's gonna happen?
Basically...
[Shouting]
Pepperon's going to confront the Phoenix.
And I guess we'll get a look at the Phoenix's Fantasy?
And then...
Hmm? Ohh!
Meat! Yummy meat!! Meeeaaat!!
Right? He's gonna get sucked into the Fantasy and get hurt in the process.
Of course not! This isn't a gag comic!!
[Stomach grumbling]
- Uhh...
I get hungry when I hear the word "meat."
Come on, Pepperon!
See, this is exactly what I mean!
Mmm... if we don't plan something ahead for this, it'd be bad.
Oink...
Hmm... Ah! I have a good idea!
Oink!
- What is it?
It's like my grandmother said!
If you're prepared... HEYAH!
If you're prepared,
HEEEYAAH
-Tome
What was that?
So we just have to prepare for battle in advance by getting something to eat!
I get it!
Good idea, Chup!
My stomach and my back can concur.
Well then, let's go get something to eat!
Huh?! Chup, you're just doing this because you're hungry, and...
[Stomach grumbling]
Hm?
- Oink?
[Mayone stuttering]
Here! This place has just the perfect meat with bones lunch!
That's our gourmet Mayone.
Huh? It feels like I've been to this place before.
See? I'm sure Pepperon will be satisfied with this place too.
[Pepperon grunts]
Huh?
[Pepperon sighing]
- Pepperon, what's wrong?
Uh- It's nothing, nothing at all!
[Pepperon chowing down]
I told you we'd want to fill up first and I was right!
This is going to cost us a lot, isn't it...?
Mmmm... perfection!
This meat promises and it delivers.
Waiter, 10 more orders of this meat plea---huh?
Hm? Pepperon?
[Laughing]
[Pepperon gasping]
What's wrong, do you know them?
Ah, what are you suggesting?
Ah- aah, I can't be here.
I have to practice using my axe!
What's with this all of a sudden?
Ey, wasn't that guy Pepperon?
Eh? Pepperon?
Of course, it looks he does know them.
I remember now! This is where Pepperon and I met!
Huh?!
[Pepperon panting]
Did those guys bully him?
Uh-huh. Pepperon's strong physically, but he's very timid.
I can see what you mean.
Hm?
Oh!
Hehe, that tickles!
He couldn't stand up for himself when his friends picked on him.
Then how is he fit for a warrior?
Pepperon is hopeless.
He has the strength, so he needs to toughen up more.
That's right...
Uh, Mayone?
We'll never take down the Phoenix with him acting like that!
Wait, Mayone!
Oink!
Hand it over.
Hah, uh, hand over what?
I'm confiscating your axe.
N...never! This axe is mine!
You're not gonna beat the Phoenix acting like a coward. Now, give it!
Come on, Mayone, give him a break!
You're overstating things like usual.
- Oink!
You get it, Pepperon?
- Mm?
Men can't just act tender and kind.
I-I understand. I have to be brawny!
You can't just be brawny, either! You should be a bit more ruthless.
I'm... I'm ruthless! I've stayed up late before, and eaten sweets right after buying them!
That's NOT what I...
I'll do it! I'm gonna use this axe...
...and slice that Phoenix right in half!!
For real?
Because despite everything...I'm just a normal ol' warrior!
[Sighs] What do I do with you...
Trouble's afoot!
- Huh?
Look over there!
- What?!
Keep your eyes peeled for the Monster out there!
What is it?!
- Oink?
Hmph. There’s just four of you?
You must be down outta luck to catch me here.
I got no quarrel with ya… but yer toast!
W- I'm not mentally prepared yet!!
[Monster shouts]
- Here he comes!!
Hmph!
Baby Knight
Mm?
He's tiny.
OY! Which one of ya brats just called me tiny?!
Ah'm gonna tear ya limb from limb!!!
Sorry, you just seemed much more impressive before.
What was that!?
Oh, right! Hey, Pepperon?
You should show your true strength by defeating this kid!
Don't call me "this kid"!!
I agree! I'm on this, fellas!
Hmph. Allow me to demonstrate the true power of a genius swordsman.
Bring it on!
This is getting intense.
- Gulp.
Hmph. [Shouts]
Weak spot!
- Hm!
Ow-ow... it's going numb...I can't move my arm!
Is everything okay over there?
It's brokennn! You totally broke ittt!!!
Isn't he over-acting a bit?
He sure is.
And Pepperon's being too gentle!
I didn't cut you, right?
Idiot. It was when my sword and yer axe collashed! I can't feel my arm!!
Ah- aaaooww....
I'm extremely sorry about that...
And he apologized.
Pepperon, just take care of him!
Oh, that's right!
Well, it's all healed up now.
You're gonna have to try harder if you wanna knock me down!!
Alright, bring it on!
Gulp.
I can't feel any tension here.
Weak spot!
[Baby Knight grunting]
[Pepperon grunts]
[Baby Knight shrieks]
How about that? I'm feeling confident in my strength!
Yeah, right...
He's a lot less talkative now, huh...
He was shown to be outmatched.
Alright, next time, I won't go easy on you!
Uh, for real?
Here I come!!
AAAH! DON'T!!
Hm?
I have a test tomorrow!
This is really, really bad!! I haven't studied at all!!
Ahh, are you okay?!
It's bad! I haven't even opened the textbook once!!
I'm gonna have to stay up all night!
What's he trying to play here?
I feel real bad for ya.
And he's apologizing again!
Come on, Pepperon!
- Oink, oink!
Welp, you can stick around here today.
But next time we meet will be your grave! Adios.
W...wait right there!
What now...?
This is fully, flawlessly over, right?
So d'ya mind surrendering?
That's right! We've had our fun, but it's time for the treasure chest.
Y'guys really think this is funny?
How am I supposed to take a test tomorrow if you take me down now?
You don't know when to give up.
I wasn't fighting with 100% of my strength anyhow...
If I'm fighting all four of you, I can only use 1/4th of my power, 15%!
- Wha?
- 15 percent...?
Wouldn't 1/4th of 100% be 25%?
Huh?
Lemme guess...not the star student in math?
Whaaa?! I ain't that bad!!
Oh dear, you sure you can handle tomorrow's test?
I'll do just fine!! I know all about maths!!
My teacher praises me for it!!
Sure.
Why don't we see just how good your math is?
Huh?
This is a fresh go about things.
You solve this right, you win.
Now: What's 42 divided by 3?!
Ghh...we can't just do this on the spot, that's unfair!
I can normally get this perfectly if I'm prepared, but I didn't get any sleep last night!!
What kind of excuse is that?
Well, what's 7 plus 3?
10?
Ooh!
That's not worthy of an "ooh," he took way too long on that!
Welp, that's my win in the bag. Adios!
Final question.
- Guh.
You go to the store and buy two biscuits 50 gillan each and one hard candy worth 80 gillan!
If you pay with a 1,000-gillan bill, how much will your change be?!
Uhh...wait...
Answer the lady, Monster!
Gu-guh...I just ask for no change!!
Ooh!
What a manly move!
Don't encourage him!! Answer the question, brat!
Err...there's two biscuits, one hard candy, strike the biscuits...ah, no, don't strike them...
Crap, I broke it! Now I can't count 'em! [Sobbing]
What's the matter with him...?
Okay. 3, 2, 1...
I dunnnoooooo!!!
Sweet, we beat him!
And very unusually too.
Curse you, addition and division...
What is it?
It's a healing drink.
Really? That drink will be gone in a gulp.
Well, you take down a small fry, you don't expect a big prize.
I'll register your Snack just in case!
Heheh!
Do we really need to register the small fry?
Who...which one of ya brats just called me a small fry?!
You sure do have the energy to fight...
[All gasp]
- What the?
Daddy!!
Over here, Masao!!
He's huge...
- Holy...
[Baby Knight panting]
D'ya think yer slick skipping out on watching the shop?!
No, I was preparing for tomorrow's test!!
Excuse me?! You better cut out this dilly-dallying and come home at once!!
I'm sorry, daddy!!
Please don't spank me, daddyyyy!!
Don't mind it. Let's get out of here.
As expected, his father is strong.
What store do they handle, though?
Alright, I feel like I'm really at full power now!
There's no way the Phoenix ain't going down!!
Glad to hear it, Pepperon! Come on, guys. Let's move out once again!
[All shout]
But in the end, Pepperon didn't really beat him, did he...?
Mmm...I can't get used to it no matter how much we come.
It's very unsettling, isn't it?
Hm? Pepperon?
- Huh?
Are you afraid?
W...what are you talking about? Of course not!
But you're trembling?
W-with excitement!
Ah-choo!!
- [Pepperon screams]
You startled me!
[Sigh] Hey, Pepperon? Why don't you let Chup handle it this time, huh?
Let him have the axe!
- N-never!
Pepperon, don't be stubborn with us.
We really should just let Chup have this one.
I know, but...
You've been acting weird all day, Pepperon.
Here, I'll give this to Chup.
[Exclaims]
Here. You be careful too, Chup.
Pepperon, I'll do my best today!
You can't... I must...
I must do my best today!!
Huh?
What's wrong, Pepperon?
I've decided to follow my heart.
Today will be the day I pay you back, Chup!
"Pay him back?"
Pay him back for what?
Back then, Chup was the one who helped me out.
I was a pathetic warrior who kept getting picked on by my pals.
What's this, oolong tea again?
Say, Pepperon.
You didn't cower from another battle, did you?
I bet ya ran home trembling and hid under the futon.
I... I would never, I swear.
Well, what happened, then?
Did you run?
No matter how much strength you have for a battle, you're nothin' but a little weakling.
What a shame.
I couldn't open my mouth then.
Oh?
Master! A glass of orange juice with strong orange!
Who are you?
It's like my grandmother said!
Those who bully the weak piss ammonia!
Those who
bully the weak
piss ammonia!
Those who
bully the weak
piss ammonia!
- Oink, oink!
-Tome
What was that?!
Uh...uhh...ignore him! I don't want to get strangers involved in this...
My name is Chup. What's your's?
Huh?
What's your name?
P-... Folks call me Pepperon.
Nice to meet you!
From now on, we're no strangers. We're friends!
Ohh...
That's enough blabbering.
[Pepperon stumbles]
- Oink...
Go!
- Take this!
[Chup and men fighting]
Chup stood up for me back then.
Meanwhile, I was still shivering in fear.
It's just like Mayone said, I'm a useless man.
Pepperon...
But Chup...Chup didn't give up on me despite that.
Are you doing okay, Pepperon?
[Pepperon stuttering]
Don't worry. They ran away with their tails between their legs.
W-wow...Chup, you're amazing!
Huh? Hehehe...
That day, I made a vow to my heart.
That I'd follow this person until I could pay him back, no matter what!
Didn't know you had a troublesome past like that.
Chup, that's so you.
Hehehe, well...
After all, I can't just sit in the corner and cower in fear.
I have to stand up and fight!
Well said, Pepperon!
Hm... I dunno...
Today, this job is in Pepperon's hands!
Chup...
It's alright. You're strong!
Fully, flawlessly strong!
That's something I can guarantee. So don't worry one bit!
Alright! Today's the day I become a man!
[Screeching]
It doesn't get any less frightening...
It’s just otherworldly…
I will be your opponent today!
Ooh!
- He's a much different Pepperon today!
[Screeching]
[All gasp]
Where are we...?
Watching another Fantasy, it seems...
[All gasp]
- Is this place...?
Oh!
That's...that's me!
This must be the day we met! Look, I'm over there!
My goodness!
What's this, oolong tea again?
Say, Pepperon. You didn't cower from another battle, did you?
I bet ya ran home trembling and hid under the futon.
Pepperon's getting tangled up...
I feel pity for myself watching this.
It's like I thought, I'm a failure of a warrior.
It must be trying to show us the places we want to see the least.
[Mayone sighs]
Pepperon, don't look away!
Stand up and face the facts...no, face the truth!
"The truth?"
What do you mean, Chup?
Oink-oink?
That's right, Butako. Now's when you find out the truth!
Let's go!
Take this! Hyaah!
[Shouting]
[Chup struggling]
I will protect my friend even if I die doing it!
[Gasps]
[Exclaims] Ahh... I'm going...down.
Wait, he lost?!
Chup?
Where does it go from here?
Heh. All bark and no bite.
That's what he gets for crossing us.
I'm putting an end to this.
I won't let anyone...bully my friend!!
[Bullies gasp]
What the?! Why's Pepperon actin' up?!
P-Pepperon?
Don't get cheeky! [Shouts]
Darn you... [Shouts]
[Pepperon shouts]
Haah!!
- [Bully exclaims]
So strong!
Pepperon, that was amazing!
I don't remember any of that...
This is the truth!
What is?
That you didn't help him at all, but Pepperon stood up for himself?
I suppose it's like he exploded with feelings for his friend!
Heheh, you could say that.
Don't "heheh" me! Why didn't you bring this up earlier?
Because it feels nice to know Pepperon idolizes me...
Gah!
Idiot!
I had that much power?
Damn it.
Let's get outta here.
You've gotten better, Pepperon.
I'm sorry I wasn't honest with you, Pepperon.
Thing is, I'm just nowhere near as cool as you think I am.
On the contrary, Chup. You're still very cool!
You have the bravery to stand against any opponent!
And I want to follow your example!
[Chuckles]
[All gasp]
Ooh! The Fantasy is gone!
Let's do this thing!
Go for the gold, Pepperon!
Deathblow - Tender Yet Brawny Attack!
Hi-yah!!
[Screeching]
You did it!
- Pepperon, you're the best!
konbini de kuda wo maku ukiyo wo samayou wakoudo yo
All you youngsters loitering about your lives,
shrouding the convenience stores
omaera wa genjitsu ni torinokosaresugi andeddo
You’re like undead who have left behind reality
itsumade son na koto kurikaesu no o-tsu-ka-re
How long are you going to keep doing this?
Don't you get tired of this same old routine?
hashiridase yo ENDLESS ROAD
Run forth through the endless road
koetemiroyo BORDERLINE
Go on past that borderline
sekai wa mugen ni hirogaru kouya
The world is an endless, limitless wilderness
omae no dokyou wo tameshiteiru
Where you can put your courage to the test
sumafo nankaja kensaku dekinai
It’s not something you can search for on your smartphone
sekai wa mugen ni hirogaru PARADISE
The world is an endless, limitless paradise
omaera wa giragira no
Soon you'll come to life taking in the blazing sun
taiyou kuratte ikiteiru
Raws
Translation/Typesetting/Timing
ED Karaoke
QC/Review
Raws
Translation/Typesetting/Timing
ED Karaoke
QC/Review
AnimeLand (BSJ)
Lumpstud
Noroino Hanako
NeSubs
(Specter Subs)
AnimeLand (BSJ)
Lumpstud
Noroino Hanako
NeSubs
(Specter Subs)
That was awesome, Pepperon!
For real, that was so cool!
That's our Pepperon!
Yeah, you did it!
Nah, hehehe...
On the other hand...isn't it getting hot in here? Hm?
[Screeching]
[Chup gasps]
I- I forgot! The Phoenix is a firebird.
No matter how much you beat it, it keeps coming back!
I'm feeling a lot of déjà vu here.
Come on, Pepperon! Slice it to pieces!
[Stomach grumbling]
- ...Huh?
No can do.
When I get hungry, I have to lump my back down.
Darn it! His lunch got cut short when we left...
[Screeching]
That's it, Chup! Why don't you recreate what happened back then?
Back then?
When his friend was getting beaten up?
Of course, because Pepperon's power exploded when he needed to protect his friends!
Alright!
Gob-san!
Agh, what the heck?
If it's come to this...the day has come when you'll get a taste of my strongest spell- aack!
Ooh, meat! Meat well-done and roasted to perfection!
Huhh?!
Meat! Yummy meat!
He's looking at him as meat instead of a friend!!
Wha!? Hey, don't you dare, Pepperon!!
Thanks for the fooood!!
[Gobson shrieks]
- Blegh, this is awful! What kind of meat is this?!
It's...it's me...
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone!
What are you teaching us about today?
"Clanarine"
Today's about Clanarine!
Clanarine is designed by living national treasures,
with its beautiful form refined by leading industrial technology.
One of the finest brands out there!
But like most popular brands, watch out
for counterfeits like "Klan Areen."
I won't fall for something like that!
Next Time
Mayone's always very strong and confident, but she has a sad past?
Don't lose, Mayone! Use your deadly magic and take down the Phoenix!
Next time: The Little Match Mayone!
The Little Match Mayone
Alright, it's time for a big adventure!