This is Snack World, the hallowed ground
of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam
and people have handy smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
And my name's Chup!
My village was burnt down by
the evil land-destroying merchant Vinegar Khan,
so I've embarked on a journey
to get my revenge 1000-fold!
At last, my journey has brought me
close to Vinegar.
In order to defeat him, I will overcome
any impossible mission that comes my way!
Alright, let's go on another big adventure today!
Episode 27: Plan Butako! A Close Encounter with Scardon!!
For the past few days, I've been in town
collecting intel on Vinegar Palace.
So that's why we haven't seen you
for a while!
I see! Though, I never took you for someone
who was good with strangers.
What gave you that idea?
I thought maybe you were wallowing
from playing side character,
and went to a good place to drown yourself
in hot ladies every night.
Don't lump me in with you.
I fought tooth and nail to
collect the intel I needed...
and I finally figured it out.
Our ticket into Vinegar Palace...
Well, tell us!
There is none!
We have no way of getting in at this moment!
What?! Come on!
What was all that dramatic build-up for?
I want my expectations back!
I'm not done yet.
Our top priority is to stop Vinegar
from resurrecting the evil overlord Scardon.
And to do that...
I know! We need a good night's sleep!
Yes. Tucking in early is good for the body.
And with a healthy body comes a healthy soul,
that we can use to stop...
No!
You really rode that one out, huh?
Listen up. In order to
stop Scardon's resurrection...
we need...
I know! We gotta focus on
eating our greens!
Yes. Eating lots of veggies
helps the blood circulate,
and keeps our bodies lively and healthy
so we can stop...
Not that either!
You could probably afford
to cut the bit sooner...
In order to stop Scardon's resurrection,
we need...
I know! We need love!
Bunnilla, my sweet...
Yes. Love stimulates the pheremones
in our bodies,
keeping us healthy... No, not that!
Will you all cut that out?
You say that, but you keep going along
with their suggestions...
What is Scardon anyways?
You forgot?! I told you that already!
The king of dragons who once
was a threat to our world!
Vinegar is trying to bring him back,
and make the monsters go out of control!
Oh, yeah! That!
How could you forget
an important detail like that?
The jewel with the ability to revive Scardon
is the Dragon Heart.
Oh, yeah! The one Vinegar stole from us!
Yes. Now, if we can take back
the Dragon Heart from under Vinegar's nose,
we can stop Scardon's resurrection!
Oh, finally...
So where's the Dragon Heart now?
As I've been told,
it's in the underground lab in Vinegar Palace.
Supposedly it's being stored
with Scardon's skeleton.
Huh? But you said we couldn't
get into Vinegar Palace...
We can't, but we do have another option...
Come with me.
This is it.
How will we get through there?
Look over there.
We're not gonna fit in those small holes.
That's right. We humans
aren't getting in through there.
But you should squeeze through easy.
Huh? You're sending Butako in?
We'll have Butako sneak in
and retrieve the Dragon Heart.
Butako's gonna go all the way
to the Dragon Heart on her own?
It's gotta be humongous in there!
Don't worry. I've planned ahead for that.
We've prepared the ceremony
for Scardon's resurrection.
Please come down
to the underground laboratory.
Give me 45 minutes.
Is something the matter, Khan?
You seemed to be hasty
about this resurrection...
Hold your horses,
we're not in a rush.
I mean, no, but...
Put a sock in it!
I'm in the middle of a TV show.
And on the finale, no less!
There's nothing more insulting
than interrupting me during the best parts!
My apologies, sir.
TV first, ceremony later.
Stand down.
Unless you wanna be a zombie.
Can you hear us, Butako?
If you can,
say something.
What'd she say?
"It's so dusty in here,
I'm getting sniffly."
No wonder dust would get
in that big nose of hers.
Are you the only one who understands her?
Yep, but she can understand all of us!
Alright. Proceed.
She should be able to find her way
if we keep guiding her like this.
What's she doing?
D-Devil Bowie!
Oh? Do you mean me?
Oh, isn't that...!
It's that guy from Mr. Fishburger's mansion...
The one who finished off
Inspector Chilipepper!
I'm one of your biggest fans...
I brought you a gift!
Thank you...
Today is a big day, isn't it?
Huh? What for?
It's the day I realized
just how captivating you are!
Ohh, Bowie!
Good lord, this dude is all talk!
How despicable!
I hate guys like this
who are so full of themselves!
I'll take good care of it.
Also, don't forget to tell everyone online
how kind I was to you, 'kay?
See ya later!
Okay!!
H-Hi, Bowie!
Another one?!
I wrote you a fan letter!
Please take it!
Someone's a ladie's man.
What do they see in this jerk?
Thanks.
If you don't mind, please write back!
I even included a reply card!
I'll need another one of those.
Huh?
I'll need to write back
to your parents as well!
To thank them for giving life
to such a beautiful young lady.
Oh, Bowie!
Ugh.
Does he not cringe at his own lines?
Don't worry, I'll reply to you too.
Oh, and don't forget to tell everyone online
just how fine and charming I was, 'kay?
See ya later.
Okay!
Bunch'a easy marks.
Thanks to those dumb broads,
my numbers are off the charts!
Dang, he looks so sinister
with the women out of the picture.
Shocking how well his PR is going.
Butako, give that twerp
some fire breath!
Yeah! Burn his hair clean off!
Hold on. If we cause a scene,
the whole operation is a bust.
We have to focus on the Dragon Heart.
Come on...
Just drip some snot on him.
It's raining indoors?
Is it a goddess shedding tears of jealousy?
Ugh, even his monologue
is painful...
Why is there a monster in the vents?
Butako, get away!
He hasn't noticed you yet!
He saw!!
It's not what it looks like!!
I wasn't slacking off,
I'm just taking a break!!
W-Wait, who are you?
A trainee?
He doesn't know you're an intruder.
Engage in small talk.
Ah, so you are!
No wonder I haven't seen you around.
Are you lost or sumthin'?
It happens. Follow me!
What is this place?
It's full of items!
Look! It's the Black Märchen Shield
from Peffany!
That variant is so rare!
Oh, I want it!
What in the world...?
What's with the look?
Your mouth's gaping open!
This is where we work, right?
It's the treasure chest delivery center!
The treasure chest delivery center?
Whew, you're clueless!
You know how treasure chests
drop down all over the world?
It's weird, right?
Yer just goin' for a walk,
and all these humans are opening chests!
Don'tcha ever think
"They put out another one of those?!"
Come to think of it, he's right!
There's a mechanism behind that!
What is it?
Them chests are being set up
by arms dealers,
for those human adventurers!
Think of it like this!
Humans all over the world
thirst for treasure chests!
So they prepare for adventure!
And to do that,
they buy weapons and armor,
making the arms dealers
a pretty penny!
No way!
Arms dealers are behind
the treasure chests in dungeons and so?
And that's the trick!
Well, there's a bit more to it than that.
Look over there.
This is how many adventurers
we've had in the past 30 years.
The amount increased nearly tenfold
thanks to the treasure chests!
It's like my grammy used to say!
If the wind blows,
the bucket makers prosper!
If you leave treasure,
the arms dealers prosper.
If the wind blows,
the bucket makers prosper!
If you leave treasure,
the arms dealers prosper.
the arms dealers prosper!
-Mimiko
Aw, man! He even took my thing!
Let's cut off the detour here
and get moving.
Oh, done already?
Aight, I better get back
to work too! Good luck!
But what was the monster doing there?
I don't think we've ever
seen him before.
I wonder how my grammy's doin'!
Oy, Mimic! Get in line
for your assignment!
Y-Yessir!!
Did you get your assignment yet?
Nope, not yet.
I hope I can get a chest in the forest!
Ain't a lotta humans,
but plenty'a food!
I feel ya. The desert is pure hell.
It's like a sauna in there...
By the time humans get to ya, yer already weak.
How're ya supposed to fight like that?
You, in the back!
H-Here!
Get in that chest.
You're bound for a cave
on the northern end of Macaron Mountain.
Your trip is coming up,
so don't dawdle.
Huh?!
Winters up there are cold.
What's this room?
Enter.
Bingo. It's their underground lab.
And this is the evil overlord
Scardon's skeleton...
He looks so daunting...
Even through a screen,
this looks terrifying...
He's just a skeleton,
but he looks so alive...
Have you found the Dragon Heart?
There it is!
The Dragon Heart!
Now's your chance!
Now take it!
What the?!
Is that Scardon?
They haven't even brought him back yet!
This must be his spirit!
He's so powerful,
his wicked grudges are taking form
even before his resurrection.
He can attack as a spirit?!
This guy is bad news!
Someone took the Dragon Heart!!
What?!
Th-That's the thief!!
Oh, no, Butako!
What now?!
I prepared the P Switch for this eventuality!
Oh, wow! Sounds awesome!
Alright! P Switch, activate!
Wait, "P" for potato?
Whenever Butako eats potatoes,
she gets a 10-second power boost!
The screen is shaking!
Butako's quivering...
She's gonna run out of time...
Give up the fight!
Run for it, Butako!
What's the fuss?
How am I supposed to focus
on my TV time with all this noise?
There's an intruder!
They've taken the Dragon Heart!
An intruder? Of what kind?
It appears to be a small dragon.
They won't get off easy
for interrupting the climax of my finale.
Keep going, girl!
Uh-oh, it's a dead end!
Butako, shrink and go up!
We lost her!
Must've broken the camera.
Butako...
It's no use...
She's late...
Is she gonna be okay?
Butako...
Butako!
Awesome!
Good job, girl!
What is it?!
What happened?
Looks like it can only travel
a limited distance from its skeleton.
We're safe.
Oh, my word!
Wonderful work, Butako!
She got the jara for the Dettonic Sword
and Dettonic Shield from Detton!
What's Detton?
Originally a shipbuilding company,
they're a luxury brand
that produces weapons now!
Their weapons are known to be very sturdy!
What are they doing out here?
She must've grabbed them
when she flew through the delivery center!
Lucky us!
Good job, Butako!
We've been spotted!
Run, Chup!
Let's get out of here!
Got it!
They ran off with it, you say?
My deepest apologies.
However, our serveillence camera
picked up one of the perpetrators.
You've got some nerve
to come swipe the Dragon Heart.
Have them arrested
and fed to the dragons.
At once.
There's no time to relax.
Pack your bags so we can get going.
Wait, already?
Butako still needs time to heal!
They've placed a bounty on you, Chup.
Dang, they even know your name!
That little punk!
Couldn't have even used a better pic of me?
That's what maddens you about this?
Not only are Vinegar's lackeys after you,
but so is the whole town.
We're not safe here.
So where do we go?
Dragon Shaolin Temple.
Dragon Shaolin Temple?
I've told you about it before.
They teach you the Way of the Dragon.
Vinegar won't be able to mess with us there.
Plus, if we bring the Dragon Heart,
then with the power of Seiryu Darefalcon
enshrined in the temple,
we'll be able to awaken
as Dragon Knights.
Who's Seiryu Darefalcon?
There's no time. I'll explain later.
Is "Chup" staying here at your hotel?
Hmm... Chup, you say?
Answer honestly.
His bounty is 100 million gillan.
We're also offering 10 million for any information.
Huh?! 10 million gillan?!
Listen, Bunnilla...
Oui, oui, we have a Chup staying here!
Do you now?
Alright. Take us to him.
Oh, boy.
Bad news! Vinegar's lackeys are in the lobby!
They're gonna come straight to this room!
Huh?
Wait, they're coming here?
I heard them win Bouiyong
over with the allure of money!
Man...
Ugh, I hate that old geezer!
We have no choice.
We must fight!
Exodus Blade!
Exodus Blade.
Oh, is that weapon new?
Yep. The Exodus Blade!
Chup, you should try out that new
Detton sword & shield too!
Alright!
Dettonic Sword!
Dettonic Shield!
Dettonic Sword.
Dettonic Shield.
Chup's room is up this-a-way!
Bounty, o bounty...
Oh, here it is!
B-Bunnilla?
Chup! Vinegar has placed a bounty on you.
Show yourself now!
Don't bother hiding!
Come out, Chup!
Huh? I'm not Chup.
Ah, whoops! My mistake.
That would be Puck, not Chup!
Mr. Yon says "run while you can."
Huh?
Wanted to return the favor.
Mr. Yon...
Guess he's not all that bad!
Where's Chup?!
He's staying here, isn't he?!
Oui, oui! Chup, right?
It sure makes us happy to receive
after giving you service!
That's a tip, not a Chup!!
If you play dumb with us,
you'll be in a world of pain.
Answer us! Where is Chup?
Oh, yeah, Chup!
I use it when I wash my hair.
That's shampoo!!
Ah, yeah, oh, yeah!
Here I am,
Born 'n' raised in Oystah
That's a rap!!
shobokure gao no mobukyara domo ga
On and on these tired old NPCs
iiwake shinagara aruiteru
Keep walking around excusing themselves
itsumo miteiru michisugara
As I took the same old path again
mita koto mo nai wakuwaku wo mita
I found the thrill I've sought for my whole life
itsumade shibonda mama nano
Just how long will I keep drooping around like this?
minikui ahiru no mama nano
How long will I stay an ugly duckling?
ima no reberu wa ichi dakedo
I'm still only level one
ima ni mitero yo sono uchi JUMP UP
But watch me, soon I'll jump up
saikin no wakai mon wa tte
"Why, kids these days..."
toshiyori domo ga boyai teru kedo
...Our old boomers grumble and complain
soro soro omei henjou da
But it's not too late to clear my name
iya ga ou ni mo mattanashi daze
I might not like it, but I can't wait any longer
ketsu no ana kara jetto funsha daaa
I gotta blast free from my cowardly shell!!
ore wa itsuka hana ni naru
Give me time and I'll bloom like a flower
sora ni nobiru hana ni naru
A flower spread out to the sky
kimi ni todoku hana ni naru
The flower that reaches you
Thank you, Bunnilla.
Give our regards to Bouiyong too.
Will he be alright?
Probably.
Bunnilla, my sweet,
do you think I'll ever see you again?
I'll be fine.
Ehh...
Chup, let's get a move on.
Alright! Off to Dragon Shaolin Temple!!
Whoa there!
Don't yell!!
Sorry, couldn't help it...
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone!
What are you teaching us about today?
Today's lesson is on Detton!
Detton
Detton is a luxury brand of equipment
from the shipbuilders Detton Company.
They're known for being very sturdy
thanks to their shipbuilding abilities.
Wow! Detton's awesome!
They're also well-known
for their mechanical design!
Next Time
We're on the faraway road
to being Dragon Knights!
The foe lying in wait for us
at Dragon Shaolin Temple is...
Huh, Pinocchio?!
Next time:
"We Made It! Dragon Shaolin Temple!!"
We Made It! Dragon Shaolin Temple!!
Alright, time for a big adventure!