These fan-made subtitles are not for sale, rent or any profit whatsoever.
Please support official  Snack World anime releases in your home country.
See lumpstud.tumblr.com for certain translation notes.
This is Snack World, the hallowed
ground of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam and
people have smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
...And my name's Chup.
My village was burnt down by the evil
land-destroying merchant, Vinegar Khan,
and I've embarked on a journey
to get my revenge 1000-fold!
The tickets to King Oyster City, where
Vinegar is, cost 20 million gillan.
So I'm on an adventure searching for
big treasure to make loads of cash!
[Chup humming theme song]
Alright, let's go on another big adventure today!
Ep. 6: The Cutlass That Can Tear Anything?!
[Chup giggles]
- [Mayone grumbles]
- Oink...
I would have never guessed Mayone's paper fan
sword would be the strongest weapon.
Come on, Chup.
Aren't we here to report to the king?
Open your mouth and get talking so we can get out of here!
Oh, right. Your majesty!
Hm? What is it, Chup?
Since the Kraken's body is very squishy,
trying to chop it will just bounce us back!
Agh! My axe didn't like that!
It's squishy, you say?
Er, well, yeah.
Sort of like your earlobes?
Like Pepperon's cheeks?
Nah, more like your belly.
Hey, don't, that's...
Or maybe...like Princess Melora's bottom?
Hehe...squishy...
Any day now, Chup.
Oh! Your majesty, point is, we can't chop it!
At this rate, trying to get the
moisturizing cream is all but a waste!
That's why we're giving up on our current quest.
Ahh, so tearing the beast is a lost cause, hm?
- Guess it's a given, are you giving up?
- Mhm.
Nooo, my skin's so dry...
I can't put up with this! Daddy, how's
the moisturizing cream coming?
Are you still getting it? Is it running late?
I just can't stand this at all...
If you don't hurry, your youthful Melora...
She'll start looking like a wrinkly old woman!
Oh dear...
You heard her, Chup! Resume your quest!
Of course! I'll be sure to fully, flawlessly
get my hands on that moisturizing cream!
Y-you brats...
[Sighs] Even after that, we still
have to go to the Kraken again.
What are we gonna do?
Being real, we've got no strategy.
We're really in a pinch now.
It's like my grandmother says!
A pinch is an opportunity. Pink-colored
panties are 20% better!
A pinch is an
opportunity.
Pink-colored
panties are
20% better.
A pinch is an
opportunity.
Pink-colored
panties are
20% better.
-Tome
Grr...what does that mean?!
Is that to say we need a 20% increase in femininity?
Oh, of course! I'd help you with that...
if it was relevant to anything right now!!
We can't give up yet, there's still plenty
of opportunities rolling around us.
Hmm...where are they, though?
Opportuuunities, opportuuunities!
You're the only one rolling around here...
[Chup yelps]
Carbonara's Weapon Store is holding a big campaign!
We're giving away a cut--ass
that can --ear anything.
Giving it away! First come, first serve!!
[Gasps] "A cutlass that can tear anything?!"
We can use it to tear through the Kraken's limbs!
An opportunity really did roll by us!
Haha, thank you! You're our savior, bullhorn!
You should roll around in
hopeless situations more often.
That's dumb and you know it!
Err...
Mr. Carbonara!
Do you still have that "cutlass
that can tear anything?"
Chup, is it? Yes, it's still here.
Had a hunch you'd be stopping by here.
Can we have it, please?
This is usually worth 10 million gillan,
but our campaign is putting it on
discount at 10 thousand.
Dang, what a steal!
Awesome!
This campaign must be a godsend for you, Chup!
Yeah!
[Chup and Pepperon humming gleefully]
This is such a simple scenario.
It's quite sketchy that they're discounting
it so much from 10 million gillan.
We'll buy it, Mr. Carbonara!
Aah! I only have 9,500 gillan!
Agh, it must be since I bought from the 16th Melora
Card pack at the convenience store earlier...
Eh?
Wow, super rare!
Hey, Mayone, you think you can work
part-time here to cover the rest?
Huh?! What are you blabbering about?
You shouldn't have bought that stupid card!
It's not stupid!
Princess Melora isn't stupid!
Yeah!
Well, what is it? Buying it or no?
- The seductive act might come in handy.
- You should try it out now!
Alright, you can do it!
Hnng...fine, I'll do it. Watch.
You don't think you could...change the price of
the cutlass that can tear anything?
Hmmm?
Meh. Alright, fine.
15 thousand gillan it is!
[Gasps] You made it more expensive...
Talk about an opposite effect...
You wanna tell me how my charm played into that?
Hmm...if only it could be sold for 9,500 gillan.
We're just gonna have to take defeat here.
Oh, right. Mr. Carbonara.
That sword & shield you sold me
back then was a counterfeit.
Huh? What are you talking about, and why now?
It kind of put us in a lot of danger.
Haha...that's...very unfortunate...
But there's no real evidence of them being fakes.
No, we have evidence.
Oh, here it is. Take a look!
It...it's time for a special limited-time offer!
N-now?
You customers are very lucky, as we're offering a huge discount right now!
The item you've requested,
previously 15 thousand gillan,
will be sold for 9,500 gillan to the
first buyer! Only for a limited time!
Oh, sweet! I'll buy it!
Today's our lucky day!
You've sure changed your tune.
We'll be able to get a clean tear with this!
Should we tell them?
Shh!
Here it is!
- So cool!
- Ooh!
Chup, now you can be on your
way and enjoy your new product!
Come again!
Thank you, Mr. Carbonara!
The box seems small, but I'm sure
it'll be a very effective sword.
Well, people don't say it "can tear anything" for nothing!
So, Chup, aren't you gonna open it?
Yeah!
[Everyone gleaming]
The cut-pass that can bear anything
Huh?
Whaaaaaaaat?!
The cut-pass that can bear anything
"The cut-pass that can bear anything?!"
The cutlass that can tear anything
bear
cut-pass
So instead of "cutlass," it's "cut-pass,"
and instead of "tear," it's "bear?!"
X
O
N...no way...
We've been duped again.
Hold on, it seems to be a pass
you can equip and check
before making a purchase with a
Continental Trade Association certification.
It's not necessarily that much of a coax.
What about that should we be
happy about? It's entirely pointless!
We're going right back to the shop.
They've already closed for the day.
What?! So that old man's gonna get away with
forcing us some damn thing we don't need? Again?!
Still very irritated...
We're all going to think as one on this.
About Mayone's "can swear over anything" thing.
What was that?
I'm swearing, huh? You wanna go into detail on that?
N-no, it's just that right there...to say, you...
Yeah?!
...a-are kind of trapping me here.
We're right back where we started.
If we don't hurry up, slay that
Kraken, and get the cream,
Melora's skin will...
Ohh, Melora's skin...
What is with you and that stupid girl?!
[Chup grunts]
[Chup yelps]
No!
Oh...I'm so sorry...
I should be the one apologizing...
Oh, you must be...
Are you hurt?
No, I'm okay. Thank you! Later, hero!
Penne! Pay back your last loan!
That guy again!
Still hasn't learned, has he?
[Penne panting]
Get back here!
Aah, I'm scared...
He's coming!
[Grunts]
Wh-whaaat?!
Ho!
Hey, I'm not the bad guy here!
Striiike!
- Hahaha!
- We got him!
Nice shot!
The heck is this? Tch.
We really should just go and tell them we can't do it.
We just don't have any effective
weapons against the Kraken.
That's right, acceptance is crucial for humans.
But you're a Monster.
[Gob-san grunts]
- Nuh-uh.
- Huh?
Nuh-uh! Not a chance!
Yelling "nuh-uh" won't get you out of this.
Do you have some plan?
I do!
That's our Chup!
Well, what is it?!
I have a plan, I just haven't come up with it yet!
That's the polar opposite of having a plan!!
[Sigh] Guess it's still a no-go...
Hnn...we're in trouble...
Don't you dare just sob your faces!
'Cuz "impossible," "excuses," and "sleeping in"
don't exist in Cinderella's vocabulary!
Do you have the guts to invoke me again?!
Commander! No more excuses! Except
that sleeping in sounds kind of...
[Grunts]
- It's been a while...
- Oink...
I've been hearing a lot from you!
"We can't beat the Kraken!" "We can't find a sword!"
"Mayone won't stop snapping at us!" It's annoying!
I'm not snapping! Besides, how long
have you been eavesdropping on us?!
- But you're snapping right n...
- Oi!
You better not tell me you forgot
about our special training!
Uhh...
Err...I didn't forget.
I couldn't forget a day like that even if I wanted to.
Eating ice cream with Princess Melora...aah...
Guh! Where am I?
You must have some nerve to be
sleeping at a time like this!
It's like my grandmother says!
A well-slept child is a well-kept child.
A slept-in child is a better-kept child!
A well-slept child
is a well-kept child.
A slept-in child
is a better-kept child.
better
-Tome
- Feels...nice...
- Oink...
Don't give up after failing once!
My troopers!
Come hell or high water, you will push through to the end!
It's like my grandmother says!
It's always darkest before dawn sky.
It doesn't matter, so don't cry.
It's always darkest
before dawn sky.
dawn sky
It doesn't matter,
so don't cry.
don't
-Tome
Hmph, you...
Heh, guess sometimes you do say decent things.
Whaa, how'd that get through her?
In any case, you better be done
with your bickering and whining.
Yes, sir!
Alright, I'm gonna show you something you might like.
Hm?
"Trying to shake around the destroyer axe"
Hyah!
Aha, what's that strong axe?
It seems to say that it's the..."Destroyer?"
"Trying to shake around the destroyer axe"
Mhm, it's called the "Destroyer Axe!"
It's well-known as the "hatchet that can tear anything!"
That's it! That's our key to victory against the Kraken!
We'll fully, flawlessly flatten it!
[Panting]
Wait up, wait up!!
[Gasps]
There's no escape.
That guy doesn't give up, does he?
This is bad, she needs help!
Hmm...ah!
Hm?
That's it!
Wh...? Whaaat?!
You make a really good support!
Hey!!
[Chuckling]
Pepperon, now!
I've got this!
- Hyah!
- [Gob-san grunts]
[Tartar chuckling]
You won't be prepared...
Aah! What is this? I can't see anything!!
Agh, help!! Guh...
Are you safe?
Hero, thank you, as always...
If someone's bullying you, give us a shout!
- Thank you! Goodbye!
- Later!
Hm? Oh...
"The cut-pass that can bear anything"
The cut-pass that can bear anything!
Must have been from when we
took care of this guy before...
N-no...it's Penne, not me!! Nooo!
[Rooster crowing]
The Next Morning...
Mr. Carbonara!
Oh!
Do you have the Destroyer Axe that can tear anything?
Just like you, Chup, right on top of
everything. Wait just a moment.
Hehe...I wouldn't say that.
That’s nothing to feign modesty over!
This is the Destroyer Axe. Ain't it a beauty?
Ooh!
Obtaining this is the least you can expect of me!
[Cackling]
We need that to defeat the desert Kraken.
A kraken? Well, with this Destroyer Axe,
you can SHPANG through just about anything!
I really wanna SPANG through the squishy Kraken!
Nuh-uh, Chup. This thing only slices with a SHPANG.
I'm planning on givin' that Kraken a nice SPANG!
That's not it, it's SHPANG! SHPANG!
Sooo...SPANG, right?
No! It's SHPANG!
Sooo...
We get it! Why are you so fixated on this?!
Whether it goes SHPANG, or SHPAT, or ZKAT, or GSAT!
Whatever the hell it goes, just sell it to us!
Hmm, well, I never really said it was for sale.
No matter how much you ask, I'm not selling it.
Huh? So you just want it to boast?
Sorry.
Then, can I equip the cut-pass that can bear anything?
Err, no, that's...
It's a pass certified by the
Continental Trade Association, after all.
If you don't follow the rules, can
you even keep this store open?
Hnng...fine.
Hurrah!
Hah, it can really tear anything!
Well, since it's an axe, Pepperon's gotta have it!
Ohh, I can feel its power inside of me!
I'm gonna slice that Kraken in two!
Chup, you happy with yourself?
Welp, later.
Oi, Chup, where are you going?!
We need to test it with the wind...
Oi, stop right there!
It's alright, we'll just shake it around.
Oi, Chup!!
Fitting it on for size!!
Get back here, you...!
Pepperon, that's dangerous, just make it a Jara.
Mmm, but I want to keep it like this!
You'll wear yourself out before battle!
It doesn't even feel heavy!
♪ Hatchet, hatchet, my gigantic hatchet~ ♪
Would you stop singing that awful song?
♪ Sword, sword, my so-little sword~ ♪
- You don't have to imitate him!!
♪ This chest, this chest, this sweet home of mine~ ♪
How lovely, heehee!
Mimic
Hm? Wah!
Haha! I've got prey! Four of them!
[Laughing]
Oh?
Oh, a treasure chest, right in the middle of the desert!
Doesn't that seem very off?
We won't know for sure unless we open it.
- Well, I guess you're right...
- [Mimic laughing]
What'dya think is in it?
Personally, I really hope it's a pendant from Peffany!
It's gotta be some food in there!
No matter what it is, I hope I get a weapon for myself!!
Hahahaha! You'll only find Mimic inside!
Come on, open it up, open it up!!
Then, how about we decide who gets the
contents depending on what they are?
I'll take it if it's a sword!
For me if it's a pendant!
I'll take any weapon that comes out!
And I'll take it if it's food!
You're the one who's gonna get eaten, you idiot.
Hm? Did it move a bit just now?
What makes you think that?
It's gotta be a legendary sword in there!
Or maybe a magic wand, or
any kind of wand, I'll take it!
That's unfair!
But what would you guys need a wand for?
Hmm, I see your point...
We should just open it!
Grrr...ugh! How long are they gonna keep babbling?
I've been waiting in here forever!! Just open it up!!
Alright, let's open it!
...But it has a lock on it.
We don't have something to unlock it with.
Chup!
I think we might have something for the job.
Hmm...
Why don't you idiots understand?!
Use that axe to break the lock and open the chest!!
I'll go "BOO!" and it'll be over for them!
Hmm......
What's going on?! Come on, figure it out already!
Can't you see, guys?
- Hmm...
- Hyah!
My hatchet that can tear anything...
It can break the lock on the chest!
Hah, we can do that, huh?
That's it, that's it, you can do it, do it! Hahahaha...
Ready...and go!
Come on, here, here!
Please be my sword!
It has to be my thing, I just know it!
Daddy needs a new weapon...
Hi-yaaah!
Alright!
WHAAAT?!
Pepperon, that's way too much!
You weren't supposed to cut the chest itself!
Now you've ruined whatever was in there!
I'm so sorry, I got carried away...
My equipment...
But we've learned one thing...
This axe is certified astounding!
You're right. Let's move past the
treasure and head to the Kraken!
Wait for me, Kraken!
Without fail, I'll give you a SPA- er, I mean, a SHPANG!
♪ Hatchet, hatchet, my gigantic hatchet~ ♪
That's enough...
Bye!
[Kraken groaning]
We're counting on you here, Pepperon!
I'm afraid my hands won't stop
shaking in front of the enemy...
What do I do, Chup?!
Uhh...leave it to us!
Huh??
We'll keep the Kraken busy while you
chop its limbs with the Destroyer Axe!
G-got it.
Come at us, Kraken! We'll be taking
that moisturizing cream this time!
[War cry]
Have some of my strongest...
You... hyah!
[Kraken groaning]
If you won't eat those moves, have a taste of Gobby!
What?!
Nice job!
[Screaming]
[Yelling]
[Gasping]
I'm A-OK, by the way!
We won't lose to a squid anymore!
I think saying "squid" makes it angry!
[Screaming]
- Guh.
- Oof.
I'll knock this guy out!
Sleep!
[Gasps]
Huh?! Don't sleep at a time like this!!
- Agh, this hurts...
- Ahh...
What's happening out there?
- Chup!
- [Gasp] Are you alright, Mayone?
No thanks to you dozing off! ...Well,
I guess that was thanks to my spell.
Hnng...now that it's come to this...
Hey, you big squid, who's not
actually a squid despite being one!
We're feeling absolutely fine and cool!
We're not fine and cool at all...
[Sighs] I feel like I'm gonna faint...
Yo, squid!
We should eat you dried! 'Cuz you're a squid!
[Shrieking]
Chup! Hnn... Oh, what's the point...
[Coughs] Pepperon! Now!
Oh? Aight, I'm goin' in!
[War cry] Hah!
Use your epic axe and give him a SHPANG!
Oh, that's what the other guy was talking about!
Hi-yah!
- [Groaning]
- You did it!
konbini de kuda wo maku ukiyo wo samayou wakoudo yo
All you youngsters loitering about your lives,
shrouding the convenience stores
omaera wa genjitsu ni torinokosaresugi andeddo
You’re like undead who have left behind reality
itsumade son na koto kurikaesu no o-tsu-ka-re
How long are you going to keep doing this?
Don't you get tired of this same old routine?
hashiridase yo ENDLESS ROAD
Run forth through the endless road
koetemiroyo BORDERLINE
Go on past that borderline
sekai wa mugen ni hirogaru kouya
The world is an endless, limitless wilderness
omae no dokyou wo tameshiteiru
Where you can put your courage to the test
sumafo nankaja kensaku dekinai
It’s not something you can search for on your smartphone
sekai wa mugen ni hirogaru PARADISE
The world is an endless, limitless paradise
omaera wa giragira no
Soon you'll come to life taking in the blazing sun
taiyou kuratte ikiteiru
Raws
Translation/Typesetting/Timing/Adaptation Attempt*
ED Karaoke
QC/Review
Raws
Translation/Typesetting/Timing/Adaptation Attempt*
ED Karaoke
QC/Review
AnimeLand (BSJ)
Lumpstud
Noroino Hanako
NeSubs
AnimeLand (BSJ)
Lumpstud
Noroino Hanako
NeSubs
*emphasis on "Attempt"
[Groaning]
Ah...
Now we can make Melora's wish come true!
But if he's dead, where's the moisturizing cream?
Wait...what?!
Whaaat?!
- [Sighs]
- Oink...
So that didn't net us the cream?
What are we supposed to do now?
To get the moisturizing cream from the Kraken...
Hmm, this mystery only gets deeper.
Huh?!
Kraken, I'm so sorry, but...
Err, we kinda needed your limbs, so...
uhh, that's why we had to chop it.
I don't suppose there's any meaning to
it drying up, right? 'Cuz you're a squid?
[Roaring]
[Screaming]
Well? Did it tear? Did it slice with a SHPANG?
Just like you'd expect, the
Destroyer's power is the real deal.
Well, I'll have that back now.
This is farewell I suppose... [sniffle]
Huh? Where's Pepperon?
An axe I'll have, an axe I won't.
Aww, come on, Pepperon...
You can't be that heartbroken...
Pepperon, you still have an axe.
So, cheer up!
An axe I'll have, an axe I won't.
- [Chup sighs]
- He's really hurt by this...
It's best we just leave him be for now.
- Okay.
- Oink...
An axe I...won't...
Aaaaagh!
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone!
What will you teach us about today?
"Rare Variants"
Today's about rare variants!
Weapons and armor often have rare variants with
slight differences in their color and/or shape.
You don't see them often!
Because of their spares availability,
it's something to be proud of finding!
Ooh, really?
I wanna have a rare variant too!
Next Time
We're finally in the final stages of
the battle with the Kraken.
Plus, Mayone will play the role of a squid!
Uhh...how exactly?
Next time: Then, We Knew It All.
Then, We Knew It All
Alright, it's time for a big adventure!