This is Snack World, the hallowed ground
of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam
and people have handy smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
And my name's Chup!
My village was burnt down by
the evil land-destroying merchant Vinegar Khan,
so I've embarked on a journey
to get my revenge 1000-fold!
At last, my journey has brought me
close to Vinegar.
In order to defeat him, I will overcome
any impossible mission that comes my way!
Alright, let's go on another big adventure today!
The Final Match of Ups and Downs!
Episode 34: A Challenge to the Holy Dragon!
Who would've thought Darefalcon
would be our final opponent?
What will we be battling you in?
Your final course will be... this!
Yo, rock-paper-scissors!
I'm great at that!
I beat Gob-san at it
five times in a row!
Don't remind me of that nightmare!
How could I lose five games
of rock-paper-scissors for a cola!
I wish I could erase that from my memory...
Not rock-paper-scissors...
Dude, you only ever play rock!
Darn! My strategy's been exposed!
How naïve do you have to be
to lose with rock five times?
Like you're one to talk!
You only ever use scisosrs!
I can't help it, it looks like a peace sign!
How 'bout we see which one of us
is the rock-paper-scisosrs champ?
Sounds good.
Bring it on!
I won't go easy on you!
Rock-paper-scissors!
Dang it, I lost!
Why did you throw rock again?!
Force of habit...
You'll be fighting for your life!!
What?!
So no rock-paper-scissors?
That's no way to get you into shape.
So what is it?
A normal battle, that's what!
The same way you fight monsters!
Huh? But that's dangerous.
Yes, hence "fighting for your life"!
I won't be holding back.
I bear no responsibility if you die.
Understood?
Y-Yes, sir!
Yes! We'll do anything to become Dragon Knights.
This area is too cramped for battle.
I shall warp you to Dragon Shaolin Temple.
Now, Dragon Wa—
Wait!
Hmm? What is the matter?
Can I stop by Hero Mart?
Must you now?
Of course! Today's the last day
of their One-Shot Lottery.
I don't care!!
Aw...
Does that really matter?!
Now, off we go.
To Dragon Shaolin Temple! Dragon Wa—
Wait!
Hm? What now?
I feel like I'm forgetting something important...
Huh? What is it?
Oh, I forgot what it was.
Cut it off!
Listen!!
Do you understand
what fighting for your life means?
You must be prepared to die in battle!!
Yes!
I understand.
Now, to Dragon Shaolin Temple!
Dragon Wa—huh?
You about to fight for your life!!
Can't you be more tense about it?!
Dragon...
Warp!
Are you prepared?
Yes!
You may call on the monsters
you have collected for support.
You may use any weapon
or spell of your choosing.
Consider this the fruit of your efforts,
and use whatever you bear!
If we win, will we become Dragon Knights?
Yes, you will.
Heck yeah! I'm so ready!
Then be here at 3:00 PM.
In the meantime, wrack those brains of yours
and come up with a strategy.
I'm on it, sir!
Hey, Sir Laozi!
Teach me how to knock out
Darefalcon in one hit!
How could you ask him such a question?
There are no shortcuts.
You silly billy.
Everyone has their weakness!
For example, Pepperon's afraid of heights!
Mayone's stingy!
Huh? That's just plain badmouthing!
Gob-san smells like an old man!
Hm? You're mistaken.
I've been scrubbing with a special soap
of mine, so I smell just fine.
What's with the looks?!
If I stink, just tell me!
You stink.
Ouch!
I didn't think you'd just tell me...
Darefalcon has no weakness.
Like a spirit, his flesh is resilient
and he has strong powers.
His strength is also spirit-like...
So, he's a spirit. Got it.
Have anything more helpful?
Simple... he's crazy powerful!
Well, that's worthless.
Hey, Pinocchio! You know anything?
I think he still has a grudge
from when you beat him.
Leave him to me!
Monsters and robots!
We may be different genres,
but I know we have something in common!
Whoa!
Hey, Pinocchio.
How about we talk about your feelings?
He took you out like it was nothing.
And we didn't manage to get
any information here.
Looks like we'll have to figure
something out all on our own.
We must use every resource we have
if we want to defeat Darefalcon.
Bring me everything that you have.
Is there anything else?
Yeah!
These babies!
You can't use Melora Cards in battle!
Why not? These rare cards
seem pretty strong to me!
It's not a card battle!
I have no choice.
How about these?
We don't need to see
your after-dark business cards!
Thank goodness.
I didn't want to lose touch with any of them!
Sure, whatever.
Anything else?
I'm not certain what we can use,
so take everything out.
What are you hiding?
I can't!
You have to!
I can't let anyone else eat it!
No one was gonna take those now.
Huh? Man, I could've saved it for later...
What about you, Mayone?
Surely you're holding on to something.
What? Of course not...
Uh-huh?
I knew you liked zombies,
but not this much...
This is just creepy.
Is that a body pillow?
I could never sleep with that.
That's messed up.
Why are you giving me all this?
You told me to take it out!!
Here's my monster snacks.
The proof of our battles!
I see. Are any of these monsters
good for use?
Hmm, I wonder.
Oh, how about this one?
Buttery!
Machine (Machine)
Huff puff puff!
The name's Buttery.
Who's this guy?
Are you sure about him?
Of course! He's perfect!
Look! You can use him
to charge on-the-go!
You said it! No monster's
more useful than I, huff!
Rejected!
Huh?
He's no good for battle.
You can get rid of him now.
Get rid of him?
I don't know how to do that!
What?
So what happened to the monsters
you've summoned so far?
I dunno. They just walk home, I think?
Nothing special.
So you summon them
then abandon them?
Chup!
You have to press the "Retreat" button
to get rid of the monsters you summon!
Retreat?
Wait, huff! There's more to me!
Retreat!
Whoa, that's awesome!
I love this button!
Huff-puff-puff!
The name's Buttery.
I knew you'd come to see...
Retreat!
Whoo, this is so fun!
You don't have to say "Retreat".
Huff-puff-puff! The name's...
Retreat!
Monsters aren't your toys!
Again, again!
Hey!
Wait, Vinsant!
Chup, do you remember
the first thing I asked?
Yeah! Do I have any other monsters
that are useful like this?
Not for charging your battery!
I'm looking for monsters
that are good in battle!
I see...
Oh!
How's this one?
I'm Yeti...
It's so cold...
No, this is useless!
Wait!
This is a brutal monster which can create
blizzards at absolute zero.
Really?
Here comes the blizzard!
Ah-choo!
So cold...
So adorable!
I had a good feeling about him!
Chup.
Yeah?
This is the last time I'll ask you.
Do you have any powerful monsters
that are good for battle?
Y-Yeah, tons!
This one's perfect!
It's me, Slime!
I give up...
Aw, man. And I finally got summoned...
You idiot!!
I kinda feel bad for him...
What kind of monsters
have you guys been fighting?!
Forget it, I'll pick one.
This guy looks useful.
Ay, I'm Scopeion!
With these scopes, I can see through
anything, anywhere!
He's no good.
He may seem strong, but all he thinks to do
is peep in on Melora's spa room
from far away.
We'll use him.
My word! You want to see
Princess Melora naked too?
No!
It's weird if you get mad about it.
Yeah! If you wanna see her naked,
just say it loud and proud like me!
Maybe you should have a bit of dignity!
That's not what this is about!!
One of Darefalcon's aces is that
his movements are too swift for us to see.
We'll be able to catch him
with his scope.
This one looks good too.
Good day, I'm Cyborg!
What can I do you for?
He looks like he could pack a punch.
He does a mighty tackle
when he flips out.
But he can only charge in a straight line.
But we can put him to work!
Want me to fight? I can make that work.
I'll have to warm up first!
That'll do.
Next, we'll try... this one.
I am known as Mayou Yoroi.
Still no sense of direction.
Don't even try this one.
He's strong, but he can't
tell left from right.
How is his swordplay?
He's pretty good, when he's not hestiating.
I see.
Now we have the perfect team.
Perfect how?
How do you plan to use those three?
I'll tell you.
Here we have Scopeion,
Cyborg, and Mayou Yoroi.
And this is Darefalcon.
An eraser...? I mean, I guess
it's white and squishy like him...
Okay.
First, Scopeion will zero in on Darefalcon.
Then Cyborg will charge and tackle him,
putting him to a halt.
Then, when Darefalcon has stopped,
Mayou Yoroi will slash him.
Wow!
All three of them play a role!
It's like my grandmother said!
"Three breads are tastier than one!"
Three breads are tastier than one.
-Tome
You already used that one
not too long ago.
Sh-Shoot!
We'll take him with the help
of these three monsters.
Good thinking, Vinsant.
I was going to say the same thing.
As if.
Alright! We're gonna beat Darefalcon!
Yeah!
Uh-oh, it's time! We gotta hurry!
Aah! We forgot the box!
Come on...
You're late!
Only three minutes late.
We're safe!
No you are not!
But it's fine.
Are you prepared
for your final lesson?
Yes.
We're confident we will defeat you.
That's promising!
Then let the battle begin!
Oh, no!
Fireball!
Shiver! Itchy Legs!
Bone-Dry! Cloudy!
Flash!
Looks like I'm up.
Take this, my ultimate spell...!
...Except it's just
a rock-hard headbutt instead!!
Where'd he go?!
Hah. Must've run away
with his tail between his legs.
G-Gob-san!!
Chup! Summon the monsters
and begin our strategy!
Got it!
Slime!
Yeti—ah-choo!
Huff-puff-puff!
The name's Buttery!
What?!
Why these ones?!
Crap! I picked up the wrong box!
What's wrong with you?!
You useless twat!!
That perfect plan's gone to waste...
It's like my grandmother said!
Failure is the foundation of success!
Failure is the
foundation of success!
Sucking breasts is the
foundation of failure!
Failure is the
foundation of success!
Sucking breasts is the
foundation of failure!
Sucking breasts is the foundation of failure!
-Tome
You're right... Breasts have ruined my life...
Her words are more profound than you'd think!
Is this really the time to be
reflecting on boobs?!
How are we supposed to get out of this?!
Those things are going to fight me?
You must underestimate me.
We're not! I picked up the wrong box!
You don't have to fill him in!
Allow me to show you
the power of a spirit!
He awakened.
This isn't good.
He's gone!
Wh-Where is he?
He's too fast...
Scopeion was supposed to
figure out his movements.
Dang it! It's all or nothing!
You guys have to fight!
No way!
Nuh-uh, huff-puff!
Get out there! Go!
I... feel bad for them...
So scary...
All hope is lost...
What the?!
Holy cow!
Ah-choo!
Whoa!
They got 'im!
I can't believe they were able to weaken Darefalcon...
Even if it was just dumb luck.
Now's our chance!
Dettonic Sword!
Dettonic Sword.
Exodus Blade!
Exodus Blade.
Let's go!
He's still weakened!
We've got this!
He's got nowhere to run!
Y-You best not believe...
that this is enough to defeat me!!
Where does he get this power?!
Oh no!
Look at that!
They controlled the cold!
Their training paid off!
I'm not done yet!
Cha-cha-cha!
Whoa!
Ta-tata ta-ta-ta!
Look at those beautiful steps!
That must be their dance training in action!
Ta-tata ta-ta-ta!
Don't be impudent!
Ow...
Ta-ta-ta-ta-ta...!
Holy cow!
This can't end well!
Dodge it!
Is this how it ends?
Ta-ta-ta-ta-ta...!
Chuuup!!
Use your mind's eye...
See him wtih Dragon Chakra!
Sha-sha-sha-sha-sha-sha-sha-sha!!
My word!
Yeah!
We've got this!
It's not over!
Chup!!
You did very well pushing me this far...
We did it!
Th-That means we're Dragon Knights...!
But I still have a second transformation.
Behold, my ultimate form!
What in the world?!
A second form? I wanna see!!
That's not the right reaction!!
It's... V-Vinegar!!
I take it you're Darefalcon.
Do not speak with me now!
Darefalcon!!
I've retrieved it at last.
Welcome back, my little Dragon Heart.
Vinegar...
How dare you...
He's become a ghost again!
He's just a bit faded.
Vinegar!
Chup!
I-I'm stuck!
Dark powers.
Now I can finally resurrect Scardon.
Every last one of you is dead meat.
You'd best enjoy your final days.
Why, you...!
Vinegar, you scoundrel!
Get back here!
Take care, everybody!
I'm sure it's the last time we'll ever meet.
Vinegar!!
shobokure gao no mobukyara domo ga
On and on these tired old NPCs
iiwake shinagara aruiteru
Keep walking around excusing themselves
itsumo miteiru michisugara
As I took the same old path again
mita koto mo nai wakuwaku wo mita
I found the thrill I've sought for my whole life
itsumade shibonda mama nano
Just how long will I keep drooping around like this?
minikui ahiru no mama nano
How long will I stay an ugly duckling?
ima no reberu wa ichi dakedo
I'm still only level one
ima ni mitero yo sono uchi JUMP UP
But watch me, soon I'll jump up
saikin no wakai mon wa tte
"Why, kids these days..."
toshiyori domo ga boyai teru kedo
...Our old boomers grumble and complain
soro soro omei henjou da
But it's not too late to clear my name
iya ga ou ni mo mattanashi daze
I might not like it, but I can't wait any longer
ketsu no ana kara jetto funsha daaa
I gotta blast free from my cowardly shell!!
ore wa itsuka hana ni naru
Give me time and I'll bloom like a flower
sora ni nobiru hana ni naru
A flower spread out to the sky
kimi ni todoku hana ni naru
The flower that reaches you
Damn it!
We were this close to becoming Dragon Knights!
Even so...
I feel much stronger!
Your inner Dragon Knight
may have awakened amidst the battle.
It's quite possible,
seeing how far you've come.
Whoa!
We won't defeat Vinegar like this.
But now that the Dragon Heart has been stolen,
we have no choice but to raid Vinegar Palace.
We'll risk our lives to destroy the Dragon Heart.
Do you think we might die there?
Not might—we almost certainly will.
Huh?
N-Now, hold on,
let me look up another way...
There is none!
If we don't do anything,
the world will end.
I'm in.
I'll do the impossible if I have to!
I'll defeat Vinegar,
and as for Melora...
...and as for Melora...
I'll take a bath with her!!
His fighting spirit is powerful...
Erm...
We'll pass.
A-Agreed.
Sorry about this.
If Vinegar is defeated,
you'll get a very big reward.
Huh?
My apologies. I suppose you all couldn't be
blinded by such a huge compensation.
Here's your reward: a complete Peffany set!
Feel free to take as much as you like.
Wow!
I'll do it! I'm in!
A gift to you: a free lifetime
all-you-can-eat special VIP card.
Whoa!
You can rely on me!
Gobby, you're the one who saved the world, right?
You're just so handsome! Mwah!
Whoo!
I'm gonna save the world!
Alright! Off we go!
Yeah!
My... They're all quite blinded.
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone!
What are you teaching us about today?
Today's lesson is on the Snack Trunk!
Snack Trunk
The Snack Trunk is a carrier
that can hold lots of snacks!
With one of these, you can carry
many snacks mid-adventure!
Whoo! Awesome!
I love this Retreat button!
Hey! Stop summoning and retreating
monsters for fun!
Next Time
We may very well die.
In order to move forward
with no regrets,
I take a visit to Princess Melora.
Next time: "The Final Battle Approaches—
Saying Farewell to Melora".
The Final Battle Approaches
Saying Farewell to Melora
Alright, it's time for a big adventure.