This is Snack World, the hallowed ground of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam and people have handy smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
And my name's Chup!
My village was burnt down by the evil land-destroying merchant Vinegar Khan,
so I've embarked on a journey to get my revenge 1000-fold!
The tickets to King Oyster City, where Vinegar is, cost 20 million gillan.
So I'm on an adventure searching for big treasure to make loads of cash!
[Chup humming theme song]
Alright, let's go on another big adventure today!
Princess Melora...where are you?
Ep. 17: Run, Shibuchin, Run!
- Oink...
Chup...
I'm totally gonna beat him! I'll fully, flawlessly beat him!
Anything for that kiss...
It doesn't need to be one, maybe two or three...
So your motives really are twisted!!
- Aah!
- Oink...
Goodness gracious...
- Chup, my boy!
- Huh?
How was Pilafbeak?
Your majesty, the Dragon Heart you gave us was a dupe!
We had to come all the way back.
Of course...
Huh, did you figure something out?
As it turns out, that was just a crystal party light.
I didn't catch it until I sent you off with it, and it really rustled my jimmies when I did.
In fact, it rustled my jimmies so bad, I...
My face became that of Edvard Munch's "The Scream!"
That doesn't make any sense!
Why are you talking like that about your own mistake?!
[Sigh] So where can I find the real one...?
Shall we do another scavenge of your treasure house, sir?
Perhaps.
You guys, remember - this crystal is the Dragon Heart!
Ahh, I got it!
Huh? That man's screen name is "Vintaro..."
Ah, isn't it a bit rude to leave him on read after he sent you that picture?
Crap! I completely forgot to reply!
You're responding now?!
"Good job!!"
"Don't mention it"
[Chup gasps]
- Wow, he responds quick!
And those stickers are just cute...
We gotta focus on getting him the Dragon Heart at once!
Riiight...
Are you sure a priceless treasure is hanging around all this junk?
What?!
That's my rubber ducky! If you take it away from me, I'll have you executed!!!
I wasn't taking it! And I'd rather not die over something like this!
Oh, King, what's this?
Ohh, that's the thing I mistook for the Dragon Heart!
Those are party light crystals!
I was so shocked my face became that of Edvard Munch's "The Scream..."
[Yelping]
You told us that already!!
Ooh, can I have that, your majesty?
You want that ol' thing? Go ahead, help yourself.
Hup...thanks, your majesty!
Oh, my! That's a Fairy Crystal Shield!
What?!
You said I could have it, right?
I thought you meant the wooden b...
I have a hunch this will help me save Princess Melora!
F-Fine, equip it if you must.
How do you possibly know where it is in this trash heap? Don't you have any records?
I've brought the record journal.
This couldn't be any more late, could it?
It appears the Dragon Heart was found in the forest by our survery team on March 8th a few years back.
It should be in a chest like this.
Ohh! That chest is right over there!
Hup-ho.
We'll bring you back with this, Melora.
Aaagh! It's empty! It's all empty!!
Whaaat?!
Where in the world is it?
[King muttering]
Oh! Why don't we let Butako track the Dragon Heart with the leftover scent in the chest?
Good thinking! Let's put Butako's pig nose to the test!
Oink-oink.
- Do you have the scent?
- Oink-oink!
Can you look for the Dragon Heart?
Oink!
Oink-oink, oink-oink...
Oiiink!
Everyone, go follow Butako!
Good luck out there, Chup!
Huh, you're not coming with?
No can do, it's snack time for me.
Forget it and get moving!
Okay...
Oink-oink, oink-oink, oink-oink...
Sniff, sniff... Aahhh...
Aah, something smells wonderful over there!
That would be the beauty-treatment room.
Huh?! Does that mean right now I could see Princess Melora's bed and--
- Why, you!!
[Chup yelps]
You know this isn't the time for that!
Sniff sniff... Ohh! I smell something neat over there!
That would be the kitchen. They're serving curry today.
Ooh, I gotta get some grub!
It's a deluxe curry that takes three days to stew!
Just a single bite spreads the flavor of the spice throughout your mouth.
- It's so good!
- Ohhh!
- Where do you think you're going?
- Guh.
Oink...oiiink...
Perhaps it's somewhere outside of the castle?
Oink-oink.
The people love to get riled up when their majesty visits the town.
- Seems fairly normal around here.
- Sigh.
- Oink...
- Huh?
- Oink!
- Where is it?
Oiiink! Oink-oink!
Huh?!
Maybe someone sold it to the weapon shop?
Hold it, what do you...think you're doing?!
Butt out, this isn't a good time!
But you're trashing my store...!
Excuse me, could you move to the side please?
What are you pulling on us?! We can sue you for this!!
[Shrieks] Don't take that! Take anything but that!
Dragon Heart, Dragon Heart...
Wait, you're not gonna take it...?
I can't be the only one in the world who likes that stuff...
Do you want them stolen?!
I've always wanted to battle with a sword, just once.
Oink! Oink! Oink-oink!
It's over there!
Mr. Carbonara, take off your shoe!
Ey, what are you doin'?
Hnng...there!
Blegh.
- Bleh!
- Hm?
Butako, that was just his foot stench!
It doesn't matter how much someone's foot smells, don't do this again!
I really doubt the Dragon Heart smells this revolting...
That's a little harsh...
It's very rude to come in here and act brash for no reason.
Even if my master's feet do smell godawful.
Ey, Pinocchio!
Butako, we're not looking for things that generally smell.
Focus on tracing the Dragon Heart's smell!
Oink-oink!
Princess Melora...you're such a beauty...I'll save you at all costs!
- Chup...
- Oink...
So I can feel your kiss...not on my cheek, but on the lips!
You haven't learned your lesson at all!!
Mwah.
[King groans]
That'll leave a mark.
Yep...
[King yelps]
Um...my bad.
[Gasps] I remember now!
The Dragon Heart is on the collar of my pet dog, Shibuchin!
Are you for real? Have we been on a wild goose chase this whole time?
I...I was just testing your abilities.
Oh, I'm sure you were!
Your majesty, where can we find Shibuchin?
We have no idea, he escaped from the castle as of late.
He could be anywhere right now.
What kind of owner are you...?
What does he look like?
Let's see...aha!
Sort of like that dog over there! He's white, and fluffy,
and he's got "Shibuchin" written on his collar...
Oho! That must be Shibuchin!
What?! Grab him!!
Ow!!
After him!
Off we go!
[Pepperon and King exclaim]
- We must've lost him...
- This way!
Wait!!
- Hey!
- Huh?
Have you seen a fluffy white dog?
A dog? Can't say I have!
Hey, have you seen a fluffy white dog?
Oh yeah, that dog ran over there not too long ago!
Uhh, where is "there" exactly?
I told you, it ran over there!
Oh, you mean towards the plaza? Thanks, man!
[Screams]
Why me...?
[Both panting]
[Girls shrieking]
- Hm?
[Shrieking]
Where are you, Shibuchin?!
Sorry, ladies!
Get back here!!
Oh, it's you, Chup!
It's all thanks to you I could become a star like I've drea...
[Yells]
Where'd Shibuchin go?
We lost him.
Oh, Master Panpan!
What? It's you guys!
You oogling at the idols again?
What'd you expect? I never miss a day!
Sigh...
Master, have you seen a fluffy white dog?
A dog...? Listen to the wind...it will answer what you seek.
Yes, Master!
Huh?!
I've got it! He's over there!
Another random guess, I presume?
Of course not! It's my instinct.
That's just a fancy way to say you're guessing!!
Let's leave while we can. Off we go.
- [Akami yelps]
- [Panpan groans]
[Cinderella giggling]
- It's the commander!
- What's she laughin' at?
How long were you filmin' us...?
She's one unpredictable gal.
[Giggling]
Hey, have you seen a fluffy white dog?
Oho! Shibuchin ran into the forest!
Alright, let's get a move on!
You best delete that other video!!
[Giggling]
Shibuchin?! Where are you?!
What if he's not even in the forest?
We totally lost him...
Aha! Shibuchin's footprints!
He has to be here then! Let's see where they lead us!
Alright!
Ow! Owowowow...
Aah! W-Who are you?!
You're looking at Mayou Yoroi.
Mayou Yoroi
This encounter will be your last!
For I shall chop you down without a thought!
Uh, who are you talking to?
Oh, you're over there.
I am the one they call Mayou Yoroi, the lone warrior.
Err, the phantom knight of the forest...no, no...
The legend tearing down the world...maybe...
You seem a bit unsure of yourself.
You can't even introduce yourself without saying "maybe"?
Yeah! It's like my grandmother said...
Don't break and say maybe! Don't go broke like Mayone!
Don't break and say maybe.
Don't go broke like Mayone.
-Tome
Your grandmother totally never said that!!
X
Then, I shall ask you!
Which one sounds better,
"lone warrior" or "phantom knight of the forest?"
That's not our job, figure it out yourself!
I can't figure it out myself, why do you think I'm asking?
It takes me half an hour just to decide what I want at a diner!
Why are you proud of your inability to decide?!
How does one decide things so easily?
It's impossible to tell which choice is right.
Nothing in life is more troublesome than making decisions!
Would you shut up already? We're sick and tired of your bragging!
Aaagh, you piss me off!
What are you waiting for? Finish him, Pepperon!
R-Right, I'm on it!
Wooden Axe!
Your choice for adventure, Qloris!
Wooden Axe.
He looks like the real deal...I'd best be prepared!
[War cry]
- Hah!
- Hmph!
[Mayou Yoroi shouts]
[Pepperon grunts]
You're good.
But I think it's time I showed my true strength!
[Grunts]
Time to finish this! Here I come!
Like this? Err, should I face this way?
It doesn't matter, make up your mind!
I told you, nothing's more troublesome than making decisions!
Who are you talking to?!
Oh, you're over there!
Time to finish this!
Take this! Spinning Chaotic Slice!
[Pepperon yells]
Uh? Huh?
[Moaning]
Sweet!
What do we do now?
We can be on our way, right? A win's a win.
[All gasp]
What is this?
Oh, wow! It's a Paccarat Cologne!
What's its effect?
If you sprinkle it on you, you'll get a huge attack boost!
How much?
You know! It's a huge boost, you'll love it!
Ooh! We could always use a huge attack boost!
You guys aren't explaining this very well.
Ahh, I love that scent! I can feel its power already!
- [Dog barking]
- Huh?
[Dog barking]
There's Shibuchin!
Oh, my beloved Shibuchin!
...Huh?
Hahaha, stop it, Shibuchin! That tickles!
Maybe he was drawn in by the smell of the Paccarat Cologne!
Wait, what? He doesn't have anything on his collar!
Where's the Dragon Heart?
- [Woof woof!]
- Huh?
[Woof woof woof!]
He wants us to follow him!
He must be trying to tell us where the Dragon Heart is!
[Woof woof! Woof!]
What's up, Shibuchin?
This is where the Dragon Heart is hidden!
Of course! Let's go!
[Woof woof!]
Dig around here, woof-woof...
Oh, what's this?
My goodness! It's the legendary sword, Excalibur!
[Chup grunts, exclaims]
- I got it out!
- Woah!
T-That smell...
My nose feels like it's on fire...
- [Mayone hurls]
- Oiiink...
I don't quite get what's so bad about this.
That's only 'cuz you're used to your own old man smell.
Don't call me an old man!
What the heck is this sword?!
That isn't Excalibur, it's Excaliturd.
EXCALITURD
Excaliturd?!
You're telling me this is Excaliturd?!
Legend says that this sword was once stuck in the behind of an ancient king.
An ancient sword...it does seem a little rusty at the end.
The tip of the sword carries remains of its history.
What?! That's not rust! Ew, I even touched it!
- Eeegh, get it off of me...
- Watch where you wipe your hands!!
Equipping this sword will increase your bad odor by 40 points and luck by 0.03 points!
Looks like this wasn't a very lucky find after all.
The usefulness of this odor is kind of questionable.
No...I'm certain this will be of use!
Shibuchin felt an unknown power coming from it and struck gold!
He just reacted to the smell like Butako's been doing!
- Oink-oink!
- Ah...
Alright! I think this legendary sword...should go to you, Gob-san!
Me?
I already have my Fairy Crystal Sword.
You always go on about how you want your own weapon.
I mean, I do, but...why this one?
Because you can stand its stench.
Ooh, loving it! It suits you!
Really? You mean it?
I'm happy for you, Gob-san!
Ey, cut it out! Don't wipe your hands on me like that!
But if it wasn't on Shibuchin's collar, nor in that hole...
Where the heck is that Dragon Heart?
Oh yeah, I have it right here.
- Whaaaat?!
- Oink?!
Where was it?
I had it in my pocket.
Last time I bathed Shibuchin, I tucked it away to keep it safe, and completely forgot about it! Hahahaha!
Hahahaha, laugh it up! When did you find it?
Around when we met AKZ.
Excuse me? If you found it that long ago...why didn't you say anything?
It didn’t seem worth bringing up...
[Screams]
Oh, no!
[Groans]
[Quivering]
[Boys yelp, King quivering]
T-Thank you...
He's in there.
It's the door that looks like it'll open slowly but swipes open instantly.
Won't catch us off guard again.
- Huh?
- Oink?
I tooled with that door so it looks like it opens in the center, but opens upwards instead.
It's the latest door teach Opunapwerd.
...Because it opens upward.
Why did you change the door?
Give us back Melora, Vintaro!
Hey, don't call me my screen name!
I get it, Vintaro.
I said don't call me that!
You named yourself that...
We've brought the real Dragon Heart this time!
Hmph. And you're sure it's not another counterfeit?
- Take a good look!
- Oink!
It's fully, flawlessly the real thing!
Oink!
Good to know. Now hand it over.
If I hand this over, you give back Princess Melora.
It's a deal.
Can we trust this guy for real?
It's like my grandmother said!
A samurai never goes back on his word.
A summer always lacks hot soup!
A samurai never goes
back on his word.
A summer always
lacks hot soup.
A samurai never goes
back on his word.
A summer always
lacks hot soup.
-Tome
You can really feel winter coming up when convenience stores start selling soup.
Oh, things have changed!
These days the soup's been coming at the end of summer.
Seriously? That early in the year?
Why are you getting riled up over soup?!
Hey, catch it!
Oink...oink!
WHAAAT?!
I was afraid of this.
[Roaring]
Butako, you look epic!
Huh?
I don't think it's just the outside that's changed...
She must not recognize us.
Butako! It's me, Chup!
[Roaring]
She's under the full control of the Dragon Heart!
Fairy Crystal Sword!
Fairy Crystal Shield!
Downloading Fairy Electronics...
Fairy Crystal Sword.
Fairy Crystal Shield.
Hey, Butako! Snap out of it!
[Butako roaring]
Hey, Butako!!
Chup!
[Chup moaning]
How do we snap her out of it?
Gob-san, it's your turn!
Excaliturd!
No Brand!
- Hmph.
- Ooh!
- Ew.
- That's awful.
[Gulps]
Butako is very alert to smells.
A good thrust in the nose should snap her out of it!
Gob-san, watch out!
Huh?
Ooh!
Oops.
His luck has raised thanks to the Excaliturd!
Lookin' good out there, Gob-san!
He hasn't done anything but pose...
Pepperon, go!
Aye-aye!
Hey, Butako, I'll get you outta this!
Hi-yah!
Hah!
Ooh!
You did it! Butako, look, it's me, Chup!
Snap out of it, hey!
It's back in my hands.
Come on, all you did was make her mad because of the stench!
[All screaming]
Aaah! We can't do it!
Y-You're...
Get out of here, the exit's that way!
Vintaro...
Aah! Vintaro!!
That's just his screen name!!
konbini de kuda wo maku ukiyo wo samayou wakoudo yo
All you youngsters loitering about your lives,
shrouding the convenience stores
omaera wa genjitsu ni torinokosaresugi andeddo
You’re like undead who have left behind reality
itsumade son na koto kurikaesu no o-tsu-ka-re
How long are you going to keep doing this?
Don't you get tired of this same old routine?
hashiridase yo ENDLESS ROAD
Run forth through the endless road
koetemiroyo BORDERLINE
Go on past that borderline
sekai wa mugen ni hirogaru kouya
The world is an endless, limitless wilderness
omae no dokyou wo tameshiteiru
Where you can put your courage to the test
sumafo nankaja kensaku dekinai
It’s not something you can search for on your smartphone
sekai wa mugen ni hirogaru PARADISE
The world is an endless, limitless paradise
omaera wa giragira no
Soon you'll come to life taking in the blazing sun
taiyou kuratte ikiteiru
Raws
Translation/Typesetting/Timing
ED Karaoke
QC/Review
Raws
Translation/Typesetting/Timing
ED Karaoke
QC/Review
AnimeLand (BSJ)
Lumpstud
Noroino Hanako
NeSubs
(Specter Subs)
AnimeLand (BSJ)
Lumpstud
Noroino Hanako
NeSubs
(Specter Subs)
[All panting]
Butako was crazy strong! So epic!
If you think almost being killed is "epic."
That was a close one.
Huh, where's Gob-san?
Huh? Whaaat?!
It's up his behind like the ancient king!
That's disgusting! You didn't help in the slightest.
Can you get rid of that yucky sword already?
You sure? I think this sword's pretty neat. Heheh!
Quit putting on cool poses!
I can't do it anymore!
Take some of this!
[Gob-san mumbling]
He smells good now!
Bye-bye, old man smell!
My word! The Excaliturd has become a Danger Sword!
Danger Sword
It doesn't have the quirk of its stench anymore.
Alright, guess I'll take it then!
Hey!
Oh, I like it! This is great!
Give it back, we decided it was mine!
How could you just take it from me now that it doesn't smell?!
Take this, then! I picked it up while we were fleeing.
Hm?
Ooh, a treasure! That'll do nicely.
Let's see...
Hnngh?! I don't want this!!
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone!
What are you teaching us about today?
"French Toaster"
Today's lesson is about French Toaster!
French Toaster is a castle town in the middle of the continent.
In the heart of this town full of greenery and river streams is the castle where the King and Princess Melora reside.
If Princess Melora needs me, whenever or wherever I am, I'm on my way!
You seriously need to stop doing everything she tells you!!
Next Time
We must snap Butako out of this savage form!
We must work together with Vinsant to form a plan!
And then, before me appears...V-Vinegar?!
Fury Unleashed! Reunions with Vinegar
Next time: "Fury Unleashed! Reunions with Vinegar"!
Alright, it's time for a big adventure!