This is Snack World, the hallowed ground
of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam
and people have handy smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
And my name's Chup!
My village was burnt down by
the evil land-destroying merchant Vinegar Khan,
so I've embarked on a journey
to get my revenge 1000-fold!
At last, my journey has brought me
close to Vinegar.
In order to defeat him, I will overcome
any impossible mission that comes my way!
Alright, let's go on another big adventure today!
Episode 21: Moonlight Old Man Rhapsody
Gob-saaan!
What'cha up to?
You going incognito with those sunglasses?
You're not quite fooling anyone.
Oh, nah, it's nothing.
What are you hiding?
Oh, I know! Is it a weapon?
Y-Yeah, that's right.
I asked Bouiyong to get me
one of them strong boys.
You should'a just said so!
Hell's easy on the richer guys!
Here's your cut, Bunnilla.
Selling weapons on the black market?
Didn't think Bouiyong would run
such a shady operation...
Maybe he has a super-powerful weapon
we can use to beat Vampire!
This should be very effective for the
mighty enemy standing in my way.
Whoa, cool!
Well, how much is it?
Oh, um, how much was it?
You got swindled. It was expensive, wasn't it?
Ugh, my memory fails me...
Whatever. I'll go ask Bouiyong.
How much?
Oui, oui! I'll answer if you give me a tip.
You want money to answer my question?
You want someone to help you
in the city, you gotta tip!
Mayone, if you don't pay the man,
you'll look like a dumb hillbilly.
You've gotta be...
That'll be 10,00 gillan.
– Yikes, that's steep!
– Huh?!
But it's the price to pay for beating Vampire!
Open it, open it!
Uh, alright.
Huh. It needs a key.
Wha?!
Bouiyong, do you have the key for this?
10,000 for the suitcase.
Never said it came with a key.
Whaaat?!
Oui, oui, that'll be another 10,000 for the key.
What a jerk move, right?
Fine, Mr. Yon. Can you help us pick it?
Oui, oui. But you need to tip.
Again, really? Fine, whatever.
Here's your gloves.
Huh? I said I needed pliers.
Sir, I heard you were going to pick a fight!
That's not what he said at all...
We need a lock-pick!
Oui, oui. You want someone
to help you in the city...
We get it, you greedy pig.
Whatever. Gob-san, drop the case.
I'll burst it open with my fire spell.
No magic in the building!
Unless you can tip me.
NO MAGIC
Fine! I'll have you know, I'm no hillbilly!
There. Scooch over.
Here we go... Fireball!
There we go, just what we
need to beat... Vampire...?
A tonic? I thought it'd be a weapon.
Oh, perhaps it boosts your
ATK when you drink it?
Oh, yeah! Maybe!
Alright. Hup to it.
Gob-san... What are you doing...?
Oh, I see! Maybe it makes
you smarter instead!
Really? Gimme some too!
Well, a mage like me deserves some...
Uh... What?
Hair Restoral Tonic?!
Bunnilla told me she's into
men with long hair, so...
I never said that.
Gob-san... Don't tell me the "mighty enemy"
you were talking about earlier...
You were talking about Bunnilla?
What are you thinking,
buying all this useless crap?
Knowing Bouiyong, I wouldn't even be surprised
if that tonic is complete balonga.
What a waste, dude!
And for that, no dinner for you
until we beat Vampire!
Oh, really?
Then I can lose weight
and the ladies will love me even more!
He's taking that lightly.
Hm? Do you guys hear all that racket?
Yeah, why?
What is that?
It's coming from the room above us.
Should we go warn them for you?
Doesn't matter.
That customer generously paid me
his fees for the week in advance!
So long as you pay up,
dine and dashers, robbers,
murderers, and monsters?
All good with me, oui oui!
If it bothers you, can you go warn them?
They're in Room 204.
– Huh?
– Room 204?
But that's right next to our room!
We can't sleep with that noise!
It's like my grandmother said!
Don't call your neighbors to annoy them!
Don't call your neighbors
to annoy them.
Call about your husband's
life insurance.
Don't call your neighbors
to annoy them.
Call about your husband's
life insurance.
Call about your husband's life insurance!
-Tome
No one should suffer without insurance!
Hello? We need to speak with you!
Can't get out 'cuz of this damn drumset.
If you need t'talk, get in here.
So you can't get out, but you
had no trouble getting in?
Hi, sorry.
Well, what is it?
Isn't it obvious?
Can't you even talk without
going off on the drums?
What's your problem?!
You're disturbing the other guests.
Can you keep it down, please?
Who d'ya think yer talkin' to?
I'm the legendary drummer of the band
that took my generation by storm,
Demon & Carbuncle...
Demon Futohara!
Demon Futohara
Ring a bell, Gob-san?
Nope, not at all.
Without a vocalist, he just seems
like a crazed drummer.
You said it.
A band's nothing without a vocalist.
For yuck's sake! Vocalist this, vocalist that,
you all think they're sooo great!
Vocalists here, vocalists there...
Why are people so vocal about them?!
What's with this strange
complex against vocalists?
Oh, Carbuncle! Why'd ya have
to leave me behind?
D'ya really think my drums
were holdin' our band back?!
P-Preach, man!
He needs to show some gratitude for you!
But he only cares about the sales,
that's why he went solo!
See? You guys gets me!
But on the other hand, drumming doesn't
quite help your resume.
Say that again.
I don't wanna hear that BS, goddamn it!
He's gonna cause the building to collapse!
It's like my grandmother said!
A retreating dog howls from afar!
A big dog should be kept outside!
A retreating dog
howls from afar.
A big dog should be
kept outside.
A retreating dog
howls from afar.
A big dog should be
kept outside.
-Tome
That makes us the retreating dogs
for getting angry at him!
Shuddup! Don't lecture me!
I'll knock you out with all I got!
Drum Roll Power!
Whuh? What's that so-and-so power?
What's your deepest, darkest secret?
W-Why are you asking me?
I don't keep secrets that big!
I still wet the bed sometimes!
You what?!
So do I!
What did I just say...?
What did you just do?
This drum roll will make ya
answer any question I ask!
Huh?
I've lost count of how many rival bands
I've broken up with this thang!
Don't it just make ya quiver?
I'm sooo scared...
I even got our lead vocalist
to tell me how he really feels,
and we broke apart
'cuz it turned out he hated me!
So you broke up your own band too...?
Don't talk back to me, boy!
You've got secrets too!
Tell me what you've been bottlin' up deep down!
Pepperon wet the bed just yesterday!
Oh, shoot!
That "sometimes" was yesterday?!
Chup, did you just pretend
you found out before?
So is the reason my bed got wet
because you sneakily swapped it with yours?
That was already wet.
I'm so sorry, Pepperon!
I can't believe I exposed your secret like that!
You're next, Grandpa!
Give me your best joke!
Why do I have to tell comedy...?
You're under a lot of pressure
with that drum roll, too.
From manure!
Wow, ROFL.
Sprouts...
A rice ball!
Is that really your best work?
Don't know if I can recover from that one...
That's terrifying!
You, quick-lips!
Is that supposed to be me?
What should I ask you...?
Don't ask her what color her undies are!
Don't even think about it!
Are you trying to give him ideas?
I know! Just the right question for a girl your age!
What's a womanly desire you've
kept hidden from your friends?
Spill!
Oh, no! Not that! Anything but that!
I wish I had a hot boyfriend!
Mayone...?
Didn't think you had that stuff on the brain.
I don't, stop it!
What do you wanna
do with this boyfriend...?
I want to smooch him in the deepest dungeon!
A dungeon...?
What a sad place for a smooch.
As if a prude girl like you...
Why are you trying to get the last word in?
I can't take it anymore!
How's it taste? Takin' all my hits, huh?
But it's nothin' like the pain I've gone through.
Oh, how traumatic it is,
to be abandoned by my vocalist...
I can't hear myself think.
Huh? Who's there?
Vinsant!
Just in the nick of time!
Oh, one of their buds, eh?
Vinsant, you've got the name of a vocalist,
and the style of one too!
I hate yer kind so much!
Keep your guard up, Vinsant!
Drum Roll Power!
Alright, fancy-pants. Ya seem tough,
so let's crush some friendships.
Who do ya hate the most
of everyone in this room?
Uh-oh, I don't think I can take this face-to-face.
It can't be me, right, Vinsant?
Or me, right?
Surely, it's not everyone's favorite Gob-san, no?
The one person in this room
who disgusts me the most...
Who's it gonna be?!
Huh?
...Is you!
Yay!
Oh, yeah! He's also "in this room" with us!
But Vinsant. You love me, don'tcha?
Oh, you're here too?
Whoo!
We did it!
A treasure chest!
He may not have aged well, but he was once big!
It must be a valuable treasure!
Ooh, it's the Phantom Brooch!
It's a must-have for snappy adults
who are tired of plain-old fashions.
Not only do cool guys love it,
but it's exploded among
temptresses in modern day.
Mine it is, then!
Hey, no fair!
This should make up for you
learning my dark secret, no?
Secret?
Mayone wants to kiss a hottie in a dun...
Ow-ow-ow-ow-ow!!
Have any new details on Vampire?
I met someone in town
you might find interesting.
Way to go, Vinsant!
Already making friends in the city!
Ain't a hillbilly no more!
He told me that he wants
to defeat Vampire himself.
Huh?
Defeat him? Is he like, crazy strong?
He will arrive at Squid Ink Lane shortly.
The rest is in your hands.
I'm going to try to find more intel on Vampire.
I can't believe someone's
able to handle Vampire!
I can't wait to meet him!
Huh?
What the? What's a down-on-his-luck
office worker doing here?
Let me guess, did he get laid off?
Must be hard living the city life.
Are you the kids that are out to defeat Vampire?
Huh?!
Are you...?
I thought I could probably
take on the Vampire myself.
That was you?!
No way, this guy's just... some guy!
All dismissed! Let's go back
into the hotel and split.
Not happening.
Uhh, here's my info.
A business card? He's like
the definition of some guy!
Moonlight Press
Accounting
Were Wolf
Moonlight Press
Accounting
Were Wolf
Moonlight Press
Accounting
Were Wolf
Moonlight Press
Accounting
Were Wolf
Moonlight Press
Accounting
Were Wolf
Moonlight Press
Accounting
Were Wolf
Moonlight Press
Accounting
Were Wolf
Moonlight Press
Accounting
Were Wolf
Moonlight Press
Accounting
Were Wolf
"Were Wolf?"
Moonlight Press
Accounting
Were Wolf
Moonlight Press
Accounting
Were Wolf
Moonlight Press
Accounting
Were Wolf
Moonlight Press
Accounting
Were Wolf
Moonlight Press
Accounting
Were Wolf
Moonlight Press
Accounting
Were Wolf
Moonlight Press
Accounting
Were Wolf
As you can see, I'm a
long-standing rival of Vampire's.
We've fought 500 times,
but they all ended in draws.
But tonight is the one full moon of the
decade where my power is at its peak...
I have to defeat him.
And when it isn't a full moon,
I work for accounting at Moonlight Press
here in King Oyster City.
Are you even listening? Hello?
I was talking...
Sorry, dude, you were just going on...
I'm not normally like this...
Can you repeat everything after
"As you can see?"
Of course...
I think we get the gist of it.
But for someone called "Were Wolf..."
You sure don't look the part.
There's a full moon tonight!
I can transform once it appears.
The moon sure is shy tonight.
Patience is rewarding.
Would you like to hear about
my relationship with Vampire?
We'd rather stay awake, so we'll pass.
By the way, you're not gonna like,
charge us for your assistance, right?
I heard there's hitmen in the city
that make a lotta money off their work.
I don't need compensation.
Oh, wow. Didn't think there were
such kind people here.
I know I will bring about his downfall...
Look, the moon!
Here it comes, here it comes!
Come on out!
– You can do it, moon!
– At last!
Even his voice is starting
to sound more ferocious!
Oh, Vampire...
I will take you down...!
I need to make sure I have a
copy of tomorrow's records.
Aw, come on!
I apologize, but alas, I'm just
a man without my moon.
Gob-san, what's happening to you?
The Hair Restoral Tonic took effect!
I can't back down! Bunnillaaaa!!
Huh? What happened?
Seems that paper fan smacked it all away.
Yeah, yeah. Heck of a cloudy day, though.
I'm afraid those aren't clouds.
Vinegar Enterprises is polluting the air
with toxic gases emitting from their factory.
Yuck, what the hell?
Vinegar, how dare you go this far...?
Chup, look!
The clouds are out of the way!
Sweet, the moon's free!
Here it comes, here it comes!
Here I am! It's showtime!
He can so do this!
Vampire!
After all these years, our battle
will finally come to an end...!
I better process all the receipts I have piling up.
Come on!
I apologize, but alas, I'm just
an office worker without my moon.
This is going nowhere!
Are you sure you can't transform
without the moon?
I think I once transformed when
I saw something bright and round.
What was it?
It was my first date after I got my job.
I worked up the courage and...
Are you listening?
Um...?
Oh, what was that after "It was my first?"
It was my first date.
I worked up the courage and
asked out Tomoko, the receptionist...
You worked up the courage, and...?
And asked out Tomoko,
the receptionist. I gazed into her...
Aah! You asked her out, and...?
I gazed into her eyes, thoughtlessly...
Oh, I see. She turned you on, didn't she?
You gazed into her eyes, and...?
Thoughtlessly, I...
You were turned on, right?
You transformed after
looking into a girl's eyes?
Yes, but then she dumped me
after I transformed.
So d'ya think you can
transform with Mayone's?
Huh? Hold on, what?
Worth a shot!
Allow me to try.
This is so awkward...
I know you're just some old man, but still...
One girl, one man, hidden away in the city...
They really do look like
a messy couple from over here.
Oh? I think it's happening.
Really?
I actually worked!
Alright! At last, the time has come...
...to finish the withdrawal and deposit vouchers
and write up a transfer voucher.
Suppose I was wrong. Apologies.
I may not be able to transform
without Tomoko.
Come on, Mayone.
You're blaming me?
For Tomoko, the flames of her love
must have made her eyes glow like the full moon.
You gotta turn up the magic!
But not your literal magic!
Could've done without the quip.
If only Tomoko were here...
Why did she dump me...?
Receptionist Tomoko!
Huh? Wait, is that...?
Tomoko!
Were Wolf?
Weird timing!
Nothing weird about it—
that's the city for you.
Thank goodness Tomoko took over!
We might still have a chance!
These two look just right for each other!
Tomoko's a lot more into
balance than I expected.
Please quiet down, it's distracting.
Tomoko.
Yes?
Tomokooo!
Finally... At last!
I can feel the strength!
Werewolf
I think I'll pass!
Forgive me, Tomoko.
Hey, Vampire! You're going down tonight!
Vat brings you here?
Have you come to taste defeat yet again?
We've got ultra-strong backup today!
Backup? Who could desire
to face me head-on?
Could it be...?
Problem?
Looking paler than usual!
Tch... You're at your strongest
because of the full moon!
I'm no match for you on a day like this!
Time to put an end to our days of youth, Vampire!
shobokure gao no mobukyara domo ga
On and on these tired old NPCs
iiwake shinagara aruiteru
Keep walking around excusing themselves
itsumo miteiru michisugara
As I took the same old path again
mita koto mo nai wakuwaku wo mita
I found the thrill I've sought for my whole life
itsumade shibonda mama nano
Just how long will I keep drooping around like this?
minikui ahiru no mama nano
How long will I stay an ugly duckling?
ima no reberu wa ichi dakedo
I'm still only level one
ima ni mitero yo sono uchi JUMP UP
But watch me, soon I'll jump up
saikin no wakai mon wa tte
"Why, kids these days..."
toshiyori domo ga boyai teru kedo
...Our old boomers grumble and complain
soro soro omei henjou da
But it's not too late to clear my name
iya ga ou ni mo mattanashi daze
I might not like it, but I can't wait any longer
ketsu no ana kara jetto funsha daaa
I gotta blast free from my cowardly shell!!
ore wa itsuka hana ni naru
Give me time and I'll bloom like a flower
sora ni nobiru hana ni naru
A flower spread out to the sky
kimi ni todoku hana ni naru
The flower that reaches you
You really are the same old Pie, huh?
Pie? Excuse me?
He's so strong!
He's totally gonna win this battle!
Let's help him out!
Fairy Crystal Sword!
Fairy Crystal Shield!
Downloading Fairy Electronics.
Fairy Crystal Sword.
Fairy Crystal Shield.
Fireball!
Now!
Take this, my ultimate spell...!
Guh... I can't move...
Crap, he's too quick!
Say good night!
Dang it!
His business card?
He transformed back!
What happened?
I turn back when I see anything triangle-shaped.
Triangle-shaped?
...Like a rice ball.
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone!
What are you teaching us about today?
Today's lesson is on King Oyster City!
King Oyster City
King Oyster City is a metropolis
housing Vinegar Enterprises.
It's covered by a barrier absorbing the sunlight,
run by the power of their factories.
The whole city is plunged
in eternal night as a result.
Grr, Vinegar. I won't let you get away with this!
It's a dangerous place, so we'll have to
be prepared for any eventuality!
Next Time
The final battle against Vampire begins,
with the help of Werewolf and Franken!
And we'll strike the final blow
with this secret weapon!
Next time: "Fire the Sprightly Silver Bullet!"
Fire the Sprightly Silver Bullet
Alright, it's time for a big adventure!