These fan-made subtitles are not for sale, rent or any profit whatsoever.
Please support official  Snack World anime releases in your home country.
See lumpstud.tumblr.com for certain translation notes.
This is Snack World, the hallowed
ground of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam and
people have smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
...And my name's Chup.
My village was burnt down by the evil
land-destroying merchant, Vinegar Khan,
and I've embarked on a journey
to get my revenge 1000-fold!
The tickets to King Oyster City, where
Vinegar is, cost 20 million gillan.
So I'm on an adventure searching for
big treasure to make loads of cash!
[Chup humming theme song]
Alright, let's go on another big adventure today!
My quest for you today is to get an item my Melora
Ep. 8: Peter Panpan the Super Explorer
has been longing for lately, a love potion.
- [Chup giggling]
- [King talking]
- What's Princess Melora doin'?
- I saw this on TV.
- I'm pretty sure it's a beauty treatment
where fish eat at her corneum.
- Aha...I wish I was one of those fish...
That'll be your mission! Did you catch all of that?
Ah, darn it! I was distracted watching Princess Melora!
I'm sorry, please repeat that again!
It sure takes quite some guts to ignore the king.
Thanks a ton!
He's not praising you...
Oh, whatever. I'll start over.
It's okay, daddy! I can tell them!
Oh, the thing I want the most right now is...
The Siren Sisters'...ah, oh, wait~!
Their love potion, ohhh!
Oh no, I didn't quite catch that. Can you say it again?
We've heard enough!!
Princess Melora wants the Siren Sisters' love potion.
So where exactly are these Siren Sisters?
What? Uhh...
The Siren Sisters are...s-said to live around here...
In the west forest...about this area for
some reason, or maybe a bit nearby...
O-or considerably around here...
Doesn't this explanation seem sketchy?
I suppose...
Thing is, there's not an awful lot of
eyewitness info on the Siren Sisters.
Umm...I don't think that's nearly enough information for us.
Really, even you guys can't handle it?
Ohh, Chup... Mmm, is the love potion a lost cause?
Of course not!
One love potion fully, flawlessly coming up!!
Quest
Get the Love Potion
Huuuh?!
Quest
Get the Love Potion
I can't believe you!!
Why do you always have to bite
off more than you can chew?!
On the other hand, what would Princess
Melora need a love potion for anyhow?
She's already a super-popular person in
the kingdom without the need for one.
Maybe there's just that one person she truly has feelings for, right?
[Gasps] What if...
Princess Melora, I got your love potion!
That's my Chup! Thank you so much!
I'd do anything for you, come hell,
high water, or dragon guts.
Hey, Chup, there's one more thing I ask of you.
Can you drink this while looking right at me?
[Gasps]
After all, the thing I really want is...your heart.
- Oh, Princess Melora!
- Ohh!
Heheh...she might want the love potion for m--
Agh!
That's not gonna happen!
Guh, don't hit the hard part!
Oink!
You're having another impossible delusion.
Nothing about it is "impossible!"
But, for you, Chup, you don't need a love
potion to be madly in love with Melora.
That's not true!
Princess Melora appeared in my
dreams seven times this week.
Whenever I wake up, my heart
starts pounding out of my chest!!
That's the definition of madly in love!!
Besides, shouldn't we should figure
out how to find the Siren Sisters?
Even the king and his subjects were stumped on that.
We'll figure it out! We just have to look all around the forest!
Are you aware of the size of the forest?
I have heard some rumors.
In that forest lives a forest explorer who
truly knows his way around the forest.
Forest explorer? That sounds cool!
Well, who is he?
I think his name is... Peter Pan!
Peter Pan?
So, where exactly can we find this person?
That's about all I know.
We'll have to figure that out the hard way and ask around.
Oh, it's that girl! Let's ask her!
Can we have lunch first?
I bought a yakiniku bento box from Jaja En!
"Jaja En Special"
"Yakiniku Bento Box"
For real?!
I'll have some after this.
Tell me, do you know Peter Pan?
Peter Pan? Oh, yes, I've seen him.
Huh, really? Where can we find him?
I'm sorry, I don't know...
Ah, but I can draw a portrait of him!
Really? Draw him, draw him!
Done!
Huh, does he really look that cool?!
We're going straight to the forest!
Drop everything we're doing for that potion!
Maybe let Peter Pan drink it if he wants it, hehe~
Oi, what are you waiting for?!
She's super good at portraits, so
we're letting her draw us too.
Done! First up is Chup's portrait!
Ohh, looks good!
Doesn't the drawing look better than you?
This is Pepperon!
Oho! It's like I'm looking in a mirror!
What on earth do you mean?! She
changed your body shape!!
Last up, here you go!
Uhh...is it just me, or did she go in
a different direction with mine?
But it looks just like you!
What part of it?! I'm not that gross!
Huh? Where'd she go?
[Pepperon exclaims]
Our Jaja En yakiniku bento boxes are gone!
What?! Are you kidding?! Where's our food?!
- Hm?
- Mmm... delish...
Hey, are you going around thieving again?!
Give us back our food!
What are you talkin' about?
Our fooood!
I don't knooow!
- Get back here!!
- Why, you!!
I don't know Peter Pan... heheh...
Peter Pan, hm?
I've only heard rumors, but...
I'm not sure where you can meet him.
Is that so...
However, Master...
There's no need to seriously pay attention to them.
Why, you! What attitude you have to your customers...
Cannot compute voice.
You're lying!
Well, unless you have any new images of Princess Melora,
my high-performance computer and its ability
to look up information won't come to use.
Pictures...well, I don't have anything
but the small fish biting at her feet.
When did you take that?!
Small fish and feet?
Her heels?! Were the fish biting at her heels too?!
Yeah, look.
[Melora moaning]
Yeeeess!! Her heeeels!!!
Calm down, you're gonna hit us!
Looking up at once.
Ding-ding-ding! I'm finished!
For real?!
Although there were only 12 results, the famous
info site Snapedia had an entry on Peter Pan!
In his career, he has a first-class forest survival
license, and is a second-rank treasure hunter.
High-grade certification from the forest's Kinokos, and so on.
He's got quite the career.
We could use someone like him.
Oh, but look at this.
"Kind and knowledgeable, this nice guy
has a love for animals and plants."
So he's not just nice on the outside but on the inside too!
Ahh, I want to meet him now!
Even that simple of information escapes my search.
Just as stupid as ever.
Huh, what was that?
Cannot compute voice.
If Snapedia's anything to go off, Peter Pan
should be somewhere around here.
Sniff sniff, I've got something.
Could that be Peter Pan's smell?
Nope, not him.
[Mayone humming]
Oh, Peter Pan~ I want to meet you now!
Mayone's really fallen for Peter Pan!
[Chup & Pepperon yelp]
Keep your eyes peeled! Someone's coming for us!
Huh?!
Freeze! Put your hands above your heads!
What on earth? Where's that voice coming from?
Think fast unless you want an arrow in your head!
C-can't reach...
You rats, what business do you have here?
We're looking for a man named Peter Pan.
Peter Pan? Is that what you want me for?
Huh? Are you Peter Pan?
Don't get too excited, leave this to me.
Peter Pan, we are not suspicious people.
[Gob-san yelps]
[All gasp]
You look suspicious!
But we really aren't enemies!
We have something for your
super-handsomeness to listen to.
"Super-handsomeness?" Heh...
Seems pleased by that comment.
Understood, I'll make my way there now!
Don't imitate me! Hyah!
[Grunts]
What?
[Peter Pan grunts and screams]
[All scream]
Yow!
Are you okay?
Uh...this is Peter Pan?
Don't stand behind me!
We were just trying to help you!
Don't act so naive! I believe everyone
you meet in the forest is an enemy!
To reach for help here...how ridiculous- guh!
Can you pull me up? I hurt my back.
How's reaching for help sounding now?
We don't stress the details in the forest.
What do you want from me?
First off, are you really Peter Pan?
Uh-huh, that's right.
I'm the super-explorer, Peter Pan!
Nooo, you're nothing like the portrait!
To show their respect for me, people also call me...
Peter Panpan!
Peter Panpan
Peter Panpan?
"Panpan" because you're as fat as a bread loaf?
Oh, this is the worst...
The location of the Siren Sisters, you ask?
We thought you'd know since you're a forest explorer.
I'm not a forest explorer! I'm a forest super-explorer!
There's nothing I don't know about this forest.
Then tell us!
Those sirens dwell in the deep, deep depth of the forest!
It'll take three days and three nights!
That's so far! Can we quit this mission?
We can still do it!
We'll do whatever it takes to get that love potion!
Don't underestimate the forest!
Amateurs like you that go in the forest
will be forest lunch on day one!
Unless... a pro like me stays by your
side. Then it might be different.
Then please do! Accompany us on our travel!
I knew you'd say that, but I'll only do it on one condition.
A condition?
When we trek into that forest, you
will call me Master Panpan!
Master Panpan?
Understood, Master Panpan!
So cool! You're the real deal!
Really? Well, don't act too merry.
Be prepared to be shown your means of
survival as we trek through those woods.
- Yessir, Master Panpan!
- Oink!
[Grunts]
Yes, sir, Master Panpan...
Well then, let us depart!
Master, which way do we go?
Listen to the voice of the forest...it
will tell you all you need to know.
Okay!
[All humming]
There, that way.
- Did you hear anything?
- Uhh...
That's our Master Panpan! Let's get a move on!
Hold it! What are you rats doing?
Huh? We're just walking...
You don't just walk, you push through! Follow after me!
Yessir, Master Panpan!
[Panpan panting]
Is his walk supposed to mean something?
Come on, you rats!
Huh??
Hurry up, didn't you hear what Master Panpan said?
Why do we have to mimic his movement?
[Panpan panting]
Master Panpan is really absurd, isn't he?
Everyone halt!
What do we do, Master Panpan?
Take a break here.
We haven't even walked 100 meters.
Are you really a forest explorer?
I'm not an explorer...I'm a forest super-explorer...
Is this guy in his right mind?
[Gasping for breath]
[Mosquito buzzing]
Ugh, it bit me again! So itchy!
This forest has a lot of mosquitoes!
It's evidence you still haven't taken a liking to the forest yet.
Once you come to love it...you'll adapt...
Then the insects won't bite you!
Seems like you've been bitten more than all of us, Panpan.
Call me Master Panpan!
These bruises are from when I
fought a bear with my bare hands.
All that was from a bear?
Don't stand behind me!
But there's no one standing there.
Everyone, halt!
What, another break?
No, I sense a Monster.
Huh?
Over there!
Nope, over here.
What's that guy?!
Master Panpan, what's that Monster?
Huh?
You know everything about everything in this forest.
Of course, I am a forest super-explorer!
Yes, we get it.
That guy's name is certainly Pink Pata...
My name is Fairjii.
Fairjii
Looks like you got his name wrong.
Could it be you didn't know at all?
No, of course I knew it!
This must be an old lady who got lost in the forest...
I'm no old lady! I'm clearly a man!
The "jii" in "Fairjii" means grandfather.
You sure can tell from his beard.
Panpan doesn't know squat.
This is the first time I've seen him...he must be
a new guy who recently migrated to the forest.
I've lived around these parts for 400 years.
People around here sometimes call me the Forest Elder.
Forest Elder...
It's your face that I'm seeing for the first time.
And Panpan, you don't know the Forest Elder...?
Don't stand behind me!!
Would you quit dodging the questions?
Forest Elder, would you know
where the Siren Sisters dwell?
Oh, but of course.
Sure seemed much quicker to
ask that Monster than Panpan.
He surely knows more about
the forest than Master Panpan.
O-oi, you rats! You really believe this Monster?
Alright, Panpan. Do you really
know where the Siren Sisters are?
O-of course I know. I'm a forest super-explorer!
Uh-huh. So, where are they?
Guh...got it.
Since he knows too, let's say it at the same time.
The place the Siren Sisters live is...
- [Panpan] Beauty Garden.
- [Fairjii] Siren's Garden.
What was that, Panpan?
I said Siren's Garden.
Okay, and which way do we go to get to Siren's Garden?
Guh! L-let's say that at the same time too!
The way to get to Siren's Garden is...
- 2000 steps south.
- [Mumbling] to that place.
Did you just say "north?"
No, I was saying south.
Fairjii, can you tell us more about the Siren Sisters?
No problem.
Yay, now we don't have to rely on Panpan!
Aah, you guys! Careful!!
Hey, why'd you attack?!
Don't let him fool you!!
He was about to strike you rats just now!
Wow, really? Thanks for saving us, Master Panpan!
Nope, he showed no signs of attack.
Don't tell me you just wanted to shut him up
because he knows more about the forest than you.
Don't stand behind me!!
Knew it.
Got it!
A treasure chest!
Sweet, let's open it!
Wait!
My intuition of the wild says that this is a Mimic!
Ooh!
Oi, you guys, listen to me!
Looks like a strong knife!
This must be the well-known weapon
company Fairy Electronics' Fairy Crystal Knife!
- Sweet!
- [Gob-san yelps]
So, about those "instincts of the wild?"
[Sniffling]
This is where the Siren Sisters will appear.
[Shivering]
Panpan, are you scared?
W-who do you think I am? I'm a forest super-explor-aah!!
He's so clearly scared...
[Singing]
Siren's Garden
Singing? Master Panpan, what is that voice?
T-this might be...the singing voice
of the Siren Sisters, it must be!
It must be...maybe...I feel like it could be, or could not be...
You have no idea, do you?
The fog's getting thicker!
Everyone, keep an eye out!
What is this?
Are you all okay?
I'm okay, I just can't see anything...
Ah- who are you guys?
I am Si.
And I am Ren.
Together, we're...
♪ The Siren Sisteeeers.
Siren
Sisters
You Siren Sisters will give us your love potion!
♪ Nuh-uh-uh, no, nuh-uh-uh
Give it uuup! Hyah!
Stop it, stop it! It's me!
Gob-san, are you okay?
I'll never forgive you, Siren Sisters!
To subject Gob-san to something like that!
That was you, Chup.
- [Singing]
- [Gasps] They're back!
[Singing]
♪ We won't be giving you no love potion!
♪ Won't be giving you it, won't be giving it~!
Give us the love potion!
- Quit iiiit!
- Gob-san?
Didn't you learn last time?!
No, not the singing again!!
Master Panpan, what are we supposed to do?
- [Panpan crying]
- Master Panpan?
He's crying?
Master Panpan, what do we do?
How do we beat the Siren Sisters?
I-I don't know...
I thought you knew everything
about everything in the forest?
No, I don't!!
I really don't know anything about anything in the forest!
I'm no forest explorer...
I'm really just a forest super-shut-in!
Super-shut-in?
Mhm...
I couldn't adapt to city life,
so I shut myself in the forest...
But I'm still the same as always...
No way...
But how come you still know a
lot about forest survival means?
I just looked at online blogs...
No way!
But what about the "glorious career"
Snapedia wrote about you?
I edited that myself so people would think I was cool...
No waaay!!
Nah, that one's kind of expected.
Oh...I see!
Master Panpan's trying to get me to rise
and beat the enemy without his aid!
That's why he's lying on purpose!
Whaaa?! After all that, you still believe in Panpan?
I believe in him!
It's like my grandmother said!
What you believe in will keep you safe.
Your skin in the winter will be steep and chafed!
What you believe in
will keep you safe.
Your skin in the
winter will be
steep and chafed.
Your skin in the
winter will be
steep and chafed.
Your skin in the
winter will be
steep and chafed.
-Tome
Fairy Crystal Knife!
Watch this, Master Panpan!
Chup, what are you about to do?
I remember Master's words.
Listen to the voice of the forest...come
to love the forest...adapt to the forest!
That's it!
Don't Stand Behind Me Slash!
konbini de kuda wo maku ukiyo wo samayou wakoudo yo
All you youngsters loitering about your lives,
shrouding the convenience stores
omaera wa genjitsu ni torinokosaresugi andeddo
You’re like undead who have left behind reality
itsumade son na koto kurikaesu no o-tsu-ka-re
How long are you going to keep doing this?
Don't you get tired of this same old routine?
hashiridase yo ENDLESS ROAD
Run forth through the endless road
koetemiroyo BORDERLINE
Go on past that borderline
sekai wa mugen ni hirogaru kouya
The world is an endless, limitless wilderness
omae no dokyou wo tameshiteiru
Where you can put your courage to the test
sumafo nankaja kensaku dekinai
It’s not something you can search for on your smartphone
sekai wa mugen ni hirogaru PARADISE
The world is an endless, limitless paradise
omaera wa giragira no
Soon you'll come to life taking in the blazing sun
taiyou kuratte ikiteiru
Raws
Translation/Typesetting/Timing
ED Karaoke
QC/Review
Raws
Translation/Typesetting/Timing
ED Karaoke
QC/Review
AnimeLand (BSJ)
Lumpstud
Noroino Hanako
NeSubs
AnimeLand (BSJ)
Lumpstud
Noroino Hanako
NeSubs
Alright...I did it!
That's our Chup for you!
Where's the Siren Sisters?
Did they run away?
I did hear a response though.
If that's so, where'd they vanish to?
Uh...
Uhh...
Uhhh...
Uhhhh...
Oink.
Whaaaat?!?
Ch-Chup slashed Gob-san?!
[Gob-san shrieks]
Aha, this knife is super sharp!
Aren't you concerned?! Put me back together!!
Aah! Don't come near!
Quickly, stick me together! Someone stick me back together!
I'm begging you, stick me back together!
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone!
What are you teaching us about today?
We're talking about Jara Holders today!
"Jara Holders"
Jara Holders can hang up to 6 items in Jara form.
It's very convenient to immediately hang Jaras you store in your bag.
I like the way it jangles!
I'm gonna get all kinds of Jara!
Choosing which Jara to hang on your holder can be troublesome, though!
Next Time
Snow White knows the Siren Sisters' secret.
But the only way to wake her up is...with a kiss?!
That's just ridiculous!
Next time: Snow White's Deep Zone!
Snow White's Deep Zone
Alright, it's time for a big adventure!