Shota, look, it's her!
The girl on the stage!
This way, Lilly!
Lilly-san!
Wait up!
Oh no!
Lilly-chan!
Slow down!
Shake my hand!
Excuse us! Make way please!
Lilly!
It's Sho-chan and his friend!
Is it true you just debuted today?!
I'm a big fan of yours!
Really?
U-Um...
Your performance was awesome.
Thanks!
Lilly-chan!
Look over here!
What now? There's no escape!
I know!
Lililula palilula,
make us fly away from this!
Weird...
What's wrong?
I cast a spell, but...
Excuse us! Please make way!
I messed up again!
You stink. You're not wishing hard enough.
Say that again!
What the heck is going on?!
Now's our chance!
Got it.
Bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae
Bae, bae, bae
Bubee, bubee
Bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae
Ooh, ooh, ooh
You're my little buddy
Hey, bubee love
Bubee, bubee, bubee love
My heart is racing like crazy
And right before my eyes
Are the colors of a brand new world
Whoa
Stay with me today
We'll walk hand in hand
Dreaming of the place where we can become light
I can hear the magic
I wanna sing with you
Let's sing together
You're a bright shining star
My bubee, bubee, bubee love
We can be shining stars
Forever and ever
That's our secret magic
My bubee, bubee, bubee love
Ooh, ooh, ooh
You're my little buddy
Hey, bubee love
Bubee, bubee, bubee love
Bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae
Bae, bae, bae
Bubee, bubee
B-U-B-E-E, bubee
Bubee love
When I Look Up to the Moon
That was amazing...
CompatoLilly - Debut Performance!
I...
I should continue my homework.
MOURI
BUILDING
NO. 1
We made it.
This is my agency!
Huh?
Your agency is in here?
This isn't what I pictured at all!
Production Once More
Come on in.
Here we are!
Take a seat.
O-Okay!
Make yourself at home.
O-Okay...
Wait right there. I'll put on some tea.
O-Okay!
Welcome back.
Oh?
Huh?
Oh, that's the girl you talked about?
Yep! She's our next big talent!
Ah, he's our agency's president.
President?
I keep telling you,
you're way too impulsive.
But I just found our future star!
I can't just sit on this and relax.
You saw her concert too, didn't you?
Even if I did...
Ah, I'm Toko's uncle,
and the agency's president,
Kandachi Yasuo.
N-Nice to meet you.
It's too much of a hassle
to do everything myself,
so I founded the agency
and made my uncle the president.
You just started going off about
wanting to be an idol.
It was a pretty big burden, y'know.
Really? You were lazing about so much,
I figured you had time to kill.
We're still pretty small,
but we're on track to get even bigger!
And now we have just the member
to help us with that!
Right?
Come on, Toko-san!
We can pull through with you on our side!
Well, Toko's found you, so you must be for real.
I'm still not cut out for this!
Believe in yourself!
I'll leave the rest to you.
So, Lilly-chan?
Wanna join the agency and work with us?
I just...
Didn't you enjoy being up on stage?
I know you can shine even brighter than that!
You really think so?
Oh, yeah.
I said we'd have some yummy food.
Don't want you getting hounded again,
so how does takeout from the café next door sound?
Yummy food?!
Their pasta is super good!
We can get parfaits too!
Yeah!
You think that'll win her over?
Hello, this is Once More!
Can I place an order
for two servings of pasta and parfaits?
Man, I'm starving.
When's it gonna get here?
I'm back.
Welcome back, Sena. How'd it go?
Did you find the studio?
Yeah.
They'd said they liked me.
That's amazing!
So many girls explode with popularity
after modeling for that magazine!
It's basically the entryway to idolhood!
I see.
They might even ask you
to be their exclusive model!
You're getting ahead of yourself.
Let me introduce you.
This is Aozono Sena, a member of the agency.
She's my classmate in high school.
Nice to meet you.
This is our new member, Lilly-san.
I-I haven't decided if I wanted to join yet!
Yeah, Toko's a hard one to shake.
Glad to work with you, Lilly.
It's, um, my pleasure.
Delivery from Café Love-Love!
Coming!
It's here.
Kabappy?
Oh, do you like Kabappy?
Sort of, yes.
You do? Me too!
Neat.
Alright, you two!
Let's dig in!
It looks so good!
Where's my food?
Sorry, didn't get you any.
Can we split your pasta, then?
That was the plan.
I know how much you like this.
Some parfait too.
Alright, fine.
Being in an agency is actually...
kind of fun.
It's not just fun and games.
We're serious about this.
Yeah.
I want to give it a try.
You do?!
Thank goodness!
Let's do this together!
So what do I have to do as an idol?
I'm home!
Welcome home, Fuu.
Phew, I had a blast!
Really? What were you up to?
Hmm... well, you see...
It's a secret!
Did something good happen to her?
Dinner will be ready soon!
Okay!
Uguisu, today sure was full of fun, wasn't it?
I'm beat.
I had so much fun.
I got to perform out of nowhere,
and ended up joining an agency.
I forgot Kabappy at the agency!
Klutz.
Whatever. Time to sleep.
Good night.
Su-Sugar Sugarly La Lu Sugarin'
I'll coat even your sighs in sugar
Even the same old bustling intersection
Comments (2525)
Amazing performance
I'm sold
That was adorable!
What a surprise~
What's going on?!
So cute!!
That was great!
That transformation is crazy
That was breathtaking
Amazing performance
I'm sold
That was adorable!
What a surprise~
What's going on?!
So cute!!
That was great!
That transformation is crazy
That was breathtaking
Comments (2525)
That transformation was crazy
That was breathtaking
Just the cutest!!
I'm glad I watched
Didn't know Shibuno 106 could transform like that
Fantastic performance
Stunningly amazing!
Went back to normal after so it's prob just part of the show
So Lilly...
really did just debut today.
And she still gave such
an amazing performance...
Wow...
It all seemed like a fairy tale on the screen
Something far, far away...
I used to love singing, a long time ago.
I made a wish to the stars
Up in the twinkling sky
The clouds in the sky are so fluffy
Just like cotton candy
You're so good, big sis!
Can you sing more?
Okay!
Fuu, let's sing together!
But one day, just as
I was about to head to school...
Rui?
What's the matter?
Are you feeling sick?
Do you have a fever?
I'm... okay...
Good...bye.
Rui?
Rui?!
I fell sick and went
to the hospital for a long time.
I couldn't even go to school.
It's okay. I'm all better now.
But...
All the time I spent alone
after I got sick
became a part of me
somewhere along the way.
Hey, big sis!
Wanna play?
Sorry.
I think I forgot how to sing too.
But Lilly's song made my heart throb.
It's as if those emotions
I've forgotten are coming back.
So I...
Want to give it a try, then?
Yeah.
Darn, I overslept.
Morning, big sis.
Good morning, Fuu.
B-Big sis?
That...
It's a real mountain.
Looks delicious to me!
I had no idea Rui liked anko paste that much.
Well, she was raised in a confectionery shop.
Did you see it yesterday?
I did!
Morning!
I watched it over and over again!
What'cha talking about?
There was this amazing show
in Shibuya yesterday!
By this girl named CompatoLilly!
Her performance was super cool!
She's this mystery idol, right?
Yeah! Her livestream was super big
and went viral!
She was just so cute!
I want to be just like her!
Oh, I'm not all that...
Uhh, I haven't heard about that!
You haven't? Are you living under a rock?
It's almost time for class!
They still haven't revealed anything about Lilly.
I guess that's how they're marketing her.
No one knows her real name or age either.
Oh... Now I'm even more invested in her!
Her singing is so good,
and she's so cute.
I could listen to her forever.
Me too!
Alright.
That's not right.
Let's try...
How about this?
Shota, since our club is off next week,
wanna go out somewhere?
Right before the end-of-term exam? No way.
You'll be fine, man.
Are you studying at all, Kadoya?
Nope!
Well, you should.
Anyways, I'm so curious
about that girl from yesterday.
That I agree with.
Nonoyama?
What on earth is she doing?
Beats me.
Hey, Nonoyama!
What are you...
Off she goes.
What's gotten into her?
I read up a bit at the library.
A lot about magic is still
beyond our understanding.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
But I figured I'd prepare some
before I start casting magic.
Big sis!
I took in these cats!
I see!
They're very cute.
Azuki, I'm Rui. Nice to meet you.
So your name is Rui!
What a cute name.
I am not an ordinary cat.
I come from a magical land.
Y-You're... talking...?
Everything I say must stay a secret
between us, okay?
Even from your family.
Rui, you can use magic.
If you have strong feelings,
you can use magic.
I could tell from the moment
I met you before.
I'm sorry for startling you.
I believe you will cast wonderful spells.
So would you like to give it a try?
I...
I can't do it.
I understand.
Then I'll go back to being a cat.
I wonder if we have any black curtains at home.
As for the offering...
should I go with some confectioneries?
Offering?
It was in the book I read.
They say preparation is key for casting magic,
so, since it's my first time,
I want to make sure I get it right.
Really?
Let's get back!
I'm home.
What's going on here?!
This is what you meant by preparing?
Yeah. I read up about it.
I think she has the wrong idea...
I'll leave it be.
I'm ready.
Let's begin, Azuki!
Are you sure about this?
I've been thinking it over since then.
I think I really do want to sing.
Do you remember the words I taught you?
Yeah.
Letto.
Lululila pululila!
Pop'n pam!
You're beautiful!
Is this...
me?
Courage is in two worlds, yeah, together now
(Proof!)
It's what binds us together
Everyone smiles at the beautiful girls
(My dream!)
I just wanna know what the future holds
(Alone!)
Even if the stars in a moonless sky
Still twinkle
(No magic!)
Even if the clouds in a sunless sky
Still drift
I feel so lonely
(I was always right beside you)
I'm searching for you
I'll frame a photo of us two and hang it up
Let's set things the way we want, the way we will, the way they are
Take our chemistry, plus+, minus-, multiplied×, divided÷ by...
I love it every way
Calling me, calling you
(And you)
I want to walk up the stairs of the future with you
Lucky lucky shiny, our beating hearts dreamin' away
If there's clear skies tomorrow, everything will be okay
Maybe I'm a bit sad and weak
(But I'm happy!)
But when I'm with you I feel safe
There's no such thing as wasted time
Let's wait until the rain stops
Check it out, look up at the sky
Courage is in two worlds, yeah, together now
(Proof!)
That's what binds us together
Everyone smiles at the beautiful girls
What kind of future will the spotlight shine on?
Lulu Comes to Visit