Bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae
Bae, bae, bae
Bubee, bubee
Bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae
Ooh, ooh, ooh
You're my little buddy
Magical Sisters LuluttoLilly
Hey, bubee love
Bubee, bubee, bubee love
Magical Sisters LuluttoLilly
My heart is racing like crazy
And right before my eyes
Are the colors of a brand new world
Whoa
Stay with me today
We'll walk hand in hand
Dreaming of the place where we can become light
I can hear the magic
I wanna sing with you
Let's sing together
You're a bright shining star
My bubee, bubee, bubee love
We can be shining stars
Forever and ever
That's our secret magic
My bubee, bubee, bubee love
Ooh, ooh, ooh
You're my little buddy
Hey, bubee love
Bubee, bubee, bubee love
Bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae, bae
Bae, bae, bae
Bubee, bubee
B-U-B-E-E, bubee
Bubee love
The Day I Reached for the Stars
Morning, big sis.
Good morning, Fuu.
I had a weird dream.
I see.
FURYU
CONFECTIONERY
I should check up on the kids soon.
Sounds good.
You're still not dressed?
Good morning, Mom!
At least you can give a first-class greeting.
Thank you for breakfast.
You're leaving already, Rui?
I have classroom duties.
It's hot out, so stay safe, okay?
I will.
Goodbye, Mom.
Take care.
Fuu, hurry up and get to school!
I know...
Bye, Mom!
Big sis!
Wanna go to the pool with me
over summer break?
Is that a no?
I need to use my break
to catch up on my studies.
Studying over your break?
You're such a hard worker.
See you later.
Later!
Darn, I really wanted to
go to the pool with her...
S-Sorry!
Hey, Fuu.
Oh, Sho-chan!
You never change, huh?
Good morning!
Mornin'.
How's Rui doing?
She's great!
Ahh... good to hear.
You wanna play with me
over summer break?
You can teach me basketball!
Whoa there.
No can do. My club's got a game.
Aww...
See ya.
Aw, man. No one has any time
to play with me.
It wasn't always this way...
I made a wish to the stars
Big sis would always sing for me.
Up in the twinkling sky
Beyond the fluffy clouds
Rui?!
But then she got sick
and went to the hospital,
and lost her spirit.
I think she's all healed up now,
but still...
Where did everyone go?
I'm so lonely...
Just when summer break
is around the corner...
Fuu-chan!
Hurry up, or we'll be late.
M-Morning!
As you'll remember from our observation,
tadpoles hatch from frog eggs.
Birth of fish
Himedaka
Egg
So how do you think that medaka fish are born?
They also hatch from eggs.
Birth of fish
Himedaka
Female
Male
Egg
Birth!
We're going to observe medaka in a tank...
Is that a spaceship?
Are the aliens here to abduct me
from my boredom?
There's no way.
It really is a spaceship!
Please, come over here!
Wait up!
Nonoyama-san?
Nonoyama-san!
Sensei, look outside!
Egg
There's nothing there.
A spaceship just passed by, I swear!
Did you see it?
Nope. Didn't see nothing.
Nonoyama-san, please take your seat.
Sorry.
Let's resume the lesson.
Hey, wanna go do karaoke after this?
Sure, I'd love to!
Same place?
Yeah!
Let's ask Rui-chan.
Yeah.
Wanna join us, Nonoyama-san?
Rui-chan, we're doing karaoke! You in?
Sorry, I don't really sing.
Darn.
I see. I forgot you don't
like noisy places.
We'll hang out some other time.
Sorry again.
See you tomorrow!
See you tomorrow.
What's the matter, Fuu-chan?
I swear, I really saw one.
You mean the spaceship?
Are you still looking for it?
I mean, that thing was huge!
How did no one else see it?
Like, it was this big!
And it went right up past the window!
Are you sure?
We didn't see it.
How? It flew right past us—
Those are funny-looking cats.
What was that for?
Take it easy.
I'll handle the deliveries tomorrow.
Are you sure?
Of course. It's hot out.
Aww, you.
Thank you for dinner.
Hey, big sis!
Anything fun happen at school?
I have a super big story!
Today, huh?
Well, my homeroom teacher...
Yeah?
...said it was his birthday today.
Ooh! Go on!
That's about it, I think.
Oh, okay.
What's your "super big story," Fuu?
It's nothing, actually.
I see.
I'm going to go take a bath.
Okay!
Why don't you go with her?
I'm good.
Didn't they usually bathe together?
Guess she's growing up.
Am not...
Slow down, big sis!
I made a wish to the stars
It was a dream...
I made a wish to...
I want to hear big sis sing again...
Fuu!
I'm up!
2 meters of red ribbon costs ¥32.
Cost
Length
1 m length
How to Multiply Decimals
1.6 meters of blue ribbon also costs ¥32.
1 m length
What is the price of 1 meter each
of red and blue ribbon?
1 m length
No sign of it.
Let's start with the red ribbon.
To get the price of 1 meter,
you divide the cost by the length.
If I run into it again,
maybe things will change.
You going anywhere for summer break?
I'm going to my grandma's house
by the beach!
Aw, that sounds nice!
What about you?
I dunno... maybe the beach too!
Later!
See you tomorrow!
Oh, uh, bye!
Please, spaceship, come here again!
I'm begging you!
It's back!
Wait up!
The view here is just wonderful.
It's so hot...
They call this "summer!"
Take a look. The sun is about to set.
Let's see here.
Hup.
How beautiful!
It's so bright.
Oh?
There's a child chasing after us.
Please, wait for me!
It's the one from yesterday.
That little brat!
Strange. Humans shouldn't be able
to see this ship.
Wait for me!
What's going on?
Please stop!
I'm almost there...
Oh no!
Owie...
That was a close call.
Those cats from yesterday!
Who are you?
Are you okay?
They're talking!
Yes we are.
I actually made it
on the spaceship...
Ehem.
Who would you be?
I'm Nonoyama Fuu.
Is this really a spaceship?
It's a magic ship.
I am Meeter. I come from the magical land Felix Star.
We're visiting this planet—
Um, I...
I had to make it onto this ship, because...
the way things are going,
big sis, Sho-chan,
and everyone else is gonna grow up
and move on,
and leave me behind...
I just want big sis to smile more,
but I don't know how to help her.
So...
You want things to change, do you?
If you have strong feelings,
you can cast magic.
Want to give it a try?
Yes!
So cute...
This is a Glass Heart,
the source of your magic.
Humans can only cast magic
for one year.
And you cannot let any other humans
find out about your magic.
Not even my mom and dad?
Or my sister...?
No one.
So long as you follow the rules,
you can make something wonderful of your magic.
Now I would like to see your wish.
How do I use it?
Give it a tap and say "litto."
Litto!
A magic wand?
Now use the wand
and chant the magic words.
Those words are up to you.
Give it a go.
Okay.
Lililula palilula!
Pam pam power!
I'm all tall now!
You transformed into your ideal self!
You look great!
You can use that wand
to cast any kind of spell.
Any kind, you say?
As long as you truly wish for it.
That spaceship sure stands out.
Other humans can't see it!
Oh, I see.
What kind of spell should I cast?
I think it should be something
that everyone will enjoy!
Lililula palilula,
fill the sky with great big fireworks!
What the?
Is there a fireworks show going on?
Haven't heard of any.
Hey, Rui! Look outside!
You'll be amazed!
What is it?
It's beautiful...
The spell ended.
That was great.
Not bad.
Fantastic job.
Well done for your first spell.
It was a beautiful display.
You think so?
I do.
I'd better be on my way now.
I'll leave those two with you
in case anything happens.
Hey!
If you have any questions, just ask them.
We're happy to help.
So you're leaving already?
No matter what, you must keep
your magic a secret from other humans.
Farewell.
We shall meet again in one year's time
at the Festival of Magic.
The test of all magic?
It's so dark! I gotta get home!
How do I turn back?
Just say "tohri!"
Tohri!
Are there any spells
to get me home quickly?
Or to make me fly?
If you mess it up, you'll fall.
Whoa, that's no good!
I'm home!
Please let me keep them!
I'll do tons of chores
and finish all my homework!
What do you think?
They're funny-looking cats,
but it seems fine to me.
As long as you take care of them.
Thank you so much, Mom and Dad!
What will you name them?
Azuki and Uguisu!
Good choice.
Oh yeah, did you see, Fuu?
There were fireworks going off earlier.
Y-Yup, I saw them!
I'm gonna go change.
Wrong way, Azuki.
What is it?
Big sis!
I took in these cats!
I see!
They're very cute.
There were these great big fireworks
in the sky earlier. Did you see them?
Yeah.
They were beautiful.
Things are about to get a lot more fun!
Courage is in two worlds, yeah, together now
(Proof!)
It's what binds us together
Everyone smiles at the beautiful girls
(My dream!)
I just wanna know what the future holds
(Alone!)
Even if the stars in a moonless sky
Still twinkle
(No magic!)
Even if the clouds in a sunless sky
Still drift
I feel so lonely
(I was always right beside you)
I'm searching for you
I'll frame a photo of us two and hang it up
Let's set things the way we want, the way we will, the way they are
Take our chemistry, plus+, minus-, multiplied×, divided÷ by...
I love it every way
Calling me, calling you
(And you)
I want to walk up the stairs of the future with you
Lucky lucky shiny, our beating hearts dreamin' away
If there's clear skies tomorrow, everything will be okay
Maybe I'm a bit sad and weak
(But I'm happy!)
But when I'm with you I feel safe
There's no such thing as wasted time
Let's wait until the rain stops
Check it out, look up at the sky
Courage is in two worlds, yeah, together now
(Proof!)
That's what binds us together
Everyone smiles at the beautiful girls
What kind of future will the spotlight shine on?
Nice to Meet You, I'm Lilly!