Morning, Uguisu.
Oh, right! I can use magic now!
It wasn't a dream!
I know!
Fortune in wealth
We're going out to play, Uguisu!
Huh? Where?
The city!
Babe, babe, babe, babe, babe, babe, babe, babe, babe
Babe, babe, babe
Bubee, bubee
Babe, babe, babe, babe, babe, babe, babe, babe, babe
Ooh, ooh, ooh
You're my little buddy
Hey, bubee love
Bubee, bubee, bubee love
My heart is racing like crazy
And right before my eyes
Are the colors of a brand new world
Woah
Stay with me today
We'll walk hand in hand
Dreaming of the place where we can become light
I can hear the magic
I wanna sing with you
Let's sing together
You're a bright shining star
My bubee, bubee, bubee love
We can be shining stars
Forever and ever
That's our secret magic
My bubee, bubee, bubee love
Ooh, ooh, ooh
You're my little buddy
Hey, bubee love
Bubee, bubee, bubee love
Babe, babe, babe, babe, babe, babe, babe, babe, babe
Babe, babe, babe
Bubee, bubee
B-U-B-E-E, bubee
Bubee love
Nice to Meet You, I'm Lilly!
Morning!
Good morning.
Fuu, you're up early for a Sunday.
Morning, Dad! I'm gonna go out to play!
Where to? A friend's house?
Oh, Azuki!
Were you with big sis this whole time?
She was.
She's gotten attached to me.
Is that okay with you?
Yeah. She's cute.
Gotcha.
Good for you, Azuki!
Big sis, can I...?
What is it?
Those fireworks last night...
What was that all about?
I don't know.
They sure were amazing though.
They were amazing, weren't they?
Come eat breakfast, Fuu.
Okie-dokie!
You coming with, Azuki?
She wants to stay home.
Then off I go!
Welcome in!
Take care!
I've always wanted to go out into the city
wearing something pretty when I grew up!
First off, I wanna try a crepe!
Why's that?
Because when I told Dad
I wanted a crepe,
he gave me a dorayaki instead!
All because we run a confectionery.
Isn't that unfair?!
What's the difference?
All of it!
Though I haven't had it before.
Wowie!
It's so cool!
So crowded... Scary...
I gotta find somewhere to transform...
Hey.
No one can find out about my magic, right?
Right. Else you'll explode.
Y-You're kidding!
Then how should I...
So cute!
Excuse me!
Yes! Would you like to try on some clothes?
Is it okay if I try on this dress?
It might be a bit big for you...
That won't be a problem.
I'll grow into it in a sec!
Litto!
I like it!
Does it look good?
Sure, I guess.
I knew it.
Can I buy this and keep it on?
C-Certainly. You look great in it.
Thanks!
Thank you for shopping!
That worked perfectly!
What a handful.
I'm so happy! I've always wanted to wear
mature clothes like this!
Let's go have some fun!
One creamy crepe, please!
Time to dig in!
You've got cream on your face.
Want to try it, Uguisu?
Take a big bite!
Are you okay staying behind?
You must like being at home, huh?
You're just like me.
Though it wasn't always this way...
Where's Fuu off playing right now?
I turned her invite to the pool down.
I just can't do it.
Right.
I should learn more about you.
t
ta
tak
taki
takin
taking
taking c
taking ca
taking car
taking care
taking care o
taking care of
taking care of f
taking care of fi
taking care of fir
taking care of firs
taking care of first
taking care of first c
taking care of first ca
taking care of first cat
Hey, it's Kabappy!
I want one...
Again.
Again!
Lililula palilula...
Win the stuffie!
Why?
You stink.
You're so useless, magic!
Why didn't it work?
If you truly wish for it,
it'll come true.
But I did truly want it!
Magic's a lot more worthless
than I thought.
Aw man...
I thought I'd be able to do anything.
Say what?!
What's going on here?
My drink turned into a stuffie!
That's your magic.
Huh?
So the spell I cast before
only just activated?
Though it looks a bit different
from Kabappy...
Whatever.
What should I do next?
I've basically done everything I wanted to...
I can't think of anything else.
What haven't I done yet?
Hey, Uguisu.
What should I do after this?
Go home?
No way!
I came out all this way.
I gotta do more things!
Like what?
I don't know. That's why I asked...
I got nothing.
There's gotta be something fun to do...
This girl...
She's perfect!
Mind if I sit with you?
Huh? Sure.
Thanks.
So, listen.
Yeah?
Wanna be an idol?
My name's Kandachi Toko.
Producer / Idol
PRODUCTION ONCE MORE
Production Once More?
Yeah. It's my own agency.
What, you're the founder?!
Yep.
It's fresh, so we don't have
a lot of talent yet...
This is one of our performances.
I'm an idol myself!
Wow, you really are!
I have a dream.
I want to be recognized as a great idol by all!
Once I do that, I know I can change the world!
Oh really? Good luck with that!
And I know I can do it with you on my side!
Please, I could never!
Only super cool people become idols, right?
My grades are pretty average,
and I always mess up my chores.
You have this curious charm about you, though.
Aw, you think so?
Though now that I talk to you,
you also seem kind of childish.
But that contrast is just cute!
Becoming an idol will turn your life upside down.
You'll get to experience so many exciting things,
and maybe catch the eye of a loved one.
Really?
Yeah!
The moment I laid my eyes on you,
I thought, "this is the one!"
If we work together,
I know things will start to shift.
Will you do it?
Do you think...
I can do it?
I know you can!
Also, you'll get to eat
a lot of yummy things as an idol!
And wear all the cute clothes
your heart desires!
You like the sound of that?
Oh, I do!
I like your honesty.
Is this a good idea?
It's fine.
Let's get a move on!
What is this place?
The stage of our next performance...
Uh-huh?
Starring you.
Huh?
I was actually supposed to perform,
but you're perfect for this!
What?!
I messaged you about this before.
This girl is our agency's promising new idol!
Oh, right. You mentioned a change to the casting.
Pleased to work with you.
Huh?!
H-Hold on a minute! I haven't even...
What's your name?
I'm...
Lilly.
Lilly?
Could use a bit more oomph...
Anything you like?
Like a favorite snack?
I guess konpeito?
Good, we'll roll with that.
Your stage name will be...
CompatoLilly!
What?!
It's time to go live.
Please get on standby.
Thanks for waiting!
It's time for the
Shibu-Yeahhh Teens Meeting
to get on the road!
Oh no...
I know I agreed to this...
but I have no idea what I'm doing!
I mean, I can't go on stage!
I'm not ready for this...
Relax. Just sing whatever you want.
Come on!
Now, allow me to introduce
the idol making her grand debut!
CompatoLilly!
Have fun!
Break a leg!
N-Nice to meet you, I'm Lilly!
I h-hope you enjoy...
Hey, not over there!
Move up front!
Huh? What?
Ouch!
Darn it, I messed up...
What do I do?
I knew I wasn't cut out to be an idol...
Relax! Now sing!
Big sis, I can't sing very good...
Relax!
Fuu, let's sing together!
I've got this.
After all, doing this was my decision.
I may as well have fun doing it!
Just like when I used to sing
with my big sis!
Lililula palilula!
Pam pam power!
What is she doing...?
So cute!
Let's get it on!
What a crowd.
Looks like some concert.
I take off my sneakers, feeling I've grown
Bout to head out in my new fit
Earrings dangling, lip gloss on
Somehow dazzling even inside
It all seemed like a fairy tale on a screen
Something far, far away I could never reach
But I leap onto the crossing, perhaps I'll find my love
And cast a spell on you
Sing with me
Su-Sugar Sugarly La Lu Sugarin'
I'll coat even your sighs in sugar
Even the same old bustling intersection
Can become a stage with a touch of magic
Su-Sugar Sugarly La Lu Sugarin'
President, I've found her.
Every lost gaze, come to me
She's the one!
I'll stuff a balloon full of sparkly lights
And create a wonderland
That was crazy cool!
Thank you, everyone!
You did it.
Did I do good?
Did you do good?! Look!
All those people came to watch!
You did fantastic!
That's great!
Your performance blew my expectations away!
It was so magical!
I could see the world changing
right in front of me!
Now that I have you,
I think I can dream even greater than before.
So let's keep at this together!
I appreciate all of that,
but I don't know...
I messed up on stage,
and I'm not sure if
I really want to or not.
Then how about we go eat
something yummy like I promised?
Remember? I said you'd get
to eat a lot as an idol.
Hooray!
Thank you for your support!
Shota, look, it's her!
The girl on the stage!
This way, Lilly!
She's so cute...!
Her smile is everything
That was super fun!
I'm glad I watched~
So energizing!
Amazing performance
Is she really a newbie?!
Who is this girl?!
That was adorable...!
Seated for the next stream!
She's got my support!
New oshi unlocked!
That was so cute~
Talk about an earworm!
She's so cute...!
Her smile is everything
That was super fun!
I'm glad I watched~
So energizing!
Amazing performance
Is she really a newbie?!
Who is this girl?!
That was adorable...!
Seated for the next stream!
She's got my support!
New oshi unlocked!
That was so cute~
Talk about an earworm!
Chat
I...
want to do that too...
Courage is in two worlds, yeah, together now
(Proof!)
It's what binds us together
Everyone smiles at the beautiful girls
(My dream!)
I just wanna know what the future holds
(Alone!)
Even if the stars in a moonless sky
Still twinkle
(No magic!)
Even if the clouds in a sunless sky
Still drift
I feel so lonely
(I was always right beside you)
I'm searching for you
I'll frame a photo of us two and hang it up
Let's set things the way we want, the way we will, the way they are
Take our chemistry, plus+, minus-, multiplied×, divided÷ by...
I love it every way
Calling me, calling you
(And you)
I want to walk up the stairs of the future with you
Lucky lucky shiny, our beating hearts dreamin' away
If there's clear skies tomorrow, everything will be okay
Maybe I'm a bit sad and weak
(But I'm happy!)
But when I'm with you I feel safe
There's no such thing as wasted time
Let's wait until the rain stops
Check it out, look up at the sky
Courage is in two worlds, yeah, together now
(Proof!)
That's what binds us together
Everyone smiles at the beautiful girls
What kind of future will the spotlight shine on?
When I Look Up to the Moon