This is Snack World, the hallowed
ground of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam and
people have handy smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
...And my name's Chup.
My village was burnt down by the evil
land-destroying merchant, Vinegar Khan,
and I've embarked on a journey
to get my revenge 1000-fold!
The tickets to King Oyster City, where
Vinegar is, cost 20 million gillan.
So I'm on an adventure searching for
big treasure to make loads of cash!
[Chup humming theme song]
Alright, let's go on another big adventure today!
Is it true, you've yet again failed to defeat the Phoenix?
Ep. 15: The Little Match Mayone
We're sorry...
- Oink...
How's Melora doing with her illness?
We regret to tell you that time has run out.
[All gasp]
Please take a look.
[Melora grunting]
- Ahh!
Doesn't she seem super healthy?
What's she doing?
Boxercise.
Oh, Melora!
I've been feeling plump around my rear end because I've been sleeping away for a while!
Hyah!
So, where has "time run out?"
Her condition is sort of like that of a candle burning brightly just before it goes out.
That means that the fire that is Melora's life is about to disappear.
Huh?! Princess Melora's life?!
Uh, isn't she just recovering fine?
Oh, you're very precious, my darling Melora!
She's clearly moving very well!
Princess Melora!!
What is he using this opportunity for?!
Princess Melora!
Melora, my Melora!
Her response time is astounding.
She's a lot healthier than when she first fell ill.
Chup, we can't keep up!
You can't expect me to be calm seeing Princess Melora like that!
I understand how you feel,
but if we rush into this, there's no way we'll win.
It's like my grandmother said!
Strike while the stove is hot, and the noodles will be plump!
Hold the green onions and bean sprouts.
Strike while the
stove is hot,
and the noodles
will be plump!
Strike while the
stove is hot,
and the noodles
will be plump!
Hold the
green onions
and bean
sprouts.
Hold the
green onions
and bean
sprouts.
-Tome
"Hold the green onions?" You're a madman!
Though it's not like we can rush out there anyways, can we?
Mayone, what's the matter with you?
We're running low on travelling funds,
and if we don't find out the secret of Phoenix's Eternal Life and get rewarded, we can't keep staying at the inn.
Really?
But how long will the rest of our money last?
This is what I'm talking about! You're buying and eating!!
But I haven't been wasting any of my money at all..
Those cards are a waste!! When did you even buy those?!
Now, now! It's not like adventures cost money, hehehe.
Don't say that while looking at your porn movie bills!
At any rate, no more buying and eating!
No more Melora merch!
No more billing sites!
Come on...
That's not fair.
No complaints. Heed my warning, or you lose the pet too.
Oink!! Oink-oink...
Butako isn't a pet, she's our friend!
I wasn't talking about Butako, I was talking about that big green pet over there!
Who are you calling a pet?!
Gob-san isn't a pet either!!
He's just an old guy that follows us around!
Agh.. Is that what you think about me?
You're so stingy!
I'm not stingy, I'm saving money.
Mayone, I think I understand.
Huh?
Don't you waste your money on things too, Mayone?
What? You can't badmouth me like that!
Well then, what exactly is that jara?
Guh.
Oh, you're right! She has more jara equipped we haven't seen!
That must be Britannia Enchant's Pink Panther!
That's not one that comes cheap!
B-but it was on sale..
It's still quite an extremely costly splurge compared to my porn site bills.
It's unfair, Mayone. If you can buy that, I should be able to buy Princess Melora's 10-year premium calendar set!
And I should be allowed to buy a large top-class beef!
And I wanna visit the eating house with the beautiful hostess whenever I want!
Stop trying to gang up on me for this!
I bought this as a counter-measure for the Phoenix.
Did you really?
I mean it! It's this cool staff that boosts my magical abilities.
So that means you can beat the Phoenix, is that right?
Huh?
You oughta show us what your pricy staff can do!
Uh.. no, that's a...
Welp, off to Macaroni Mountains we go!
Ho!
That's a lot of weight on my shoulders...
Hah.. How many times have we scaled this mountain?
It's been 4 times.
Y'know, today'd be a really good day to just ride on Butako's back.
No matter how many times you ask, she still doesn't have a permit to carry people!
Well, if you're gonna keep saying that, when will you get her a permit?
Ever since we met I've been convinced she's failing flight training.
Oink...
Ahahahaha!
Huh?
Aha, aha, aha! Ahahaha!
You aren't gettin' past me, bear!
Scram, Monster!
Who is this fella anyhow?
Mah name's Zombie Kuma! What'cha gonna do, bear?
Zombie Kuma
Bear?
Hold it, rewind a little.
Mayone, what's the matter?
- Bear?
Say your name one more time.
I'm Zombie Kuma!
Does "Zombie Kuma" mean you're a zombie?
Bingo, I'm a zombie, bear!
Hmmm?
[Sighs]
Alright, all of you take a seat.
What are you doing..?
Ey, what about the battle, bear?!
You join them too!
Uh-.. bear..
Class, today, I'd like to teach you about zombies.
Where'd all that come from?
Mayone, do you know a lot about zombies?
Zombies
Have you never heard me talk about them?
I've probably watched the most zombie movies out of anyone in the world.
Zombies
And I own the complete DVD set for the zombie drama The Hiking Dead.
I lined up at 5 A.M. a whole day early just to shake hands with the actors.
Plus, I dress up as a zombie every Halloween!
You sure are a huge zombie enthusiast.
I have a question for you all.
Don't you find there's anything strange about this Monster being called a zombie?
I know!
Yes, Chup!
He's got a lot of energy!
That's right!
Heheh...
- Ooh!
Zombies have always been corpses.
It'd be weird for someone dead to have a lot of energy!
ENERGETIC
I
Huh...?
- Oh yes, that makes sense.
Now, anyone else?
Me! He moves around very quick for a zombie.
Yep, that's correct!
Ahahaha...
- Bear..
One of a zombie's most important traits is the way one slowly creeps up on you!
ENERGETIC
If you don't take care of that, you could never call yourself a zombie.
I.. I see, bear...
CUTE
Would you describe yourself as cute and cuddly?
Aw, well, I wouldn't..
Agh, that's awful!
- Huh?
Zombies.. shouldn't feel.. emotions!!
CUTE
I
That said, don't you feel you're generally made to look like something children would like?
I think I was a plush toy before I became a zombie..
Really?
If you were a plush toy, weren't you never alive at all?
How could you have even become a zombie anyhow?
I hate when people like you try to loosen the rules.
Mayone, you're being a bit rough.
Introducing yourself as a zombie but half-assing the role..
I could never allow this!
Half-assing the role...
Zombies are supposed to be unpleasant and terrifying.
If you can't even figure that one out, you have no right to call yourself one!
NO POINT
IN FIGHTING
So there's no point in fighting you! Understood?
NO POINT
IN FIGHTING
I
NO POINT
IN FIGHTING
I
NO POINT
IN FIGHTING
I
NO POINT
IN FIGHTING
I
NO POINT
IN FIGHTING
I
NO POINT
IN FIGHTING
I
NO POINT
IN FIGHTING
I
NO POINT
IN FIGHTING
I
NO POINT
IN FIGHTING
I
NO POINT
IN FIGHTING
I
NO POINT
IN FIGHTING
I
NO POINT
IN FIGHTING
I
NO POINT
IN FIGHTING
I
NO POINT
IN FIGHTING
I
NO POINT
IN FIGHTING
I
NO POINT
IN FIGHTING
I
NO POINT
IN FIGHTING
I
NO POINT
IN FIGHTING
I
NO POINT
IN FIGHTING
I
S-seriously?
Zombies don't cry!!
They would walk all over you in the zombie world for that!
Mayone, you're really going a bit far.
If it doesn't concern you, Goblin, can it.
Question: What do you, as a zombie, do when you encounter a human?
I guess I'd make them afraid of me and then finish them off and then...
Disqualified.
- Huh?
Zombies don't feel things at all.
All they do is loiter around and instinctively search for human flesh.
That's to say that the moment you start blabbering around, you're no good as a zombie.
I'm.. sorry, bear.
Zombies don't apologize.
I'd also like to question why you end your sentences with "bear."
You take a lot more from your bear side than as a zombie.
I'm sorry.
How many times do I have to say zombies don't apologize?!
APOLOGETIC
CUTE
NO POINT
IN FIGHTING
ENERGETIC
END SENTENCES IN "BEAR"
I
APOLOGETIC
CUTE
NO POINT
IN FIGHTING
ENERGETIC
END SENTENCES IN "BEAR"
I
APOLOGETIC
CUTE
NO POINT
IN FIGHTING
ENERGETIC
END SENTENCES IN "BEAR"
I
APOLOGETIC
CUTE
NO POINT
IN FIGHTING
ENERGETIC
END SENTENCES IN "BEAR"
I
APOLOGETIC
CUTE
NO POINT
IN FIGHTING
ENERGETIC
END SENTENCES IN "BEAR"
I
APOLOGETIC
CUTE
NO POINT
IN FIGHTING
ENERGETIC
END SENTENCES IN "BEAR"
I
APOLOGETIC
CUTE
NO POINT
IN FIGHTING
ENERGETIC
END SENTENCES IN "BEAR"
I
APOLOGETIC
CUTE
NO POINT
IN FIGHTING
ENERGETIC
END SENTENCES IN "BEAR"
I
APOLOGETIC
CUTE
NO POINT
IN FIGHTING
ENERGETIC
END SENTENCES IN "BEAR"
I
APOLOGETIC
CUTE
NO POINT
IN FIGHTING
ENERGETIC
END SENTENCES IN "BEAR"
I
APOLOGETIC
CUTE
NO POINT
IN FIGHTING
ENERGETIC
END SENTENCES IN "BEAR"
I
Guhh.. how do I become even more zombie-ish?
Good, that's the next part of our lesson.
Class, please stand.
The director of my favorite zombie drama once said:
"Zombie movement is sort of like the way a guy drudges out of a bar drunk at 3 A.M."
Picture that in your head.
3 A.M..
I'd be sleepy...
Snap to it!
No good, you still seem alive and well. Act more dead!
That's a fiddly order...
Good work, Gob-san!
Wha? I haven't done anything yet.
Come on, guys, move like you don't have any muscles!
More, you're still very energetic! Especially let your shoulders go blahhh...
Blah...
Not your mouths!!
Uhh...
- Hm?
I don't have shoulders.
[Sigh] Doesn't matter. You can compensate with your facial expression.
The key to your expression is your eyes.
Just one glance will tell you how smart someone is.
Let them go off on their own.
Off on their own...
Guh-hah!
- Too fast!
Zombies are slow, and their mouths go blah!
Blah...
You don't say it!
Look at that!
- Huh?
Hm?
- Gob-san, you're a natural!
I told you, I'm not doing anything!
Good work, class!
You've all shown great progress!
No matter how you look at Gob-san, he just screams "zombie!"
Me?!
Your appearance, the grotesque color and texture, it's perfect!
She really isn't kidding.
Have you ever considered being a zombie instead?
Not a chance! Never in hell am I taking the job of a zombie.
Um, how did I do?
Umm.. awful, actually. You don't have the talent to be a zombie at all.
Gah!
Maybe you should take out "Zombie" from your name.
...Ehh?
Zombie Kuma without Zombie would just be..
Kuma?
Right. From now on, you will introduce yourself as "Kuma!"
N-no way.. I'm no Monster anymore.. or anything...
The Phoenix has come out.
Doesn't seem to have noticed we're here yet.
This is our chance!
Oi! Listen here, Phoenix!
Why did you draw attention to us?!
Here it comes!
Alright, everyone, become zombies!
Blahh...
- What?!
We weren't supposed to turn into zombies!!
You think we're gonna put up with this anymore?
Today's the day you go fully, flawlessly down!
Thanks to Mayone!
Me?!
Isn't that why you bought the staff?
Now you can show us the power of your expensive staff, Mayone!
Don't leave me by myself, we have to fight it together!
Mayone, you shouldn't be looking away!
Huh?!
[All screaming]
Where are we?
Another Fantasy?
I'm starving!
- Huh?
I'm starving, I'm starving!!
Be patient with me, Cornet.
This is my Fantasy...
Here's your dinner.
Aw, come on, bread crust again?
That's such a darn plain meal..
Mayone, your family was dirt-poor!
Gee, how modest of you to say.
I wanna eat meat, meat!
Cornet, remember we agreed on having meat every half a year?
Ugh, you're so stingy, sis!
I'm not stingy, I'm saving money.
I heard you say that remark earlier!
Her attitude about money must stem from her experiences here.
Mayone, Cornet, I'm so sorry.. I just haven't been working well lately...
Mama, don't worry about it, go rest. I'll do something about this.
Oh...
- Oink...
Would you like a match? Would you like a match?
She's the Little Match Girl..
Didn't think you had such a noble side to you, Mayone.
You're so much different from back then.
Care to explain how?
Would you like a match?
- Hah, selling matches? What year do you think this is?
I'm better off just buying a lighter instead!
[Mayone gasps]
I feel bad for her..
You wait right there.
Hm?
What school are you from? What grade and class?
What you just did can be described as obstruction of business.
If you ask for it, this can put you in court. Do you understand?
I...  I'm sorry!!
That really is Mayone.
So after this she became more talkative.
[Sigh] It's so cold...
I'm sure I can use just one of them.
Ow, hot!
Huh? Oh-- crap!!
What do I do?!
If this house burns down to the ground, we'll have to reimburse them in full!
But we don't have that kind of money... I'll be selling matches for life!
No-no, I can't possibly make that much with matches!
We'll lose our home and our family will be separated.. What to do, what to do...
Oink-oink!
- Huh?
Oink-oink-oink!
Mayone, Butako says she's seen this all before!
Huh?
This is where you and I first met!
Oh, that's right! After this..
Oh no, what do I do...
Aah! Huh? Thank goodness, the fire's out. But what..?
Butako, if you can't hold it in while you're flying, you'll never be licensed to carry humans.
Hold it in??
Agh, you're soaked! But if it makes you feel any better, you don't smell worse than normal humans.
So that wasn't water, but Butako's piss?!
Butako, apologize with me.
We're sorry.
- Oink-oink-oink.
See, we apologized anyways!
You didn't flip out at us then.
That's because I didn't realize I was soaked with her piss.
That's settled. It's like my grandmother said!
Don't sweat the small stuff. With my husband I've had enough.
Don't sweat the
small stuff.
With my husband
I've had enough.
Don't sweat the
small stuff.
With my husband
I've had enough.
-Tome
Uh. What does that mean?
I'm Chup, and this is my friend - the pig-looking-nosed Butako!
Oink-oink!
Butako, that's a strange name.
Aha, funny!
I'm Mayone, I sell matches!
Really? Aw, I got your matches all wet too.
You can't sell these.
Oh, I know! To make up for it..
You don't have to make up for it, I'm just glad you put out the fire...
Here you are.
What's this?
I picked it up during flight training.
I don't know what type of jewel it is, but it's pretty, so you can have it.
Th-thank you!
Later!
Ooh, the Fantasy is gone!
Yeah, it was because of Chup and Butako that fire didn't grow out of proportions!
You picked the wrong Fantasy, Phoenix!
Watch out!
- Aah!
Mayone?
Mama?!
Is this..?
This happened to me too!
The Phoenix's power is making the illusion a reality!
Mayone.. Please come home...
Without your work, our finances are in trouble...
Huh?
Mayone...
Sis!
Cornet!
Sis, please come home soon!
I'm starving, I wanna eat meat!!
Don't abandon us, Mayone..!
Mayone, are you alright?
[Cracking up] Yeah, better than alright!
Uh?
- Oink?
Thing is, Mama and Cornet aren't anything like this now.
Huh?
What?
[Phoenix warbling]
Didn't you even take a good look at my memories?
My family's not dirt-poor anymore. In fact, they're practically celebrities!
Celebrities?
But you were all living in poverty in that Fantasy...
Oh yeah, we were poor back then.
But then Chup gave me that pretty jewel!
And it was actually a super-rare gemstone!
Wait, it was?!
We sold it for a high price,
and Mama used the funds to start an online business!
And boy, did it skyrocket!
Now Mama's an industrialist considered one of the "10 People That Changed The World,"
and my brother Cornet is helping her out as her right-hand man.
You've got one amazing mother.
What an unexpected development.
If I had known how valuable that gemstone was, I'd have never given it away!!
Of course, I was very thankful for you, Chup, so I became your friend!
Who needs a gemstone when you've got a sorceress?
Eh, when did I get one of those?
She's right here next to you!!
Well, Phoenix.
I don't appreciate you digging out memories of mine I'd rather not see.
Pink Panther!
Pink Panther.
Prepare yourself!
Ooh, Mayone, you look so fired up to battle!
Though how are you going to take it down?
That Fantasy gave me an idea.
Butako!
- Oink!
Oink-oink!
I'm counting on you!
- Oink-oink!
Oink-oink-oink!
Oiiiink!
Goooo!
Oiiiiiiink!!
Butako stands no chance against the Phoenix's fire!
We can't fight fire with fire. We'll fight fire with water!
Butako, now!
Oink!
Take this, Phoenix!
Shiver!
Ohoho! You turned it into clumps of ice!
I've got it!
Drop Water Ice Attack!
Though it's really more number one..
Doesn't need a name to know we've won.
Phoenix, ready to accept defeat?
[Warbling]
Then tell us the secret to Eternal Life!
Quest
Get the Eternal Life
So this is the remedy for Eternal Life?
Quest
Get the Eternal Life
If you drink it, your body will become immortal.
Could I have just a little bit of it?
You can't, this is for Princess Melora!
I'm sure they won't mind a little!
It's not like I need the whole bottle.
Wait!
This label says it's Zombie Powder!
[Coughing]
Zombie Powder?!
[Spitting and coughing]
So to have an immortal body..
You have to become a zombie? We can't save Melora with this!
Ugh, forget about you!
Wait, don't!!
- Hm?
If you don't need that, can I take it off your hands?
Huh?
I want to become an even more genuine zombie!
konbini de kuda wo maku ukiyo wo samayou wakoudo yo
All you youngsters loitering about your lives,
shrouding the convenience stores
omaera wa genjitsu ni torinokosaresugi andeddo
You’re like undead who have left behind reality
itsumade son na koto kurikaesu no o-tsu-ka-re
How long are you going to keep doing this?
Don't you get tired of this same old routine?
hashiridase yo ENDLESS ROAD
Run forth through the endless road
koetemiroyo BORDERLINE
Go on past that borderline
sekai wa mugen ni hirogaru kouya
The world is an endless, limitless wilderness
omae no dokyou wo tameshiteiru
Where you can put your courage to the test
sumafo nankaja kensaku dekinai
It’s not something you can search for on your smartphone
sekai wa mugen ni hirogaru PARADISE
The world is an endless, limitless paradise
omaera wa giragira no
Soon you'll come to life taking in the blazing sun
taiyou kuratte ikiteiru
Raws
Translation/Typesetting/Timing
ED Karaoke
QC/Review
Raws
Translation/Typesetting/Timing
ED Karaoke
QC/Review
AnimeLand (BSJ)
Lumpstud
Noroino Hanako
(Specter Subs)
Jewelforest
AnimeLand (BSJ)
Lumpstud
Noroino Hanako
(Specter Subs)
Jewelforest
I'm so so sorry, your majesty!
We took down the Phoenix, but..
The secret to Eternal Life was actually Zombie Powder...
Uhh..  well, about all that...
Hmm-hmm!
- Huh?
She's even healthier than before.
If.. if she's this healthy now, does that mean she's closer to death than ever?
Uh, no, thing is..
I'm sorry, Princess Melora! I'm sorryyyy!!!
Chup!
- Oink!
So what's the deal here?
Yeah, the thing about her incurable illness was a big misunderstanding.
Misunderstanding?
[Both] Me!
Hold it, enough. Cut it out, you two!
As a matter of fact, my parents have decided who I'm marrying.
What?!
Then you have to cancel it now!
The wedding is next week, it's too late.
Huh?
IT'S TOO LAAAATE!!
It's... too late?!
T-t-t-too late?!
Waaah...  how awful!!
- Your majesty!!
This is unfair!!
I-i-it can't be good if the nurses are crying!!
Your majesty!
I've done all that I can. Girls, wait!!
Even the doctor threw in the towel!
Meeeloooraaa...
- Your majesty!!
Huuuh?! What kind of misunderstanding is that?
So Princess Melora was in perfect health the whole time.
Very sorry to have worried you lot so much.
Right, I'd also like all of the Clanarine equipment I entrusted you with back.
What?!
You mean you weren't just letting us have them?
Well, it might be a good idea to get a move on and let Chup know about the misunderstanding.
He's probably trying to join her in the afterlife right now...
No biggie. If it gets bad, I still have some Zombie Powder.
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone!
What are you teaching us today?
Today's lesson is about spells!
"Spells"
Spells are when you use magical powers to do fantastical moves.
You can use spells to
both attack opponents and support your teammates.
For example, I use a fire spell called "Flame-Poof".
And "Snooze" can put opponents to sleep.
I want to use such wicked cool spells too!
Next Time
Princess Melora's been kidnapped, and the culprit is... me?!
And the start of our adventure is revealed at last!
Next time: "Chup: The Beginning!"
Chup: The Beginning
...Wait, who's this guy?!