This is Snack World, the hallowed ground
of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam
and people have handy smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
And my name's Chup!
After a long battle,
I've finally defeated the evil merchant Vinegar Khan,
and now I'm moving towards a new goal!
Whatever perils await me,
I'll fully, flawlessly overcome them!
Alright, let's go on another big adventure today!
Episode 45: The Horrifying Scarzone
Scardon!
Stop right there, Scardon!
All clear?
Huh?
Isn't this...?
French Toaster?!
What? Why?!
Did Scardon warp us back?
Hold on.
Something seems off.
Man, we were right on Scardon's tail!
Now we have to start all over.
Oh! Let's go see Princess Melora first
then go after Scardon!
What? We can't go off course like that!
We have an important mission on our hands:
we must retrieve Melora's panties!
What was the other thing?
Won't the world be in danger
if we don't defeat him, or something?
Vinsant?
No. Let's go into town.
Huh?
Did something just fly past us?
Something's running super fast!
Is it a new monster?
It's far too fast to see!
Chup, summon Scopeion!
Got it!
Scopeion!
Nature!
Say cheese! It's Scopeion!
Scopeion!
You have to figure out what's running
super fast around us!
Uno momento!
I'll scope it out!
Don't bother! My Goblin eyes can figure this out!
I'll try to get a look at it too!
They all got run down!
Still couldn't figure out what that was.
Okay!
I gots a good video of it!
Wait, what? Snow White?!
My word! She's running laps
with her eyes wide open!
She's sure full of surprises.
Ugh, why'd they have to land so far away?
Romeo!
O, Romeo!
Huh? Isn't that Juliet?
But Romeo's not with her.
O, Romeo!
Wherefore art thou Romeo?
Wait, is he with her?
'Tis because of my love for thee, Juliet!
Yikes, they're so far apart!
Romeo!!
Juliet!!
What am I watching?
This isn't how they were
last time we met.
It isn't? Explain!
They used to be wrapped in the same scarf,
holding no distance at all
and constantly locking eyes!
Romeo!!
It's weird to see them so far apart.
Weird, you say?
Anyways, where the heck
did those guys go?
Oh, I have a thought!
Good afternoon!
There you are.
Oh? Hey!
Came here to get some weapons
that might work on Scardon.
Welcome to our humble business.
Please take your time
to browse our offerings.
What's gotten into you?
Normally, you have a big attitude with customers.
I do?!
M-My sincerest apologies!
Did I bear insolence
towards you, my valuable customers?
Huh? Uh, yeah.
You were pretty rude
last time we came in.
My sincerest apologies!!
How could I treat my
Level AAA customers like this?
I'm such a great big dimwit!
I-Is he broken?
That aside, is Carbonara in?
Do you have business?
One moment, I'll call for Carbonara.
Carbonara, ya there?
Coming!
W-Welcome in...
What?
Why do you look so bashful?
If you gotta go, don't hold it in, dude.
"Gotta go?" Why would you say that?
So dirty!
Blegh, why is he reacting like a girl?
Please excuse my daughter.
She's growing, and gets a bit shy.
Your daughter?!
I'd hate to brag,
but she's done a real fine job
at drawing eyes to our establishment.
Pinocchio, Carbonara is your daughter?!
I guess it's true love knows no race!
Don't be ridiculous!
This goes way beyond race!
Don't be shy, Carbonara!
Show our customers around!
Okie-dokie, Daddy! I'll do the very best I can!
Seriously, what am I watching?
This here is our shop's
current number one recommendation:
the Bird Staff!
Ha, looks funny! Can I give it a try?
Of course!
Oh no!
Huh? Gob-san, what's wrong?!
I'm so sorry.
The Bird Staff has poison in it
strong enough to defeat 100 old men!
Say what?!
Whoopsy-daisy! I'm such a klutz!
Teehee!
He's starting to get on my nerves.
Carbonara, take these for a second.
Oh, beigoma!
No way, I can't!
I've never held beigoma before!
They're heavier than chopsticks!
So heavy...
There, three. Don't cry, Carbonara!
Everything's okay. Yes, it was heavy.
Daddy hears you.
Okay, what was that?
I thought they were just doing a bit at first.
But that felt real.
Yeah. Real scary.
They're not the only ones.
Something's off with
just about everyone here.
Oh?
It's an AKZ48 concert!
Wait, hold on! Is that who I think it is on stage?
Commander Cinderella?!
She's performing?!
Is everyone hyped up?
So quiet!
Girl, you gotta speak up!
Hold out your pinkie
when you have the mic!
And don't stop smiling like an idol!
I-I'm sorry, managers!
So Cinderella's the idol...
and AKZ48 are her managers.
What the heck?
That's ridiculously unbalanced!
Please listen to my songs...
Careless Little Red,
and Dreams, Courage, and Little Red.
Aren't you gonna dance?
Go on, move like an idol!
One, two! One, two!
I can't even hear her sing...
Thank you all.
What? Can't hear you!
Here is the next guest.
You cut off in the middle of the song!
Hey, it's Minister Gastank!
Didn't he go missing after all that stuff
with the Siren Sisters?
Is he back to being a minister again?
Ehem!
Apologies for the lack of warning,
but I will be announcing new kingdom laws.
New laws?
French Toaster citizens must
keep earthworms as pets.
keep crocodiles as pets.
French Toaster citizens must
remain fans of their ruler until death.
Thank you.
Some of the stupidest laws I've ever heard.
It's strange, the new laws we heard about lately
were a lot more earnest and royal.
We will soon announce these new laws
to the world,
and with time, the economy
and the people will return to normal.
So that did seem pretty strange.
This is really confusing, huh?
Minister Gastank!
How are ya? Did you get away
from the Siren Sisters?
Who are the Siren Sisters?
Actually, who are you?
Whuh?
I guess Minister Gastank
forgot all about us.
Shibuchin and the king!
Woof? Woof-woof!
Meow? Myaa!
Wait, what?
— Woof, woof!
— Meooow!
— Myaoh!
— Ruff-ruff!
Now that's just wrong.
I'm so confused!
Everyone seems to be all sorts of weird.
I think...
Panpan!
Oh, Candoll.
We can't say for certain
if that's actually Panpan or not.
Let's watch them for a bit...
Master Panpan!
Hey!
Master!
Don't stand behind me!
Yeowch!
I found treasure!
Look at him!
It's the timid, crafting, geeky
Master Panpan we know!
Hold on, Chup. We can't be certain yet.
Excuse me, Panpan.
I have a question.
Oh, it's you.
This is a monster we found
when we first met.
Do you remember his name?
Of course I do.
Okay, then. On the count of three,
we both say it.
One, two, three!
Fairjii.
Pink Flying Dur—jii.
There we have it.
That know-it-all attitude and him cowardly trying
to cover up his mistake—that's Panpan.
Indeed.
A know-it-all and a coward?
That's how you guys see me?!
Oh, don't cry, Panny!
But Candoll...!
There, there. It's shokay, Panny!
That is not Candoll!
He's acting way off!
Go on, take a look.
The flames of my candle
will soothe your soul.
It really does.
My tears have stopped.
It's easing my pure serious geek heart!
Seems like you're real too!
Real?
So that's what's going on here.
Follow me. I'll explain everything at my base.
Here's my base!
"Base" is being generous.
Oh hey, are those Princess Melora's panties?
Why would you hang up
a pair of panties like a flag?
That's just begging to get made fun of.
I wouldn't be hasty, Mayone.
Everything's purpose is all messed up
in the world we're in.
Perhaps using panties as a flag
is a normality here!
A flag? No.
It's exactly what it looks like: panties!
Yeah, that's what I thought.
But they're no ordinary panties.
They're my savior!
What?!
I was caught in Scardon's talons,
en route to Demi-Glace Castle...
Wait, really?
Whaaat?!
I-I'm slipping! It's over!!
Or so I thought,
but then I got a hold of...
...a pair of panties!
I'm gonna fall!!
U-Unbelievable!
The item only a legendary hero
can obtain: God Panties!
There you have it.
I share my fate with those panties!
Melora's panties are awesome!
They don't even look stretched out!
Yes. That's why they're defective.
Those were my mom's invention.
They're made with a super-elastic material.
That way, anyone can wear it,
and they last a long time.
The problem is, you buy one,
you never have to buy another one.
Those are some cool panties.
But it was deemed entirely
unprofitable for M&C Technologies,
so they were recalled.
That's one reason to do a recall.
Moving on...
You mentioned that we were "real."
By any chance, is this the Scarzone,
the fake world Scardon made?
That's right.
Sca... Scar...
Scardon!
Yeah. That place Scardon made,
the Starlone...
The Scarzone.
I've heard about this.
Scardon lures humans
into this fake world
and traps them here for eternity.
A fake world?
So that's why the king
was acting all funny.
Well, he's not the king no more.
Huh?
Didn't he just announce new laws?
Wait a minute.
"French Toaster citizens must
keep earthworms as pets."
keep crocodiles as pets."
"French Toaster citizens must
remain fans of their ruler until death."
I've got it! Princess Melora
wrote those!
She did?
This French Toaster is governed by...
Queen Melora!
Wow, a queen? That sounds rad!
I gotta meet Queen Melora!
Shouldn't we focus on
finding a way out of this place?
No way! Let me meet her! Come on!
I gotta see Queen Melora!!
Wow!
Oh hi, Chup! What's up?
The Princess Melora here... I mean,
Queen Melora is so cute!
She sure doesn't look like a fake.
I gotta get your autograph
while I still can!
Sister!
By Jove!
Did you say sister?!
She's your sister?!
Your sister? Really?
It's been too long.
How have you been, Vinsant?
Are you really her?
Of course I am. After all, you're real too!
Got lost here in the Scarzone
during my travels.
This place is so peaceful!
It's a great place to live.
Vinsant, would you like
to come stay here with me?
Just us brother and sister.
Great move.
You are not my sister!
My sister wouldn't accept
some fake imitation of peace!
Chup, you'd best take down
Queen Melora while you're at it.
Say what?!
She's a fake too.
An evil being binding you here,
trapping you for eternity.
Sh-She vanished into thin air!
This seems real bad, Chup!
Get rid of the queen quickly!
Huh? I...I can't!
I'll do it.
Vinsant?!
You fake posing as Princess Melora...
your very existence is a stain on her being!
It's time you die!
Chup?!
Why are you blocking me?
This is the real Princess Melora!
She's fully, flawlessly real!
So I won't let you lay a finger on her!
Chup, do you have any proof of that?
It's just a hunch!
But I'm certain!
Princess Melora!
Give us the crab pose!
Really?
I don't really want to, but fine...
Just for you.
Take a good look!
Her kneecaps angled toward the sky!
The position of her ankles!
Only the real Melora
can do that full, flawless crab pose!
You're right!
This is the real crab pose,
from the real Princess Melora!
You believe it?!
You finally figure it out?
I'm the real Melora, in the flesh.
Princess Melora!
I nodded off while relaxing in the spa room,
and when I woke up, here I was!
Then Daddy started acting like a doggy...
Woof, woof!
And I was told to take over as queen,
so I rolled with it...
But I'm so tired of it!
I wanna go home!
Chup, can you help me?
She gets bored quick
and spoils Chup...
And has an inflated ego...
That's the real Melora we're dealing with.
Oh, I get it!
If we had killed Melora,
we would've never recovered from it.
Then we'd have been trapped in here in despair.
Yikes, that's awful!
That's what Scardon wanted.
Come on, let's go home!
O-Okay!
S-Sure, but how?
I believe the legend of this place goes
that the escape will be revealed
by a treasure
with a strong connection to the real world.
A treasure with a strong connection
to the real world?
Where do we find that?
Do we start looking?
Scardon could wipe out the whole world
while we search!
I know where we can find a treasure
with a connection to the real world!
Huh?
Where?
This is it!
Princess Melora's panties!
It's a super rare treasure to us Melorers!
That makes sense! It even has the affection
of many other humans!
Which gives it a strong connection
to our world!
Yeah! Melora's panties will be our way out!
Wow! My panties are amazing.
Good going, Chup!
Alright! Let's get back home
through her panties!
Please give us a way out!
That's our way out!
Let's go, guys!
Hey, what's goin' on down there?
I have no idea! What the?
What's wrong, boys?
Eek!
What's happening to me?!
Yo, what are you doing, man?
You're leaking some sort of gold!
Aah, it won't stop coming!
Oh, it stopped.
It did?
Aha, we're back in the real world!
No way! Chup, is it really you?
Oh, Genies!
What the? Why are you wearing
M&C's panties?
We have a critic.
We always need our lucky underwear!
Never know when we'll meet a prince!
So true!
I get it...
We were connected through
someone else wearing the same panties.
Did it have to be Genies, though?
Yeah...
It's like my grandmother said!
All's well that ends well!
Welling through ends? Hell yeah!
All's well that ends well.
Welling through ends?
Hell yeah.
All's well that ends well.
Welling through ends?
Hell yeah.
-Tome
Yeah!
No matter. We made it out of the Scarzone.
Great!
Scardon!
You're sharper than I thought.
What was that?
Telepathy?
Records never said Scardon
could speak our language!
What's the meaning of this?
You will soon meet your end.
And with you, the world as well!
Watch your mouth!
We won't let that happen!
nee kimi doko kara kita no?
Where are you from?
ima boku hima shiten dakedo
I've got time to spare
ochashite morae masenka?
Can I pour you some tea?
dame? dame? doushite desuka
No, you say? What's wrong?
jinsei wa rooringu sutoon
Life is like a rolling stone
tamaru konbini bukuro
Shopping bags piling up
seishun wa kumori zora
Youth is like a dark cloudy sky
sumafo izonshou sa
They're all glued to their phones
donzoko demo iijan
So what if we've hit rock bottom
ki ni shinakute iijan
Don't get so hung up on it
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
tabetara kateru kamojan
Maybe it'll help us get this katsu-done
dame dame demo iijan
But if it won't? Oh well
doutte koto neejan
Don't worry 'bout it
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
megezu ni ikouze
And keep moving forward
charanporan de iijan
Maybe we're kinda sloppy
muchakucha de iijan
And sure we're kinda reckless
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
tabetara kateru kamojan
Maybe it'll help us get this katsu-done
masshigura de iijan
So let's go full speed
tsuki susumeba iijan
And keep pushing onwards
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
tokoton yarouze
And see our goals all the way through
nee kimi doko kara kita no?
Where are you from?
ima boku hima shiten dakedo
I've got time to spare
Why don't we eat KATSUDON?
Chup!
Dang it! Scardon, you little...!
We won't stand a chance!
Oh no!
Was that...?
It's Griffon!
Everyone, get aboard!
Let's fall back!
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone!
What are you teaching us about today?
Today's lesson is on Demi-Glace Castle.
Demi-Glace Castle
Demi-Glace Castle is a castle
located on a big island in the seas
southwest of the continent.
Legend has it Scardon made this place
his stronghold.
Feels like a big boss fight is coming!
Like the big final dungeon!
Chup, don't say stuff like that!
Let's brace ourselves
and head in there!
Next Time
There's a legendary hero
who knows how to defeat Scardon!
And he's Master Panpan's rival!
I'm not so sure about this guy...
Next time:
"Hang in There, Brave Robin Hood!"
Hang in There, Brave Robin Hood!
Alright, it's time for a big adventure!