This is Snack World, the hallowed ground
of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam
and people have handy smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
And my name's Chup!
After a long battle,
I've finally defeated the evil merchant Vinegar Khan,
and now I'm moving towards a new goal!
Whatever perils await me,
I'll fully, flawlessly overcome them!
Alright, let's go on another big adventure today!
Alright!
Last thing we need for the Great Airship
is the black magic engine.
Episode 43: A New Item from Fairy Electronics
We've gotten the support of
Detton, Peffany, and Paccarat Lapa.
All that's left is Fairy Elecftronics.
Aye-aye!
Let's warp straight to them!
But where are they headquartered?
They're very protective of their tech,
so they're cut off from the world.
I've been told that they live in the woods,
just like fairies.
But no one has seen their
building with their own eyes!
That makes no sense.
What about their business partners?
That's what they have branches for!
Their HQ, the hub of their tech,
is what's hidden deep in the woods!
So how do we get there?
I don't know! That's my whole point!
Man, you're hopeless.
Yeah.
Why do we rely on you?
What's with the judgment?
I just gave you good info!
Whatever. Let's head to the woods!
Darefalcon!
Warp-pa!
Take us to the woods!
Woods? The woods where?
The one where we can find
Fairy Electronics' HQ!
That doesn't narrow it down.
Man, you're hopeless.
Yeah!
Why do we rely on you?
Why do you judge me?
I came all this way!
I understand your pain.
Wanna grab a drink
and let it all out?
I could do that.
Yeah!
Ugh, it doesn't matter!
Just take us to any woods!
O-Okay.
Dragon Warp!
Guys?
Where are we going?
I wanna say... the woods!
I knew that much!
Do you really think we're gonna find
Fairy Electronics by just wandering around?
If only Master Panpan, Super Explorer
of the Forest, were with us now...
How would that help us?
He's just as aimless!
That's not true! He's an amazing guy!
You still look up to him?
What are we supposed to do?
We have to get there soon!
It's like my grandmother said!
No running, just walk!
Keep spinning, then bark!
No running,
just walk.
Keep spinning,
then bark.
-Tome
The heck?
Over there! Arf-arf!
There's nothing there.
I was so sure that would work...
It's me, Slime!
See, I told you!
That's just a Slime.
He might know the ins and outs
of these woods.
You happen to know where we can find
Fairy Electronics?
I do!
Where are they?
Very deep in the woods...
Where?
A-Across the river...
Yeah? And?
Th-There are three...
He ran!
Wh-Why is he running away?!
We were this close!
At least we have a general direction!
Yeah! Off that way!
Look, Fairies!
Excuse me, Fairy.
We're looking for Fairy Electronics' headquarters.
My word! This Fairy's been turned to stone!
D-D-Did Medusa do this?!
Dude, they're just statues.
Whoops, sorry. Got scared there.
Is this some sort of sign?
There's three of them.
This must be what Slime
was about to say.
Look!
It's Jarasta!
Huh?!
What's a Jarasta machine doing
all the way out here?
Welcome to Fairy Electronics!
What the heck?
To get inside,
you must solve the riddle of these stautes!
But you're in for
a world of pain if you get it wrong!
What?!
This is no ordinary Jarasta machine.
It's controls the test needed
to get into their headquarters.
Do you accept?
Yes!
Good to hear!
The invisible door will soon open to you.
That escalated quickly.
What's the riddle of the statues?
If I had to guess, we need to move
these statues to face the right ways.
Lemme give it a push.
Huh?
Did you just solve it like that?
My intuition was right!
Oh, no!
That's one world of pain!
That's freaky.
No moving the statues willy-nilly!
We gotta look for clues!
Are there any clues on the screen?
Numbers?
315? What could that mean?
I know!
It means we gotta push it
with our 315%!
What does that even mean?
Why would it be something so silly?
I was so close!
No you weren't!
Do we have to use those
containters for something?
They do stick out.
A Kinoko?
There's a ton of them!
How beautiful.
There's red, yellow, and blue ones!
Red, yellow, and blue Kinokos...
Oh, I know! They're traffic lights!
That's irrelevant!
Three colored numbers,
three colored boxes, three colors of Kinokos...
I see. We have to put
three red Kinokos in the red box,
one yellow Kinoko in the yellow box,
and five blue Kinokos in the blue box!
Look at you!
You actually figured it out!
What d'ya mean "actually"?!
Let's get straight to it!
C'mon, over here!
Ow, you stubborn little...!
I told you to get out of the way!
Just need one more blue one.
Guys!
I got 'em!
Uhh, we only need the one!
Slam dunk!
Oh, no!!
I tried to warn you.
That makes 3, 1, and 5! All done!
Sweet! A hole!
What's inside of it?
Treasure, perhaps?
Here I...
Ow-ow-ow-ow-ow!
Stop acting so goofy!
Just tell us what's inside!
He really did get caught in a trap.
So you were in pain!
Why didn't you say so sooner?
What kind of reaction is that?!
Get this off of me!
There has to be something in there, though.
Who wants to go next?
'Kay, me then!
I'll do it!
No, me!
Then I'll go!
Help yourself!
Now I'm not so sure.
I found this inside.
Whoa!
You're a lot more reliable
than everyone else here, Goemon.
I was just about to do it!
Then you tossed it to Pepperon.
What's that, Goemon?
It's blank.
Aww.
What is that mark for?
Is it telling us to burn it?
We can't.
Maybe there's invisible ink,
and we have to hold it up to a flame.
Oh! I know who to call for that!
Hidra!
A soul, a ghost, a Spirit
It's Hidra. You need somethin'?
'Cuz if you don't, I'm goin' home.
Still not in it to win it, huh.
Hidra's flame bursts
whenever he snaps back at us.
So let's rile him up!
Alright!
Hey, mind helping us out
with something, Beater?
Sure, yeah.
Want me to mix your yolk and whites
until they're blended together?
Wait, who are you callin' Beater?!
It's Hidra!
Darn, so close.
Chup, say something else similar
to his name to rile him up!
Let me think...
Uh, how's it been, Lemur?
It's not Lemur, it's Hidra.
How's he supposed to fight back
when it's so far from his name?
Pepperon, say something closer!
O-Okay!
Umm... Hello, Salad Dressing!
Whatevs.
See? If it's not similar enough,
he flat-out dismisses it!
What's the big idea?
That scorches!
That was too close!
Huh? There's writing!
Wow! It looks like a drawing of a door!
You think God heard me praying?
What was that for?!
Hmm...
What's the deal with this drawing?
What's the circle and triangle mean?
Chup!
Yeah?
Look at these.
It's these statues from above.
I think we have to move the square
and triangle statues to match the drawing.
I get it!
If you mess up,
you'll set another trap off!
Be careful, Pepperon!
Leave it to me.
Alright.
It was correct!
Sweet!
Now just push the triangle one back!
Okay!
Oh, no!
Now what?! He broke the statue!
This isn't good.
We'll never finish the test
without the triangle statue.
Hate to say it,
but we might have to give up.
We can't do that!
Besides, you have some nerve saying that
when your nonsense
is the reason we're here!
Why didn't you look up
how to get into their building?!
H-Hey now! You better not be
planning to smack me!
Huh?! What's going on?
Is it accepting Gob-san
as a triangular substitution?
Nice!
Really?
That's allowed?!
What's going on here?
Fairy Electronics HQ
Hot dang!
Congratulations on completing the test!
You may now enter!
Awesome! Let's go!
Whoa, sweet!
So Fairy Electronics
really does employ Fairies.
Since they're small,
they can make precisely-detailed machinery.
Oh, it's you!
Hey, Chup!
Chup, it's me, Pom!
Whoa, Pom! It's been a while!
You've gotten a lot stronger
since we last met!
Me? Look at how big you've gotten!
Also, can I ask you something?
Who are you again?
You don't actually remember?!
Huh? Did you forget me?
It's me, Pom! You saved me
from a trap in the woods.
O-Oh, the Fairy from back then.
And I gave you a Fairypon to thank you!
Do you still have it?
Yup, sure do!
Saving a Fairy? That's surprisingly kind of you!
Y-Yeah, I guess so.
I sure did save him!
Well, see ya round!
Chup! When I got caught in that trap,
I was flying a drone to call for help!
And I held on to the video of you
saving me to this day!
Huh? A video? That's no good.
Here, watch it!
It's stuck in a trap!
Free EXP for me!
You saved me! Thank you!
Uh, h-happy to help...
Huh? Chup, were you about to defeat him?
You said something about free EXP.
D-Did not! Right, Pom?
Real sus.
There's some Fairies gathering up!
Hello there!
App
Ricot
I'm the president
of Fairy Electronics,
App Ricot!
A master engineer
that can build anything!
It's top secret,
and I'm not supposed to tell you...
but I normally work as separate fairies
to keep my appearance concealed!
You said the loud part quiet
and the quiet part loud...
We seek your technologies
so we can build the Great Airship.
We're almost done, we just need
to make a black magic engine!
Do you mind helping us out?
No can do! It's secret technology!
Please make an exception!
We'll do anything!
I might have an idea.
Now, we haven't announced this yet...
Next week, we will launch a ground-breaking
next-dimensional new product!
Whoa!
I told you, keep your voice down!
It's a confidential project
we've pioneered ahead of other brands...
A weapon
utilizing the Transjara System:
The Fairy Cross Edge!
Well, now you've announced it!
I can't show it off quite yet, but...
One second, a sword,
the next, an axe...
It's an astounding weapon
that can switch between the two!
What?! That's awesome!!
And now you've shown it off.
I would like you to make a commercial
showing this Transjara defeating enemies.
In return, I'll help you out.
You got it! One excellent commercial
coming right up!
I'm gonna borrow this.
I must perfect this no matter what.
It's a private matter,
so I can't detail it.
But I have to pay 200 billion gillan
in alimony!
We don't care!
Also, you're a fantastical sprite,
don't give us your bland marriage problems!
I'll direct the commercial.
And I'll handle the camera!
Huh? Is it a good idea
to let the seniles handle it?
Don't call me that!
There's a reason people say
I'm gifted among Goblins!
I've dwelled here for 400 years.
I know these woods like the back of my hand,
so I know how to get good shots.
Well, hop to it!
I'll provide the big baddie!
Cyborg!
Machine. (Machine.)
Hello again! This is Cyborg!
What'cha need me for?
Cyborg, mind sparring with us
for a bit?
We'll deal with the pay later.
Just lookin' for a fight?
That's nothin'.
Let's get this show on the road!
And... action!
You're overdoing it!
Vinsant, you're on next!
And action!
Now! Smile for the camera!
Say cheese!
You look tortured.
And cut!
I think we got what we needed.
You're kidding, right?
Everything looked unnatural,
Vinsant was all tensed up,
and you didn't even film the Transjara!
Er, you're right,
I forgot about the Transjara.
That was a goof-up.
What do you mean goof-up?
It's the whole point of the commercial!
This time, we'll make a good commercial
that highlights the Transjara!
Vinsant, since your smile stinks,
you'll man the cue card.
Fairy X Edge
(Sword)
Fair enough.
Fairy X Edge
(Sword)
Let's begin! And action!
Now!
Fairy X Edge
(Sword)
Okay!
Fairy Cross Edge!
Downloading Fairy Electronics.
Fairy Cross Edge.
Here I go!
Awesome!
Fairy X Edge
(Sword)
Now transform it!
Fairy X Edge
(Axe)
Hmph. Nailed it.
And cut!
Fairy X Edge
(Axe)
I think we got a good one!
Fairy X Edge
(Axe)
That was great!
It's perfect!
Let's check the tape!
The heck?
Fairjii, what's this?
You didn't get any of the good stuff!
I'm taking this very seriously!
But my body can't keep up,
and my hands keep trembling.
That's ridiculous.
Don't we have a younger cameraman?
Don't worry.
Next time I'll hold my right hand
with my left as I film.
It'll stay in-focus!
But both your hands are trembling!
You're no good!
Want me to film it?
I've handled that camera before.
I did an independent film.
That's cool! We'll let young talent run the show.
Senile cameraman, senile director: you're out!
Why, I'd never!
Even your reactions feel ancient...
Chup and Pepperon will be the main cast.
You three will be spectators,
so just stay where you are.
But Cyborg just doesn't have
the impact I'm looking for.
Say that again.
Oh no! It's Dullahan again!
Run for it!
Dullahan?! Now that's an impact!
I'll roll the tape, just follow your cues!
Is now really the—
Let's begin! And, action!
Good afternoon!
Viewers, have you ever been ambushed
by Dullahan while taking a stroll in the forest?
All the time.
Since when?!
In times like these, you need a Transjara!
The Fairy Cross Edge!
Just like this! It's so robust!
That's it, keep going.
(Axe)
Fairy X Edge
Neat, ain't it? But wait, there's more!
Behold: it transforms into an axe!
A sword and an axe?!
It's the perfect weapon for when you
only have space for one!
It's super destructive!
Quality guaranteed!
And it comes with a one-year warranty!
This is great!
And if you act now...!
we'll include this clothesline!
It can't actually come with that!
He's coming back!
We really oughta get out of here!
It's super long
and can fit a lot of clothes!
Wait... what?!
I couldn't breathe!
That feels so much better!
Wait, you were just choking this whole time?
Yep! Thanks for saving me!
Are you serious?
See ya!
Bye!
And cut!
That's the impact I was looking for.
It felt like a Hollywood movie!
Forget impact, that was nonsense!
Plus the clothesline took the spotlight
away from the Transjara!
Their commercial's real innovative.
We're getting put out of our jobs.
nee kimi doko kara kita no?
Where are you from?
ima boku hima shiten dakedo
I've got time to spare
ochashite morae masenka?
Can I pour you some tea?
dame? dame? doushite desuka
No, you say? What's wrong?
jinsei wa rooringu sutoon
Life is like a rolling stone
tamaru konbini bukuro
Shopping bags piling up
seishun wa kumori zora
Youth is like a dark cloudy sky
sumafo izonshou sa
They're all glued to their phones
donzoko demo iijan
So what if we've hit rock bottom
ki ni shinakute iijan
Don't get so hung up on it
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
tabetara kateru kamojan
Maybe it'll help us get this katsu-done
dame dame demo iijan
But if it won't? Oh well
doutte koto neejan
Don't worry 'bout it
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
megezu ni ikouze
And keep moving forward
charanporan de iijan
Maybe we're kinda sloppy
muchakucha de iijan
And sure we're kinda reckless
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
tabetara kateru kamojan
Maybe it'll help us get this katsu-done
masshigura de iijan
So let's go full speed
tsuki susumeba iijan
And keep pushing onwards
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
tokoton yarouze
And see our goals all the way through
nee kimi doko kara kita no?
Where are you from?
ima boku hima shiten dakedo
I've got time to spare
Why don't we eat KATSUDON?
I don't like this atmosphere.
I think we overdid it.
How is it, Mr. Ricot?
I think... I think...
Bravo! I've never seen
such an innovative commercial.
You've made this master engineer
very impressed!
Sweet!
He really loves it?!
We'll air it all over the world
when the Transjara launches!
So will you lend us a hand
on our Great Airship?
Absolutely!
Yay! Thank you so much!
We've got everything we need!
The rest is up to you, Goemon!
I'm on it.
We'll have to come up with a name
before it's finished.
I have the perfect name.
Huh?
The Great Airship...
SS Chup!
SS Chup
Bleh. That sucks.
I'd rather not save the world like that.
We'll handle the name.
Huh? I think it's good! Hey!
SS Chup
Let's call it the SS Chup!
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone!
What are you teaching us about today?
Jarasta
Today's lesson is on Jarasta!
Jarasta is a game machine
you can use Jaras and Snacks with.
It's trending across the continent!
I've played it before!
There's also some machines
that have been reformed and give quizzes.
There's all kinds of them!
Next Time
The Great Airship is finished at last!
But it feels like it's missing something...
Aah! We forgot to find a pilot!
The Sky Barracuda's Great Takeoff!!
Next time: "The Sky Barracuda's
Great Takeoff!!"
Alright, it's time for a big adventure!