This is Snack World, the hallowed ground of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam and people have handy smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
And my name's Chup!
My village was burnt down by the evil land-destroying merchant Vinegar Khan,
so I've embarked on a journey to get my revenge 1000-fold!
At last, my journey has brought me close to Vinegar.
In order to defeat him, I will overcome any impossible mission that comes my way!
Alright, let's go on another big adventure today!
Episode 19: Chup Adventures Into a New Realm
Vinegar Palace - Underground Lab
I see you've yet to resurrect Scardon?
Scardon's powers were far beyond our expectations!
We can't even measure how much it will grow.
If you wish to control it, we'd need to collect a fair amount of mana...
I'm not especially fond of waiting.
What would happen if you resurrected it now?
We'd be setting a beast with the power to destroy the world free into the wild.
If that happens, the company might face some severe losses.
Very frustrating we've gotten this far and we still hit a roadblock...
- Hurry it up, will you?
- Understood.
I mean it, or else I'll bang-bang-bang your heads off faster than you can even collect that mana...
Yooo!
It's the real transcontinental railroad!
Oink-oink!
I can't believe we're actually about to leave French Toaster!
Isn't there any place we can get lunch before we board?
No need—I already bought food before we left town!
What?! Why didn't you say anything?!
Are you seriously talking about food during our emotional departure?!
Mark my words, Vinegar...I'll never let you get away with this!
This is goodbye, Princess Melora.
But one day, I'll fulfill my goal...
...and come back to see you again.
Wait for me.
W-W-Wait just a minute...!
Did you just try to skip to the ending theme?
What's wrong, Mayone? I just felt like recalling some painful memories.
King Oyster City is a very dangerous place compared to French Toaster.
We need to be prepared for it.
Prepare for it...how?
First, you need to know that King Oyster City is covered in a barrier that makes it always nighttime.
Huh?!
Vinegar sucks up all of the city's solar energy and uses it to power his factories.
- Goodness!
- Oink!
Didn't you used to be one of Vinegar's allies?
I was only pretending to work for him so I could get the Dragon Heart.
But he outsmarted me.
What a klutzy move.
Excuse me?!
Listen up, Vinsant.
You can't be clumsy when you're dealing with Vinegar!
You're talking to the guy who's saved us multiple times.
I don't think it's fair to blame him for the way the Heart got stolen...
Oh, I see. All is forgiven, teammate!
Since when were we teammates?
I see. Then as your teammate, let me make something clear.
I told you, we're not teamma—
What's the deal with you and Princess Melora?!
Well, so much for Chup being serious.
I told you, we're not... Oh, that.
Fine, I'll tell you. But only so you don't make me out to be the kind of guy that falls weak to ladies.
I'll start by telling you who I am...
I don't care! Just tell me what the deal is with you and Melora!
I need to tell you who I am first!
I said I don't care! What's your deal with the princess?!
If you just let me tell you who I am...
You seem awfully familiar!
Listen to me and you'll find out why!
I'm all ears.
I come from Whipson, the same village of yours that Vinegar destroyed.
- W...Whaaat?!
- Oink?!
- Hot dang!
- What a small world!
I was there fighting them the day Vinegar struck.
But the dragons under their control were extremely powerful.
All of the village's warriors were taken out except for me.
Wait just a minute. I've never seen you before!
Of course you haven't.
The Dragon Knight recruits chosen by the village trained in the Valley of Dragons from a young age.
D-Dragon Knight?
Legend has it that Whipson is the village of a clan descended from dragons.
Whaaat?
That's crazy.
I heard that the villagers descended from dragons and could control powerful dragons to their will.
Correct. But as the years went by, our clan forgot how to wield that power.
Those that had the potential to awaken...
...were then sent off to train at the Dragon Shaolin Temple so they could inherit the ancient arts of combat.
Dragon Shaolin Temple
All in the hopes of becoming a Dragon Knight one day.
I never heard about that before.
Seems to me like your mother didn't want you to go out and become a warrior.
- Mom...
- Oink...
I lost my family too.
That's why I swore I would become a Dragon Knight like the legends and defeat Vinegar.
Now hold on just a minute! I'm the one who's gonna defeat Vinegar!
As if.
I can do it!
No, you can't!
Vinsant, if you become a Dragon Knight, I'll...!
You'll what?
I'll become a Super-Great Dragon Knight!
You? A Dragon Knight? Good one.
Do you wish to become a Dragon Knight?
Dragon Monk
Yes.
That won't do.
Why is that?
There are certainly good things about you.
But I know for a fact there is something you lack in.
Please tell me what it is I'm lacking, Lord Laozi!
There's something you need in order to control the power of a raging dragon so it doesn't overtake you.
You must have pure intentions at heart.
Pure?
Whatever that may be, you can be certain I'll come to understand it.
Go give it a shot. If you work hard, then perhaps...
I'll become a Dragon Knight and take down Vinegar, I know I will!
Don't get a big head. You won't beat Vinegar.
...Why is that?
You won't beat him because...
So... What did you do when the village was demolished?
I was beaten up by Vinegar's dragon troops.
Without a home to return to, I wandered aimlessly for ages.
- Yeah, just like me!
- Not like you!
I made it to a kingdom with my own effort.
But I hit my limits, and ran out of energy right in front of it.
And you were saved in French Toaster by Princess Melora?
That's right.
That woman from who-knows-where came to my rescue.
But...
I knew if I stayed in the kingdom too long, Vinegar would pick up on me.
I could attract danger.
I left as soon as I recovered.
Vinsant, I won't let you have Melora!
I swear in her name!
She sure is one fine lady if I say so myself.
But I can't say she's the one for me.
She's not one to flirt, and she's a free spirit, just like the sky above us.
Heheh... Not so sure about "the sky", but she's a free spirit, that's for sure.
But that's besides the point.
Vinegar has been trying to resurrect Scardon, a powerful dragon that was once a huge threat to our world.
So that he can use Scardon to manipulate monsters.
All so he can boost his profits in the weaponry business.
I get it, making monsters around the wild go out of control would drive more to buy his weapons...
Not only will that Dragon Heart allow him to revive Scardon,
but it will awaken his Dragon Knight power as well.
So, basically, whoever has the Dragon Heart is bound to win this battle, right?
And since it's been stolen, does that mean we're dead meat?
Not quite. From what I learned from my time with Vinegar,
They'll need to collect lots of mana to assure they'll have control over Scardon before they revive him.
Huh? What do you mean?
To put it short - it'll be a while before they resurrect Scardon.
So we should have time to steal the Dragon Heart back before they do!
That is correct.
- Hmm...
- Oink...
I'm leaving town today, ma'am!
Y'sure? I'm gonna miss you around here.
I'm going to do what I set out to! I'll fully, flawlessly succeed!
Chup, I see something in you no one else does.
I know if anyone can, you can do this!
Yeah, Vinegar's so going down!
One step at a time, got it? You've got quite the journey ahead of you.
Take these with you.
Delish!
- Chup!
- Mm?
Aren't those the kingdom-exclusive melonpan cookies?
Can I have one?
Hehe, okay! Huh?
Me too!
- Give me one!
- Oink-oink!
Heheh, I've been caught red-handed.
Yummy!
I love the melonpan taste in my mouth!
Oink!
Haha, gimme another!
I can't! We're just going to waste through the whole bag!
No fair.
What she said, cheapskate.
I overestimated you, Chup.
Oink...
C-Come on... Huh?
You too, Vinsant?
What the?!
- Huh?
- A tunnel?
We are now crossing the border.
Please be aware it may be dark inside the cars for the time being.
It's going to be dark as we cross through the continent's magic barrier.
Magic barrier?
You seriously don't know?
A magic barrier is used to divide several areas in the continent.
They call it the national border.
It's because of these invisible barriers you can't travel to different areas by air.
The Transcontinental Railroad is our only option.
You're sure smart for a hillbilly.
Tch, who are you calling a hillbilly?!
King Oyster City
Wooow!! Oh wow, oh wow, oh wow, oh wooow!
Oiiink!
Keep your voice down, you sound like a hillbilly.
Yeah, 'cuz I am! We came from the same village, right?
Oink.
Ugh... Stop acting like we're the same.
Living in a city like this... It's everything I've ever dreamed of!
The town is so pretty at night!
Hate to break it to you, but we're not staying here.
Huh?
Wooow! Oh wow, oh wow, oh wow, oh wooow!
Look who's drawing eyes to "Wow" Village today!
You know, this is a very handy way to get around.
We're on a bus.
You could say it's like a carriage of some sort.
You're amazing, Vinsant! I'd almost think you're from the city!
Even though you're a hillbilly!
Grr...
We've arrived at our base in King Oyster City.
This is where we're staying?
Looks abandoned.
This whole place feels so sketchy...
So it's just a hotel, right?
Calling it a "base" to sound cool...
Very hillbilly of you if you ask me, Vinsant.
Urrh!
Whatever, let's go in!
Oink-oink!
Now more than ever you're really exposing your tastes.
Indeed.
I don't really care, as long as they've got good food.
Urggh...
Oui, oui, welcome in!
We'd like to check in five guests.
Chuck-in!
It's check-in!
Oui, oui, I'll check you in!
Make that four guests.
I've been in town lately so I already rented a room.
Okay, four guests.
Oink-oink!!
Specifically, four guests, one tiny guest.
Oui, oui! Will one room for all four do?
Well, maybe a separate room for the lady.
What lady?
What? Are you blind or something? I'm right here!
My eyesight's not the best.
So I'm using the atmosphere and your auras to judge.
Do I not give off the heavy aura of a lovely woman, then?
Hmm?
Don't you feel something?! What am I giving off?!
You're giving me the sense of a dangerous wild animal!
I'm a what?!
- Are you a snake?
- A snake?!
- How about a shark?
- We're not in the ocean!
A hot steamy bath?
That's not even a living thing!
You better shut your damn yap or I'll burn this place to the ground with my magic!
Aaaaah, B-Bunnillaaaa!
What's the matter, Mr. Yong?
Bunnilla
Oohoo, a real city lady!
Wait, why does she call you Mr. Yong?
My name is Bouiyong Arakuda!
But you can call me Mr. Yong for short! Oui, oui?
Bouiyong
It is not "oui oui" to me!
Bunnilla, get these guests a room, will you?
Whatever.
This is your room. Here's your key.
Good day.
What hospitality.
- B-Bunnilla!
- Yeah?
How long have you been working here?
About 5 years.
5 years, hm?
Don't you think you're a little
too used to the usual guests?
Perhaps a more dangerous
love sounds enticing?
Uh, I think you've got the wrong idea about this hotel, old man.
- Hm?
- Oink?
Ey, Yong, you here?
Cyborg
Puck
There you are.
You have the money we loaned ya?
B-But I already paid you back!
Hmph. All you paid back was the interest, ya dig?
Interest is only part of what came with the loan.
Really?
What's going on?
He must be the debt collector.
They made a Monster the debt collector?
Yo, Bunnilla! Ain't you ever gonna ditch this dump and be with me?
That's it, I've had enough! Time to kill Yong and crown myself owner of this place!
Tch.
Oink?
- Haah!
- Oiink!
Whoa mama!
Special Move: Save-the-Man-About-to-Get-
Stabbed-by-Throwing-Butako-at-Him Attack!
Doesn't that sound a bit forced?
- Oiiink...
- Yah!
What do you think yer doin'?
You say you've had enough, huh?
Yeah, and what's it to you?
It's like my grandmother once said...
You can choose your own limits!
You can choose
your own limits!
You can also choose
to live it up in the
liquid as a mudskipper
if you desire!
You can choose
your own limits!
You can also choose
to live it up in the
liquid as a mudskipper
if you desire!
You can also choose to live it up in the liquid as a mudskipper if you desire!
-Tome
Wut?
You'll push on through even when you live in the mud!
You know, your grandma's proverbs are starting to get more practical.
Boy.
I don't think you have a decent grasp on societal norms around here, kid.
I know the societal corn very well!
Norms, not corn!
We've got your back, Chup!
I'll be okay! Let me handle him myself.
I say we take this infuriating boy and toss him into a machine press at the scrapyard!
- "Oh, so scary!"
- Scary.
He's not much better with names either.
Yeah...
As if I'd let you!
Fairy Crystal Sword!
Fairy Crystal Sword.
Woah, you've got big boy weapons?
Talk about pearls before swine.
Well, aren't you flexible?
Fradulent transactions... Offensive behavior... Data leaks... Insider trading... Et cetera!
I won't stand for it!
Ooh!
Did you just get all of that off some website?!
You memorized all that?!
Special Move: Big Boy Weapon Pearls Before Swine Slash!
You don't need to name every move...
A treasure chest!
Woah!
It's a ring!
It's a Natural Ring from Qloris!
Is it good?
Qloris' products are very popular nowadays because they're affordable yet very efficient!
But because of that, I haven't had an easy time getting their newest item, the Natural Ring.
So was that collateral he took from someone else?
I have a Qloris sword and shield!
I've got their axe on me!
What, are you trying to advertise for them?
Here, Bunnilla! You can have it!
- No thanks.
- Aww...
Hey, are you trying to pull the rug out from under us?
Vinegar Palace has high security.
Just charging in through the front entrance won't work.
So as we approach Vinegar Palace,
there's a path by the waterway glimmering beautifully but oddly in the moonlight,
a.k.a. the Moonlit Highway. We'll take that path to sneak into their sewers
and work our way into the palace from there.
- Hmm...
- Oink...
Well, that'll be easy, right?
I wouldn't get ahead of yourself.
At the end of the Moonlit Highway, there's this strange mansion shining in the light,
a.k.a. Vampire Mansion.
Yeah, you can just stick to the alias next time.
So at this "Vampire Mansion"...
I take it we'll take down Vampire, and then Vinegar comes next?
Come to think of it, how strong is Vinegar really?
Have you seen him? He's lazy! Makes him super fat.
The real question is what kind of guards does he have?
Doesn't matter what kind of guards, I'm gonna take Vinegar down!
Chup, you're sure pumped up about this.
What do you mean?!
Master Laozi, why won't I defeat Vinegar?
Because he is far stronger than you.
Stronger than me? How?!
After all the training I went through?
There's no way I can't...
Master Laozi!
Do you remember?
I once told you about the strongest priest who had completed all the trials in this temple.
Yes. No one else has completed all of them since.
Don't tell me...
Vinegar isn't just some evil merchant.
He was blessed with incredible
powers from the dark lord.
He is the Dark Dragon Knight!
Dewicious...
shobokure gao no mobukyara domo ga
On and on these tired old NPCs
iiwake shinagara aruiteru
Keep walking around excusing themselves
itsumo miteiru michisugara
As I took the same old path again
mita koto mo nai wakuwaku wo mita
I found the thrill I've sought for my whole life
itsumade shibonda mama nano
Just how long will I keep drooping around like this?
minikui ahiru no mama nano
How long will I stay an ugly duckling?
ima no reberu wa ichi dakedo
I'm still only level one
ima ni mitero yo sono uchi JUMP UP
But watch me, soon I'll jump up
saikin no wakai mon wa tte
"Why, kids these days..."
toshiyori domo ga boyai teru kedo
...Our old boomers grumble and complain
soro soro omei henjou da
But it's not too late to clear my name
iya ga ou ni mo mattanashi daze
I might not like it, but I can't wait any longer
ketsu no ana kara jetto funsha daaa
I gotta blast free from my cowardly shell!!
ore wa itsuka hana ni naru
Give me time and I'll bloom like a flower
sora ni nobiru hana ni naru
A flower spread out to the sky
kimi ni todoku hana ni naru
The flower that reaches you
You can't sleep either, Vinsant?
No, I'm okay.
We've finally gotten closer to Vinegar.
Indeed, we're only a hair away.
Just thinking about him makes me burn inside.
Inside me...inside my chest, I can feel my heart thumping strongly...
Hm? What's up, Vinsant?
You really went this far just to get your revenge?
Yeah, is something wrong with that?
No, but watching you, I can't help but get the feeling you have a greater purpose than just revenge.
I only came here to defeat Vinegar... Isn't that what you came for too?
Well, you're not wrong.
Our battle's only going to get harder from here.
I know that.
But there's something about Vinegar...
Hm?
Nothing, never mind it.
It's like my grandma once said!
You beat Vinegar no matter what! Even if he dies! Even if he turns into a zombie!
You beat Vinegar
no matter what.
Even if he dies.
Even if he turns
into a zombie.
You beat Vinegar
no matter what.
Even if he dies.
Even if he turns
into a zombie.
-Tome
Fairly certain your heart said that, not your grandma.
X
Hehe, you caught me.
Wait for me, Vinegar! You're totally going down!
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone!
What are you teaching us about today?
Today's lesson is on the Magic Barrier!
Magic Barrier
The Magic Barrier is an invisible wall separating the separate areas of the continent.
It's what defines our borders!
You can't cross the barrier without taking the Transcontinental Express.
There's rumors around that the other areas have wide oceans and huge volcanos!
Wowza! I'd love to go see some of them!
Next Time
A ruthless vampire stands in our path!
His weaknesses: Garlic! Sunlight! Holy water!
And there's one more...
Vampire Hunters, Through-and-Through
Next time: "Vampire Hunters, Through-and-Through"!
Alright, it's time for a big adventure!