Raw Source: Anime DVD Box 1
Translation, Timing, Typesetting: Lumpstud
QC/Review: NeSubs, Noroino Hanako
Lenny, Hater of Humans
♪ Oh, mommy, is that a human? ♪
♪ Should I purge it for you? ♪
♪ They're the ones that hurt Connie, you know? ♪
♪ You mustn't, Lenny! ♪
♪ It's not fair to say that all humans are bad ♪
♪ Whether this one is good or bad ♪
♪ We'll find out soon enough ♪
♪ No, no, no, you're such a bore ♪
Lenny, I'm going to go fetch us some food.
And I'm going to be heading out a bit far this time, so it might take at least three days.
Three days?! For real?
And if you get really, really hungry, please go fetch some food on your own.
Huh, by myself? I can't do that!
Lenny, you're not a kid anymore.
Only when you're strong at heart can you be a grown-up dragon.
I don't wanna be grown-up dragon.
Be a good boy and listen to me... or forget about getting any delicious food.
[Lenny grumbles]
Huh..
Tch!
Connie...I will avenge you...
[Chup mumbling]
[Lenny yelps]
Huh?
Hm? What was I doing? I can't seem to remember anything...
[Gasp]
[Light gasp] He must be out to kill me...!
Aah! A dragon..?
Sorry, I didn't mean to scare you.
Are you by yourself?
Well, yes or no?
[Stomach grumbling]
♪ Tummy's rumblin', tummy's rumblin', tummy's rumble-rumblin' ♪
♪ Left with no choice but to hunt for food all on my own ♪
♪ I'll get some, I'll get some, I'll get some, I'll get some ♪
♪ Tree fruit, tree fruit, tree fruit, tree fruit ♪
♪ Fishy-fish, fishy-fish, fishy-fish, fishy-fish ♪
Aah!!
Hm?
[Gasping]
♪ I'll get some, I'll get some, I'll get some, I'll get some ♪
♪ Bunny hare, bunny hare ♪
♪ Bunny hare, bunny hare! ♪
Aagh!
[Chup chuckles]
[Lenny chuckles]
♪ Combining our forces to hunt, hunt, hunt ♪
♪ It's working out fully, flawlessly well! ♪
♪ I believe that we can do it, try, try, try! ♪
♪ Through hell and high water, we can face it all! ♪
♪ We're like kings out here in the forest, you and I ♪
♪ There's nothing that we can fear, no, no, no! ♪
♪ We're like kings here, standing tall above all ♪
♪ Walkin' down the roads of Chup and Lenny ♪
Heh!
[Both laughing]
[Flam groans]
- Mommy!
Lenny...I'm glad you two are getting along well.
What's wrong, mommy?
Did another human do this to you?!
Lenny, you have to get out of here, quickly.
[Flam roars]
[Lenny gasps]
Bullseye!
- Aah!
Finally found ya!
- Are you sure she's dead this time?
Stop this!!
Hold on, she isn't a bad dragon!
Hah!
[Flam roars]
[Men scream]
[Flam grunts]
Mommy, mommy, are you okay?! Mommy!!
Lenny!
Stay back!
Lenny...
I was right about humans all along.
[Flam sniffling]
Listen to me, Lenny, my darling child...
Don't hate the humans.
Humans only but fear us dragons.
Mommy...
Once we get to know each other better,
the day dragons and humans get along will arrive.
That's why I ask...
please be a dragon who can get along with humans.
[Lenny tearing up]
[Lenny sobbing]
I am right to hate humans!
Humans are evil!
I understand...so, let's go take care of 'em!
We'll get the guys who did this to your mom!
Huh?
Over there!
Oi, you there!
We're back for more!
This dragon meat's gonna make us rich!
Let's get liftin'!
- Hold it!
I won't let you touch that dragon!
Move aside before something bad happens, brat!
Never!
As my grandmother once said!
There are things one must never surrender to the likes of you,
and this is one of them!
[War cry]
[Chup gasping]
Heheh, take this!
Thought you could stand up to us, huh?
Ya think we could sell him off to a slave trader?
[Lenny roars]
[Men screaming]
General　Director/Created　and　Written byAkihiro　Hino
Mom...
I may hate humans...
Based　on　the　IP　by　LEVELー5 Inc.
But I wonder...
if I could be friends with them someday.
Raw Source
Translation/Timing/Typesetting
QC & Review
Anime DVD Box Vol. 2
Lumpstud
NeSubs
Noroino Hanako
Chup
Lenny
Flam
Man　A
Man　B
Man　C
Man　D
Man　E
Megumi　Han
Ayana　Taketetsu
Fumiko　Orikasa
Tadashi　Miyazawa
Nobuaki　Kanemitsu
Yuu　Seki
Takaki　Ootomari
Mutsuki　Iwanaka
CG　Art　Director
Animation　Producer
Supervisor
Tatsuro　Maruyama
Masashi　Kobayashi
Toshiaki　Okuno
Music
Music　Producer/Audio　Director
Sound　Director
Sound　Assistant
Sound　Production
Recording　Director
Recording　Production
Rei　Kondoh
Taro　Hara
Yutaka　Takahashi
Hiroyuki　Hamada
T's　Music　Co.
Satoshi　Yano
HALF　H·P　STUDIO　Co.,　Ltd.
Takeshi　Nishina
Akiko　Nakamura
Animation　Production
Farewell, Chup.
Directed　by
Motonori　Sakakibara
Produced　by
SNACK　WORLD　Project