This is Snack World, the hallowed ground
of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam
and people have handy smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
And my name's Chup!
My village was burnt down by
the evil land-destroying merchant Vinegar Khan,
so I've embarked on a journey
to get my revenge 1000-fold!
At last, my journey has brought me
close to Vinegar.
In order to defeat him, I will overcome
any impossible mission that comes my way!
Alright, let's go on another big adventure today!
Episode 22: Firing the Sprightly Silver Bullet
Bleeegh!
How much longer
do we have to live in this creepy hotel
with these creepy monsters?
What's gotten into you?
Not to mention the eternal night!
Oh, how much I miss
French Toaster's blue skies...
How I yearn for
the ultraviolet rays I once hated!
She's getting homesick.
You must control yourself!
If we don't beat Vampire,
we can't face Vinegar.
And we can't leave this city, either.
But you know...
What if we didn't go after Vampire?
Huh?
We can just sneak past Vampire
and break into Moonlight Highway.
Of course! You're a genius!
It can't be that easy, right?
What about his telekenesis?
What if we used someone as
a distraction while we slipped past?
Gob-san would make the perfect distraction!
Gob-san's practically Mr. Distraction himself!
That's not a compliment!
"Mr. Distraction," really?
Oh, remember how Vampire said
that garlic was his favorite food?
Let's use that!
Use it how?
Let's fry Gob-san up in garlic for Vampire...
and slip past him while he's feasting!
Nice idea!
Nice idea, my foot!
Stop planning to use me!
Oh, we'll fry him in garlic,
butter and soy sauce instead...
That's not the problem!
Don't fry me up and serve me!
It's like my grandmother said!
All for one, and one for all!
All for one, and one for all.
You for frying in garlic.
You for frying in garlic!
-Tome
In what context did
your grandmother say that?!
Think of another option!
What if we simply cut him up
and made Gob-san Soup?
I did not mean meal options!
Forget it. I'll look up a strategy.
I actually went ahead and
asked about this on a Q&A Site!
Why didn't you say so?
Ooh, look at all these replies. Let's see...
"Vampire is totally weak to garlic."
Yeah, I was worried about that kinda response.
Is there anything else besides
commonly-known weaknesses?
Next is... "Garlic," "Garlic..."
"Get in the game."
Get in the game and do what?!
"Garlic..." "Sunlight, garlic, holy water..."
All stuff we've already tried.
"Garlic..." "Don't even bother!"
I need to know
Vampire's weakness!!
Tommy
it's sunlight!
Kuwacchi
isn't it garlic?
Anko
like holy water or smth
Saito
totally garlic
Tommy
it's sunlight!
Kuwacchi
isn't it garlic?
Anko
like holy water or smth
Saito
totally garlic
Tommy
it's sunlight!
Kuwacchi
isn't it garlic?
Anko
like holy water or smth
Saito
totally garlic
Kuma
it's sunlight!
Kuwacchi
isn't it garlic?
Anko
like holy water or smth
Saito
totally garlic
Kuma
don't even bother!
Kuwacchi
isn't it garlic?
Anko
like holy water or smth
Saito
totally garlic
Kuma
don't even bother!
Kuwacchi
isn't it garlic?
Anko
like holy water or smth
Saito
totally garlic
Kuma
don't even bother!
isn't it garlic?
Anko
like holy water or smth
Saito
totally garlic
Kuma
don't even bother!
Yagimame
Anko
like holy water or smth
Saito
totally garlic
Kuma
don't even bother!
Yagimame
garlic, duh!
"Garlic," "garlic," "silver bullets..."
like holy water or smth
Saito
totally garlic
Kuma
don't even bother!
Yagimame
garlic, duh!
Tomo
u gotta use garlic!
Saito
totally garlic
Kuma
don't even bother!
Yagimame
garlic, duh!
Tomo
u gotta use garlic!
Saito
totally garlic
Kuma
don't even bother!
Yagimame
garlic, duh!
Tomo
u gotta use garlic!
totally garlic
Kuma
don't even bother!
Yagimame
garlic, duh!
Tomo
u gotta use garlic!
Higematsu
his true weakness is
Kuma
don't even bother!
Yagimame
garlic, duh!
Tomo
u gotta use garlic!
Higematsu
his true weakness is
silver bullets!!
Kuma
don't even bother!
Yagimame
garlic, duh!
Tomo
u gotta use garlic!
Higematsu
his true weakness is
silver bullets!!
don't even bother!
Yagimame
garlic, duh!
Tomo
u gotta use garlic!
Higematsu
his true weakness is
silver bullets!!
Tama
Yagimame
garlic, duh!
Tomo
u gotta use garlic!
Higematsu
his true weakness is
silver bullets!!
Tama
p sure it's salt...
Silver bullets?
First time we've heard that one.
"Silver has high sterilization
and is most effective in repelling vampires."
"Even vampires strong against garlic, etc.
are no match for silver."
No match? Then we gotta get
silver bullets right away!
Hey, uh, quick question.
Know anyone selling silver bullets around here?
Oh, I've got one of those.
Oui, oui. I'll bring it right out. Here you are.
Ho-ho! I can feel the power
surging through my lower body!
Vampire, you're so going down!
Come on! That's not a silver bullet,
it's a silver pull-up!
Mr. Bouiyong! Silver bullets, man, bullets!
Oui, oui, my bad. One second.
Here you are.
There we go! You're the man, Bouiyong!
Once I gulp this down, Vampire's going...
We didn't ask for a sip down your gullet!
Also, could you not burp
during your one-liners?
That's our Mayone, forefront of the
straight man routine!
Hey, Mr. Bouiyong!
We need silver bullets!
Oui, oui, I hear you. Here.
There we go!
Just you wait, Vampire! I'll stab this pin
right through your...
Good lord, that's a pin for bowling!
How is that supposed to harm him?
M-Mr. Bouiyong!
Oui, oui, I've got it now.
Just you wait, Vampire!
We'll defeat you together!
That's just some guy who's full of it!
These are getting colder by the second!
How are we supposed to
connect the dots on that?
Very sharp, Mayone.
Yikes, wrong again! How about...
Enough! I don't trust you'll get
any closer to what we're asking for!
Looks like we'll have to look for
silver bullets on our own.
Hmm...
If you're looking for silver bullets,
I think one of our guests has some.
Why couldn't you have lead with that?
You didn't ask if guests had any.
You're just being dense.
Show us where this guest is staying!
Right in here.
Hello? Hello?
Are they out right now?
Nah, probably not. Want the key?
Huh? Are you sure?
Didn't ask me not to give it away.
No one would think to.
So big!
A big dog?
A dog... or a monster?
There sure are a lot of monsters staying here.
What should we do, Chup?
Should we come back when he's awake?
Well, it's already past noon.
Maybe we should wake him up.
Excuse me!
Excuse me! Wake up, please! Hello?
Ow-ow-ow... What was that for? Huh?
He fell back asleep!
Come on! Wake up, wake up,
wake up, wake up, wake up...
Is he using Chup as a towel?
Whoop, rookie mistake.
I'm sorry?
He's normally a peaceful guest,
but waking him up is a handful.
You could'a told us earlier!
You didn't ask.
Again with that.
Aagh, lemme go! Stop that!
Let go of Chup!
Yikes, now he's using Pepperon
as a cushion!
Gobson, do something!
Ow-ow-ow...
W-What now?
Probably needs to go.
What?!
He might mistake you for a phone pole.
Nooo!!
This is awful on so many levels!
Don't you dare!
Johnny Honekawa!
Unde-dead dead-dead!
Undead-dead de-dead! Undead!
Milkshake it, baby!
It's ya boi Johnny Honekawa!
Huh?! Who's this big dawg?
Someone help! Help me!!
Whew, I'm saved...
Thanks, Chup!
Just had to throw the dog a bone!
Not often your intuition saves the day!
There you are.
Huh?
Hey, Vintaro!
Stop calling me that!
I brought a guest today.
Oh, Were Wolf?
Well, look who it is! It's Were Wolf,
the guy who was absolutely no help
in our battle with Vampire!
I'mterribly sorry about that.
A bought you a treat to make up for it.
The kingdom-exclusive
melonpan cookies?!
Yay! How'd you get it, though?
I went and fetched it just for you.
We know just what our clients enjoy.
Thanks a ton!
You really are a fully-functioning
member of society.
Is that all you came for?
No. I did some research,
and it looks like Were Wolf
and Franken over there
are just what we need to
fight back against Vampire.
Huh?
But Were Wolf lost before, like, hard.
Wha? Why am I chewing on bones?
This brings me back.
Good ol' deep-sleeper Ken.
Were!
"Ken?" "Were?"
His name is Franken.
Franken
So I just shorten his name down to "Ken!"
And I shorten Were Wolf's
name as just "Were!"
What? At least use the "Wolf" part!
Here, Ken!
Were!
Who's a good dog?
These two know each other?
Yes. Were Wolf and Franken both used
to work for the Marlon family up north.
And so both of them lived under the same roof.
The Marlon family? I've heard about them!
I believe they're arms traders
that have been around for generations!
That's right.
Back then, I worked as a butler
in Glacé Marlon's mansion,
And ol' Ken was being kept as a watchdog.
Around the same time,
they also hired a bodyguard —
that being our well-acquainted Vampire.
Huh?!
Vampire was there too?
Vampire and we were
very good friends back then...
Lord Glacé was very kind,
and treated us with warmth and compassion
even though we were monsters.
We miss the Little Master so much...
It felt like we were a real family.
Vampire, Were Wolf, Franken,
and a Little Master...
I feel like I've heard of these connections before.
I don't follow.
Were Wolf and Vampire
were so angry at each other!
Honestly, you three
seem worlds apart from a glance.
That I cannot deny.
There's a lot of reasons for that.
Like I mentioned before,
the three of us were good friends
and lived together with the Marlon family.
But that peace and calm didn't last long.
It was suddenly destroyed
when a dragon flew into the mansion.
The Marlon family,
with the top shares in arms sales,
intimidated Vinegar with their presence,
so he had them attacked by dragons.
We naturally didn't go down without a fight.
But we were overpowered.
He took Lord Glacé from us.
Vinegar's attacks really did
go far beyond our village...
Having lost its head,
the Marlon family went bankrupt.
Vampire, Franken and I
swore our revenge on Vinegar.
And we split Lord Glacé's hat.
But we were no match for Vinegar.
We lost the battle, and managed
to flee baring our wounds.
Afterwards, we scattered apart.
Were and I continued seeking our chance
to get our revenge on Vinegar...
But...
What about Vampire?
Vinegar recruited him as a bodyguard
because of his combat abilities.
But why?! What happened to
his grudge against Vinegar?
I'm afraid he may have underwent
some sort of conversion,
having his memories taken away from him.
They took his memories?
Indeed... Alas, he has no recollection
of the times he spent living with us.
So even we get attacked trying
to pass through Moonlight Highway.
That's why I have that at the ready.
Are those silver bullets?
Yes. None other than the silver bullets
that Vampire is weak to.
As much as I hate Vinegar,
I just can't stand to see an old friend of mine
acting as a pawn to him.
We're going to try to put a stop to Vampire
using those silver bullets.
I know how you feel!
Chup?
I had Vinegar take away
people precious to me too.
I just won't stand for it.
I'll fight with you!
Chup!
First I get Vampire,
then I'll fully, flawlessly take down Vinegar!
Hey, be careful with that thing!
What are you doing?
There's only so many of those!
Yeah! I only have those ten bullets!
Huh? Really?
It got in my butt!!
Why would you waste it like that?!
Where's Vintaro?
I think he's trying to figure out
what's beyond Moonlight Highway.
Said he'd join us when we beat Vampire.
Oh, I see.
You really like that thing, don'tcha?
It's so awesome!
I can be the one to shoot Vampire, right?
Isn't that best left to Were Wolf or Franken?
Huh? Wouldn't it be awkward
to shoot an old friend, though?
I suppose so, yes...
Then I'll shoot, case closed!
This won't end well...
Watch this!
Yo, it hit!
You big liar! Also, stop wasting
our bullets, numbskull!
Now there's only five left...
I'm not so sure you're skilled enough
to handle this, Chup.
Let me take care of...
You can't!
Why not?
You don't look good with a gun.
What do you mean by that?!
He's not wrong. You look like you'd be putting
a silver ball while going "ooga-booga."
Do I look that prehistoric to you...?
So I'll take on the job then!
Leave the firing to ol'
Arnold Gobson Foodenegger!
Is that actually your name...?
Alright, Chup, hand it over!
Nuh-uh!
Hand it!
S-Stand back!
Stand back or I shoot!
But you're already shooting!!
How many more bullets
are you gonna waste?!
Only three left...
Oh, there's Vampire!
What's he doing, anyways...?
He's obsessing over himself.
How big of a narcissist is this guy...?
He still hasn't noticed us.
Now's your chance!
Get as close as you can
and take your best shot!
Got it!
You have three bullets left.
Don't you dare miss.
I got it.
Tiptoe, slowly, steadily...
No noises!
Your paper fan is much louder!
Safe...
He's getting very close...
Good, he has a shot!
Say your prayers, Vampire!
Sprightly Silver Bullet Shot!
What was the point of all that
if you were just gonna shout?!
He missed!
And you had to use all three shots?!
Hey, boy!
You'll never get away with that dirty trick!
Oh, crud!
That's what you get for shouting!!
It's your own fault that you missed!
Whaaat?!
Vampire...!
Fairy Crystal Sword!
Downloading Fairy Electronics...
Fairy Crystal Sword.
Let's go!
Gaze at my nimble movements!
Such foolish attacks and even bullets
have no use on me!
You haven't lost your memories
after all, have you?
Why do you still have the Little Master's hat...?
You do remember...!
P-Put a sock in it!
Of course I don't, you weredummy!
Weredummy...
That insult brings me back.
You're the only one who ever called me that!
What's going on here...?
You really haven't forgotten
about the good ol' times!
Don't come! Stay!
Sit! Beg!
Just the way you trained me back then!
I knew you remembered!
But why?
If you still have your memories,
why are you working for Vinegar...?
I realized something after that battle.
We don't stand a chance against Vinegar.
But I knew that you two wouldn't
stray from your revenge.
And if you went up against him again,
you would almost certainly meet your end.
'Twas my thought.
Thus, I shall not let you pass this point!
So you were doing this to protect us...?
But you vowed to avenge
the Little Master, did you forget?!
I haven't forgotten for a moment.
Huh?
I thought if I guarded Moonlight Highway,
gained Vinegar's trust,
and worked my way up to his attendants,
I would be able to bring punishment
upon him myself.
Why did you keep something
so important from us?
You don't have to carry this alone, Pie!
We're family, no?
Uh, "Pie?"
Pie! Like the "pi" in "Vampire!"
You guys have a strange way of nicknaming.
Were...
Pie!
Were!
Sit!
Shake! Beg!
Who's a good boy? You are!
I'm sho happy...
we got efryone bagh togesher...
From now on, let's all stay together.
I hope you're watching, Little Master.
Rest assured, Little Master, we will avenge you!
S-Seriously, what the heck is going on here?
Wh...
What the heeeeck?!
H-Hey, guys...
We vanquished Vampire!
Vanquish Vampire
Quest
That was not a good thing
and you know that!
shobokure gao no mobukyara domo ga
On and on these tired old NPCs
iiwake shinagara aruiteru
Keep walking around excusing themselves
itsumo miteiru michisugara
As I took the same old path again
mita koto mo nai wakuwaku wo mita
I found the thrill I've sought for my whole life
itsumade shibonda mama nano
Just how long will I keep drooping around like this?
minikui ahiru no mama nano
How long will I stay an ugly duckling?
ima no reberu wa ichi dakedo
I'm still only level one
ima ni mitero yo sono uchi JUMP UP
But watch me, soon I'll jump up
saikin no wakai mon wa tte
"Why, kids these days..."
toshiyori domo ga boyai teru kedo
...Our old boomers grumble and complain
soro soro omei henjou da
But it's not too late to clear my name
iya ga ou ni mo mattanashi daze
I might not like it, but I can't wait any longer
ketsu no ana kara jetto funsha daaa
I gotta blast free from my cowardly shell!!
ore wa itsuka hana ni naru
Give me time and I'll bloom like a flower
sora ni nobiru hana ni naru
A flower spread out to the sky
kimi ni todoku hana ni naru
The flower that reaches you
We're almost through Moonlight Highway.
Not much further until Vinegar Palace.
Oh, it's from Were Wolf!
The silver bullet barely
missed his weak spots,
so they saved Vampire!
Really? Thank goodness.
It was bouncing around for a while,
so it must have lost its momentum.
Let us move forward for Vampire's sacrifice!
The heck is this door?
There's something written on it!
Dear Vampire, we've installed
a door that cannot be opened.
Thus, you're fired. -Vinegar
Dear Vampire, we've installed
a door that cannot be opened.
Thus, you're fired. -Vinegar
Dear Vampire, we've installed
a door that cannot be opened.
Thus, you're fired. -Vinegar
Dear Vampire, we've installed
a door that cannot be opened.
Thus, you're fired. -Vinegar
Dear Vampire, we've installed
a door that cannot be opened.
Thus, you're fired. -Vinegar
Dear Vampire, we've installed
a door that cannot be opened.
Thus, you're fired. -Vinegar
"Dear Vampire, we've installed a door
that cannot be opened."
"Thus, you're fired. Vinegar."
For real?!
A door that can't be opened?
Can you even call that a door?
No way, it has to be openable!
Fairy Crystal Sword!
No good.
Chup, leave this to your ol' pal!
Not even a dent...
After all that time trying to
get through Moonlight Highway...
Do we really have to give up on this route?
Better go back to the hotel
and restrategize.
What on earth...?
Vintaro?
I can't believe it...
How could this be...?
Is he... crying?
He was the one who found
the intel on this route, after all.
Can't blame him for feeling frustrated.
Why, this door...
It's so beautiful!
That's what you're crying about?!
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone!
What are you teaching us about today?
Today's lesson is on the
kingdom-exclusive melonpan cookies!
Melonpan Cookies
These cookies are a very
popular snack in French Toaster!
They're the #1 snack souvenir
across the continent!
Everyone just loves the way the taste
of melonpan spreads through your mouth!
Nothing beats the melonpan cookies
my grandmother made!
Next Time
A puzzling mystery is afoot!
The one who stole the painting is among us?!
Can you expose the trick
in the locked room?!
Solving a Mystery for Inspector Chilipepper
Next time: "Solving a Mystery
for Inspector Chilipepper!"
Alright, it's time for a big adventure!