This is Snack World, the hallowed ground of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam and people have handy smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
And my name's Chup!
My village was burnt down by the evil land-destroying merchant Vinegar Khan,
so I've embarked on a journey to get my revenge 1000-fold!
At last, my journey has brought me close to Vinegar.
In order to defeat him, I will overcome any impossible mission that comes my way!
Alright, let's go on another big adventure today!
Episode 20: Vampire Hunters, Through-and-Through
'Morning, gang!
Wakey wakey, eggs and bakey!
How do you live with that, Chup...?
Oink-oink.
My neck feels cricked...
These pillows are very uncomfortable.
G'morning, Vinsant!
Good morning.
Why the frown, dude?
It's like my grandmother said!
In the right mood, you can do anything!
With cash on you, you can buy anything!
In the right mood,
you can do anything.
With cash on you,
you can buy anything.
Bwa-ha-ha-ha.
In the right mood,
you can do anything.
With cash on you,
you can buy anything.
Bwa-ha-ha-ha.
Bwa-ha-ha-ha!
-Tome
That hits very close to home
given our money troubles.
Are you listening, Vinsant?
Yeah, yeah.
What's with the fancy man pose? Look at me!
Come on, Vinsant, turn around!
No yelling in the lobby!
Oww... Why all of us?
Oh? That fixed my neck!
It did!
Oui, oui, my frying pan does the trick!
Excuse me, Bouiyong, can you hit me as well?
Non, non, it would be unbecoming to hit such a gentlemanly guest.
You had no problem whacking us!
Please hit me, Bouiyong.
I couldn't, it would do damage
to your handsome face.
I'm telling you, just hit me already!
Oh, okay.
At last, the crick is gone!
It got you too...?
Mhm, sleep in this hotel and you're
guaranteed to wake up with a crick.
Seriously?
Seriously!
I didn't know you were a cat person, Bunnilla!
That reminds me, I have something to ask of you...
Yes?
You see, well...
Take me out this instant!!
Why would you ask her like that?
She's ignoring him? Is this how Hotel Habanero treats its guests?
Darn, no luck with Operation: Maybe She's Into Pushy Guys!
New plan!
How about if I pay you 100 gillan an hour to go out with me?!
He's offering her a job?
That's a pretty cheap offer if you ask me!
But Bunnilla hesitated!
Go fetch the fees from the guest in room 202.
Wait, will you go out with me if I do that for you?
So you will? You will, right?
Gob-san, you're getting the wrong idea here!
You know this, she's just gonna tell you she never agreed to something like that!
Sir, are you heading up to room 202?
Much appreciated. He hasn't paid his fees in well over a month.
Hmph. I'll handle this.
Please come with me! You have my word!
This is what you're using your word on?
It means that much! Bunnilla truly is my soulmate!
Your soulmate? I understand, I've got your back!
Oh, Chup, my dearest companion!
Why are they playing up the drama...?
You've barely known that woman long.
He doesn't mix well with youthful, chatty girls,
so he prefers girls who don't talk that much.
Or so he said yesterday at the Happy Nightclub.
Wait, what? When did you go there?
Vinsant?
I have business to attend to.
Huh? What kind?
Business.
Don't you wanna beat Vinegar too?
Don't tell me you're SnaLine-ing Melora?
No.
Vintaro!
I told you not to call me that...
Huh?
Whatever. I have to go.
Take care, Chup.
Ugh, my neck...
Behind this door is the
nefarious evil not paying his bills!
We'll barge in all at once!
I'll open the door.
3...2...1...
Go!
Hm? No one's here.
That's weird.
Huh?
Aah, a bone!!
Something happened here!
I knew the resident here was a nefarious evil!
Milkshake it, baby!
Nefarious evil? That ain't very rock 'n' roll of you to call me!
– Whaaat?!
– That skull is talking!!
Oh, yeah! What a way to scream, kid!
You've got mad promise!
With that promise, I got a request.
Put me together, hell yeah!
Uh... Put you together?
So, are you a Monster?
Hell yeah, the name's Johnny Honekawa!
I was so worried when the door flung open,
but you saved my bacon! Thanks a ton, kid! Oh, yeah!
Johnny Honekawa
Monsters stay here too?
That's right, were ya born yesterday, sister? Milkshake it, baby!
The heck does "Milkshake it, baby!" mean? Do you just like ice cream?
Ey, you! It ain't very rock 'n' roll to ask what it means!
You gotta feel it, sister!
Milkshakes are the best!
Add some malted power and it's just irresistible.
He knows what I'm talkin' 'bout!
Huddle!
What is it?
Looks like that Monster really is lodging here.
So, should we try to collect his fees, or what?
This guy is a pain in the neck though...
I can't stand how he points at me over everything.
Ey, you guys! Talking behind my my
back ain't very rock 'n' roll either!
Y'get me? Words are meant for shoutin' out loud!
Shout, shout, shout!! Milkshake it, baby!
Lemme see the rock 'n' roll spirit in your heart!
I've got it here!!
Sorry, kid! Think you can put me back together?
Milkshake it, baby...
Aww, again?
Oh, yeah! Now's my chance.
You think I can register his
Snack while he's scattered?
Sweet, it worked!
Why are you messing around?
Let's just forget about this and go down to Moonlight Highway.
Ey, you rock 'n' rollers!
Ya got beef with Vampire?
Huh?
Oh, right! We never came up with anything to counter Vampire.
Hell yeah! You wanna know his
weaknesses? 'Cuz I can spill!
You can? Spill, spill!
Alright! You want to hear from me,
then put me back together!
Ugh, what a pain.
Oh, that might work!
Mayone?
Ey, sister!
Talk to me while the boys put you together.
Huh?
Well, get talking, Johnny Honekawa.
Whoo, I can get used to this!
So what are Vampire's weaknesses?
He's got 3 weak points.
Ejo, luz del sol, y holy water! Hey!
Garlic, sunlight, and holy water?
Wait, why wasn't "holy water" in Spanish?
You don't know what it is in Spanish, do you?
Don't sweat the small stuff!
That's rock 'n' roll for you! Milkshake it, baby!
I don't get you sometimes...
But I see. Monsters know a lot about other Monsters, right?
Correcto!
We might just be able to beat him first try this time!
Chup, how's it going over... there?
Whoa, whoa, oh, boy.
You can do this, Chup!
Fall! Fall! Fall!
– You guys!!
– Aah!
Aw, man, it fell over...
Stop playing around and let's go!
Did you figure out Vampire's weakness?
On the nose! And we should be
able to make good use of them!
Good work, Mayone!
Awesome! Let's get a move on!
Yeah!
Vanquish Vampire
Quest
Hell yeah. I may be alone,
but that's rock 'n' roll for you!
Bunnilla, my beloved!
I'm terribly sorry, we forgot to collect his lodging fees...
Please forgive this Goblin!
Why is he talking like that?
He must be trying out plan "Act like an
old man tired out from a hard day's work!"
But I did my best, sooo...
Please take me...out?
Here.
What the? What a very antique spear.
Huh?
You wanted me to take you out?
Yeah!
Then I'll take you out, here and now.
N-No, that's not what I meant by "take me out..."
Also, damn, you got a Dark Lance?
That's one strong weapon!
I'm no match for you at all!
En garde!
Gob-san, I'm happy for you!
Getting Bunnilla to take you out.
Hey!
I've got your stack of garlic cloves!
Hey, it's Master Panpan!
What brings you here?
I was just worried my sweet pupil was bawling his eyes out in this distant new land!
Master!
I don't suppose it had anything to do with AKZ48's concert tour
that you were short on money for and picked up part-time jobs to cover?
Grr... Don't stand behind me!
Ooh, did the garlic arive?
I ordered them online earlier.
Used Chup's Fairypon for it.
My Fairypon?! When did you do that?
Time to pay up, Chup.
I'm broke...
Mayone!
Ugh, fine.
Well, it's all going to Vampire's defeat.
Take it.
Thank you!
Great, I can still make it to today's show!
Don't fail me, ultra-super geek vitality!
Off I go!
What's his deal? Makes me wanna barf.
Whatever.
Now we can use this garlic as our weapon!
But carrying all of this to Moonlight Highway is going to be quite the hassle.
Oh, I know what we can do!
There's no better carrier than our stomachs!
Hm? What do you mean?
We eat the garlic!
And then we become one with the garlic!
Becoming the weapon that takes down Vampire!
Whoa, amazing idea, Pepperon!
– Let's dig in on them!
– What?!
Looks so good!
Time to eat!
Mmm, so good!
The strong smell of it is just amazing!
Even better when I alternate with water over and over!
Hm? What's wrong? Not gonna eat?
Nope, not happening.
Could you imagine a girl with garlic breath...?
How d'ya expect to vanquish Vampire like that, Mayone?
Yeah...
Vampire's only other weaknesses are sunlight and holy water...
But sunlight seems like a no-go.
How come?
King Oyster City is in endless night.
No sun, no sunlight.
Of course!
Which leaves holy water...
But we only have drinking water.
Wait, what is holy water?
It's water that's been purified through the
holy prayer offered by someone in the right profession.
I see. Well, is there anyone around that can offer holy prayers?
Over here! I can do it.
W... Wait, no lie?
Oui, oui, mackerel does taste best fried.
That's completely irrelevant!
You want it chopped? Minced?
How should I make...
Huh, you want fish cakes? Coming up, oui, oui!
I never said that! It's all your own blubbering!
Oui, oui.
– Mr. Yon!
– Hm?
Please purify this water for us!
Oui, oui!
There are many steps you
must follow to purify water.
First, you must contain the water with your mouth.
My mouth?
The inside of the mouth is the
perfect spot for purification.
Huh, I didn't know that.
The human body is full of secrets.
Hold the water in your mouth
while I say my holy prayers.
Do not swallow or spit it out at all costs!
If it isn't contained for 30 seconds,
the purification won't hold.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir!
Wait, you guys are doing it too?
Yeah, sounds like fun!
Huh? But we're not here to play!
Now, we begin!
Sir, it's already pouring out of your mouth...
Come on, Gob-san, don't make us laugh!
I'm trying my best here!
His tusks are messing him up.
Do we have them pulled?
Don't say things like that!
Well, that's the breaks...
Bunnilla, bring them out!
That'll do it.
Gob-san, we said not to make us laugh!
How on earth are you built anyways?!
I'm not gonna plug up this hole!
It's all I have to show from my time with Bunnilla!
You're weird, old man.
What's wrong, Gob-san?
I need the bathroom.
No way! We've lost too much time because of you.
Now bring us our holy water.
O-Okay...
Now I will say my prayers.
Gob-san!
Now he's leaking water from below!
Wait, guys, look at him!
He's still holding on to the water inside his mouth!
What?! Then what's coming out from below?
What liquid is that?!
The tears of a warrior enduring his trials.
Mr. Yon, how much longer
until the purification is done?
Hm...
It ends in 5...
4...
Hang in there, Gob-san!
3...
– Gob-san!
2...
1...
0.
Whoopsies, farted.
Ugh, Chup!
Couldn't you hold it in for... ack, ew!!
What is this godawful smell?
Heh, just gas.
Oh, I get it!
The smell of the garlic you ate
earlier got stronger in your body!
It was even strong enough to
knock out Mr. Yon and Bunnilla!
That's it!
Huh?
We'll turn our garlic-y farts into our special attack
that fully, flawlessly takes out Vampire!
It's time to train for our Garlic Fart Attack!
Yeah!
Now I wish they didn't eat that garlic...
Listen up, Chup.
Try to fart right in Vampire's face!
Alright, let's do this!
Crap!
Darn!
You farted too early!
– You're up, Gob-san!
– Let's go!
You can do it, Gob-san!
Prepare yourself, Vampire!
Darn it!
That was way too late!
It must be too slow for the
command to reach his muscles!
Go on, Pepperon!
I'm on it!
You can do it! I know you can,
with those strong butt muscles!
Bring in the gold, Pepperon!
Oh, come on, come on!
That wasn't just bad timing,
that was just bad all around!
Can you give it up already?
We're not done yet!
This time, we'll work together!
Yeah!
What...?
Listen, Pepperon. Don't let it out this time.
I've got it memorized.
Sorry, it got out.
Gob-san, hold it in! You gotta hold...
Sorry, went loose.
Chup!!
You need to focus your energy into your butts!
O-Oink...
Like this!
Like this?
No, like this!
Cut it out already!
Why do you idiots keep farting?!
Don't try to make your farts look cutesy!!
Moonlight Highway
Wow... Moonlight Highway is as pretty as its name implies.
Oh, there it is.
That must be Vampire's mansion!
– Let's head in!
– Okay!
Vampire Mansion
What a big place he's got.
I have a feeling getting into this
mansion won't be an easy task.
Fairy Crystal Sword!
Downloading Fairy Electronics...
Alright, in we go!
Huh?
Whaaat?!
– What the heck?!
– Paper mâché?!
Th-That's so cheap!
There's no "Vampire" Monster in here!
Maybe the intel you got on Vampire
guarding Moonlight Highway was bogus?
Is it you who seek me?
Wh-Who are you?!
Greetings! It is I, Vampire!
Vampire
Welcome, all, to my club,
my mysterious mansion
eerily glimmering in the moonlight,
a.k.a. Vampire Mansion!
You mean the mansion that fell apart?!
However, I'm afraid I cannot let any of you pass!
Bats?!
Chup, watch out!
Chup!
Ugh... Crap!
Can't cut through it... So we have one last option!
Why bother, Chup? You haven't
even pulled it off once!
We have to try anyways!
You two! Become one with your butts!
Yes, sir!
Take this! Leaping Fart Attack!
Now!
Th-This smells like...
We did it!
We finally pulled it off!
How d'ya like that?
I'm... so weak to this smell...
I'm so weak to it!!
Huh? Uh... What?
That's right, I'm weak to garlic...
...weak to my knees because I love it so much!
All it did was make him stronger!
Oh, come on!
It's time for you lot to perish!
This is my final attack!
You alright, Chup?
Vinsant!
You're absorbing my attack?
Now, Chup!
Alright!
shobokure gao no mobukyara domo ga
On and on these tired old NPCs
iiwake shinagara aruiteru
Keep walking around excusing themselves
itsumo miteiru michisugara
As I took the same old path again
mita koto mo nai wakuwaku wo mita
I found the thrill I've sought for my whole life
itsumade shibonda mama nano
Just how long will I keep drooping around like this?
minikui ahiru no mama nano
How long will I stay an ugly duckling?
ima no reberu wa ichi dakedo
I'm still only level one
ima ni mitero yo sono uchi JUMP UP
But watch me, soon I'll jump up
saikin no wakai mon wa tte
"Why, kids these days..."
toshiyori domo ga boyai teru kedo
...Our old boomers grumble and complain
soro soro omei henjou da
But it's not too late to clear my name
iya ga ou ni mo mattanashi daze
I might not like it, but I can't wait any longer
ketsu no ana kara jetto funsha daaa
I gotta blast free from my cowardly shell!!
ore wa itsuka hana ni naru
Give me time and I'll bloom like a flower
sora ni nobiru hana ni naru
A flower spread out to the sky
kimi ni todoku hana ni naru
The flower that reaches you
Do not underestimate me!
– Chup!
Vinsaaaant!!
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone!
What are you teaching us about today?
Hotel Habanero
Today's lesson is on Hotel Habanero!
Hotel Hanabero is an inn in King Oyster City.
They seem to be okay with Monsters and even thieves staying,
so long as they pay their fees.
Ooh, Mr. Yon's so generous!
What kind of business is he trying to run...?
Next Time
We finally meet someone
who can take down Vampire!
He just has to be someone very strong!
Wait, he's just some old dude! Can he really help?
Moonlight Old Man Rhapsody
Next time: "Moonlight Old Man Rhapsody!"
Alright, it's time for a big adventure!