This is Snack World, the hallowed ground
of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam
and people have handy smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
And my name's Chup!
After a long battle,
I've finally defeated the evil merchant Vinegar Khan,
and now I'm moving towards a new goal!
Whatever perils await me,
I'll fully, flawlessly overcome them!
Alright, let's go on another big adventure today!
Scardon!
So Scardon's the one who took your panties!
Demi-Glace Castle, eh?
The Great Airship should be able
to make that trip!
No way.
Aw, man. You can't do it?
Not with that lame husk of a ship.
Huh?
If I'm gonna make a ship,
I'm gonna make it my way.
But building the Great Airship requires
mobilizing several different brands' technologies.
To begin with,
we need Detton's shipbuilding tech.
How is it, Mr. Rice?
It's finished!
I'll get back to Detton and begin
work on the airship's hull!
Hooray!
What else is needed for the ship?
We'll need instruments
that measure to a nanolevel,
and only Peffany makes those.
Alright, Mr. Yonekawa.
Glad to have you on board!
I'll do what I can.
We also need high-level
maneuvering equipment,
something we can only go to
Paccarat Lapa for.
Ho-Horse-Horse!
Welcome to Paccarat Lapa!
Mr. Mallow,
we've captured Mangolas Si!
So will you help us build
the Great Airship?
Absolutely!
And lastly, a black magic engine.
If we want to break through
the magic barrier,
we'll need Fairy Electronics' technology.
How is it, Mr. Ricot?
Bravo! I've never seen
such an innovative commercial.
So will you lend us a hand
on our Great Airship?
Absolutely!
We've got everything we need!
The rest is up to you, Goemon!
I'm on it.
Scardon's going down!
I'm gonna fully, flawlessly
retrieve Melora's panties!
Yes.
Episode 44: The Sky Barracuda's Great Takeoff!!
That's good, thank you.
They'll be doing finishing touches
on the Great Airship tonight.
Wow! It's finally ready!
They're really making haste, too!
Talk about professionals.
I call dibs on getting on first!
Hey, that's no fair!
We'll head straight towards
Demi-Glace Castle tomorrow.
Time for us to go into battle!
Scardon's going down!
Scardon has to be much stronger
than Vinegar, right?
Of course. Like night and day.
Are we ready for this...?
Hmm... You're right, there's no saying
if we come back from this one.
Alright! Once the battle is over,
I'll tell Princess Melora I love her!
Calm down there, Chup!
You're setting yourself up to die!
What'cha mean?
Whenever a movie character talks like that,
it practically guarantees
they'll die afterwards!
Wait, what?!
Disregard what I just said!!
Aah, Chup!
Your shoelace ripped!
You're right!
That's a bad omen...
I think you might actually die!
A black cat! Yet another bad omen!
I saw it too...
Me too.
I don't think I can sleep tonight!
Off we go then!
Good luck out there!
I believe in you.
Thanks! Take care, Ms. Yamamoto!
Take this with you!
Oh! Melonpan cookies!
Uh, wait...
Melonpan cookie
ice chocolate crackers?!
Huh? What even are those?
They made crackers?
The makers must've
lost sight of their course.
Where's the airship?
C'mon, Darefalcon,
couldn't you have warped us closer?
Oh, I mean, Warp-pa!
Couldn't you have...
You don't have to repeat yourself,
you were right the first time.
Wa-P, go check over there.
Don't shorten it!
Also, I'm not your gofer!
Chup!
It's finished!
The Sky Barracuda
Wowie-zowie-wowie!
This is the new Great Airship.
We call it the Sky Barracuda.
The Sky Barracuda!
Now that rolls off the tongue!
Yeah, wicked cool!
Ho-Ho-Hose!
Why did we call it that, you ask?
Allow me to explain
from the beginning...
Don't you dare go on for ages!
We'll be able to break through
the magic barrier with this, right?
In theory, yes.
Don't worry 'bout it.
If it doesn't, deal with it when that happens.
Why are you brushing it off?
What'll happen if we can't break the barrier?
This should stay on the down-low...
but it'll crash into the wall
and explode into wood chips!
That's awful!
Shouldn't you do something about that?
Worry not.
You'll be much at ease
once you've seen the interior.
This is the cockpit.
Allow me to detail
its primary features.
The pilot's chair is
a grade-5 recliner.
You can press this button
to activate the massage,
and select from both vertical and horizontal.
Why does this matter?
Over there is the refridgerator.
It may be small, but it can make ice
every 30 minutes.
Thank goodness it
makes ice on its own!
Through that door and downstairs
is a karaoke booth with scoring.
The other door leads to a tanning salon.
These additions are, well, Great!
But we don't need all of this, no?
Also, if you go on the deck at night,
you'll be able to stargaze.
However, I'd advise against going out
mid-flight as it would be dangerous.
If it's dangerous, don't add it on!
That concludes the primary features.
What?!
I feel in it to win it!
What? Why?!
I wish you all the best in your battle.
Hold on! Who's going to pilot?
Me, me! I'll do it!
Excuse me?!
You realize that's a big task, right?
The time has come.
We're now preparing for takeoff.
Are you ready?
Yes, ma'am!
Okay. Set the operation gauge to level theta,
then pull the acceleration lever to full.
While you do that, change the
ignition command to formative.
Umm...
All good?
All good!
No it isn't, and you know that!
None of you know how to pilot an airship?!
No...
Are you kiddin' me?
That's pathetic. Now what?
Should we train 'em on the tech now?
We don't know if any of them
are new-types.
What's "new-type" mean?
Ho-Ho-Horse!
I'll explain it from the very beginning...
Save it, okay?
Boo-horse... I just wanna be a part of this.
New-types are those who have
the makings of a pilot.
Only one with good eyesight,
judgment, and concentration
can adequately maneuver an airship.
Maybe we should seek out
a new-type through auditions...
Splendid idea!
You scared me!
Let's work on a commercial
for those auditions right away!
URGENT AUDITIONS!
SEEKING PILOTS OF THE FUTURE!
EXPERIENCE PREFERRED!
Take a trip with us on the Sky Barracuda!
That's so lame.
SKY BARRACUDA
PILOT AUDITION
NO.1
SKY BARRACUDA
PILOT AUDITION
NO.1
SKY BARRACUDA
PILOT AUDITION
NO.1
SKY BARRACUDA
PILOT AUDITION
NO.1
SKY BARRACUDA
PILOT AUDITION
NO.1
SKY BARRACUDA
PILOT AUDITION
NO.1
SKY BARRACUDA
PILOT AUDITION
NO.1
SKY BARRACUDA
PILOT AUDITION
NO.1
SKY BARRACUDA
PILOT AUDITION
NO.1
SKY BARRACUDA
PILOT AUDITION
NO.1
SKY BARRACUDA
PILOT AUDITION
NO.1
SKY BARRACUDA
PILOT AUDITION
NO.1
SKY BARRACUDA
PILOT AUDITION
NO.1
SKY BARRACUDA
PILOT AUDITION
NO.1
SKY BARRACUDA
PILOT AUDITION
NO.1
SKY BARRACUDA
PILOT AUDITION
NO.1
SKY BARRACUDA
PILOT AUDITION
NO.1
SKY BARRACUDA
PILOT AUDITION
NO.1
SKY BARRACUDA
PILOT AUDITION
NO.1
SKY BARRACUDA
PILOT AUDITION
NO.1
SKY BARRACUDA
PILOT AUDITION
NO.1
SKY BARRACUDA
PILOT AUDITION
NO.1
SKY BARRACUDA
PILOT AUDITION
NO.1
SKY BARRACUDA
PILOT AUDITION
NO.1
SKY BARRACUDA
PILOT AUDITION
NO.1
SKY BARRACUDA
PILOT AUDITION
NO.1
SKY BARRACUDA
PILOT AUDITION
NO.1
SKY BARRACUDA
PILOT AUDITION
NO.1
SKY BARRACUDA
PILOT AUDITION
NO.1
SKY BARRACUDA
PILOT AUDITION
NO.1
SKY BARRACUDA
PILOT AUDITION
NO.1
SKY BARRACUDA
PILOT AUDITION
NO.1
SKY BARRACUDA
PILOT AUDITION
NO.1
SKY BARRACUDA
PILOT AUDITION
NO.1
SKY BARRACUDA
PILOT AUDITION
NO.1
SKY BARRACUDA
PILOT AUDITION
NO.1
Wait, you guys are entering too?
Well, yeah! I wanna steer that ship!
Same here!
All men dream of being pilots!
I think steering an airship
suits me best.
You never change...
We will be checking your suitability in stages,
starting with an eye exam.
Tell me, can you see this?
I do! It's C!
C!
Correct! You all pass!
Sweet!
We did it!
That didn't narrow the crowd down!
Next is a judgment exam!
LUNCH A
LUNCH B
Which one would you rather eat:
Lunch A or Lunch B?
I-I couldn't choose!
Both the main dish and the side
are different in both...
This is impossible!
You fail!
Fail! Fail! Fail! Fail!
Now, make your pick!
Both!
That was quick! You pass.
Wow, now those two are the only ones left.
Perhaps they're suited for it after all!
I'll pilot the airship!
No, I will!
Does it even matter at this point?
It does. Their suitability needs to be checked.
Have either of you flown before?
Yes! My airship is called Butako!
I also have a dragon of my own!
I see.
I know how to settle this.
Huh?
We'll be testing your flight
with your dragons as your ships.
What do we do?
There's a fish called the Pink Ribbonfish
living in the sea south from here.
This saltwater fish got its name for
the resemblance of its gills!
Ride there on your dragons and catch
a Pink Ribbonfish.
Whoever shows me their fish first
will be nominated pilot.
So it's a matter of who gets back here first.
Alright, Butako! Let's win this!
Now, begin!
Beaujolais, go!
Hey, you cheat!
Let's move, Butako!
You can do this!
Let's go!
There's a world of a difference
between their dragons' specs.
Yeah, Chup's not winning this one.
Chup, it's time to throw in the tow—
Hey, Ms. Karen!
You said whoever shows you
the pink thingamafish first wins, right?
I did.
Then come on!
You're coming with!
I get it!
Instead of catching the fish
and bringing it here,
he's bringing Ms. Karen to the fish!
Saving time with a one-way trip!
Who knew the boy was so crafty.
He might just have the flexibility of a pilot.
I've got this in the bag...
Wait, you're already back?!
I win!
I caught it, therefore I showed it!
No way!
I brought Ms. Karen there,
which means I showed it!
So which one of them wins?
The judges don't seem to have a clue either.
We've made a decision.
Both of you fail.
Aw, why?
Please give me a reason!
I can't accept this!
Simple.
The fish you caught was not
a Pink Ribbonfish.
It looks similar,
but it's a different species:
the Crimson Pseudo-Ribbonfish.
The Crimson Pseudo-Ribbonfish
has a darker "ribbon",
and is known for having a strong chomp.
Get it off me!
It's gonna rip my head off!
Get it off of me!!
Aw, man!
What are we supposed to do
if you fail everybody?!
Of horse...
Hard to say.
Do you happen to know who piloted
Goemon IV's Great Airship?
Beats me. Happened so long ago.
But 6oemon might know.
Okay! Let's go visit 6oemon.
Chup, summon Warp-pa!
I knew you'd ask.
Dragon Warp!
The pilot of the Great Airship...?
Not quite sure...
Oh, I believe I wrote my associates' names
on the back of the blueprint.
You did?
What did we do with the blueprint?
We gave them back to Mr. Carbonara.
I see. Well, then...
Dragon Warp!
Here it is!
Show us the back.
Let's see...
It says the name of the pilot is
Griffon VIII.
Huh? Griffon?!
The one we met before?
Or his ancestor?
Let's go ask him!
Hey!
Warp-pa's running away!
Dragon Warp!
Hey! Chup!
Running away is futile!
You never learn, do you?
I apologize...
I'm gonna fly an airplane
like my grandpa someday!
You loser! You can't fly a plane!
Dang it!
What do you want?
I wanna show you something!
Wowie-zowie-wowie!
Griffon, go take the test
to see if you can pilot it!
C!
You pass!
LUNCH A
LUNCH B
Which one do you wanna eat?
Both!
So fast! You pass!
I bought a Pink Ribbonfish!
You pass.
Unbelievable! They sell them at the fish store!
Feels kind of beside the point, though...
Griffon, nice shopping!
Shopping's a piece of cake!
Looks like we've found our pilot.
Yeah. Griffon, get on board the Sky Barracuda!
Surely he's not gonna be able
to pilot it just like that.
They didn't teach him anything!
I've got a good feelin' about this!
I guess what they say is true.
What do they say?
An outstanding aircraft and pilot
will understand one another.
A phenomenon called synchronization.
His qualities may even tower
over other new-types.
The kind you only see once a century.
System commencing.
Preparing for takeoff.
Entering flight mode.
Launching in 30 seconds.
I'm finally gonna fly!
Scardon
Scardon?!
Is he going to attack us?!
This can't be happening...
Has he picked up on our movements?
Do we fight him?
If we do, we'll cause damage
across Durian.
Get the ship flying!
The Sky Barracuda is capable
of combat in mid-air!
It is? That's awesome!
All clear, Griffon?
One sec...
He's gonna attack!
Griffon!!
Are you almost done?
I hear you! Just give me a sec!
How's the Sky Barracuda?
It must've melted into nothing.
Our technology was the right choice
after all.
Good going, Griffon!
Alright! You're on, Scardon!
Stay calm! A few hits won't break it!
Can we even attack him back?
It's equipped with the Neo-Beam.
You just need to push the button
to attack.
The Neo-Beam?
Just the name makes it sound mighty!
It certainly has a high attack power...
All clear, Griffon?
Uhh... This one!
Wait!
What's wrong?
Will something bad happen?
The Neo-Beam consumes
a lot of energy. One firing...
...will render the tanning salon unusable.
Fire at will! You hear me? Fire!
Don't look back for even a moment! Just fire!!
Bullseye!
Well done, Griffon!
He's toying with us!
Oh man! If he keeps rising,
I won't be able to fire again!
So he's already figured out
the beam's blind spot?
He's one mighty foe...
Griffon, get us to his altitude.
What's your plan, Vinsant?
Fight me, Scardon!
Chup!
Have you figured out
how to become a Dragon Knight at will?
I haven't gotten it just yet!
But it's fine. I don't have to be a Dragon Knight.
You're on, Scard—Huh?
Where's he going?
Make chase!
You got it!
What's he doing?
I had a feeling about this.
He's not running from us.
He's drawing us into his own territory:
Demi-Glace Castle.
Drawing us in?
He might be leading us into a trap.
Magic barrier detected.
Switching to breakthrough process.
All systems switching to autopilot.
Guess I gotta sit back for now.
What'll happen if we can't break the barrier?
This should stay on the down-low...
but it'll crash into the wall
and explode into wood chips!
A-Are we gonna be okay?
We have to go!
Do we, though?
It's like my grandmother said!
Once you give up...
Once you give up,
your life is over.
your life is over!!
-Tome
No, I don't wanna die!!
Ten seconds to magic barrier breakthrough.
Everyone, find a seat!
Darn, there's not enough seats!
What am I supposed to do?!
Now breaking through the magic barrier.
Go!!
nee kimi doko kara kita no?
Where are you from?
ima boku hima shiten dakedo
I've got time to spare
ochashite morae masenka?
Can I pour you some tea?
dame? dame? doushite desuka
No, you say? What's wrong?
jinsei wa rooringu sutoon
Life is like a rolling stone
tamaru konbini bukuro
Shopping bags piling up
seishun wa kumori zora
Youth is like a dark cloudy sky
sumafo izonshou sa
They're all glued to their phones
donzoko demo iijan
So what if we've hit rock bottom
ki ni shinakute iijan
Don't get so hung up on it
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
tabetara kateru kamojan
Maybe it'll help us get this katsu-done
dame dame demo iijan
But if it won't? Oh well
doutte koto neejan
Don't worry 'bout it
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
megezu ni ikouze
And keep moving forward
charanporan de iijan
Maybe we're kinda sloppy
muchakucha de iijan
And sure we're kinda reckless
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
tabetara kateru kamojan
Maybe it'll help us get this katsu-done
masshigura de iijan
So let's go full speed
tsuki susumeba iijan
And keep pushing onwards
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
tokoton yarouze
And see our goals all the way through
nee kimi doko kara kita no?
Where are you from?
ima boku hima shiten dakedo
I've got time to spare
Why don't we eat KATSUDON?
Magic barrier, passed.
No damage to hull nor any systems.
Autopilot disengaged.
Yeah, we made it through!
We're safe...
Wait, where's Gob-san?
I'm all alone...
Left to die all by my lonesome.
Gramps, guess what? I'm flying!
Huh? Are you crying, Griffon?
N-No, I ain't!
Looks like our warm-up is done.
Yeah! Let's go! Scardon's going down!
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone!
What are you teaching us about today?
Today's lesson is on
the Sky Barracuda!
The Sky Barracuda
The Sky Barracuda is a world-class airship
combining the technologies
of four brands: Detton, Peffany,
Paccarat Lapa, and Fairy Electronics!
Whoo, sweet!
This chair massage is bliss!
Hey, stop playing with the seats!
Could've done without the karaoke booth
and tanning salon too.
Next Time
Our pursuit of Scardon
brings us to French Toaster!
Wait, something's wrong here!
Why are the King and Mr. Carbonara
acting all funny?
What happened here?!
Next time: "The Horrifying Scarzone!"
The Horrifying Scarzone
Alright, it's time for a big adventure!