Snack World, the hallowed ground
of dreams and adventures.
A world full of dragons, smartphones,
and convenience stores.
It's a pretty cool place!
But like any world, it has a villain.
Vinegar Khan.
He is an evil merchant who has taken
everything from our young hero, Chup.
And so, the boy embarks on a
reckless journey for revenge!
What perils await him?
The answer lies in his...destiny.
Ep. 5: The Desert Kraken
[Princess Melora moaning]
I want it, I want it, I want it~
Please, daddy?
There, there, my little Melora. I hear you, I hear you.
I'm going to divert this request to Chup now.
Princess Melora, what's got you talking so weirdly?
She's getting eyelash extensions.
They're still drying, so she can't open her eyes.
Huh?
Mhm, I've been thinking of growing out my eyelashes.
Err, and probably my hair too.
But why are you doing this now?
Doesn't it seem extremely rude?
No, it's fine!
Princess Melora's kissy face...is really fine!
I-if I were to end up kissing Princess Melora...
That face would be... [cackling]
Why are you so deluded?
After all...you could say a princess with no make-up would be a crisis!
A "make-up-less battle," perhaps!
You could say one needs skin to shine from the inside, so...
I want daddy to get me the Ultimate Moisturizing Cream! Mwa!
Oink...
- Huh?
- Hah!
I got an air kiss from Princess Melora!
Darn.
That should explain it, Chup.
You can collect the Ultimate
Moisturizing Cream from the Kraken.
Quest
Get the Ultimate Moisturizing Cream
That's just like you, Minster, so smart.
Mwa!
Kraken...
Ohoho, I got it that time!
Hmm.
The Kraken? Hm, that's the squid monster
with a bunch of twisting legs, right?
So we should head off to the sea!
No, it'll be in the desert.
The desert?
The Kraken lives in the desert.
It often attacks the oasis and steals its water.
Why would it be doing that in the desert?
Wouldn't it make more sense for a squid to live in the sea?
Hm...maybe it has a motive behind that?
Now, that trivial matter is not of our understanding.
Moving on, head towards that desert!
The means behind this request feel off...
I'm trusting you with this, Chup!
Ur- yessir!
That was just a delayed reaction!!
Mmmm...mwa!
Ahh...this time, I'll fully, flawlessly catch it!!
I'll do it for Princess Meloraaaa!
- Goodness, you're so desperate!
- Oink...
First order of business, we need
weapons to take down Kraken.
Kraken-striking weapons, weapons...
Hm? What's this...?
- [Vinegar Khan laughing]
- Vinegar Shopping.
Agh, Vinegar...
Time is money!
Let Vinegar tell you how spendin' money is done.
Oh, joy! Oh, boy! Oh, my!
It's time for Vinegar Shopping!
I present to you today, the Crystal Sword!
Looks fascinating!
It really is the Crystal Sword!
That's right, it's epic...but!
[Man shrieks]
Vinegar Corp. has prepared this for the occasion!
It'll boost your ATK!
The amazing Crystal Sword just got even amazing-er!
Introducing the Crystal Sword Z!
How d'ya like this brilliance?
Don't ya want it? Don'tcha just wanna have it for yourself?
[Vinegar cackling]
Tch...
Chup...
Take a good look, you can even slash through apples!
Slashin' through radishes!
Look, you can even slash right through
something turned to stone by Medusa!
M-mom...
Ugh...I'm hungry, mom!
Now, Chup, you really want it that bad? Here.
So good!
Your stew is fully, flawlessly the best!
You think so? That's great!
- I wanna have this tomorrow too!
- Okay!
How about tomorrow and the day after?
Hehe, alright. I'll always be there to make it.
Always being able to have my mom's food...
I thought those days would never end...
All of that...all of that was...
All of that was ruined by Vinegar!
In need of a lady?
Hahahaha!
I'm going to get revenge against Vinegar, no matter what!
Oink!
Let's go, right now! Straight to the desert!
Oi, slow down, Chu-
Oh!
Why are you trying to cover yourself?!
You need to calm down, Chup.
Oink...
We still haven't gotten weapons.
My bad, I started getting tense.
Hm, it's likely that this spell might
be effective against Kraken.
"Bone-Dry" "▼ Effect"
"This spell, when used, will cause all of the water in the opponent's
body to go dry at once. As a result ..."
"Bone-Dry?"
Hi, Mr. Carbonara!
Hey, Chup!
If it isn't the disappointing as ever chums entering a store with a Level F aura. 'Sup?
And aren't you a blabbermouth like usual?
Unable to recognize voice.
Tch...
So, what brings you here today?
We want to buy a spell called "Bone-Dry".
Bone-Dry, huh? An unusual thing to buy.
Oh, if I'm not mistaken, it should be on the back shelf.
Pinocchio, help me look for it.
Certainly, sir.
Oh, man! That's an awful lot of Snacks!
So, Mr. Carbonara, which one is Bone-Dry?
Yes, that one must be...
I do not know.
Hmm...and it looks like the labels stuck on wore off too.
I don't really know which one is Bone-Dry.
Huh?! Well, what do we do now?
May I suggest trying them out one-by-one?
Is that alright with you?
It'll do for now.
After all, you can't buy a spell if you don't know what it is.
Alright! Sounds like fun, I'll give it a go!
Let's go!
Alright!
What?!
Why me?
Uh...
What? Nothing happened?
Don't go shooting any more spells, Chup...wha?
What's with this raspy voice?!
Mayone, your voice is acting up.
[Chup guffawing]
Looks like instead of a "Bone-Dry"
spell, it was a "Hi-Fi" spell.
Haha...guess it was wrong. Here, let's try again.
Click!
- Cast!
- Ah, careful!
A-ah...huh?
What's up, Pepperon?
A-a-ahh, my head feels all dizzy...
Seems like this one was an "Outcry" spell.
- [Pepperon groaning]
- Ow! Move over, Pepperon!
I'm deeply sorry.
Gah, that smarts!
[Groaning]
Alright, this time for sure!
- Here!
- Hm?
Yo! Feelin' wild here tonight, whazzup?
Check it out, yo!
Dang, he's acting flashy.
That must be the "Amplify" spell.
Yo, little lady, feelin' pretty?
Wanna exchange e-mails? Hehehe.
Something about this feels wrong.
You've got a raspy voice, that's what feels wrong!
You really ain't doing fine.
Aaagh, the dizziness won't stop, aah...
Chup, hurry up and look for the right one!
This will be it! Let's try it out!
Wh-whaat?!
What's THIS?!
- We're mullets!
- Mullets?!
Saltwater fish that live in the ocean near estuaries.
I've seen them swim towards surface water in schools.
- That can't be!
- Hm?
Hopping around to move feels annoying!
I can't settle my posture!
It's a bit of a stretch, but...
You could call it the "Walleye" spell.
Oink!
B-Butako, wait, don't!!
Oink, oink~!
Woah, Butako, stop! They aren't delicious!
Stay away from us!!
Please!!
[Pepperon yelping]
My leg keeps bending!
Oink!
Chup, why are you just standing there?!
That's just like you!
Oink!
Alright, this one!
I'm so tired of the Walleye spell...
[All gasping]
I'm glittering, I'm dazzling!
We're all sparkly!
I've got it!
- The "Beautify" spell.
- Beautify spell!! ...Huh?
Oi, why do you look so happy about this? It's so radiant...
Agh...I can't even see anymore...
Ooh, but the idea of me having a sparkling
character just moves me so much!!
Uhh...
- I've got it! I've got it!
- Huh?!
I have the "Bone-Dry" spell!
- Really?
- You bet!
Though, we might want to test it.
Gah!
Eh..ah...I suddenly feel so parched...
Yep, that's the Bone-Dry spell!
Gah...w-water please...
That'll be 10 gillan.
Will you take gold?
Well, do you want water or no?
I want it...I want it...
Sorry for the wait.
No problem!
Thank you, come again!
[Chup sighs]
What an awful experience...
Look who's talking!
Given that you've been casting all those spells on us.
But hey, we bought the Bone-Dry spell.
Wild! There's one of them Hero Marts here!
Before we go to the desert, let's get
ourselves some water! Check it out, yo!
Yo, whazzup?
Why haven't the effects of that
spell worn off Gob-san yet...?
And only the first one he got.
Could it be his age?
Yeah, maybe he'll come back two
days later with muscular pain.
You think that guy's acting like that from age?
Whazzup? Yo, yo, check it out!
He sure has his ways of acting perfectly
like a flashy kid for such an old man.
[Grunting]
Hm...
Where are you, Kraken?
- Huh?
- You find it?
Who's that over there?
Hm?
That must be Mermaid!
Mermaid?
What would a sea-dwelling Monster be doing in a place like this?
I wonder...
Uh, Chup, that's a monster, are you sure
you're feeling up to fight so suddenly?
I'm just gonna try to talk to her.
Who knows, she might have info on the Kraken.
Mermaid
- Hey, you!
- Eh?
Would you happen...
I'm sorry, privacy, please?
Err, well...
Privacy, please.
But, the Kraken...
Come on! What don't you get about "privacy, please?!"
You still think it's worth it?
She's clearly not listening to us, so let's go.
- We're not going anywhere!
- ...What?
It's like my grandmother says!
Listening is a temporary disgrace, like Keanu is Reeves.
Listening is a temporary disgrace,
like Keanu is Reeves.
He signs with an oil-based pen!
He signs with an
oil-based pen.
-Tome
What does that mean...?
Makes sense you'd use a specific pen.
Ohhh!
Of course, you want my signature, don't you?
Oh, what the heck.
Being popular sure is tough.
- [Gob-san grunts]
- There! Signed.
If you put this up for online auction,
you'll get crushed in every way!
Even though I came to the oasis
just to get away from fans...
I guess my overflowing idol aura just can't be concealed.
But that's just fate for the top idol of the ocean.
I can't live with a loss!
All you fans out there!
Welcome to today's Mermaid concert!
Are you ready?
[Giggles]
Oho!
Let me hear the energy in your voices! Yay!
[Pepperon mumbles]
What's wrong? I can't heeeear you!
Don't be shy! 1...2...Yay!!
[All mumbling]
Hooraaaay!
Whaaat?!
Why so quiet? One more time! Yay!
Yay!!
There it is! Yay!!
Yay!!!
3rd level seats, you ready?!
Yaaay!!
2nd level seats, you ready?!
Yaaaay!!
All good? Come on, arena!
Yay! Yay!! Yaaaay!!!
I didn't know Pepperon liked this sort of stuff.
She's probably not even going to listen to us.
Should we just go?
Y-yeah...
Holding a concert really is the best!
Thank you, everyone, I love you!!
Yay! Yay! Yay! Yay! Yay! Yay! Yay!
All this excitement's got my throat dry.
On that note...
W-what? Why did the mood here suddenly...
You three will give me every moist belonging you have! Yay!!
Yaa- [Gargles]
[All gargling]
Your moist belongings!
We're gonna drown!
At this rate...
I can't counterattack with this water pressure...
Chup! Butako can fight with her fire!
That's right! Butako-
Oink...
Butako's drowning with the water in her nose...
Agh, I can't help it. Here, some water!
Take it, Mermaid!
Hooray!
[Gasping for breath]
But that's far from enough!
I'll need some more from you!
Wait...don't!!
Please gimme more!
Agh, no, no...
Please gimme more!!
- Aah, no!
- More, more!
Gob-san, quick, the water!
I gave her all I had before.
Alright, since it's come to this...
More!
Why are you so persistent towards me?!
'Cuz, if I attack boys, won't my fans quit me when they find out? Hehe.
Huh?!
- Mermaid!
- Huh?
We've brought every moist belonging we have on us!
A used tissue.
A used sock.
Oh no, the worst kinds of moist...
I've got this!
"Keiko Campbell"
"Come again, Gobby. -Keiko Campbell"
Moist like water, not moist like a girl!
Here! Take it all!
Uh...well...n-no thanks, sorry.
I- I can't accept handmade gifts
without talking to my manager, haha...
Mayone, now! Use the Bone-Dry spell!
Alright!
Bone-Dry!
Noooo!
I have wrinkles around my eye... Ca...can
someone refer me to a beauty salon?
[Sighs]
Snap!
[Chuckles]
We got Mermaid!
Man...that sure wore me out a lot.
I glimpsed the dark side of an idol's public image...
Kraken's Dwelling
Mermaid said that the Kraken
lived somewhere around here...
She sure was a halfhearted idol...
We might be better off looking somewhere else...
- You good with that?
- Yeah, let's go.
[Kraken roaring]
Huh?!
- Aah!
- Oh!
That must be Kraken!
Kraken
Frightening...gigantic!!
[Roaring]
Come!
Leave this to me!
Wooden Axe!
Your choice for adventure, Qloris!
Let's go!
Lookin' good, Pepperon!
Hi-yah!
Hnng... Take this! Yah!
Oh, no! That didn't work out for me!
If that's what you want, get a
taste of my strongest spell...
Mayone, use Bone-Dry!
Okay!
Take this, Kraken...Bone-Dry!
[Kraken groaning]
Hurrah! You took down the Kraken!
We've won!
Hehe, I did it!
konbini de kuda wo maku ukiyo wo samayou wakoudo yo
All you youngsters loitering about your lives,
shrouding the convenience stores
omaera wa genjitsu ni torinokosaresugi andeddo
You’re like undead who have left behind reality
itsumade son na koto kurikaesu no o-tsu-ka-re
How long are you going to keep doing this?
Don't you get tired of this same old routine?
hashiridase yo ENDLESS ROAD
Run forth through the endless road
koetemiroyo BORDERLINE
Go on past that borderline
sekai wa mugen ni hirogaru kouya
The world is an endless, limitless wilderness
omae no dokyou wo tameshiteiru
Where you can put your courage to the test
sumafo nankaja kensaku dekinai
It’s not something you can search for on your smartphone
sekai wa mugen ni hirogaru PARADISE
The world is an endless, limitless paradise
omaera wa giragira no
Soon you'll come to life taking in the blazing sun
taiyou kuratte ikiteiru
Raws
Translation/Typesetting/Timing/Comedian
ED Karaoke
QC/Review
Raws
Translation/Typesetting/Timing/Comedian
ED Karaoke
QC/Review
AnimeLand (BSJ)
Lumpstud
Noroino Hanako
NeSubs
AnimeLand (BSJ)
Lumpstud
Noroino Hanako
NeSubs
Sure was an easy win, huh?
But it is a big dried squid.
I'm sure if we grill this baby, it'll taste like heaven.
A full, flawless victory for us!
- Hehe!
- Oink!
- However...
- Hm?
In this condition, how are we supposed to
obtain the Ultimate Moisturizing Cream?
- Whaa?
- Oink...
Let me get this straight.
Were we not supposed to dry up the Kraken like this?
Gah, this is bad! What do we do?
Oh, of course!
Mermaid!
Marine! Marine, marine! Marine, marine!
Oh, how bothersome...I was hoping
for some privacy right now.
Mermaid, use your water attack to hydrate the Kraken!
Eh, why would you leave that kind of work to an idol?
Please? I'll even cheer you on!
I'll look at your website!
Oh, what the heck! I'll do it.
It's also the fate of an idol to
make her fan's wishes come true!
Here we go! Are you ready? Yay! Yay, yay!
Alright, let's get this show on the road!
Yay! Desert Kraken, you feeling lively?
[Kraken groaning]
Whaaat? I can't hear you! Alright then.
Have some more water!
Yay, yay, yay-yay-yay, yay-yay!
Wait, hold on, don't you think you're
going a bit far with the water?
Yaaay!
[Kraken roaring]
Yay, yay, yaaay!
[Roaring]
You guys think he looks livelier than before?
Yay, yaaay!
[All screaming]
[Kraken groaning]
Ugh...I'm all dark, sticky, and I smell like fish...
I can't help but wonder if this squid ink is the cream.
That sounds like something to ink about!
Hah!
We sure showed that monster we're not squiddin'!
Aha! Me too!
I want to make a squid pun too!
That battle was inkredible!
That actually wasn't half-bad.
Seafood sure is ex-squid-sit!
Oh, barnacles.
This is kraken me up!
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone.
What are you teaching us about today?
"Britannia Enchant"
Today's about Britannia Enchant!
Britannia Enchant is a luxury brand made for experienced wizards.
They make magical weapons and armor.
They're very popular with adventurers, too.
Chup's equipped with a Crystal Sword from Britannia.
I see! I've got the coolest weapon!
Next Time
There exists a sword that can cut through anything in the world.
We can definitely take down the Kraken with it!
Next time: "The Cutlass That Can Tear Anything?!"
The Cutlass That Can Tear Anything?!
Alright, it's time for a big adventure!