This is Snack World, the hallowed ground
of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam
and people have handy smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
And my name's Chup!
My village was burnt down by
the evil land-destroying merchant Vinegar Khan,
so I've embarked on a journey
to get my revenge 1000-fold!
The final battle is here at last!
He's going down!
Alright, let's go on another big adventure today!
Will We Serve Justice 1000-Fold?!
Episode 36: The Battle at Vinegar Palace!
We've prepared the ritual
for Scardon's resurrection.
The palace is fully-guarded as well.
No intruders will have a chance
of swiping the Dragon Heart.
I'd better hope not!
The ritual will take place at noon.
At your command.
Today's going to be one hell of a day
to remember.
We're back.
Have you said goodbye
to your loved ones?
Yes.
Okay.
Then I'm sure when I turn my head,
I will see you looking vigorous and prepared...
What's with the weird looks?!
We didn't get any sleep...
The seats on the train were so stiff...
Wish we had gotten a sleeper train.
I thought you kids were capable
of falling asleep at a moment's notice!
Oh, shoot! I forgot I could do that!
I was going to,
but I was cramped next to Pepperon!
Now I have a crick in my neck.
Where even is your neck,
Gob-san?
But I've made up my mind.
I'm gonna defeat Vinegar,
fully, flawlessly...
Don't say that while you're yawning!
Are you sure I should send you out there?
Our sleep deprivation isn't of any concern!
If we want to stop Scardon's resurrection
and defeat Vinegar, it's now or never.
Yeah, just like my grandmother said!
Opportunity knocks!
Facing south is a clock!
Opportunity knocks.
Facing south is a clock.
That's not good feng shui.
Opportunity knocks.
Facing south is a clock.
That's not good feng shui.
That's not good feng shui!
-Tome
What?! My old home
has a clock facing south!
Which direction should it be facing?
Can we move on?
I would suppose Vinegar is looking
to hurry up Scardon's resurrection.
If you're prepared for it,
then follow me.
There's something I'd like to besto—hey!!
Stay awake!!
Whoa, sick!
The sword is called Sky Hawk,
and the shield is Turtle Shell.
They're the most powerful sword and shield,
reserved for Dragon Knights.
Bring them with you.
We can have these bad boys?
What a score!
However, you may only equip them
when your Dragon Knight has awakened.
Can't we just use them like any old weapons?
Wait, what?
Yeah, no dice.
I told you, you can't equip them.
It's like when an RPG tells you
you can't equip something.
But what's the point of carrying around
a sword you can't use?
Thanks to their training,
Chup and Vinsant are both very close
to becoming Dragon Knights.
It's very possible they may awaken
amidst their battle.
It's best you bring them in that case.
Thank you very much.
Sir Darefalcon, can I ask you
one more favor?
What is it?
I'd like the assistance
of the Dragon Brothers.
Come again?
Your wish...
...is our command!
Ta-dah!
Bludo!
Redra!
Gregon!
All together, we're the Dragon Brothers!
You're still not all together here!
What brings you to seek their assistance?
I was thinking of launching an attack
on Vinegar Palace from the skies.
The skies, you say?
The ground is heavily guarded.
We've yet to find another route
that will take us to Vinegar.
But with them, all five of us can ride
towards the palace on our own dragons.
I suppose. But there's only three Dragon Brothers.
You won't have enough for all five of you.
I have Beaujolais.
You're covered too, Chup.
Huh? I can't fly!
Not like that!
You have a dragon right there!
Oh, right! Butako!
Hm? That dragon's capable
of something special, isn't she?
Yeah! She just got her flying license yesterday!
Ain't that right?
Okay, so, Chup: you ride Butako.
Got it!
Mayone: you ride Bludo.
Let's do our best!
Yeah!
Pepperon: Redra.
I'm counting on you!
Leave it to me!
Gob-san: Gregon.
Let's make this a good one!
Uh, can we do rock-paper-scissors instead?
Why are you so brazenly disappointed?
I wanted a human to ride me.
Mayone would've been nice...
Well, too bad, too sad!
Do they even need this guy anyways?
Of course they do!
I still have my ultimate spell
kept under seal!
Brag about it once you've actually used it.
Over here, guys.
I received this map while
searching for an infiltration route.
If we come in from the sky,
can't we just crash right into
wherever Vinegar is?
Easier said than done.
The palace still has heavy defense
even above ground.
They have attack systems
at every corner,
and the moment you enter his property,
you'll get attacked by his dragon slaves.
So how are you planning on breaking
through his defenses?
We won't have much time,
so there's only one way to go.
A frontal assault!
Vinegar Khan.
We will soon begin the resurrection ritual.
Please come to the underground laboratory.
Sounds good.
I've made it, Vinegar!
Who might you be?
It is I, Devil Bowie!
Who?
The big new talent, Devil Bowie!
The talent chosen by your project
to be produced into a new artist!
Ah, yes. I do recall such a project.
Leave! Vinegar doesn't have
time for the likes of you.
I have but one question.
When will I be able to make my major debut?
Come again?
I finished recording my first song,
and I've done a lot of marketing.
The video I took of myself performing
got over 100,000 views online!
I have the popularity to become
a top musician and break the charts...!
Bowie.
What is the most important thing you need
to become a successful musician?
I-I don't know, what?
Not making me upset.
I have important things to attend,
so if you keep babbling,
you'll become Scardon's first meal.
We have intruders in
the palace's airspace!
There are unidentified dragons
coming in at high speed!
What?!
Vinegar Palace, up ahead!
Let's keep moving! Stay in formation!
Aye!
Who are the intruders?
We've identified them!
It's the bounty Chup and his party!
Looks like they're coming to take
the Dragon Heart back.
Those kids never learn their lesson.
Oh!
Devil Bowie, prepare to make your debut!
R-Really? When?
Why, today!
Huh? Vinegar!
Today's a big day, so go nuts out there!
It's showtime!
I didn't think there'd be so many!
Looks like around 15 of them.
5-vs-15... Looks like we have to
take out three each.
Let's go, Butako!
Gain speed with potato power!
What's going on?!
It's their attack lasers!
No one stop!
If you do, you're done for!
Move, Butako!
What the?!
It's a barrier.
Fall back!
Dang it!
Oh no, Chup...
What's that down there?
Isn't that...?
You're a little imp
And I'm your devil
Is that Devil Bowie?!
(Yes! Nightfall!)
(Yes! Vine-vine!)
I'll pierce through your heart
With my wicked blade
(Yes! Vine-vine!)
I lurk within the twilight
This feels off.
With a strong bloodlust
This is painful to listen to.
Stay focused, pay him no mind!
You're unable to call for help in the dark of night
It's time for the grim reaper's feast
I'm partying tonight
My perfectly broken heart
This dangerously broken world
My gorgeous broken body
This pleasurous broken ecstasy
I love you so much I want you dead
We got one!
What a weak baby dragon.
Gonna embrace you from behind
With my devillish hate
You let your guard down!!
Damn it...
Gregon!
(Crush crush crush)
Gob-san!
You're a little imp
Pepperon!
And I'm your devil
(Yes! Nightfall!)
(Yes! Vine-vine!)
Sorry, it's 2-vs-13 now!
Much, much worse!
I'll pierce through your heart
With my wicked blade
Forget them! You'll get shot down too!
(Yes! Vine-vine!)
(Yes! Vine-vine!))
And come sunset in Hades
I'll dress you up like a maid
Is that all you got?
I thought I'd get to play a bit longer.
And sing from the depths of hell
For my name is Devil Bowie
Broken heart
What are those snipers aiming at?!
Let's go!
I struck another one!
Pepperon, take down the barrier!
I'm on it!
Good job, Pepperon!
Let's go, Chup! Time to break  in!
You got it!
Say your prayers, Vinegar!
So how are you planning on breaking
through his defenses?
We won't have much time,
so there's only one way to go.
A frontal assault!
But then I thought about it more
yesterday,
and decided we're better off with a plan
that gives us even barely
a better chance of survival.
Mayone, Gob-san, Pepperon.
You need to show some fight
then get struck down.
Get struck down?
Rather, pretend to.
Once you've fallen to thte ground,
Mayone, Gob-san,
you'll take control of their attack lasers.
Move outta the way!
What do I do?
You'll go after the barrier device.
Use your superhuman strength
to destroy it.
Alright, I'm on it!
All according to plan.
It's over, Vinegar!
Today, I get you back 10 times, 100 times,
1,000 times!
You don't know when to give up.
Stand back, Worcester.
But Khan...
If you stay by me, I can't guarantee
I won't kill you.
U-Understood.
It's been too long since I've used my powers.
Dark Dragon Knight
Vinegar
Could it be?
It's the power of
the Dark Dragon Knight.
You sure know your stuff!
Cut it out! What are you doing?!
If this is enough to hold you down,
then how could you possibly
get me back 1,000 times?
Would you mind if I keep crushing you?
Chup, Vinsant! Are you guys okay?
Say your prayers, Vinegar!
At last, I shall set loose
my ultimate spell...!
I got cut off again...
Doubt you'll ever get to use it.
Do you realize how annoying it is
to squash insects who are in over their heads?
I think I'll dispose of all of you first.
Pepperon, what are you doing?
My body's moving on its own!
Vinegar's controlling him!
S-Stop, Vinegar!
I'm not gonna!
There's nothing better than the look of despair.
P-Pepperon?!
Restrain yourself, Pepperon!
I-I'm trying, but I can't!
Stop it!!
Close call...
Wh-What's the meaning of this?
Don't tell me...
Dragon Knight
Chup
His Dragon Knight awakened!
Wait, for real?!
I'm actually a Dragon Knight?!
Aah, I wanna see!
Mayone, you got a mirror?
I gotta take a selfie!
Oh, for crying out loud!
You beat me to the punch.
Aw, what? Come on, let me see!
Chup!
Now's the time to take out
the sword and shield from Darefalcon!
Oh, you're right!
Sky Hawk!
Turtle Shell!
Force and magic, Britannia Enchant
Sky Hawk.
Turtle Shell.
Wow! You look so cool, Chup!
I'll back you up, Chup.
Good luck.
A-Am I...?
Dragon Knight
Vinsant
Vinsant's a Dragon Knight now too!
Is it really just as easy
as making contact with him?
Maybe he was already
moments away from awakening.
B-But, hey,
since I was Dragon Knight first,
I get the weapons, okay?
All good with me.
I'll use my usual.
Exodus Blade!
Exodus Blade.
Vinegar! We're gonna defeat you,
fully, flawlessly!
So you've become Dragon Knights, eh?
Well, that certainly makes things
much easier for me.
Explain yourself!
You'll figure it out soon enough!
Whew, I feel so light!
This must be Dragon Knight
powers at play!
Fighting two Dragon Knights at once
takes up a lot of energy.
Then I'll have to play my next card...
Wave of Darkness!
Vinsant!!
What did you do to me?!
That darkness is born from your soul:
your grudges, jealousy, envy...
Things that Dragon Knights are not immune to.
There it is!
I spy a deep jealousy
inside of you!
You're far more considerate
than the man beside you,
and yet he beat you to the finish line.
That's enough!
Am I really the one you hate?
After all, if he was gone...
Oh, if he was gone, you would be
more recognized for your efforts!
That's what you're really thinking,
is it not?
What's happening to him?!
Snap out of it, Vinsant!
Stay back!
Is he going to attack Chup?
Vinegar's your enemy, not him!
Open your eyes, Vinsant!
Vinsant...
Vinsant!!
Vinsant turned into a dragon?!
shobokure gao no mobukyara domo ga
On and on these tired old NPCs
iiwake shinagara aruiteru
Keep walking around excusing themselves
itsumo miteiru michisugara
As I took the same old path again
mita koto mo nai wakuwaku wo mita
I found the thrill I've sought for my whole life
itsumade shibonda mama nano
Just how long will I keep drooping around like this?
minikui ahiru no mama nano
How long will I stay an ugly duckling?
ima no reberu wa ichi dakedo
I'm still only level one
ima ni mitero yo sono uchi JUMP UP
But watch me, soon I'll jump up
saikin no wakai mon wa tte
"Why, kids these days..."
toshiyori domo ga boyai teru kedo
...Our old boomers grumble and complain
soro soro omei henjou da
But it's not too late to clear my name
iya ga ou ni mo mattanashi daze
I might not like it, but I can't wait any longer
ketsu no ana kara jetto funsha daaa
I gotta blast free from my cowardly shell!!
ore wa itsuka hana ni naru
Give me time and I'll bloom like a flower
sora ni nobiru hana ni naru
A flower spread out to the sky
kimi ni todoku hana ni naru
The flower that reaches you
What's gotten into you?
Vinsant!!
I was too late.
Darefalcon!
Apologies I didn't come sooner.
Being a ghost is not easy.
There he is, Darefalcon,
the Holy Dragon.
And yet you're utterly powerless
as a ghost! What a shame.
He turned Vinsant into a dragon!
Indeed. Vinegar can do that...
as a Dark Dragon Knight!
I mentioned it previously.
Dark Dragon Knights can turn Dragon Knights
into dragons and control their movements.
You know your stuff too!
The dragons you fought against earlier
were also Dragon Knights I transformed myself!
Oh yeah, Darefalcon mentioned it
when we first met him...
He's found their mental weak spots
and pulled them into the darkness.
Those he won over
became his dragon servants.
Indeed. Of those who awakened their Dragon Knights
at Dragon Shaolin Temple,
Vinegar transformed every last one
into dragons!
No way...
Go on, Vinsant.
Show these heroes to their graves!
How could you...
How could you, Vinsant?!
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone!
What are you teaching us about today?
Today's lesson is on
Sky Hawk and Turtle Shell!
Sky Hawk and Turtle Shell
Sky Hawk and Turtle Shell are a top-class
sword and shield that Dragon Knights can equip!
They're from Britannia Enchant.
They're amazing equipment
and the result of lots of research.
These are so cool!
Thanks, Darefalcon!
Next Time
I must battle against Vinsant,
who's under Vinegar's control.
Please, snap out of it!
Just when I think it's all over,
a miracle befalls me!
Next time: "The Battle Continues! Chup Cries Out!"
The Battle Continues! Chup Cries Out!
Alright, it's time for a big adventure!