This is Snack World, the hallowed ground
of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam
and people have handy smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
And my name's Chup!
My village was burnt down by
the evil land-destroying merchant Vinegar Khan,
so I've embarked on a journey
to get my revenge 1000-fold!
At last, my journey has brought me
close to Vinegar.
In order to defeat him, I will overcome
any impossible mission that comes my way!
Alright, let's go on another big adventure today!
Hmm...
Episode 33: Snow White's Dangerous Zone
It's sure taking a while
to get all those stmaps.
Hey, Darefalcon?
Who do you want me to fight next?
One moment, Chup, Vinsant.
There's something I'd like to show you.
What the?
What are you doing to me?!
Now, tell me. Which one of these three chests
is Gob-san inside?
Ooh, is this a magic trick?
I was watching! It's this one!
I was too.
It is!
I agree!
Is that your final answer?
The answer was... this one!
Here I am!
Dang it! It should've been that one, I swear!
Thanks a lot, Gob-san!
Can't you read the room?
Huh? Why are you booing me?
Sir Darefalcon, what is the purpose
of this magic trick?
I wanted you to recognize
a quality that you are lacking.
A quality that I'm lacking?
Forgiveness for Gob-san?
Hey.
You lack that indeed,
but that is not it.
What you lack are mind's eyes!
What's that mean?
The ability to see that which is invisible
using your heart.
If you can acquire it, you won't be fooled
by treasure chests like these anymore.
You'll be able to see the truth clearly.
Read your opponent's minds,
predict their moves.
That sounds awesome!
And at its ultimate level is...
Dragon Chakra!
Dragon Chakra?
The ultimate form of the mind's eye,
said that only Dragon Knights can acquire.
That's even cooler!
I'm gonna master Dragon Chakra!
If you wish to train your mind's eye
and acquire Dragon Chakra,
you must battle against
the strongest out there.
I shall lead you.
Dragon...
Warp!
Oh, it's the woods!
The strongest lies in these woods.
This place seems pretty familiar.
Snow White and the Seven Kinokos
MD
Grumpers
Spreezy
Clumsy
Huffy
Smashful
Carefree
Snow White and the Seven Kinokos
MD
Grumpers
Spreezy
Clumsy
Huffy
Smashful
Carefree
Snow White and the Seven Kinokos
MD
Grumpers
Spreezy
Clumsy
Huffy
Smashful
Carefree
Snow White and the Seven Kinokos
MD
Grumpers
Spreezy
Clumsy
Huffy
Smashful
Carefree
Snow White and the Seven Kinokos
MD
Grumpers
Spreezy
Clumsy
Huffy
Smashful
Carefree
Snow White and the Seven Kinokos
MD
Grumpers
Spreezy
Clumsy
Huffy
Smashful
Carefree
Snow White and the Seven Kinokos
MD
Grumpers
Spreezy
Clumsy
Huffy
Smashful
Carefree
Snow White and the Seven Kinokos
MD
Grumpers
Spreezy
Clumsy
Huffy
Smashful
Carefree
Snow White and the Seven Kinokos
MD
Grumpers
Spreezy
Clumsy
Huffy
Smashful
Carefree
Snow White and the Seven Kinokos
MD
Grumpers
Spreezy
Clumsy
Huffy
Smashful
Carefree
Snow White and the Seven Kinokos
MD
Grumpers
Spreezy
Clumsy
Huffy
Smashful
Carefree
Snow White and the Seven Kinokos
MD
Grumpers
Spreezy
Clumsy
Huffy
Smashful
Carefree
Snow White and the Seven Kinokos
MD
Grumpers
Spreezy
Clumsy
Huffy
Smashful
Carefree
Snow White and the Seven Kinokos
MD
Grumpers
Spreezy
Clumsy
Huffy
Smashful
Carefree
Snow White and the Seven Kinokos
MD
Grumpers
Spreezy
Clumsy
Huffy
Smashful
Carefree
Snow White and the Seven Kinokos
MD
Grumpers
Spreezy
Clumsy
Huffy
Smashful
Carefree
Snow White and the Seven Kinokos
MD
Grumpers
Spreezy
Clumsy
Huffy
Smashful
Carefree
Snow White and the Seven Kinokos
MD
Grumpers
Spreezy
Clumsy
Huffy
Smashful
Carefree
Snow White and the Seven Kinokos
MD
Grumpers
Spreezy
Clumsy
Huffy
Smashful
Carefree
Snow White and the Seven Kinokos
MD
Grumpers
Spreezy
Clumsy
Huffy
Smashful
Carefree
Snow White and the Seven Kinokos
MD
Grumpers
Spreezy
Clumsy
Huffy
Smashful
Carefree
Snow White and the Seven Kinokos
MD
Grumpers
Spreezy
Clumsy
Huffy
Smashful
Carefree
Snow White and the Seven Kinokos
MD
Grumpers
Spreezy
Clumsy
Huffy
Smashful
Carefree
Snow White and the Seven Kinokos
MD
Grumpers
Spreezy
Clumsy
Huffy
Smashful
Carefree
Don't tell me she's the strongest...!
Indeed. Snow White.
Yeah, so we'd like to battle
against Snow White.
It'll have to wait,
it's our princess's dinnertime!
She's probably deep asleep right now.
Princess, it's dinnertime.
Just as mighty of a snore
as the last time we saw her.
Beating a sleeping woman
will be a piece of cake!
Have some mercy, Chup.
Here I go!
Thanks, I needed this chopped.
Say what?!
So juicy.
Oh my...
I see.
How's this on for size?
That was excellent.
How can she move like this
in her sleep?!
She's using her mind's eye.
That's right!
Our princess does so much in her sleep
that she managed to master her mind's eye!
Wowza!
I thought she was just slacking off.
Do you still wish to acquire a mind's eye?
Absolutely, yes!
Me too, yes.
Very well then.
You shall face Snow White
in blindfolded dodgeball!
Blindfolded dodgeball?
I'm sure you all played dodgeball as kids, no?
'Twas originally created
at Dragon Shaolin Temple
as a form of training for
mastering your mind's eye.
We called it Du Xi Bo Liu!
You're just calling it dodgeball!
I want you to sense the movements
of both your opponent and the ball.
Snow White won't be easy on you.
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Good luck, Chup!
We're all watching!
It's two-on-one!
The numbers are on your side!
Yeah! We're gonna win this!
Never mind.
Let the game... begin!
Alright. I'mma take her out in one shot!
Chup, be conscious of your mind's eye.
Got it. My mind's eye...
Now!
Chup, what are you doing?
What's wrong?
Out you go!
The ball smells like an old man.
Vinsant, don't worry about the scent!
Got it. That way!
Looking good!
What's with her stomach?!
That's playing dirty!
Vinsant, dodge it!
What's happening?
Vinsant?!
If you catch the ball before it hits the ground,
Vinsant will be safe!
I'm on it!
Gotcha!
Vinsant's out!
Why do you keep coming after me...?
Now it's 1-on-1...
There's no way you can sense your surroundings
in blindfolded dodgeball.
It's like my grandmother said!
Chup, go right, go right!
Wait, a bit to the left!
Good, that's perfect!
Now hit it!
Chup, go right, go right!
Wait, a bit to the left!
Good, that's perfect!
Now hit it!
Wait, a bit to the left!
Good, that's perfect! Now, hit it!
-Tome
What's that from,
watermelon-splitting?
It's a good summer activity!
Chup, don't aim at her body!
It'll just sink in again!
So where do I aim?
Chup!
Eliminate your distractions
and picture Snow White in front of you.
That'll help you find her weak spot!
Got it!
Huh?
What's he planning?
If The Body Won't Work,
Shoot For The Face Bazooka!
You've got this!
Did it work?
No way!
What the heck?
Huh? What happened?
Her lips developed in an abnormal way
because of her desire to kiss a man.
So it has nothing to do with her mind's eye?
Chup, jump for it!
Get down!
Which way?
Up I go!
That's gotta leave a mark.
I lose.
There's no way we can do this
as we are now.
How are we supposed to open our mind's eyes?!
I know!
Why don't we have Snow White
tell you your fortunes?
Ooh!
Good idea!
Snow White, we admit defeat.
But we'd like to ask, how could we acquire
our mind's eyes like you?
I can tell you.
Since I enjoyed that game,
I'll look at your fortune.
Go to the castle in French Toaster.
The castle?
There are three monsters there
which will guide you.
Three monsters?
I see it.
A sneering white face
and a deadly armor.
A sneering white face?
A deadly armor?
Giving me the heebie-jeebies.
And there's one more.
Once you reach the droppings of a beast,
you will acquire the ultimate technique
of opening your mind's eyes.
The droppings of a beast?
I'm not sure I follow,
but it sounds strong!
I'll be waiting once you acquire your mind's eye!
I'll be taking a deep nap until then.
Nyam nyam nyam...
There you go!
You will have a rematch
after you visit the castle.
For the time being...
What's the big deal?
We're blindfolded again?
I've made it so you can't remove them
until you find your mind's eye.
To the castle we go!
Well, we're here at the castle...
but where are those three monsters?
Chup, Vinny!
How's the training going?
That sounds like Melora!
What could be the matter, Chup?
Um, Princess, this is part of our training!
Oh, my!
My cleavage just got so itchy!
What are you doing?
Me? I was going to try out
this brand new face mask!
Oh, hey!
I might put some lotion on my arms after,
if you boys would like to help out.
You guys don't learn your lesson...
Y'know, I haven't heard
the king's voice at all!
He's been groaning in his sleep every night
because of nightmares,
so he's been bedridden
for about three days...
Huh? Pepperon, you're worried
about your skin too?
No! This thing stuck itself on my face...
Pepperon?!
I love being stuck on people's faces!
Something's off about him!
It's Pack, a monster that
clings onto faces!
What?!
If we don't defeat him,
he'll possess Pepperon forever!
This must be that "sneering white face"
she was referring to.
Go on, take me down!
But watch where you aim,
or you'll split this guy in half, yo!
What are you doing?!
Be careful, Chup!
Pepperon is very nimble right now!
Dettonic Sword!
Dettonic Sword.
Exodus Blade!
Exodus Blade.
Chup, concentrate on your consciousness.
My consciousness... consciousness...
My consciousness of what?!
C'mon now, hey, hey!
Take this!
Hey, hey!
Hey, hey, hey!
Hey!
Chup, Vinsant, hurry up
and slice that guy!
Easier said than done!
Where is he?!
Look out, Vinsant!
Go!
Here I go!
Yuck, nasty!
Chup, follow that scent
to find the enemy!
Nasty!
There he is, Vinsant!
Use your move: the Fart Radar Slash!
I don't really want to,
but I'll do it!
We beat him!
I admire your will to win...
...But that didn't have anything
to do with your mind's eye.
That's the king! What's going on?
Oh, Melora... Why would you marry
a man like him?
He must be having a nightmare
about Melora hitching it off with a weird guy.
Gob-san can't be the one for you...
I'm her fiance?
You're marrying Melora?
How could you!
What dirty tricks did you play,
you old man?
Just like you to cause problems
even in someone's dreams.
Oh come on, you can't get mad at me for that!
Your majesty! You gotta wake up!
King! Your majesty!!
Isn't it a bit weird he's been
sleeping for three days straight?
There you are!
Yeowch!
You've figured me out!
Knightmare
You're the one possessing the king!
Chup, behind you.
This is Knightmare, a vicious monster
that gives people bad dreams.
This must be the "deadly armor"
from Snow White's fortune!
But how is he supposed to help them
with their "mind's eyes"?
I just thought of something!
Maybe if you train under his sleep spell,
you'll be able to use your mind's eye
like Snow White!
I get what you mean!
Is that a good idea...?
If push comes to shove,
I'll wake you up with full power!
So don't worry.
Alright, Knightmare!
Hit us with your worst!
You want me to put you to sleep? That's odd.
Dream tight!
What's wrong?
I just remembered!
His hosts are the target
of eternal slumber!
What?! You shouldv'e said that sooner!!
Guys, don't do it!
Don't fall asleep, Chup!
Wait, don't? I'm about to...
Chup, we'll stay awake
if we attack ourselves.
Owww! I'm not sleeping like this.
Mayone, this is your responsibility too!
Don't you have a spell or sometihng
for staying awake?
Huh?! I'll try out a new spell of mine...
Menzol!
My eyes feel so refreshed!
What's this spell do?
It covers your eyes with menthol.
It's supposed to be good for all-nighters.
Like late-night study sessions
in the old days.
Fresh, fresh, super fresh...
Freshly tired... bed time...
It's not working!!
We can't fall asleep!
What was that for?!
You were about to fall asleep!
Come on, hit me back!
Okay!
They may as well defeat each other
before the enemy has a chance.
This is hopeless...
Finally, allow me to escort you
into eternal slumber.
Dream tight!
Don't fall asleep!!
Special attack: Dozing Off Slash!
That was close...
Instead of relying on
swinging his sword,
he let his sleepiness take care of it.
Well, I admire you breaking the spell.
But this has even less to do
with that mind's eye stuff.
I slept like a baby.
Why do you look like that?
Uh, it's part of our training...
Good morning, Daddy!
It's you, Melora!
That's good to see!
I'm glad you're okay, your majesty!
N-Not Gob-san!!
He must'a really hated that dream.
You deserve a reward for
rescuing me from my nightmare.
Minister!
This is a Clanarine, the reliable brand
beloved by nobility!
And this is their product catered to mages,
it's both light and powerful—
the Clan Metal Staff!
Which means it's all for me!
Uh-huh.
We've met two of the monsters
from Snow White's fortunes so far,
but they still haven't figured out
those mind's eyes.
Huh? What's the third monster
supposed to be anyways?
Gob-san, what do you... Huh?
What?!
Why would you fall asleep here?!
Did you get caught in that nightmare spell?
Nope, I can fall asleep at will
whenever I want to.
It's good whenever it's time
to pay the check at a drinking party.
Since I just got finished
introducing the weapon,
I thought I'd get some rest in.
Ugh, you shouldn't be slacking off at all!
You finally made it here.
Made it where exactly?
That is the ultimate technique
to opening your mind's eyes:
sleeping at will!
What?!
Sleep brings unconsciousness.
By controlling your sleep at will,
that unconsciousness—your mind—
will be free, unbound.
You'll be able to sense your enemy's movements
during a battle
by momentarily going unconscious.
That is using your mind's eye!
Huh?
Wait, does that mean Gob-san
was the third monster guiding them?
The droppings of a beast...
Was it his "manure"?
You love that bit, don'tcha?
Watch!
Manure!
Master Gob-san, please teach us
how to use the ultimate technique!
Very well. Follow me!
Was there a reason for bringing us to the pub?
I think Gob-san just wanted
to fill his stomach.
So, let's say you enjoyed this drinking party.
Pepperon, you're the organizer.
Oh, m-me?
We should pay the check soon.
When you hear "check", fall asleep!
If you fall asleep now,
I have to cover the whole cost!
Now he's pretending it's training
so he doesn't have to pay.
What a stingy pest.
It's a babe! Wake up!
Aren't you gonna pay?
Sleep!
A babe! Wake up!
Isn't this supposed to be
training for your mind's eye?
You really oughta...
Sleep!
If you fall asleep for real,
you don't gotta pay!
Okay, so...
What do you do if the waitress
with the check is a babe?
Well, I'd pay it myself, obviously!
Ugh.
How did it go?
Have you opened your mind's eye yet?
Yeah, totally!
We'd like a dodgeball rematch!
Okay. Then perhaps I should go all-out!
Is she going to wake up?
O-Our princess stood up!!
She's not moving.
Is she holding back until the battle?
Everyone, stay on guard!
Huh?
Is she standing in her sleep?
No.
It's the first time she's stood in 10 years,
so her feet are all tingly.
I'll go first this time!
She looks intense...
She can't still be asleep, right?
Chup!
Snow White's going all-out!
Be careful!
How's that?!
Wh-Whoa...
Not bad.
Vinsant!
Got it!
Take this! Our You-Can't-Run-Because-
We-Can-See-You-With-Our-Mind's-Eyes...
Bazooka!
As if!
Oh no, she saw it with her own mind's eye!
Did you read my moves?!
How's that?!
Good going, Chup!
You think you defeated me already?
What do you mean?
My heart is a dungeon.
And there's another me deep within it.
You haven't defeated me
until you've defeated her, no?
Another Snow White inside her?
What's this about? Are you saying
you have two personalities?
Yes!
The princess on the inside is responsible
for giving us her fortunes and advice.
Huh?!
Alright! We'll send that ball flying
towards the Snow White on the inside!
How are we supposed to do that?
If you wish to enter my heart,
then fall asleep touching me,
and send your consciousnesses inside.
But do you think you can defeat the other me?
Hm? Is this...
...the door to her heart?
It's quite sturdy, how elegant.
It was a common style
for castles around 300 years ago.
That must be the Snow White on the inside.
She's so slim and beautiful.
She almost looks like Melora from behind!
You're right.
Good job making it this far.
Perhaps I should greet you...
...with a kiss!
Get back here!!
I'mma kiss you!!
Chup, if we briefly fall asleep
we can get out of this!
Good idea! Wait, we're already asleep!
Dang it!
I'mma kiss you!!
Stop it!
Get away!
shobokure gao no mobukyara domo ga
On and on these tired old NPCs
iiwake shinagara aruiteru
Keep walking around excusing themselves
itsumo miteiru michisugara
As I took the same old path again
mita koto mo nai wakuwaku wo mita
I found the thrill I've sought for my whole life
itsumade shibonda mama nano
Just how long will I keep drooping around like this?
minikui ahiru no mama nano
How long will I stay an ugly duckling?
ima no reberu wa ichi dakedo
I'm still only level one
ima ni mitero yo sono uchi JUMP UP
But watch me, soon I'll jump up
saikin no wakai mon wa tte
"Why, kids these days..."
toshiyori domo ga boyai teru kedo
...Our old boomers grumble and complain
soro soro omei henjou da
But it's not too late to clear my name
iya ga ou ni mo mattanashi daze
I might not like it, but I can't wait any longer
ketsu no ana kara jetto funsha daaa
I gotta blast free from my cowardly shell!!
ore wa itsuka hana ni naru
Give me time and I'll bloom like a flower
sora ni nobiru hana ni naru
A flower spread out to the sky
kimi ni todoku hana ni naru
The flower that reaches you
Where am I...?
Darefalcon, we did it!
You've finally reached
Dragon Chakra.
Dragon Chakra?
Was that what I felt earlier?
It was unleashed thanks to your aversion
to being kissed by the inner Snow White.
Nice!
So, Darefalcon!
You've defeated a lot today,
so I'll give you a special deal!
Huh?
Didn't we just defeat the strongest being?
Why didn't you stamp all of them?
There's one opponent remaining.
None other than me.
What?!
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone!
What are you teaching us about today?
Today's lesson is on Dragon Knights!
Dragon Knights
"Dragon Knight" is a title
given to dragon-blooded people
who endure training to receive
great powers.
The legendary warrior who sealed away
the dragon overlord Scardon was one of them!
I'm gonna become one too!
I won't give up, no matter what!
Good, Chup! Don't forget that!
Next Time
The final trial: defeating Darefalcon!
It's an all-out battle,
with the help of our monsters!
Which monsters would you pick?
A Challenge to the Holy Dragon!
The Final Match of Ups and Downs!
Next time: "A Challenge to the Holy Dragon!
The Final Match of Ups and Downs!"
Alright, it's time for a big adventure!