This is Snack World, the hallowed ground of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam and people have handy smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
And my name's Chup!
My village was burnt down by the evil land-destroying merchant Vinegar Khan,
so I've embarked on a journey to get my revenge 1000-fold!
The tickets to King Oyster City, where Vinegar is, cost 20 million gillan.
So I'm on an adventure searching for big treasure to make loads of cash!
[Chup humming theme song]
Alright, let's go on another big adventure today!
Hey, catch it!
Oink...oink!
WHAAAT?!
I was afraid of this.
[Roaring]
Butako, you look epic!
Huh?
I don't think it's just the outside that changed.
She must not recognize us.
Butako! It's me, Chup!
[Roaring]
She's under the full control of the Dragon Heart!
Ep. 18: Fury Unleashed! Reunions with Vinegar
Butako...
There's nothing we can do...what we just saw was likely her true nature.
It's like the girl's gone feral...
Butako...she was in distress...
It was cool but...I hate it!
Didn't this happen because she swallowed the Dragon Heart?
You think so?
Yeah, and come to think of it, if we leave that place like this, what will happen to Melora?
Good point, she's still trapped in there, isn't she?
If we don't think quick, she'll be crushed flat as a pancake.
No! I won't let her be crushed!
You must not worry.
- Huh?
- Oh, it's you!
Princess Melora is being kept safe in a chamber.
I switched the door with a sturdy one called N-Deztructibul.
You sure have a thing for doors...
You little prick...this is all your fault!
Aah!
[Grunts] Ow...
- Why, you...!
- [Mayone] Hold on, Chup!
You know this guy saved our beans twice now, right?
Get out of here! The exit's that way!
Hm, so he did.
We could've died back there.
Mmm...my point is, Vintaro, you...!
Hey now! I told you not to use my screen name!
My name is Vinsant.
Vinsant
Vinsant?
An elegant name, is it not?
Self-absorbed much?
Please listen. This was the only way I could acquire the Dragon Heart.
What's your goal, man?
What do you need the Dragon Heart for?!
That I cannot say.
Spill it!!
I cannot.
[Grumbles]
Are you certain the princess is safe?
Yes.
Right now, she's probably crying away...
[Crying]
This drama is so tearjerking!
I will release the princess once the Dragon Heart is safely in my possession.
Then why do you want the Dragon Heart so bad?
Spill it!!
I cannot.
Fine, don't spill!!
Dang it, I thought I had him there!
What are you doing...?
Moving on. You shouldn't worry, for I'm not your enemy.
Grr...
But that bothers me, are you an enemy or an ally to us?
You should be more worried about that pig-nosed dragon.
- Hm?
- Huh?
[Vinsant] Her body has been taken over by the ancient Dragon Heart.
If we let her be, it will take full control of her heart.
Leaving her nothing but an evil dragon.
An evil dragon?!
What do we do?!
There's only one option.
Satan Blade!
Mwa-ha-ha-ha-ha... Phantom.
Satan Blade.
I must slay her before she turns into an evil dragon!
[Gasps]
Help me out.
If we work together here, we can still take her out.
Off we go.
Don't!
You can't slay Butako, she's our friend!
Then what do you suggest? Got any better plans?
I'll...think of something!
[Grunts]
We don't have time for this!
[Chup groans]
This isn't nap time!!
It's no use...I've been moving around for a whole day, I feel all dizzy...
I'm also starting to feel a bit hungry...
Is this really the best time to stop and eat?
Sweets, sweets, who wants some sweets?
Aha, a sweets stand!
Well, that's new to me.
Oh, Gob-san, not you too!
I already said there's no time!
Hey, now, a sweet pick-me-up is just what we need to keep ourselves up and at it!
Sounds good! Let's stop to eat!
How many times to I have to say...
Tons of sweets! Ohagi, dango...
Wait, they've got ohagi?!
- [Stomach grumbling]
- Uh...
[Chuckles]
Haha, wait for me, guys! Ohagi!
Sweets, who wants some sweets?
Oh, welcome!
[Both gleaming]
[Pepperon] It all looks so yummy!
I get the feeling based on what I see that the ohagi are your specialty.
You've got a good eye, kind sir!
Then four ohagi, please!
[Mayone] Uh, hold up just a sec.
Hm? What's wrong?
Doesn't this guy seem an awful lot like a zombie to you?
Huh?
Wh-Whaaaat?! What'cha talkin' about?
Mayone, how could you be so rude to a tradesman?
Yeah, that's kinda harsh, Mayone.
Ma'am, even if I don't look it, I'm super full'a energy!
- [Mayone] Are you now?
- Yes.
Mayone, you watch too much foreign drama.
Y-You think so? I guess I have been watching "The Hiking Dead" a bit much lately...
Might be making me a tad paranoid.
[Gob-san] Mmm, this is heaven!
[Chup] Hey, Gob-san, you can't get a head start!
Hey, he's giving his seal of approval!
[Vendor] Feel free to dig in, everyone!
Well, he likes it, I'm sure it's delicious.
Time to eat!
[Gob-san gasps]
- Huh?
[Gob-san grunting]
[Gob-san hurling]
Apologies for the interruption. Snack World will be back momentarily.
Be right back
[Gob-san groaning]
That was awful...
Don't tell me...hm?
[Sniff sniff] Blegh! I knew it, it's rotten!
Wha-a-a-a-at?! You really are rude.
It's 'cuz you're a zombie! They're rotten because you had your hands all over them.
Ma'am, are your eyes workin' right? I sure ain't dead, am I?
I ain't never been bitten by a zombie either!
There's no way I'm a zombie!
Mayone, we told you you were being rude.
But she's not wrong, this is a little rotten.
Are they, now? Then you can just throw 'em away.
I'll get straight to work on some kinako ohagi!
Ooh, I'll take kinako!
♪ Just add a douse...of kinako! ♪
Stop right there! That isn't kinako!
It's Zombie Powder!
What?
Wha-wha-wha-WHA-A-A-AT?!
You must've ate some of it, didn't you?!
No, you see, I traveled all 'round the world trying different types of flour with glutinous rice to see what fits the best...
Then I tried this baby, and it tasted great! I just can't stop using it, and, uh...
So you ate it? And so that makes you a zombie, right?
Wha-wha-wha-WHA-A-A-AT?!
This must all be news to him, huh?
Would be real nice if he stopped screaming.
[Vendor screaming]
[Grunts] What on earth are they doing?
- [Phone ringing]
- Yes?
You wish for me to get rid of it? I understand.
[Sigh] It must be done.
You're tellin' me I'm a zombie?
[Gob-san] He is Andead, an anko Monster who turned into a zombie.
Andead
So you're a Monster, huh?!
Grr...gosh darn it!!
Andead
You've left me no choice but to off all of y'all!
- [All gasp]
- Why are you acting up now?
Now that he's self-aware, we need to be more alert. Snapedia says...
Andead can use rotten ohagi to manipulate...
err...the stamina of his opponents...
Uggh...it's back...it's coming out the bottom this time...nope, the top too...!!
It's a combo! A combo!!
[Hurls]
Apologies for the interruption. Snack World will be back momentarily.
Be right back
[Gob-san groaning]
That was awful...
...Huh?
What the...you already defeated him?
Yep, he's a wimp!
Though he probably isn't dead if he's a zombie...
- Hm?
- Huh?
What's in the chest? Hm...it's...
- [Gob-san] A healing tonic?
- Nope.
It's an energy tonic, it boosts your body's metabolism.
Wh-Wh-Who cares!? Gimme!
Haah...agh! Again!
It's coming from the bottom...no, the top-- no, the bottom...where is it coming from?!
[Hurls]
Apologies for the interruption. Snack World will be back momentarily.
Be right back
Definitely boosted his metabolism.
[Gob-san groaning]
That was awful...hm?
- Alright, off we go!
- Yeah!
Wh...What did I miss?
We came up with a plan.
We call it: "Operation: Wake Up, Butako!"
Well, what's the plan?
- Let's get a move on!
- Roger that!
D...Don't leave me hanging!!
Vinsant, we're back! Huh?
[Pepperon] He's gone...
Maybe he's breaking for tea?
- [Notification ping]
- Oh, it's Vintaro!
"Come to the back of Pilafbeak."
"Hurry up!!"
As you wish, miss. I will get rid of it.
Thank you. I just can't get into this drama at all. Get rid of it.
Vinny, I don't understand your tastes.
Excuse me! I used to watch nearly 300 movies every year...
Is something the matter?
[Light gasp] My apologies, miss...
Princess Melora!
Alright, Vintaro! Hands off the princess!
Who are you calling Vintaro? I told you...
[Melora] Hey, Vinny?
Can I like, go home now?
- Huh?
- "Vinny?"
You'll have to stick tight a little longer.
Ugh, I'm so bored! Do you got any better dramas?
I have Season 2 of the same show.
Oh, come on! Seriously, "Hiking Dead" though...
The first episode was good and all, I cried a bit, but by episode 3 I was bored to death.
It's so slow!
Episode 3 is supposed to lead in to episode 4!!
Mayone, chill!
What's the deal between those two?
Do you have a plan yet?
I do! But before that, what's the deal with you and the princess? Spill!
I cannot!
Spill it!
Then show, don't tell!
I cannot!
[Chup whining]
Are you ready? Right behind that... [Screams]
The door...it's broken!!
Butako must have broken it earlier.
Dang it! Now I have to swap this one out with N-Deztructibul too!!
He sure has a thing for doors.
I won't let her get away with this any longer!
You want to feed her ohagi...? What kind of plan is that?!
She'll want to regurgitate the rotten ohagi and the Dragon Heart with it.
Though it could also come out the other end.
Andead!
Undead-dead-dead-deaddy-dead!
Undead-deaddy-dead! Undead!
Wha-wha-wha-wha-WHAAAT? Uh...huh?
Andead, we need you to feed Butako your ohagi!
That dragon, right? Your wish is my command, sir!
Do you think this will work?
It's like my grandmother once said!
It's worth a shot! We're having hot pot!
It's worth a shot.
We're having hot pot.
-Tome
Ahaa! That must've been one wonderful night!
Hot pot's a bit of a heavy supper, you think?
That bothers you?
Here you are, sir!
Sweet!
How will you get Butako to eat it? She has a very strong sense of smell.
Hah!
[Roaring]
- She ate it!
- Ooh!
Now spit it out, Butako! Preferably with the Dragon Heart too!
It didn't work?
Her stomach must be a lot stronger too now.
Bring it on! I'll just have to make even more!
- Here you are!
- Hah!
This ain't looking too good...
I'm all outta glutinous rice...
So this plan is a failure...?
- [Andead] Nuh-uh.
- Huh?
Sir...you mustn't forget...my head is an ohagi too!!
Wow, really?
I can see it now!
I have an idea...tear off just a bit of the corner of my head, then...
Hm? Hm...uh...huh??
Good idea. We'll have her swallow you whole.
Wh-wh-wh-WHAAAT?!
One, two...!
- Fire!
- Have a nice day!!
- She ate him!
- What now?
[Roaring]
She must be using her fire to deal with it!
That explains why she's A-OK.
He really died for nothing...
[Gob-san] Our apologies, Andead.
Butako! It's me, Chup! Snap out of it!
Chup, be careful!
It's okay! Butako and I are good pals! Right, Butako?
- [Roaring]
- Yowch!
- Chup!
- Chup, no!
[Grunting]
He can't breathe, can he?!
This is real bad!
This is my chance to teach her a lesson!
Don't you dare!
You can't slay her!!
Do you want to die?!
Butako, she's...she's my friend!
- [Groaning]
- Aah!
Butako...!
There must still be a bit of her left in there!
[Vinsant] Pepperon, right?
Huh?
I'll distract the dragon as much as I can!
There, I want you to strike its belly with as much force as you can!
If all goes well, she should spit out the Dragon Heart!
You can count on me!
Ow-ow-ow-ow...
- [Roaring]
- [Vinsant] Butako!
He's so cool!
[Grunts]
♪ Neh, neh, pig-nose, pig-nose!
♪ Yer mother's got a pig nose! Spank my butt!
The hell?
He's breaking character big time.
[Roaring]
Now, Pepperon!
Roger!
Hi-yah!!
- Why?!
[Both scream]
[Gasp]
Gob-san...Gob-saaaan!!
Wha?
-[Pepperon] Gob-san's back! -[Chup] Huh? Why?
That's it!
[In sync] Gob-san's filthier than a rotten ohagi!
Just like you to hurt me at a time like this.
Guys, look!
[Chup] It's the Dragon Heart!
[All gasp]
Huh?
Oiiink!
Butako! [Laughing]
My god...that took a while, but it's finally mine.
[Rumbling]
- What the?
- Huh?
[Vinegar chuckling]
[Chup] V-Vinegar!
Mom!! Dad!!
Where is everyone...?
[Cackling]
Grr...
Tch...
I'll take this Dragon Heart, thank you very much!
Damn it!
[Laughing]
We gotta follow him! Beaujolais!
Vinsant!
If this has to do with Vinegar, you better be ready to fess up!
Fine. Hop on.
Let's follow them!
Yeah!
The devil dragon?
Right. The devil dragon who once posed a threat to our world, Scardon.
It was vanquished by the legendary Dragon Knights and sealed away beneath the earth.
In order to bring Scardon back to life, you need the soul of a dragon - the Dragon Heart.
Vinegar is using the power of the devil dragon Scardon to make Monsters across the continent go wild.
All to maximize the profits from the weapons Vinegar Enterprise sells.
I can't let him get away with that!
I posed as his henchman so that I could grab it before he did.
Vinsant, if this is so important, why didn't you open up to us about it?
I wasn't looking to rely on you guys.
That said...if Scardon is brought back to life, you can kiss this world goodbye.
I won't let him be brought back!
We're definitely not catching up to them.
Well, she does still only have a permit.
You need to do better in class...
Oink...
[Mayone] No no, Butako, hang in there!
[Butako] Oi-iii-nk!
[Chuckling]
Vinegar!
Fairy Crystal Sword!
- Don't!
- Take this!
1,000-Fold 10,000-Fold Payback Attack!!
[Yelps]
Ow-ow-ow-ow...
The only way to cross this barrier is through the railroad.
Didn't you know that?
Gosh darn it!
[Cackling]
Wait for me, Vinegar. I will take you down at all costs!
konbini de kuda wo maku ukiyo wo samayou wakoudo yo
All you youngsters loitering about your lives,
shrouding the convenience stores
omaera wa genjitsu ni torinokosaresugi andeddo
You’re like undead who have left behind reality
itsumade son na koto kurikaesu no o-tsu-ka-re
How long are you going to keep doing this?
Don't you get tired of this same old routine?
hashiridase yo ENDLESS ROAD
Run forth through the endless road
koetemiroyo BORDERLINE
Go on past that borderline
sekai wa mugen ni hirogaru kouya
The world is an endless, limitless wilderness
omae no dokyou wo tameshiteiru
Where you can put your courage to the test
sumafo nankaja kensaku dekinai
It’s not something you can search for on your smartphone
sekai wa mugen ni hirogaru PARADISE
The world is an endless, limitless paradise
omaera wa giragira no
Soon you'll come to life taking in the blazing sun
taiyou kuratte ikiteiru
Raws
Translation/Typesetting/Timing
ED Karaoke
QC/Review
Raws
Translation/Typesetting/Timing
ED Karaoke
QC/Review
AnimeLand (BSJ)
Lumpstud
Noroino Hanako
Jewelforest
(Specter Subs)
AnimeLand (BSJ)
Lumpstud
Noroino Hanako
Jewelforest
(Specter Subs)
[Sighs]
Aaaah! Melora!
I'm home!
I missed you! ...Ow.
Quest
Rescue Princess Melora
[Melora] Ugh, I was bored out of my mind.
Wouldn't it hurt to say thanks?
Oh, uh, your majesty?
Hm? Oh, right! Your reward!
[Giggling]
Hmph!
Like I said, your reward is a medium...
...of her love!
What?
Don't tell me...
It's just a medium-size of her custom figurine...
Mhm! A medium of Melora's love!
Like the medium in large, medium, and small...
Large
Medium
Small
But I have that already...in large and medium!
Now I have a dupe!
Oh, I should've seen this coming anyways...
Can you stop tumbling around in here?
There's one more thing.
Here you go. A special ticket for the Transcontinental Railroad.
What?!
Did I hear you right?
The Transcontinental Railroad?
A special ticket for it?!
Yup. With this, you can go to King Oyster City.
[Moaning]
Chup?! Come on, didn't you hear him?
Yeah, yeah, King Oyster City, blah blah...
WHAT?! I can go to King Oyster City?!
Yup, and it's a cabin that can fit up to four people.
So you can all go together!
Oink!
Don't these cost 20 million gillan?!
Yeah, that.
- Chup!
- Yay, Chup!
With this, we're one step closer to Vinegar!
Oiiink!
Go get him, lad!
And buy me a souvenir!
- Hm?
- Oink?
[Chuckles]
[Chup humming theme tune]
Alright! Let's go!!
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone!
What are you teaching us about today?
"Transcontinental Railroad"
Today's lesson is about the Transcontinental Railroad!
The Transcontinental Railroad is a train that makes a great big lap around the continent that normal trains cannot make.
It's our way of transport that can cross the magic barriers.
But the tickets aren't cheap, they cost a whopping 20 million gillan.
Pretty much every adventurer out there wants one!
Wait for me, Vinegar!!
Next Time
[Chup] I finally have a ticket to the Transcontinental Railroad!
We gotta hurry to King Oyster City, where Vinegar is!
Our adventure enters a completely new setting!
Next time: "Chup Adventures Into a New Realm"!
Chup Adventures Into a New Realm
Alright, it's time for a big adventure!