Coming up on Punirunes...
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
The show is squishing!
Let's play, Punirunes!
Punirunes.
Before we knew it, these creatures
began to inhabit the human world.
They're squishsterious and soft to the touch!
They all love to be squished.
There's also fun, adorable puni-pals aplenty.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Kachi-Freezy Dungeon Quest♪
"Kachi-Freezy Dungeon Quest♪"
The Punirunes are here in Kachikochiland
in search of a Punistal fragment.
Jewelrune says today their quest
will be in the Kachi-Freezy Dungeon.
"Getting through this dungeon
will be no easy task," it says.
"Many an adventurer have
gone into it,
"but none have come out."
"But fear not. We can clear the dungeon
so long as we work together!"
Item Shop
They stop at a shop to pick up some gear
before venturing into the dungeon.
Everyone follows Jewelrune the lancer's example
by picking items that suit them best.
Coolrune picks the mage's hat.
Loverune picks the priest's staff.
Enerune picks the fighter's headband.
Ururune picks the entertainer's hat.
And surprisingly, Airune picks
the hero's sword.
This completes the party of Airune the hero!
Now, they set off towards
the Kachi-Freezy Dungeon at last!
How chilling, befitting a dungeon
that many an adventurer failed to clear.
Airune's remark sparks a fire in its party.
What a picture perfect hero.
Alas...
The hero is now preoccupied
collecting freezy rocks.
You're supposed to be searching
for a Punistal fragment.
A freezy bat blocks
their path.
A freezy bat blocks their path.
The freezy bat flees.
Enerune the fighter makes
the freezy bat flee.
The Kachi-Freezy Dungeon
is a maze to navigate,
making it hard to locate
the Punistal fragment.
The party is starting to run
out of stamina.
Stamina replenished.
The love of Loverune the priest
replenishes the party's stamina.
Stamina replenished.
Airune found something.
Is it the fragment?
The hero is preoccupied
collecting freezy rocks.
A dark fog surrounds them, clouding their vision.
What will they do?
It is time for Coolrune the mage
to shine.
Coolrune the mage's cleaning spell
wonderfully tidies away the fog.
"Hang in there," says Airune.
When suddenly...
A giant freezy boulder
blocks their path!
A giant freezy boulder blocks their path!
"It's time to show us what
an entertainer can do!" says Airune.
What could the entertainer's
special skill be?
Ururune does a
squishsterious dance!
Ururune does a squishsterious dance!
"What the heck?" go the other Punirunes.
However...
Ururune continues its
squishsterious dance.
"Buy me some time," asks Jewelrune.
"I'll think of something."
The freezy boulder comes to a stop.
What will Jewelrune do in the meantime?
What's this? A hammer?
And aren't these freezy rocks...
Jewelrune begins crafting.
Meanwhile...
The freezy boulder starts to move.
The Punirunes have bought
all the time they can.
Is this their end?
Jewelrune used the freezy rocks
to craft a huge baseball bat.
Jewelrune the lancer
obtains the Punistal fragment.
"I didn't know you were so good
at crafting things!" says Airune.
"Once we get all twelve Punistal fragments,"
Jewelrune responds, "I can make something even cooler!"
"Let's go home."
"Something cooler, huh?
I wonder what it could be..."
...ponders Airune.
The Puni-Puni Squestion!
I will present a question
based on the events of the episode.
Try your best to remember!
The Punirunes went off on a quest
to a dungeon in Kachikochiland.
With Jewelrune the lancer,
Coolrune the mage,
Loverune the priest,
Enerune the fighter,
Ururune the entertainer,
and Airune the hero,
their party set foot into the dungeon together.
Plenty perils awaited them.
Squestion time!
Jewelrune is a talented crafter.
What did it create by
banging its hammer against freezy rocks?
Give your frozen brain a squish
to find the answer!
Here's the answer!
Here's the answer...
A baseball bat!
Did you get it puni-right?
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
You're still awake, Jewelrune?
Sorry, you're having trouble sleeping
because of my scary story, aren't you?
Next Time
There's someone outside the window, Airune?
I don't see anyone.
No one's there... right?
Huh? What on earth is that?!
Next Time
Next time: "A Squishy Scary(?) Story♪"
A Squishy Scary(?) Story♪
"Puni" in next time!