Coming up on Punirunes...
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
The show is squishing!
Let's play, Punirunes!
Punirunes.
Before we knew it, these creatures
began to inhabit the human world.
They're squishsterious and soft to the touch!
They all love to be squished.
There's also fun, adorable puni-pals aplenty.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Kachi-Freezy Jewelrune♪
"Kachi-Freezy Jewelrune♪"
The Punirunes are having fun as always.
This is Airune, a perky Punirune
full of curiosity.
Airune
Loverune
Loverune is everyone's idol
who is full of big love.
Ururune is great at drawing.
Ururune
Coolrune
Coolrune is fashionable and tidy.
Enerune is energetic
and super athletic.
Enerune
Enerune! I'll give you a bath
when we get home, okay?
Aoi
This is Aoi.
She lives with Enerune.
So squishy! This is the life!
Yuka
Yuka here lives with Airune
and loves everything squishy.
Oh, you want gummies?
Punirunes love to eat squishy things.
Looks like they're playing
hide and seek.
Who could this be?
"I'm certain of it."
"You must be the hero!" it says.
Jewelrune
It turns out its name
is Jewelrune.
Airune introduces itself as well.
For whatever reason,
it's asking Airune to come with it.
But Airune's in the middle of hide and seek.
Airune ended up having a hard time saying no
to Jewelrune's sparkly stare.
And then...
S-S-Something super squishsterious happened!
"This is Kachikochiland," says Jewelrune.
Kachi Kochi Land
"I have brought you here because..."
Off it goes.
In squishy form...
But in freezy form...
"We must together search for
the Punistal fragments," says Jewelrune.
They are legendary treasures
spoken of through Kachikochiland.
It is said all twelve form the Punistal,
which can produce rare items.
And so, Airune and Jewelrune
set off to adventure.
Could a Punistal fragment
be inside this cave?
In squishy form, it's quite clingy.
But in freezy form, it is brave.
Two sides of Jewelrune!
Airune has an idea!
In squishy form, this sprung it up into the air.
But in freezy form...
What will become of Airune?
Where were you, Airune?
Wait, huh?
Who's this?
Jewelrune, is it?
You're from a place called
Kachikochiland? Interesting!
So adorable!
That is how Airune made
yet another new puni-pal.
The Puni-Puni Squestion!
I will present a question
based on the events of the episode.
Try your best to remember!
This is Jewelrune.
It had a marvelous encounter with Airune
during the latter's game of hide and seek.
Jewelrune is a new puni-pal
who hails from Kachikochiland.
Squestion time!
When the Punistal fragments are gathered,
they produce rare items.
How many fragments did it say
were needed?
Give your frozen brain a squish
to find the answer!
Here's the answer...
Here's the answer!
They are legendary treasures
spoken of through Kachikochiland.
It is said all twelve form the Punistal,
which can produce rare items.
The answer is twelve!
Did you get it puni-right?
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Glad to see you made a new puni-pal, Airune!
Jewelrune, you made a lot of friends,
Next Time
got to meet Komugi,
and experienced lots of new things!
Wait, your first rolled ice punieam
went missing?
Togerune swiped it from you?!
Next Time
Jewelrune Makes New Friends♪
Next time: "Jewelrune Makes New Friends♪"
"Puni" in next time!