Coming up on Punirunes...
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
The show is squishing!
Let's play, Punirunes!
Punirunes.
Before we knew it, these creatures
began to inhabit the human world.
They're squishsterious and soft to the touch!
They all love to be squished.
There's also fun, adorable puni-pals aplenty.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Gaorune
Makes Everything Squishy♪
"Gaorune Makes Everything Squishy♪"
Airune and Enerune are sumo wrestling.
Eneruneyama wins!
Airune has become even squishier than normal!
Gaorune
This is Gaorune.
Looks like its roar turns anything
it hits squishy.
I'm home!
Oh?
Is this a new friend?
So you're Gaorune! Nice to meet you!
Huh? Pet Airune?
What?!
You got squishier! How?
Gaorune did this?
That's so cool!
It's not squishy at all...
Aoi made a model of an octopus
during arts and crafts,
but is sad because it didn't come out squishy.
How do I get it to be squishy?
Huh?
Whoa, what? It's squishy now!
My little octopus!
So puni-puni!
"Let's turn a bunch of stuff squishy
and make people happuni!" suggests Airune.
Yuka is making a drawing
for arts and crafts.
However...
This stinks.
And my hand is tired...
Airune wants to support Yuka.
What the?!
My colored pencil is all squishy!
I can't draw with this!
Is it ready?
Alright!
Darling, is the baguette done?
You bet! All hardened up and ready to—
You're kidding me!
You know baguettes have to be hard!
Or did your brain get hard instead?
H-Honey...
I know!
This is no baguette!
It's a nunchuck!
That's it, Darling!
Don't think, feel!
Is the bread ready yet?
Looking cool, Darling!
(Please don't play with your food.)
What on earth are you two doing?
Do think a bit before
letting your brain get too soft.
Airune and friends
try to cheer Gaorune up.
But Gaorune has already decided
it doesn't want to roar ever again.
Airune and friends go searching
for squishy and yummy food to give Gaorune.
The bowl became squishy,
and the jar is crushing it down!
This could spell trouble
for the Punirunes!
All done!
Rolled ice punieam!
Thanks to you, Gaorune,
Dad finally cleared his mind
and came up with a new bread product!
Three, please!
I'll have two!
Is it ready yet?
Darling, is it ready?
Eeyup, all done!
Nunchuck Bread!
It's cool and it's delicious!
The customers love it!
And thanks to this squishy colored pencil,
my hands aren't getting tired out!
Thanks a ton, Gaorune!
Squishiness saves the day again!
Huh?
What the heck?!
The Puni-Puni Squestion!
I will present a question
based on the events of the episode.
Try your best to remember!
Airune makes a new puni-pal: Gaorune.
Its roar turns anything it hits squishy.
It made everyone happuni
by turning things squishy.
You know baguettes have to be hard!
Or did your brain get hard instead?
H-Honey...
Squestion time!
What kind of bread product did Yuka's dad
come up with when his brain got squished out?
Give your frozen brain a squish
to find the answer!
Here's the answer...
Here's the answer!
All done!
Nunchuck Bread!
The answer is Nunchuck Bread!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Airune, Jewelrune!
You're going to Kachikochiland today, right?
Oh yeah. Jewelrune, you lived in Kachikochiland
before you came here, right?
Next Time
Oh?
What's the matter, Jewelrune?
Have you been keeping
some sort of secret from us?
Next Time
Next time: "The Secret Jewelrune♪"
The Secret Jewelrune♪
"Puni" in next time!