Coming up on Punirunes...
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
The show is squishing!
Let's play, Punirunes!
Punirunes.
Before we knew it, these creatures
began to inhabit the human world.
They're squishsterious and soft to the touch!
They all love to be squished.
There's also fun, adorable puni-pals aplenty.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
A Squishy Recovery
with Puni-Meds♪
"A Squishy Recovery with Puni-Meds♪"
Airune and Jewelrune are full of energy.
Although... something's off.
"You have to get some rest!"
Loverune works fast.
It looks like their friends will look after them
while Yuka is at school.
There's no getting past Loverune.
Ururune draws a picture to cheer
Airune and Jewelrune up.
All done!
Oh no! This isn't good!
Nice and cool!
That's your reaction?!
Loverune can't get a break.
What's this?
Looks like that's the culprit!
Puni-Med
This is a puni-med.
One hit from it...
And it's gone!
Oh dear! They're out of puni-meds!
Everyone is going out to Puniland
to get Airune and Jewelrune more puni-meds.
They want to come along, but...
Now that's tough love.
Ururune asks them to let them handle this.
Off they go!
They split into two parties
to look for puni-meds.
It's asking if it can spare any puni-meds
for Airune and Jewelrune.
Oshirune rushes down upon hearing
that its idol is in danger!
This should be enough!
Loverune and Ururune make it back first.
Th-They're everywhere! This is bad!
Marvelous!
Super-fast love power!
Ururune does what it can!
Almost there!
O-Oh my goodness!
There's no end to this!
Its love power is at its limit!
Oh? Ururune's tears froze them in place!
That's it!
Go, Ururune!
It's time for Ururune and Loverune's
combination attack:
Urutralove Attack!
There's the final boss!
Oh no! They used them all up!
Enerune and Coolrune return.
"Loverune... Ururune...
we leave the rest to you."
Super Urutralove Tornado!
They're all better now!
I'm home!
Airune, Jewelrune, how are you feeling?
You look much better now!
Yuka!
Have you washed your hands?
Yep, all clean!
You're so squishy as always!
There's no better Punirune
than a healthy one.
Good work today, Loverune and Ururune.
The Puni-Puni Squestion!
I will present a question
based on the events of the episode.
Try your best to remember!
Something was off about Airune and Jewelrune,
so they were put to bed to rest up.
Their friends looked after them,
but it turned into a disaster.
Squestion time!
What item was used to heal
Airune and Jewelrune?
Give your frozen brain a squish
to find the answer!
1. Punicine...
2. Puni-meds...
3. Capsurunes...
or 4. Urutralove Tornado?
Here's the answer!
Here's the answer...
The answer is puni-meds!
Make sure to wash your hands
and rinse your mouth to stay healthy!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Jewelrune, we're about to throw
an awesome Christmas party!
I heard Tomorune's back too!
Yeah! We're gonna have yummy food
and exchange presents...
Next Time
Wait, oh no! All the presents are gone!
Don't worry! Tomorune and Airune
will fix this!
Next Time
Probably!
Next time: "It's Squishmas! Jewelrune♪ & Tomorune♪"
It's Squishmas!
Jewelrune♪ & Tomorune♪
"Puni" in next time!