Coming up on Punirunes...
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
The show is squishing!
Let's play, Punirunes!
Punirunes.
Before we knew it, these creatures
began to inhabit the human world.
They're squishsterious and soft to the touch!
They all love to be squished.
There's also fun, adorable puni-pals aplenty.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Fairune and the Spark♪
"Fairune and the Spark♪"
Today, the Punirunes are going to Kachikochiland.
Jewelrune laid out the fragments
and is feeling determined.
Of the twelve fragments needed
to make the crown, they need six.
They're halfway there.
"Doesn't matter whether it's 'only half'
or 'already half',
"let's get out there and have a good search!"
What's this?
Ururune, Coolrune, and Loverune
are reading something.
"Fairune—a fairy-like Punirune."
"It's kind at heart,
and surrounded by sparkly lights."
"Wherever Fairune goes, happiness follows."
"Fairune is amazing! So sparkly."
"It must be a very nice Punirune."
All of them are glued to the picture book.
Oh? Who could this be?
Erm, guys! Are you just gonna read
that book all day?
There we go.
Nothing wrong with reading,
but this is a Punistal fragment search day.
"Huh? Haven't we..."
"Yeah, we passed here already."
The fragments won't be so easy to find
in the second half of their search.
What's this? Someone is following them.
Just who is this?
"Did you call?"
"No."
"There really is someone else here!"
"I don't know..."
"It went that way! I saw it!"
Jewelrune's in danger!
A giant boulder is rolling its way!
Indeed. This here is Fairune.
It's a Punirune with squishsterious powers.
It took an interest in Airune and friends
and followed them.
Fairune
But unlike in the picture book,
it's somewhat mischievous.
Fairune's sparkles have granted Airune
the ultra-powerful state of Kachikochi Spark!
Kachikochi Spark
With Kachikochi Spark, Airune can sniff out
Punistal fragments in a flash.
Airune is unstoppable now!
In a shocking turn of events,
Airune has quickly found four Punistal fragments!
Kachikochi Spark is a force
not to be reckoned with.
Everyone shares their joys with a feast.
So it really is true that
wherever Fairune is, happiness follows.
"Alright! Let's keep it up
and get the rest of the fragments!"
I have unfortunate news:
Kachikochi Spark has a time limit.
"Just ask Fairune to turn you
into Kachikochi Spark again!"
Fairune has suddenly vanished.
Fairies do as they please, after all.
"We did make puni-pals, didn't we?"
"I wonder."
"I think we did."
The Puni-Puni Squestion!
I will present a question
based on the events of the episode.
Try your best to remember!
Squestion time!
What is the name of this sparkly Punirune
with squishsterious powers?
Here's the answer...
Here's the answer!
This is Fairune,
a Punirune who has its own picture book.
Now for another squestion!
What state did Fairune's sparkles grant Airune?
Here's the answer...
Here's the answer!
The answer is Kachikochi Spark!
Good for you, finding all those Punistal fragments!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Say what?!
Cuprune opened up a cuppunicake store
in Puniland?
They must be so yummy!
I wish I could go...
Next Time
But since its store isn't popular,
you're helping attract customers! Good luck!
Next Time
Next time: "Project: Cuprune♪"
Project: Cuprune♪
"Puni" in next time!