Coming up on Punirunes...
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
The show is squishing!
Let's play, Punirunes!
Punirunes.
Before we knew it, these creatures
began to inhabit the human world.
They're squishsterious and soft to the touch!
They all love to be squished.
There's also fun, adorable puni-pals aplenty.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Let's Go to Kachikochiland♪
"Let's Go to Kachikochiland♪"
Airune tells everyone the story
of Jewelrune bringing it to Kachikochiland.
Airune got crystallized and went on an adventure,
where it obtained one of the Punistal fragments.
Now all their friends want to go there too!
Off they go to Kachikochiland
in search of a Punistal fragment!
Kachikochiland
They've arrived in Kachikochiland.
Airune and Jewelrune have turned
kachi-freezy.
They look dashing.
It looks like they've brought along items
to help on their journey.
Where could the Punistal fragment be?
This boulder looks breakable.
Perhaps the fragment is on the other side.
Squishy power can't break the boulder.
What did I just say?
This calls for kachi-freezy power.
Alas, there's no Punistal fragment in...
They're gone.
They must find their friends.
They've gotten astray
from their friends.
Ururune is five seconds away
from breaking into tears.
Looks like Loverune has something
that may help them.
What could it be?
I'm not sure how this is helping them
find their way back to Airune and Jewelrune.
Singing did not help.
Dancing did not help.
Unfortunately...
Fashion did not help.
No one has anything useful.
Kachi-Friend
Bell
That's it.
They've spot a Punistal fragment.
Squishy power can't break it.
Which means...
This calls for kachi-freezy power.
Just one isn't enough to break it.
Even with a mightier crash,
the boulder won't budge.
They're all failing individually.
Which means...
they must work together!
Right.
They gave direction too late.
Their directions were inconsistent.
Jewelrune is starting to feel hopeless.
But just before it can give up...
"Let's give it one more shot, together!"
Everyone cheers Jewelrune on.
Through combined forces,
the puni-pals acquire the Punistal fragment.
Jewelrune gives its thanks.
The others all seem to have enjoyed
their trip to Kachikochiland.
Huh? Airune and Jewelrune got kachi-freezy
and did super cool things?
Kachi-freezy, eh?
Kachi-freezy...
Not a chance!
Wait, was that not the right reaction?
How can I help it?
Look at how puni-squishy you are!
So squishy!
Okay, okay. I'll do you next.
They may not have convinced Yuka,
but the Punirunes are happy enough
to be squished.
The Puni-Puni Squestion!
I will present a question
based on the events of the episode.
Try your best to remember!
Enerune, Loverune, Ururune, and Coolrune
visited Kachikochiland for the first time,
and went on an adventure for a Punistal fragment
alongside the kachi-freezy Airune and Jewelrune.
But none of them brought anything helpful.
Squestion time!
What was in Ururune's backpack?
Give your frozen brain a squish
to find the answer!
Here's the answer...
Here's the answer!
Kachi-Friend
Bell
That's it.
The answer is a bell!
Did you get it puni-right?
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Hey, Airune!
Wait, there's two of you?!
Huh? "Airune, you're so cute and perky as always!"
Next Time
"I'm your puni-biggest fan!"
Who is this Punirune?
Next Time
Dang, it's crazy for Airune!
Next time: "Oshirune the Super-Fan♪"
Oshirune the Super-Fan♪
"Puni" in next time!