Coming up on Punirunes...
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
The show is squishing!
Let's play, Punirunes!
Punirunes.
Before we knew it, these creatures
began to inhabit the human world.
They're squishsterious and soft to the touch!
They all love to be squished.
There's also fun, adorable puni-pals aplenty.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
What Could This Be? Nazorune♪
"What Could This Be? Nazorune♪"
The Punirunes are playing in the park today.
Oh? There's someone nearby.
What is it saying?
"What could this be?"
Meet Nazorune.
Nazorune
This Punirune loves a good mystery.
This is its first time in the human world,
so it's surrounded by mysteries.
"What could this be?" it asks.
"Water comes out of it," Airune explains.
Well done! Keep up the mystery-solving!
Nazorune asks its next question straight away.
It asks what this animal is
you don't find in Puniland.
Airune and friends have seen it plenty,
so they must know the answer.
This animal is called a cr—
"The dark one!"
"The high flier!"
"I thought it was something else..." it says.
Coolrune looks confident.
Go on, what's this animal called?
"The coughycough!"
Wait, huh? The... coughycough?
Humans call this animal a crow,
but apparently Punirunes know it as a coughycough.
That's one more mystery
solved for Nazorune,
but the Punirunes continue to be
quite mysterious themselves.
The Punirunes return home.
There's lots of mysteries for Nazorune
in here too.
Komugi the cat is on a walk.
Komugi approaches them.
"He's wagging his tail out of happiness!"
Airune says with confidence.
Looks like a cat wagging its tail...
doesn't always mean it's happy.
Uh-oh, Togerune is waiting to pounce.
"Why did you poke Enerune?" it asks.
Troubled by the barrage of questions,
Togerune took off.
"What could this be for?" asks Nazorune.
Show it how it works, Enerune.
"You use it to jump real high like this!" it says.
Well, I'm not so sure that's
how humans use it...
"That's not it!" says Coolrune.
It's about to show them
the right way to use it.
"It's used to do a cool runway walk!" it says.
That's not—
Well, who am I to say that's wrong?
Perhaps the real wrong is humans ruling
how others use things.
I'm home!
Oh! Who's this little guy?
Nazorune, is it?
Nice to meet you.
Me? I'm Yuka!
Nazorune has never met a human before,
and its curiosity is piqued.
What am I doing?
I'm studying.
It's so hard... I'm tired!
Why am I studying?
Well, obviously...
Wait, why am I studying?
I guess for the same reason
you always ask, "what could this be?"
Nazorune is overjoyed to meet
a fellow mystery-lover.
Phew, finally done!
Funny how you always feel hungry
after finishing your homework, right?
I know!
What's a strangely delicious food?
It's bread!
Let's all go eat some!
What am I to do?!
It's over!
What's wrong, Dad?
Oh, Yuka.
I made a brand new bread...
but I can't decide what to call it on the menu!
I could just call it something standard...
I don't know...
Dang it! I can't come up with a name that fits!
Why is this happening to me?
Why am I a baker, anyways?
What even is bread?
Is it like a dad?
Dad's own thought train
is driving him nuts...
Dadbread? Breadad? Perfect!
Oh, who am I kidding! Aagh!
Huh? This?
It's called French sourdough bread.
Huh? It looks like a bowl?
You can see a flower bud, too?
Good eyes, artist Ururune!
Nazorune?!
It says the marking on this bread
looks like a sparkle too!
It does?
I hadn't looked at it like that!
This bread will make you sparkle with joy!
And I'll call it: the Sparklebread!
It's perfect!
Yeah! Thanks, Nazorune!
Nazorune has always sought out mystery,
and now it helped create an answer.
Way to go, Dad!
Thanks!
This is just a prototype,
so you can have it, Yuka.
Really?
There's plenty to go around too!
Give it a try!
The bread's super yummy, right?
Thanks a toast!
Why does it taste so good?
It's only our specialty!
That, and...
I think it's tastier when you eat together!
They're all giving you a strange look.
Through everything, they all had fun
figuring out mysterious together.
So, did you guys do anything else fun today?
Huh? You saw an animal called a coughycough?
What on earth?
Anyone else know?
There's still plenty of mysteries
left in this world,
and with them, lots of excitement
left for Nazorune.
The Puni-Puni Squestion!
I will present a question
based on the events of the episode.
Try your best to remember!
Nazorune is a Punirune
who loves mystery.
It asked the other Punirunes
a lot of questions today.
What's wrong?
Oh, Yuka.
I made a brand new bread...
but I can't decide what to call it on the menu!
Squestion time!
What does Dad name the bread he made?
Give your frozen brain a squish
to find the answer!
Here's the answer!
Here's the answer...
I hadn't looked at it like that!
This bread will make you sparkle with joy!
The answer is Sparklebread.
And he wouldn't have thought of it
without Nazorune's help.
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Summer time means sea time!
Let's go play!
By the way, Dad told me there's this secret spot
here in the sea!
Next Time
Wait, where are you going?
You're gonna go look for it?!
Next Time
Wait, don't go! There's danger that way!
A Midsummer's Trip by the Seas♪
Next time: "A Midsummer's Trip by the Seas♪"
"Puni" in next time!