Coming up on Punirunes...
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
The show is squishing!
Let's play, Punirunes!
Punirunes.
Before we knew it, these creatures
began to inhabit the human world.
They're squishsterious and soft to the touch!
They all love to be squished.
There's also fun, adorable puni-pals aplenty.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
A Fluffy Flight with Cotton Puni♪
"A Fluffy Flight with Cotton Puni♪"
Puniland
The Punirunes are sunbathing.
It's pointing out that that cloud
looks like an airplane.
And that one's a star.
And those ones look like a microphone,
a hat, and crayons, they say.
Airune sees a gummy in that cloud.
This is Cuprune,
a famous pastry chef in Puniland.
It's making cotton candy—
no, cotton puni for everyone.
These friends are immediately
on board to go eat some.
Already looking for seconds!
You want thirds?!
Oh my! Cuprune's gotten serious!
Oh my! What's going on here?
This is un-puni-vable!
Airune's floating away with the cotton puni!
Talk about a puni-fluffy flight!
Nothing beats a stroll in the sky
after filling your tummy.
That looks so relaxing.
Oh no! Are you okay?
Splendid.
The whole gang's in the air.
They're going to fly up to that gummy cloud.
They gently make their way higher up.
Ururune's doing wonderfully!
Oh no! This is real bad!
They got Ururune to stop crying, but...
Good job!
Airune!
Nice combination!
You're almost to your destination!
They made it safe and sound.
Angelrune and Hikarune
are making a cloud castle.
Oh! They spotted Happyrune!
Angelrune looks happy.
Hikarune... looks timid.
Everyone else wants to make
a cloud castle too.
Fantastic work!
Alright, now. Time to go home.
Huh?
Wait a moment.
"How do we get home exactly...?"
What in the world?!
Stay calm! This situation calls for...
There goes Loverune
with the big love!
The rain has stopped,
bringing about a rainbow.
"I think if we slide down the rainbow,
it'll take us back to the ground!"
What a ride!
Did you enjoy your adventure in the sky?
The Puni-Puni Squestion!
I will present a question
based on the events of the episode.
Try your best to remember!
This is cotton puni.
This food made by Cuprune
is very squishy and fluffy.
Cotton puni has a very squishsterious ability:
When it sticks together,
it starts to float to the skies.
Talk about a puni-fluffy flight.
Though water makes the cotton puni vanish.
Squestion time!
How did Airune save Jewelrune from danger?
Give your frozen brain a squish
to find the answer!
Here's the answer...
Here's the answer!
It stuck together some new
cotton puni for Jewelrune.
You did a very good deed, Airune!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Airune, what's got you so worked up?
Say what? It's finally back from its trip?
Next Time
You mean our super-friendly puni-pal?!
Wait, Jewelrune, you know Tomorune too?!
Next Time
Next time: "Welcome Back, Tomorune♪"
Welcome Back, Tomorune♪
"Puni" in next time!