Coming up on Punirunes...
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
The show is squishing!
Let's play, Punirunes!
Punirunes.
Before we knew it, these creatures
began to inhabit the human world.
They're squishsterious and soft to the touch!
They all love to be squished.
There's also fun, adorable puni-pals aplenty.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Kachi-Freezy Dungeon Escape♪
"Kachi-Freezy Dungeon Escape♪"
What's the matter, you two?
They're arguing over which gummy is better:
the red apple flavor
or the yellow pineapple flavor.
That's all, then...?
Jewelrune asks if they want to come
to Kachikochiland to find a Punistal fragment.
Play nice, okay?
Have fun!
They're still fighting
over the better gummy flavor.
Airune the hero spots
the Punistal fragment.
Jewelrune obtains the Punistal fragment.
This button is obviously suspicious.
Jewelrune stops them.
"We would never push a weird button like this!"
responds Airune and Enerune.
Don't do it. You can't push it, Airune.
But being told something isn't allowed
only implores you to do it more.
We call this emotion
the forbidden fruit effect.
A kachi-freezy boulder starts rolling their way.
They're trapped in the cave.
"Why'd you push the button?"
"Sorry, I couldn't help it..."
says Airune.
If they make it to the very top,
they can escape.
Our athletic friend Enerune
begins wall jumping.
Alas, even Enerune lacks
the stamina to keep going.
Enerune gives up.
It sticks the landing.
Ururune breaks into tears.
Coolrune has an idea.
Loverune makes a big heart.
Very clever!
Jewelrune comes up with something.
They're super-jumping,
making use of the rope's rebound.
We call this power
the kachi-puni effect.
"The red gummies taste the best!"
Airune says, not backing down.
"No, the yellow gummies are!"
says Enerune, also standing firm.
They keep on bickering over red vs. yellow.
Airune's in real danger now.
"The red gummies are the best!"
Airune, now is not the time.
Will it save Airune with this star?
Enerune left it all up to luck...
and it paid off.
They may not have gotten
the Punistal fragment,
but their bonds have only gotten
squishier along the way.
The Puni-Puni Squestion!
I will present a question
based on the events of the episode.
Try your best to remember!
The Punirunes got a hold of another
Punistal fragment,
but got trapped in the cave.
They tried escaping but to no avail.
Then Airune found some rope
and they used it to get out.
Squestion time!
Which color gummies do Airune
and Enerune like best?
Give your frozen brain a squish
to find the answer!
Here's the answer!
Here's the answer...
"The red gummies taste the best!"
Airune says, not backing down.
"No, the yellow gummies are!"
says Enerune, also standing firm.
Airune likes red gummies
and Enerune likes yellow ones.
Both gummy flavors taste very good.
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Airune, what's that?
Cotton puni? Oh, like cotton candy!
Sounds scrumptious!
Next Time
Are you sure you can eat that much, though?
What?! Airune, you're flying away!
Okay, see ya! Wait, no!
Where are you going off to?!
Next Time
Next time: "A Fluffy Flight with Cotton Puni♪"
A Fluffy Flight with Cotton Puni♪
"Puni" in next time!