Coming up on Punirunes...
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
The show is squishing!
Let's play, Punirunes!
Punirunes.
Before we knew it, these creatures
began to inhabit the human world.
They're squishsterious and soft to the touch!
They all love to be squished.
There's also fun, adorable puni-pals aplenty.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
A Squishy Scary(?) Story♪
"A Squishy Scary(?) Story♪"
I present a terrifying, true story
which happened on the night
of a full moon.
I was sleeping in bed, when...
SCRATCH...
I heard a strange sound
from the window.
I took a look outside,
but there was no one in sight.
I figured it was nothing,
and walked back to my bed, when...
SCRATCH...
I heard more scratching,
and something tapping on the window.
SCRATCH...
I slowly turned back to check, and then...
EEK!
Sorry! Did I scare you that badly?
I just saw my own reflection in the window.
The scratching was just twigs
being shaken up by the wind.
Yuka just told the Punirunes a scary story.
Oh, look at the time!
It's curfew for you all.
Good night!
What's this?
It's Bakerune.
Looks like it's sleepwalking.
Jewelrune tries to tell Airune
it heard a sound outside the window...
but nobody is there.
Jewelrune?!
Nothing to be afraid of.
This is a puni-pal!
Bakerune, were you sleepwalking?
It's just like Airune to sleep through this.
I better get to sleep.
I have school in the morning.
Good night, Bakerune!
Jewelrune is too scared
to turn the light off.
PUNYAA
Airune is not waking up.
Airune? Jewelrune?
What's wrong?
It was just Nyarurune.
So you were going for a night walk, Nyarurune.
Cat trivia:
Cats are active at night.
There's no need to worry.
Bakerune and Nyarurune are both our puni-pals!
Alright, I really better get to sleep.
SCRATCH...
I heard more scratching,
and something tapping on the window.
Airune and Jewelrune shake their house
around in fear.
Good morning, Airune and Jewelrune!
Oh?
Togerune?
You'll catch a cold sleeping on the floor!
They're such good friends.
They had a very scary night,
but Airune and Jewelrune
can make it through anything together.
The Puni-Puni Squestion!
I will present a question
based on the events of the episode.
Try your best to remember!
EEK!
Jewelrune had a hard time sleeping
after Yuka told it a scary story.
Upon seeing strange sil-pun-ettes
outside the window,
it went, "Yikes, I'm scared!"
But they turned out to just be
Bakerune sleepwalking
and Nyarurune taking a night stroll.
SCRATCH...
Squestion time!
One more scary figure
appeared outside the window.
Whose prank is this?
Give your frozen brain a squish
to find the answer!
Here's the answer!
Here's the answer...
It was Togerune!
Togerune, playing pranks is not nice.
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Airune, who's this little guy?
Nazorune, is it?
Who am I, you ask?
I'm Yuka! Nice to meet you!
Next Time
Huh? What am I doing?
I just got home from school.
What's school? Where is it?
Why did I go there?
Next Time
Q-Question overload! Slow down!
Next time: "What Could This Be? Nazorune♪"
What Could This Be? Nazorune♪
"Puni" in next time!