Coming up on Punirunes...
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
The show is squishing!
Let's play, Punirunes!
Punirunes.
Before we knew it, these creatures
began to inhabit the human world.
They're squishsterious and soft to the touch!
They all love to be squished.
There's also fun, adorable puni-pals aplenty.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
The Secret Jewelrune♪
"The Secret Jewelrune♪"
Looks like the Punirunes
are having a conversation.
Let's listen in, shall we?
"We got a lotta Punistal fragments!"
"Jewelrune said they could make amazing things!
I wonder what they are?"
"Something cool, obviously."
"I hope something with hearts!"
"We have to go find the other fragments!"
says Jewelrune.
In response...
they'll be off to Kachikochiland
again today.
They've collected five Punistal
fragments thus far,
leaving seven away
from Jewelrune's goal of twelve.
There's no doubt the rest
will be even more difficult to obtain.
They found it surprisingly easily.
Oh? Some Punirunes have appeared.
Jewelrune has scurried off.
"Stop!" shouts Airune.
"Who goes there?"
"Move aside! We must get through!"
"You thieves will have to
go through us first!"
"Look! A cold flying kachived ice!"
"I love kachived ice!"
"We love cold kachived ice!"
"I'm so hungry and I love it!"
"Where is it?"
"I want my cold kachived ice!"
"Strawberry? Lemon? Kawaiian?"
"I can't find it! I'm hungry!"
"They tricked us!"
Jewelrune pauses now that
it's in the clear.
When suddenly, another foe appears.
Jewelrune gets cornered.
Is there no escape now?
"It is you, your majesty!"
"So this is where you've been!"
The thieves bow their heads.
What is the meaning of this?
"'Your majesty'?"
"So they're not thieves?"
"Nothing of the sort, no!"
"There's no need for such formality.
Raise your heads."
"We serve its majesty Jewelrune."
"Because Jewelrune is the prince
of Kachikochiland!"
Jewelrune gets bashful.
So it really is a prince.
"Then why were they chasing afer you?"
"Its majesty went missing some time ago,
and we've been searching for it since."
"By the way, your majesty,
what ever happened to your crown?"
"My crown..."
"I... lost it."
"You lost that valuable crown
that's been passed down generations?"
"What are we to do?"
"I'm going to fix it."
"Fix it how exactly?"
It appears they're in the middle
of a very important conversation.
But the other Punirunes are getting excited,
shouting, "Wow, you're a prince! So cool!"
"Show some respect to its majesty!"
"What's your deal?"
Halt!
What's this?
The Punistal fragment is glowing.
Something squishsterious is happening.
The Punistal fragments are projecting
an image of Jewelrune and its attendants in the past.
Airune realizes now
that what Jewelrune wants to make
with the twelve Punistal fragments...
is a crown.
"My apologies for causing you worry."
"I plan to collect Punistal fragments
and build a crown."
"I and my puni-pals here
will make certain of it."
"Your majesty... you've grown so much."
Even Jewelrune's hard-headed attendants
were squishily moved by its resolve.
What?! Jewelrune's actually a prince?
And it wants to use the twelve Punistal fragments
to rebuild the kingdom's valuable crown?
You're kidding, right?
Sorry.
But still, I'm kind of surprised by all this.
Who knew Jewelrune
was a prince? That's so cool.
Right, Airune?
Jewelrune is Jewelrune?
Yeah, you said it.
I hope you guys can find all the Punistal fragments!
The Puni-Puni Squestion!
I will present a question
based on the events of the episode.
Try your best to remember!
As it turns out, Jewelrune
is the prince of Kachikochiland.
It used to live in a castle
with its attendants.
Halt!
Squestion time!
What does Jewelrune want to make
after it has found all twelve Punistal fragments?
Give your frozen brain a squish
to find the answer!
Here's the answer!
Here's the answer...
The answer is a crown!
Quite a beautiful one, isn't it?
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Huh? What would I do if I was smaller than you?
Hmm... Let me think.
I guess I'd have you squish me,
and we'd go to Puniland!
Next Time
Sounds like so much fun.
Hm? What's with the wand?
Wait, what? I actually shrunk!
Next Time
Next time: "Yuka and Aoi Turn Mini-Mini♪"
Yuka and Aoi
Turn Mini-Mini♪
"Puni" in next time!