Coming up on Punirunes...
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
The show is squishing!
Let's play, Punirunes!
Punirunes.
Before we knew it, these creatures
began to inhabit the human world.
They're squishsterious and soft to the touch!
They all love to be squished.
There's also fun, adorable puni-pals aplenty.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Jewelrune Makes New Friends♪
"Jewelrune Makes New Friends♪"
Strange. Jewelrune fell asleep
next to Airune, and now it's gone.
What is it, Airune?
Huh? Jewelrune's missing?
The Airune Buns are ready!
Our best-selling item,
from the mind of Yuka!
How adorable!
They look so real,
they might come to life!
Jewelrune?
Where did it run off to...?
The dough came to life!
This is all because you said
"they might come to life!"
Yuka, get out of here!
It's dangerous!
Your father will deal with this!
Wait a minute. Could it be?
That's it! You're awesome!
What a relief.
S-S-So cute!
Its name is Jewelrune!
It comes from Kachikochiland.
Kachikochiland?
How interesting.
Jewelrune, this is my mom and dad.
Are you hungry, Jewelrune?
I see you're hungry too, Airune.
Alright. Let's use this rolled ice cream!
Let's get squ-ooking!
Give it some of the
squishsterious squishence...
Stir it up...
Knead it...
Give it a squishy kneading
so it'll be nice and fluffy!
Rolled ice punieam, ready to serve!
Rolled ice punieam
Jewelrune has never seen squishy food before,
and is hesitant about it.
All of Airune's friends are here
for rolled ice punieam!
Airune introduces Jewelrune to them.
Jewelrune gets nervous around
unfamiliar Punirunes.
Enerune's backflip gives
Jewelrune a shock!
Jewelrune is perplexed
by Coolrune's cool demeanor.
Loverune's hearts make Jewelrune happy!
Will tearful little Ururune
be able to handle this?
They greet one another
with squish contact!
Naturally, Jewelrune has never
seen a cat before either.
Komugi
Komugi is very curious
about Jewelrune.
Ururune's crying happened
to save Jewelrune.
Jewelrune has made good friends
with everyone.
Jewelrune's rolled ice punieam is missing.
Togerune took the rolled ice punieam!
Togerune
Togerune's a new face
to Jewelrune too.
Detective Coolrune
spots a trail of footprints!
Ururune ahead,
and Loverune behind.
Togerune is cornered!
Togerune dodges the hearts!
And Ururune falls in love!
Togerune makes a break for the attic!
Jewelrune gives chase!
It falls!
Airune, that rolled ice punieam
is for Jewelrune...
Jewelrune suggests they all split
the dessert!
Looks like Jewelrune ended up
loving rolled ice punieam.
How's it feel, Jewelrune?
Oh, where's Airune?
You're eating again?
Its day was full of new experiences,
but it seems Jewelrune had a lot of fun.
The Puni-Puni Squestion!
I will present a question
based on the events of the episode.
Try your best to remember!
I see you're hungry too, Airune.
Alright. Let's use this rolled ice cream!
The Punirunes love the squishy food
that Yuka makes.
And now, so does Jewelrune.
Let's get squ-ooking!
Squestion time!
Which squishence color combination
do you need to make rolled ice punieam?
Give your frozen brain a squish
to find the answer!
Here's the answer...
Here's the answer!
The answer is
one red and two blue.
It's a one way trip to Squishtown!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Airune, what are you all up to?
Huh, you're going on an adventure?
You're all off to Kachikochiland
in search of a Punistal fragment?
Next Time
Uhh, not sure what that means,
but it sounds real interesting!
Next Time
Have fun! Hope you find
that treasure for Jewelrune!
Next time: "Let's Go to Kachikochiland♪"
Let's Go to Kachikochiland♪
"Puni" in next time!