Coming up on Punirunes...
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
The show is squishing!
Let's play, Punirunes!
Punirunes.
Before we knew it, these creatures
began to inhabit the human world.
They're squishsterious and soft to the touch!
They all love to be squished.
There's also fun, adorable puni-pals aplenty.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Project: Cuprune♪
"Project: Cuprune♪"
Sounds like Cuprune opened up
a confectionary shop in Puniland!
"Its food has gotta be so yummy!" says Airune.
"Let's go!" the Punirunes cheer.
Off to Puniland they go!
They quickly turn up on Cuprune's shop!
It was actually the Sushirunes'
punigiri shop.
Wait, punigiri? Not sushi?!
Where could Cuprune's shop be?
They search around Squishy Market...
and the park...
but Cuprune's shop is nowhere to be found.
They walked all the way out here,
but surely it's not in the middle of nowhere—
It is!
"I want my fresh cupunicakes to be enjoyed
out in the open fresh air!" says Cuprune.
The air is fresh out here, but...
you're not getting any customers.
"Since I'm not selling,
I may as well eat it all!" says Cuprune.
"Everyone should get to have these delicious
cupunicakes!" protest the other Punirunes.
They're going to try to attract customers.
Ururune drew a sign for the shop.
Yummy, delectable cupunicakes!
Airune gives directions to the shop.
Go straight,
turn left at the second corner,
run "puni-i-i" ahead,
spin around,
and you'll make it.
Airune's directions were... unclear.
Loverune is using photos
to attract customers.
Loverune, the cupunicake
isn't in those photos!
Jewelrune and Coolrune are attracting
customers with a dance performance.
Ururune does a
squishsterious dance!
Ururune does a squishsterious dance!
"Weird...
"I feel...
"so hungry."
"Thank you."
"O-Oh my..."
"It's so delectably squishy."
"But it's even more than that."
"The squishiness changing the texture
inside of the squishiness
"intertwines two different squishinesses
into its own squishiness,
"throwing a squishy party inside my mouth."
"Pfft... squishy party. That's silly."
Coolrune, your internal praises
won't bring in any customers.
"I brought the Three Sushirune Musketeers!"
"'The Three Sushirune Musketeers'?"
"The expert on food trends, Maguro."
"The expert on inviting storefronts, Salmon."
"The expert on fun customer service, Shiromi."
It looks like they'll teach it the secrets
to a flourishing business.
They must have a good idea!
A fusion of cupunicake and punigiri:
Cupunigiricake!
The Three Sushirune Musketeers
filled Cuprune's belly
and left it with no customers.
"What's that?"
"A bird?"
"A plane?"
It's a Cuprune balloon!
Airune and friends made the balloon
as a guide to bring customers to the shop!
The balloon is drawing customers
to the shop one after another!
The plan worked!
Nazorune finally got to have one too!
Good for it.
Cuprune's busy work brought it back
to its normal state.
"No biggie!"
Airune, I wouldn't be so sure.
"What's that?"
The Puni-Puni Squestion!
I will present a question
based on the events of the episode.
Try your best to remember!
Airune and friends tried to attract customers
to Cuprune's new shop,
to little avail.
Airune brought in the
Three Sushirune Musketeers.
Squestion time!
What did the Three Sushirune Musketeers
make for Cuprune's shop?
Give your frozen brain a squish
to find the answer!
Here's the answer...
Here's the answer!
The answer is a combination
of cupunicake and punigiri...
cupunigiricake!
It looked delicious!
Cuprune, don't eat too much, okay?
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Aw, are you okay?
Are you sure?
You don't look okay...
Get some good rest!
Next Time
Huh? Loverune and Ururune
are taking care of you?
"We'll get you your puni-meds!"
What exactly are those...?
Next Time
Next time: "A Squishy Recovery with Puni-Meds♪"
A Squishy Recovery
with Puni-Meds♪
"Puni" in next time!