Coming up on Punirunes...
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
The show is squishing!
Let's play, Punirunes!
Punirunes.
Before we knew it, these creatures
began to inhabit the human world.
They're squishsterious and soft to the touch!
They all love to be squished.
There's also fun, adorable puni-pals aplenty.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Yuka and Airune's
Squishy Body Swap♪
"Yuka and Airune's Squishy Body Swap♪"
Such squishy bliss!
A squishy for you too, Jewelrune!
You love it? I'm glad!
I love giving squishes a lot,
but it must be so much fun on the receiving end.
If only I could be Airune!
Angelrune!
This here is Angelrune.
Angelrune
One hit of its arrows
can bring you luck.
Wait, are you saying
I could actually become Airune?
One problem: Angelrune has terrible aim.
Bullseye!
Amazing! Its bowmanship has improved.
Nope, not feeling anything.
Wow, what a weird glow.
That was freaky, right, Airune?
Hey, it's me.
Wait a minute, have we actually...
swapped bodies?!
What a twist!
Airune and Yuka have swapped bodies!
Why are you shocked, Angelrune?
Woohoo! I've always wanted
to be you, Airune!
How lucky!
Airune, squish me please!
Woo, this is amazing!
A stroke of luck
thanks to Angelrune's arrow.
This is the best!
There you have it!
So let's go have some fun!
Jewelrune gives them the rundown
of what happened earlier.
Alright, hit me with it!
Gimme your best squish contact!
So this is what squish contact feels like!
It's like you took squishy and squishy
and mixed them in perfect
squishy harmony!
This is bliss!
Oh? What's up, Yuka?
Is that your Airune impression?
Oh, I know! You want bread, don't you?
Bingo! That's right!
Here you are!
Y-Yuka...
I love you too-o-o!
That's not what it said.
Acting like Airune sounds like
hot-diggity fun!
Maybe I should imitate it too!
Agreed! I'm gonna join in too!
Puni-puni-puni?
Puni-puni-pu?
Puni-puni-puni!
– Puni-puni-puni! Puni-puni-puni!
– Puni-puni-pu! Puni-puni-pu!
Everything's so huge from Airune's perspective...
Alright! I'm gonna do it!
Hyah!
Whew, that was a blast!
Thanks, Loverune!
Huh?
Oh no! The crow is after Airune!
Wow! Even the crow is humongous!
Airune—I mean, Yuka!
This is no time to be happy!
Huh?
Komugi!
Komugi, help me!
"Airune is...talking?"
Komugi!
"Oh crud, Airune is talking!"
Huh?
Komugi and the crow both took off.
That was scary...
Puni-puni-puni, puni-pu?
Pu-puni puni-puni!
I'm coming in!
Yuka, wanna hang ou...
– Puni-puni-puni!
– Pu-ni puni-puni!
What in the world?
That was so much fun!
Thanks for playing with me!
This feels so awkward...
So it really is you, Airune!
I see!
You got to eat a rice cracker
and a baguette!
Looks like Airune also had
a lot of fun being Yuka.
Angelrune, thank you so much for the luck!
I think we're ready.
Can you turn us back now?
Seems Angelrune has no clue
how to turn them back!
What?!
Uh-oh...
Will shooting them
with your arrow again work?
Good idea!
Now that Angelrune has improved its aim,
it can do anything!
Hooray!
Huh?
"That one didn't count!"
Looks like the first strike
was just a fluke.
You can't hit them at all!
Well, if we're stuck like this,
then so be it.
I'll do my best to live as Airune going forward!
Whaaat?!
This is a bad idea, Yuka!
If you live as Airune...
You'll, uh...
That hits the spot.
Hupsy-daisy!
Welcome in!
That actually sounds pretty fun.
Doesn't it just?
But even still!
If you stay like this, Yuka...
you'll never get to squish Airune again!
I-I didn't think about that...
I loved becoming you
and getting squished...
but...
I want to squish you even more!
Airune!
They both feel the same way.
Wait, what?
Airune?
Yay, we're back!
Thank goodness!
This is bliss!
Thank goodness you're back to normal,
Airune and Yuka!
Puni-puni-puni-puni-puni!
Puni-pu puni-puni-pu!
Puni! Puni-puni-pu!
What in the world?
The Puni-Puni Squestion!
I will present a question
based on the events of the episode.
Try your best to remember!
Angelrune's arrow caused
Airune and Yuka to swap bodies.
Wanting to know what it felt like to be squished,
Yuka was overjoyed.
Gimme...
Squestion time!
What is the first thing Yuka-turned-Airune
asked of the other Punirunes?
Give your frozen brain a squish
to find the answer!
Here's the answer!
Here's the answer...
So this is what squish contact feels like!
It's like you took squishy and squishy
and mixed them in perfect
squishy harmony!
This is bliss!
The answer is squish contact!
Did you get it puni-right?
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
What?! You went to Kachikochiland
to find a Punistal fragment,
and got trapped in a cave?
How are you gonna get out?
Next Time
Well said! If you put together,
you'll make it out, I'm confident!
I'm... very, very confident!
Oh no, you can't escape?!
Next Time
Next time: "Kachi-Freezy Dungeon Escape♪"
Kachi-Freezy Dungeon Escape♪
"Puni" in next time!