Coming up on Punirunes...
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
The show is squishing!
Let's play, Punirunes!
Punirunes.
Before we knew it, these creatures
began to inhabit the human world.
They're squishsterious and soft to the touch!
They all love to be squished.
There's also fun, adorable puni-pals aplenty.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
It's Squishmas!
Jewelrune♪ & Tomorune♪
"It's Squishmas! Jewelrune♪ & Tomorune♪"
"Yeah!"
Today, they're having a fun
Christmas party.
I see you all brought your presents!
This is your first Christmas,
isn't it, Jewelrune?
We're gonna exchange gifts
and have a big feast!
Tomorune!
Tomorune came back to join
their Christmas party.
Welcome back, Tomorune!
We missed you!
Jewelrune got too excited to see it.
"We better dress up for the party!"
What is it, Tomorune?
Origami paper?
Sure! It's in the drawer.
Help yourself to it!
Stop!
Yuka, should we put these up too?
Togerune got off with everyone's presents!
This is bad. If Jewelrune hears
all their presents were stolen
after it got all excited for the party,
it'll be devastated.
They can't make Jewelrune sad!
They will get the presents back
before the party.
If it goes into the living room,
it'll find out the presents are gone!
They must stall Jewelrune
until the presents are retrieved.
"I think they're still setting up the party!"
"Let's go back to Yuka's room!"
"And play until they're ready!"
"Yeah! That's right! Mhm!"
Airune and Tomorune's
iconic team-up is back in action!
Tomorune's many puni-pals
are helping search for Togerune.
Mission start!
Cats are notoriously fickle.
Oh no! It's going to the living room!
"Give us back our presents!"
Oh, Togerune!
I'm glad I ran into you!
I wanted to invite you
to the Christmas party.
Wanna join us? It'll be lots of fun!
The presents are finally back.
Tomorune brought this present...
and Togerune brought this one.
I can't wait to see who wins what!
Huh? Oh, the others are, uh...
busy with something, but didn't say what.
Hey, they're back!
Now everyone is here.
Yup! Let's start the party!
Everyone...
Merry Squishmas!
"We have a present for you!"
"I already got it!"
"There's more."
Tomorune wanted Jewelrune
to remember its first Christmas fondly,
so it asked everyone for help
to make Jewelrune a special present.
And that present is an origami crown.
The surprise paid off!
Good for you, Jewelrune.
The Puni-Puni Squestion!
I will present a question
based on the events of the episode.
Try your best to remember!
Tomorune came back once more
to join Airune and friends'
Christmas party.
And alongside Airune, it searched for
the presents Togerune stole.
Squestion time!
What present did Tomorune come up with
to give Jewelrune?
1. A squishy flower
2. An origami crown
3. A big gummy
Give your frozen brain a squish
to find the answer!
Here's the answer!
Here's the answer...
It was an origami crown!
May you all have a Merry Squishmas as well!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Jewelrune, I see you're off to Kachikochiland
to get the last two Punistal fragments!
Next Time
Airune, you and the rest help it out, okay?
But don't push yourselves too hard.
Next Time
Alright! See you later!
Next time: "The Punirunes' Grandest Adventure Ever♪"
The Punirunes’
Grandest Adventure Ever♪
"Puni" in next time!