A-B-C-D-E-F-G
H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P
Q-R-S-T-U-V-W
X-Y and Z
Now you know your ABCs
Isn't it bizarre, the way we string together
letters from A to Z?
Whether it be out loud or by text,
let's find something to talk about!
How will the world end? What's for dinner?
Let's share those moments of laughter and tears
I decide what I like and hate
But that too is a barrier I can break down
Don't you see? Our words make us who we are
There's something I want to talk about with you
Just thinking about that gets me all giddy
Whether you're right next to me or not
You always brighten up my day
Of all the things you've spoken to me
I cherish every last word
It feels good to think about somebody
And it feels good to put that into words
camp
La-lala-lala, la-lala-lala, la-lala-lala
Blue skies, white clouds,
and Mother Nature,
dressed in all green!
I knew going on a camping trip was a great idea!
We're not even at the campsite yet...
I'm so hungry!
La-lala-lala...
There it is!
Hey, guys! We made it to the campsite!
Why are you guys sitting down?!
Just taking a quick break.
But the campsite is right there!
You don't even know how heavy this
deluxe two-story tent is.
I have 30 portions of meat in my bag,
and Brown has 256 fireworks in his!
Oh, don't be so weak.
Besides, the bridge is aaall the way over there!
Fine, we'll just take a shortcut!
I'll jump straight across to the campsite!
Made it.
No, you didn't!!
What are we supposed to do now?!
How are we supposed to camp without
our meat, tent, or fireworks?
I want to be mad,
but it would just make me more hungry.
All this sun, and we can't camp here...
What a nice breeze.
Alright, what's the plan?
Wanna try to salvage this however we can?
Yeah. We came all this way,
so we may as well!
Sounds good! Let's start by catching some dinner!
Yeah!
Very sharp, all of you.
What?
This is how real camping is done!
Oh, yeah?
Relying on your own wisdom and capabilities,
procuring your own food
and taking in nature around you!
That's the true thrill of camping!
You don't get to act so cool about this!
Yeah! You're the reason we're in this mess!
Let's skedaddle.
A-Aw, come on...
Ready!
I hope we can actually catch fish with these.
Huh, already?!
Hang in there, Cony!
I've got this!
Let's go!
I've got a bite!
Juby-julee!
I... nooo!
Brown, you get one?
Y'all are doing this all wrong!
Watch and learn!
Go!
A catch!
In that case, watch!
I'll catch one with my hands!
Over here!
Ack, you won't get away!
Moon, you're gonna drive all the fish away!
A fish?
What?!
Yay!
What a haul!
You're awesome, Brown!
Really, Brown?
You just had to steal my thunder...
Let's cook 'em up!
I just realized the lighter and matches
were in my bag!
Thanks a lot, Moon!
Now, hold on!
You can light it yourselves!
That's the true thrill of camping!
I've got more in me!
Ow, hot!
Blaze, blaze...
Soon be ablaze...
Burn, burn...
I give up!
It's not working!
I'm so, so, so hungry!
I'm so unlucky...
And yet,
I'm still beautiful
at my unluckiest!
Ow, that scorches!
James, that's perfect!
Huh? What is?
Like this?
Yeah!
Yay, you lit the fire! Good job, James!
Hooray, yippee!
Another chance to show them
how helpful I am, down the drain...
Yum!
You said it! It's so fresh!
Fish taste so much better
when you cook them yourself!
Spoken wisely for someone
who didn't help.
Uh...
Next on the agenda?
Time for dessert!
Hey, guys!
Come over here!
Those look delicious!
Aw, you can't climb it?
How do we get them down?
Aha! Eureka!
Moon, where are you going?
We'll get them down without him.
Oof, to the right.
I'm so close!
Hang in there, Brown!
I'm back!
Moon?
Your savior has arrived!
I'll get those oranges from here!
This should be a piece of cake!
What is your problem, Moon?!
I just wanted to help!
No excuses!
Ow!
Yay!
This is the life.
If only we had our tent with us.
Please, there's still fun to be had without one!
What'cha got there?
Found them nearby!
Firewood?
No camp is complete without a campfire!
Becoming one with nature,
as we're surrounded by a big, warm light
burning to the skies!
That sounds wonderful!
Isn't it a bit early for a fire?
Says who? I'm gonna make
an awesome memory no matter what!
A-one, a-two...!
Wow!
It's perfect.
Uh, Moon?
No need to thank me.
Moon...
I trapped myself in!
Man, you're hopeless.
Juby-julee...
It's done!
So beautiful!
But not as beautiful as me.
Let's do a folk dance!
Good idea!
And my dance partner shall be...
none other than me.
Then I'll choose...
Moon-Moon-Moooon!
I'll bring my song to the party!
Thanks, Moon!
We appreciate it!
Get ready to dance the day away!
One, two, one, two, three, four!
Moon, look at all this rain!
Why'd you do it?
Oh, come on. You can't blame me for this!
It sure isn't letting up.
What do we do? We're not prepared for a storm!
We'll use these as umbrellas!
Don't stop in your tracks like that!
Bad news!
Wh-What now?
We'll have to go upstream!
There's probably a way around!
We're stuck here!
What are we to do?!
I wish we had never gone camping!
I could've been at home
gazing at myself in the mirror!
You guys...
This is my time to shine.
Moon?
What are you doing?
You big boulder!
Are you trying to clear the path?
It's not gonna budge!
I can't...
Huh?
Um, you guys?
Run for it!
Look, the campsite!
Hey, look!
It's our home!
Hooray!
That was one thrilling camping trip!
Yeah! I feel like I really took in nature,
just like Moon said!
audition
Cony, what's wrong?
You keep staring at your phone.
I applied for a pop star audition.
I'm supposed to hear today
if I got in or not!
You're going to be a pop star?
I only applied because why not!
Oh, you.
I don't know how I'd handle it
if I actually got in!
Thank you all for cheering me on!
It's hard to stay calm while I wait for the call!
Do you suppose Moon's in the same boat?
Oh yeah, I think I saw him at the audition hall too.
L-Looks like he got rejected...
Th-They're calling me!
Wh-Wh-What do I do?
Try to calm yourself down!
Who am I speaking with?
Yes.
Oh, really?
I'm happy to hear that, thank you!
Did you get in?
Yep! I passed the first audition!
Congratulations!
Thank you, Jessica!
I hear you got picked.
Why do you get to succeed and I don't?
You know, there's still the final round.
Cony! I may have failed miserably,
but I know you will take home the gold!
Well, that's unlike you.
And if you do...
would you mind letting me have
the all-you-can-eat barbecue prize?
Huh? U-Uh, sure...
So that's why Moon took the audition.
Cony's not taking the final audition?!
Why is she chickening out last minute?!
She said she got a zit on her cheek
and is too embarrassed to go on stage.
Are you kidding?!
Nope, not happening! I'm not going!
Cony! You better not have forgotten
you promised me that barbecue!
If I answer, he's gonna force me to go!
That stubborn girl!
Maybe just let her be.
As if!
In I go!
Cony!!
Huh? She's not here.
She's running away!
Moon, open up!
Is Cony doing okay?
Uh-oh...
I'm gonna lose my all-you-can-eat barbecue!
Come on, Moon! Open the door!
Huh? Do you mean it, Cony?
You're going to take the audition after all?
Say what?
Really, Cony?
You heard her, Jessica!
Now go on ahead to the audition hall!
But where'd this come from?
Jessica! It's me, Cony!
I'll meet you at the hall!
Brown, can you stay here for a bit?
There you have it, Jessica!
U-Um, okay.
Brown, get in.
Alright, Brown. I need you to make me
a pair of Cony's ears with this cardboard.
I'm the same color as Cony,
so with these ears, no one could tell us apart!
Hey, Cony!
I came to cheer you on!
O-Oh my, thank you, James!
Your support means the moon—
I mean, the world to me!
If my voice sounds a bit off,
it's because I have a light cold.
I see! That explains why your face is swelled up, too.
Y-Yes, of course!
I'd better get to my dressing room!
I'll come with you!
They wouldn't hate me
if I changed my mind, would they?
Huh? Cony, you're la—
Uh, Cony?
Yep, that's me! Good ol' Cony!
She got a cold and it did a real number
on her voice and face!
Poor thing...
You really shouldn't strain yourself!
Are you kidding?
This is barbecue we're talking about!
I won't let some silly cold bring me down!
You're so brave! Good luck, Cony!
Ms. Cony! You will be taking turns
singing your assigned songs.
We'll let you know when you're up.
Assigned song?
What assigned song exactly?
You've been rehearsing it nonstop, no?
Are you feeling okay?
Wanna give it another try now?
I'm afraid that's not possible.
We'll watch you, okay?
Huh? I...
What's the matter?
Don't worry about it!
I'll rehearse the song on my own!
You all go take your seats!
Go on, now!
Hmm...
Gah, it's Cony!
What's going on, Cony?
I changed my mind!
Would you all watch me rehearse?
Of course!
It's a bit cramped in here though,
so I'd like to do it outside!
Let's be quick!
Quick? Why?
Hug the walls.
Is there a reason for this?
Why are we crawling around?
The moon is big and round
What in the world?
That's not even close to the song you were assigned.
It isn't?
You're just tensed up!
Jessica, why don't you sing it too?
Would you, pretty please?
Sure thing!
Yet another fun day
Huh, I forgot how it goes.
That's fine. Thank you, Jessica.
I should be fine on my own now.
Sorry I couldn't help.
Please go take your seats!
Got it! We'll cheer for you, Cony!
See you on stage!
You go with them, Brown.
Darn you, Cony.
Why'd you have to show up
outta nowhere?
I have to get her out of here.
Cony?!
Huh? Aah!
What brings you here?
I, uhh...
I didn't have a sudden change of heart
about taking the audition...
I just thought I'd let the staff here know.
Huh? But you were all into it
just a moment ago!
Ms. Cony, please report to
the reception immediately.
Sorry, we'll talk later!
Whoopsie! I thought they wanted me,
but it was just a mistake!
Huh? Didn't you just run off in that direction?
D-Did I?!
It's no matter, I'll do my best in the audition!
But you just said you weren't going to!
No, I've just been working on my acting skills!
Thought I'd try it on you all.
I see?
Go on, Brown! Take them to their seats.
Man, where even is the reception?
Huh?!
Hey, Cony.
Moon!
What are you doin' here?
I thought you weren't taking the audition!
I was just...
You realize how mad the staff will be
if you tell them you're not auditioning now!
Really?!
Well, I guess so...
I'll go fill them in for you.
You head on home.
What the?
Thanks, Moon!
Should be smooth-sailing now.
Huh? Where'd the ears go?
Cony's been off today, no?
Going on stage will do that to you!
What happened to them?
I can't go on stage without Cony's ears!
Please welcome entry no. 3 to the stage: Ms. Cony!
I'm done for.
Brown, I need you!
Ms. Cony? Where are you?
What's gotten into her?
I hope she's okay...
Ms. Cony, are you here?
Ms. Cony? Ms. Cony? Ms. Cony?!
Oh boy, he sounds mad.
Didn't Moon fill them in?
Perfection.
Ms. Cony, are you here?
If you're not, you'll be disqualified.
I'm here!
Ta-dah! It's me, Cony!
I'm sorry!
Huh?!
Why are there two Conys?
Is that Moon?!
What is he doing?
What in the world?
How many Conys are there?
Brown, what are you doing?
How do we handle this?
We sing!
O-Okay!
Yet another fun day here in Line Town
And I'm sure tomorrow will be just as fun
Yeah!
I didn't think you would show up,
since you were so stuck on that zit.
I had a blast!
I really wanted that barbecue!
You should be happy! After all, the judges
gave you three a special trophy for your performance!
I'm gonna practice real hard
and win next year!
My barbecue! My veggie barbecuuue!
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
I dreamt I was flying through the night sky
mahou no juutan ni notte
On a magic carpet
tondeku yozora no yume
And I just wanted you to see it
kimi ni mo
kimi ni mo misetakute
misetai
Oh, did I wake you? I'm so sorry
okoshichatta kana? gomen ne
I thought you sounded half-asleep
neboketa kotobatachi ni
And it made me swoon
nandaka
nandaka kyun to kita
kyun kyun
Just like the glittering scent of rose tea
kirameku kaori no roozu tii mitai ni
When my heart starts pounding, I lock up
dokidoki no sono shunkan
tojikomeru
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
Even though I could just type a <3 and send it to you
yubisaki haato wo nosete
tsutawattara ii no ni
It's hard to sum up the way I feel for you
kimi e no kono kimochi
hitokoto ja tarinai
It's like a millefeuille
egao mo namida mo zenbu
With all of my smiles and tears mixed in
tsumikasaneta mirufiiyu
I feel happy, I feel painful
ureshii setsunai itoshii
I feel longing — I'm in love
koishiteru
babysitter
temptations
Next time on Line Town...
Waah! Waah! Waah!
Waah! Waah! Waaaaah!
Do you want your diaper changed?
babysitter
temptations
Oh, no! She's saying,
"Thank you for watching Line Town!"
Waah!