A-B-C-D-E-F-G
H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P
Q-R-S-T-U-V-W
X-Y and Z
Now you know your ABCs
Isn't it bizarre, the way we string together
letters from A to Z?
Whether it be out loud or by text,
let's find something to talk about!
How will the world end? What's for dinner?
Let's share those moments of laughter and tears
I decide what I like and hate
But that too is a barrier I can break down
Don't you see? Our words make us who we are
There's something I want to talk about with you
Just thinking about that gets me all giddy
Whether you're right next to me or not
You always brighten up my day
Of all the things you've spoken to me
I cherish every last word
It feels good to think about somebody
And it feels good to put that into words
friend
And this is Wataru. He's a ninja!
Wow!
I never knew you were friends with a ninja!
How did you two meet?
I ran into him at the hair salon
I frequent!
Oh wow!
It's quite easy for you to make friends!
No wonder, since you act so naturally!
Yeah, that's right!
I suppose so!
My personality, hair, and cuticles
all come naturally to me!
Oh, yeah?
Having a ninja for a friend
is nothing special.
Huh? Do you have any
cool friends then, Moon?
Well, duh, of course I do!
Really?!
Like who?
Yeah, like who?
We wanna know!
Uhh...
You really wanna know that bad?
He's a magician.
A magician?
That's a lot plainer
than I expected.
W-Well, he's no ordinary magician.
He's, uhh, let me think...
He's not just a magician,
but he's a panda!
What? A panda magician?
Pandaman, the miracle-making magician!
He sounds cool!
What is he like?
Got any pics?
Huh?!
S-Sorry, I don't...
Aw, what?
Not even one?
Umm...
Oh, right. I might have some on my computer.
Show us!
Really?
Yeah, show us!
We wanna see!
I-I'll check for it tonight.
What do I do?
Of course I don't have any
photos of Mr. Pandaman!
He doesn't even exist!
I don't get to laugh here.
I know!
I'll start by crafting the parts...
Do this, then that...
Alright!
Finished!
This feels wrong.
That's even worse.
Perfect!
Then I'll put panda-like stickers on...
This is coming out nicely!
Good day, everyone!
It's me, Mr. Pandaman!
Witness my Bamboo Power!
So cool!
What are those leaves he's holding?
Mr. Panda uses Bamboo Power
to make his miracles!
Really?
You two look a lot alike, though.
Well, you know how it goes.
Birds of a feather flock together!
Huh?
What?
What's wrong?
Hey!
I-Is something the matter?
Look, there's a mirror here.
You can see the TV in the other room.
It's playing that TV show's finale
that aired yesterday!
Huh?!
Oh, you're right!
I watched that yesterday!
They were teasing that the old guy
from the store might be a spy,
but he turned out to just be a normal guy.
What kind of ending is that?
Yeah, it was lame.
Also, isn't that Moon's TV?
Oh, I recognize that vase!
Does that mean...
this photo was taken yesterday
in Moon's house?
What's going on here, Moon?
Cat's out of the bag.
Pandaman was staying at my place
last night.
Really?!
That's awesome!
How come?
Oh, no reason, just, you know...
Right, yeah-yeah-yeah!
There's magic auditions in town tomorrow,
and he didn't have the money to stay in a hotel.
That, and he had a lotta stuff
he needed to get on his mind,
so he asked to crash at my place
and ask for my advice!
Hey, what are you gonna do, right?
I wanna meet Pandaman!
I do too!
Me too!
I wanna see his magic tricks!
That's not possible!
Why not?
This is a professional we're talking about!
He can't just go around showing off
his magic tricks for free.
Aww.
That stinks...
It does.
He sounds quite strict.
He does.
Then how about this?
In return for his magic show,
we'll make some delicious food
and invite him to eat with us tonight!
Huh?
Nice idea!
That oughta convince him!
Right, Moon?
Pandaman's not one to be sold with food.
But on that note,
what would you make for him?
Let me think. Probably...
foie gras bamboo rice
and a caviar salad!
And I can make some fresh fruit juice.
Okay, then! I'll bring him!
I don't have much time!
I must become Mr. Pandaman,
and to do that...
I must practice!
Let's see...
Bamboo Power, 1, 2, 3...
That'll do!
Coming!
Hello!
Huh, are you by yourself, Moon?
Nah, he's not far behind.
What a yummy feast!
Not yet.
When's Pandaman gonna be here?
Huh? Uh, he's preparing his show.
I'm on the edge of my seat!
Same here.
I hope he's here soon.
The food's going to get cold.
I-I see!
I'll go get him!
Mr. Pandaman!
Bamboo Power!
Thanks a panda
for inviting me here tonight!
Allow me to show you some of my tricks
before we dig in!
Yay! I can't wait!
Here we go!
Three, two, one!
What?
That's weird...
Apologies, one moment.
Why does it have to act up now all of times?!
All I need is for you to blow up
and blow their minds!
Alright, how about now?
Apologies for the pandaruption!
Witness my Bamboo Power!
Something's off about you.
What'dya mean?
Huh? What the?
Your whole thing is different.
I'm Pandaman's assistant,
Blackcheekman!
Happy to meet you all!
Blackcheekman?
Yup!
So cute!
Time for a magic trick!
What happened to Pandaman?
He's a bit held up right now.
I want Pandaman!
I got it! I'll go get him!
This is getting on my nerves...
Just let me eat already!
Bamboo Power, everypanda!
Pandaman!
What about Blackcheekman?
Did he leave?
Just forget about him.
I want Blackcheekman...
You don't like Pandaman?
Give us Blackcheekman!
Do I have to?
Yes!
Fine, I'll go get him!
Bamboo Power!
Isn't that Pandaman's catchphrase?
Huh?
Wait, where'd Moon go?
You want to see Moon?
You don't like Blackcheekman?
Give us Moon!
Okay!
Sorry, I was in the bathroom!
You're wearing Pandaman's uniform!
Agh! Uh, he made us matching uniforms.
Where's Pandaman?
You don't want me?
No!
Hey!
Oh dear, where'd my ears go?
I'm so starving,
it's making me dizzy!
What are you up to, Moon?
Eek!
I'm not Moon.
I'm Mr. Pandaman!
Whatever you say.
Jessica!
Still in the clear.
Bamboo Power!
Here we go! Three, two, one!
Where's Cheekman?
Hi!
Where's Moon?
Yeah?
Pandaman!
Bamboo Power!
Cheekman!
Hi!
Moon!
Yeah?
Pandaman!
Bamboo Power!
Moon!
Hi!
Cheekman!
Yeah?
Moon!
Bamboo Pow—
I mean, hi!
I want Pandaman and Cheekman
at the same time!
Huh?! A-At the same time?
Let's get this show on the road, no?
Please enjoy the show, everyone!
Shall we begin?
Go for it!
Three, two, one! Bamboo Power!
It worked!
Um, I can explain!
Uhh...
I'm so sorry! I was lying the whole time!
I don't have any amazing friends!
Not one!
That's not true, you have us!
You didn't need to put on this big show.
Wait, you knew?
It got obvious real quick.
Yeah.
I can't believe it.
But your show was real fun!
It was?
It was amazing!
I bet it was hilarious, wasn't it?
Keep going!
Alright!
It's a beard!
It's a goldfish!
Stop!
salsa
Please eat up while it's hot!
Those croissants look so good!
Thanks, James!
Slow down, Moon.
Gotta eat 'em while they're fresh!
You're getting crumbs all over the floor.
That's just how croissants are!
You're not wrong.
It's hard not to be messy with croissants.
Yeah.
But don't worry about it.
I have something to help with that!
What in the world?!
That's Salsa, my robot vacuum!
It looks for messes and cleans them up
all on its own!
Whoa!
Thanks to Salsa, my home is beautiful 24/7!
Just like me.
Oh wow.
So I can do this?
Yep!
Amazing!
It can suck up large pieces of trash, too!
Really?
Nooo!
Oh, it stopped.
Don't worry.
Salsa here checks to verify
if something is trash or not.
That was close...
You're quite smart!
That must be nice.
Maybe I should get one too.
A vacuum robot, eh?
You thinking of getting one, Moon?
Nah, not one bit.
Who needs a robot
that can't combine or transform?
James, I need your bathroom.
Help yourself.
Don't follow me!
Salsa's detecting garbage!
You're getting crumbs on the floor
as you walk.
Whatever.
I already gave you my crumbs!
Moon, your sole.
Aah!
Hey, cut that out!
That tickles!
It almost looks like Salsa's
taken a liking to you, Moon.
Thanks for treating us, James!
Anytime!
Moon, we're leaving!
I know, but...
This thing keeps clinging to me
and doesn't want to let me go!
James, can I borrow it?
What? Of course not.
Come on, lemme borrow it!
This thing won't leave my side,
and it'll tidy up my room!
You'll let me have it, right, James?
Fine, take it. But only for the night, okay?
This is the life.
Salsa, fetch!
Wow, not bad!
Go long!
Keep it going!
Fetch! Fetch! Fetch!
Lookin' good!
I-Is this my room?!
It's sparkling clean!
Salsa, did you clean this place
while I was asleep?
Good job, Salsa!
It's James.
Yes, James?
Hey, Moon! How's Salsa doing?
It's awesome!
It made my whole house
sparkling clean top to bottom!
Right?
That's great! Can you bring it back to me?
Wanna go home, Salsa?
Huh? No, you don't?
Huh?
Salsa says it doesn't wanna go home.
Um, I don't...
So I'mma hold on to it a bit longer.
Hey, Moon!
Come on, Salsa! This way!
Moon!
You still haven't given it back?
It won't leave me alone.
Where are you guys headed to?
Jessica said she bought her own vacuum robot,
so we're going to check it out.
Jessica bought one?!
It's called Bongo,
and it's a size smaller than Salsa.
Bongo's so cute!
I know!
It's so comfortable to ride!
My darling Salsa is cuter than that!
Aren't you?
That's not yours, though!
Bongo was just released,
so it has more features than Salsa!
They're useless features, I take it.
No they're not!
Then let's see which one's better:
my Salsa or your Bongo!
It doesn't have to be a competition.
Wrong! Salsa's the better robot!
What are you doing?
I'm gonna spread this flour to prove
that my Salsa is the cutest and the smartest!
Go!
Moon, stop it!
Hey, what's the big deal?!
Look at those two!
Don't lose to Bongo!
Aww, cute!
They're dancing!
They're really in sync!
Salsa! Stop playing around
and show them that you're unbeatable!
Why does it matter which one is better?
Both of them are cute and smart.
They look like a perfect couple!
That's beautiful!
"Perfect" my butt!
Harumph!
Harumph, I say!
We're a way better match for each other
than you and Bongo!
Ain't we, Salsa?
Are you blushing?
Alright, let's play some tag!
Salsa, you're it!
And begin!
Huh?
Oh, I get it.
That should do it.
C'mon, Salsa!
What? Is it not dirty enough?
C'mon, now!
What's gotten into you?
C'mon! Clean it up!
Why aren't you moving, Salsa?
Does something hurt?
Run for me like you did yesterday!
You were so happy at Jessica's place!
You don't have the hots for Bongo, do you?
Are you telling me you'd rather be
with it than me?!
Suit yourself then!
Yeowch!
Why is there a package of cup noodles here...?
Salsa, do your job—
Ugh, what now?
You're giving Salsa back today, and that's final.
I'm not letting go of Salsa.
That's my robot vacuum!
I'm coming over to get it.
Aah! Hey, Moon!
You want to be with Bongo, don't you?
Juby-julee-juby, juby-juby...
Moon?
Oh, I see. You decided to give it back after all!
Aw, what?
We're almost there, Salsa!
Bongo! Where are you, Bongo?
Moon?!
Bongo!!
Salsa, Bongo's here!
C'mon, you were longing for it, no?
Moon, just give Salsa back already!
Shuddup!
Jessica, get me some trash!
I took it all out earlier.
Huh?!
Wait, let me have that trash!
What?
I'm taking it!
Knock it off!
He must be in a fuss since Salsa stopped moving.
Did it break?
Nope. I have a feeling what might've stopped it.
What the heck?
It cleaned so much, the tank filled up.
Moon wasn't even emptying Salsa out?
No wonder it stopped moving.
Sal—aah!
If you fill steamed potatoes with seafood
and add cream sauce,
it's supposed to be very delicious!
We have to try that!
Salsa...
You really do feel better
now that you're with Bongo again.
Sir, I need that trash...
I have no use for it anymore.
Huh?!
Salsa!!
I wish you the best with Bongo!
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
I dreamt I was flying through the night sky
mahou no juutan ni notte
On a magic carpet
tondeku yozora no yume
And I just wanted you to see it
kimi ni mo
kimi ni mo misetakute
misetai
Oh, did I wake you? I'm so sorry
okoshichatta kana? gomen ne
I thought you sounded half-asleep
neboketa kotobatachi ni
And it made me swoon
nandaka
nandaka kyun to kita
kyun kyun
Just like the glittering scent of rose tea
kirameku kaori no roozu tii mitai ni
When my heart starts pounding, I lock up
dokidoki no sono shunkan
tojikomeru
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
Even though I could just type a <3 and send it to you
yubisaki haato wo nosete
tsutawattara ii no ni
It's hard to sum up the way I feel for you
kimi e no kono kimochi
hitokoto ja tarinai
It's like a millefeuille
egao mo namida mo zenbu
With all of my smiles and tears mixed in
tsumikasaneta mirufiiyu
I feel happy, I feel painful
ureshii setsunai itoshii
I feel longing — I'm in love
koishiteru
space
Next time on Line Town...
Brown pushes some button like "BAM!"
And it sends us into space like "BOOM!"
The sights are like "WAM!",
and we're all like "BAM!"
space
And aliens show up like "WAM!"
The donuts go "WAM!"
Space goes "BAM!"
Tune in next time!