A-B-C-D-E-F-G
H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P
Q-R-S-T-U-V-W
X-Y and Z
Now you know your ABCs
Isn't it bizarre, the way we string together
letters from A to Z?
Whether it be out loud or by text,
let's find something to talk about!
How will the world end? What's for dinner?
Let's share those moments of laughter and tears
I decide what I like and hate
But that too is a barrier I can break down
Don't you see? Our words make us who we are
There's something I want to talk about with you
Just thinking about that gets me all giddy
Whether you're right next to me or not
You always brighten up my day
Of all the things you've spoken to me
I cherish every last word
It feels good to think about somebody
And it feels good to put that into words
guest 7
Then the taxi driver got startled!
"Who could have killed you?" asked the driver.
And the long-haired lady responded...
"You did it!"
Huh? Wasn't that scary?
Nope.
Well, that's funny.
I was scared silly when my friend
told me that story.
It's 'cuz your delivery stinks!
What?!
Think of it like this: you always sound
so pleasant and cheerful!
Right, Cony?
Yeah, that! When I say scary stories don't suit you,
I mean it in a good way!
Got it?
Aw, really?
I guess I am a pretty pleasant prince,
if I do say so myself.
Y-Yup, got that right...
Who should tell a story next?
You want me to do it?
I think you would tell a good one!
Yeah, your face just screams scary!
What's that supposed to mean?
Ignore that.
You must know a good story, no?
Hmm, one does come to mind.
But I probably shouldn't.
Why not?
Well, this story can summon a real ghost.
At least, supposedly.
A real ghost?
Yeah, so maybe let's not.
Oh, you. You're just trying to freak us out, aren't you?
You're like an open book.
Think whatever you want.
I'm still not telling it.
You can't just tell us about it then pull out,
that's teasing!
I guess I can tell the story if you really want,
but are you sure?
Absolutely!
I'm no scaredy-cat.
Right, Jessica?
Um, yeah, sure!
I'm intrigued.
Here I go, then.
This is a true story.
One summer,
a group of students went on a camping trip
to the mountains during their break.
There were three boys and three girls.
Six friends grouped together.
Hey, three boys and three girls?
That's just like us!
My bad.
The band trekked deep into the forest,
and came across an old cottage.
It looked as though nobody had
resided there for many years.
However, it had a fireplace,
so the six took a stay in there.
That night, they sat by the fire
and chatted with one another.
Just as we are.
When one of the boys spoke aloud...
"Hey, what's that?"
Wh-What is it?
He pointed above the fireplace.
They all turned to look.
There were six dolls lined up
one after the other.
But of those six,
one was missing its head.
Ha, sorry 'bout that.
That door's clatch has been broken,
so the wind pushed it open.
D-Don't startle us like that!
Did it get you?
O-Only a little bit!
Yeah, maybe I shouldn't tell this story.
Just tell us!
Then I'll continue.
"A kid probably broke it
while playing with it,"
said one of the girls,
picking up the decapitated doll.
Upon closer inspection,
she found something written
in very small letters on its back.
Holding it above the light of the flames,
she read it aloud.
This is what was written:
"The next time six people gather here,
I will make my return."
Then, there were two knocks
at the cottage's door.
Delivery.
I forgot I ordered a pizza!
So that was just the delivery man...
You really freaked us out!
That was one big scream, Cony!
Anyone would've freaked out
in this situation.
Exactly!
That was a hot minute,
and now I'm hungry!
And I need me some hot pizza!
Pizza, pizza, pizza!
Just wait.
Let's see, there's six here...
Yay, pizza!
That hits the spot!
Nothing beats a pizza
after some scary stories!
Huh?! Where's my slice?
It's gone!
Moon, are you sure you counted right?
Of course I did!
There's one, two, three,
four, five, six of us!
And I cut six slices!
Glare.
Why are you looking at me?
Cony, did you eat two slices?
I did not!
I'm pretty sure we all only took one.
I cut six slices for six people and I don't have one.
Why do you suppose that is?
It's because someone took two.
And who could that be?
Cony, it must be you!
Huh? Why do you think I did it?
Because you eat twice as much
as anybody else!
Rude!
Calm down, now.
There must be a misunderstanding!
I don't want your half-eaten slice!
What a baby, sulking over
some dumb pizza.
Say that again!
Calm down!
Oh, right! I brought some watermelon!
Let's have some of that!
Nice, cold watermelon!
And cut certifiably in six!
Yay, watermelon!
I know for a fact I cut that pizza in six.
Gosh, this is heaven!
It's so cold and sweet!
Watermelon's the best summer treat.
Huh? Where'd my slice go?
Huh?
Hey, what about me?
That's weird.
You ate two, didn't you, Moon?
I only took one!
I see! You wanted more pizza,
so you put the blame on me to get me back!
What kind of weird accusation is that?!
You did it first!!
That's enough, you guys!
This must be some sort of...
Uhh...
I don't even know!
Hold on one moment.
What is it, Sally?
Listen.
The pizza and watermelon
were cut into six slices each,
and both were missing one slice.
What's your point?
There's seven people here.
Oh, that makes sense!
Wait, no it doesn't.
Sally, James, Jessica, Cony, Brown, and me.
There's only six!
There's six of us,
but there's seven here.
What do you mean?
It can only be one thing!
What is it?
A guardian deity.
A guardian deity?
Indeed.
Mysterious beings believed to have
lived under our roofs since olden times.
Whenever it feels there's someone else
in the room with you that you can't see,
there must be a guardian deity.
There's no way.
Are you serious?
I'm going home!
M-Me too!
H-Hey, wait up!
I wanna go home...
b-but it's pitch black outside!
I'm too scared to leave!
It's not like you have anywhere else to stay!
I mean, I'd sure hope you don't leave...
If we all stick together,
there's nothing to be afraid of!
Let's play Old Maid!
Card games are a great way
to get your mind off things!
I'll go first!
Your turn!
This one!
Got it.
Here.
Yup.
Who the heck are you?
Are you a guardian deity?
No, I'm just...
Are you a ghost?!
A ghost?
Why, not at all! I'm a human!
See?
Okay, then who are you?!
Oh, you know.
Just a passerby, I suppose?
Seems like no one's home.
Wait, what?
You gotta remember to lock your doors!
Whoever lives here must be klutzy.
Nothing valuable here...
Let's play some video games!
Uh-oh!
I'm tired of video games.
Then I have just the idea!
What is it?
Telling scary stories!
Oh yeah! I'm down!
Okay!
I'll go up to bat first with my story!
This is one my friend once told me!
And here I am.
So you're the one who ate
our pizza and watermelon?
I'm terribly sorry.
I got hungry and couldn't help myself!
Man, I was so scared it was a ghost or something.
Again, terribly sorry.
I guess you're not a guardian deity,
but a guardian old man!
I'll be off now.
Apologies for the intrusion.
So who was that guy anyway?
Dunno...
Wait, a thief?!
Where'd you go? Show yourself!
He vanished! Man, that thief is quick!
What should we do now?
Go back to playing cards or tell more scary stories?
I think I've had enough scary stories.
Let's get a new game of Old Maid going!
Yeah, let's go!
devil zombie
Cony's got a big grin on her face!
Everyone knows Cony and her grin!
I never knew there was a clover field here!
It's like a big green carpet!
Did you know that four-leaf clovers
are supposed to bring you happiness?
They are?
I'mma go find one!
Guess finding one isn't so easy.
Let's move along for now.
No! Not until I find one!
We really should be at Moon's soon.
Agh, why isn't there any?!
Brown, we're moving!
Oh?
What is it?
A four-leaf clover?!
Did you find that, Brown?
Wow, look at you go!
Good job!
Huh, is it for me?
Thank you, Brown!
Here it is!
Behold!
The Make-Believe-atron?
This bad boy can turn anyone into anything!
For real?
Don't believe me?
Let's give it a whirl, then.
James, get in front.
Okay...
This good?
Save the pose.
Begin!
What the?
In three seconds, you will become
the first thing you see!
Three, two, one!
Whoa!
How do we make him normal again?
I'm pretty sure...
Reset!
What was I doing just now?
That's awesome!
This'll work for you, Jessica!
That's just an alarm clock.
Yep! And that's just what you're gonna be!
I could never!
It'll be fine!
Three, two, one!
Tick. Tick. Tick. Tick.
R-R-R-R-R-Ring!
Reset!
What in the world?
Magnificent!
Brown, you're up next!
What will happen if
you see a rice ball?
I'm not sure about that.
Three, two, one!
He's not moving.
Well, he is a rice ball.
I wanna be a princess!
Princess, princess...
Found it!
Begin!
Three, two, one!
Oh no! Cony turned into the Devil Zombie!
The Devil Zombie?!
It's the most repulsive devil in all of history!
The most ferocious villain in the world!
Quickly, grab her ears and reset her!
Me?! I can't do that!
Why not?!
My grandpa told me on his deathbed
to never grab a zombie by the ears!
What a way to go out!
Never mind that! James, you would look
awesome grabbing her ears!
Why do I have to?
H-Hey, Cony! How've you been?
Come to think of it, pollock roe
are the eggs of pollocks, yeah?
When did the eggs of walleye pallocks
become walleye pollock roe, am I right?
Rese—
If we don't grab her ears and reset her,
she'll be stuck as the Devil Zombie forever!
No way!
I don't want Cony to be that thing forever!
First things first, let's study our enemy
by watching the Devil Zombie movies.
Devil Zombie: You've Got Brains,
and Devil Zombie: The Wedding Harbinger.
Which one?
It doesn't matter!
Who knew Devil Zombie was so brutal?!
I wish I hadn't watched.
The handsome guy who attacked it at the end
was wearing a pretty cool shirt, though!
Yeah, but as far as horror movies go,
that was only a 2 out of 5.
That's none of the matter!
Did you figure out anything useful?
I took notes!
Devil Zombie only attacks people who have seen its face!
Which means it's gonna come back for us!!
But it had a weakness, didn't it?
Devil Zombie likes spicy foods
and is weak against sweet chocolate.
Perfect!
Plan A!
While Cony is roaring,
Brown will fire chocolate at her!
While she's shouting "too sweet!",
James will make his move!
Reset!
Hip hip hooray!
What's your role, Moon?
I'll call the shots from somewhere far away!
Well...
Whatever, let's get a move on.
We stand out here,
so she should find us soon.
Chocolate all ready?
I'm starving...
Here she comes!
She's on the zombie-cycle!
Get the chocolate ready!
Got it!
Huh?! What happened?
Why is it empty?!
How should I know?
Brown!
We're not giving up!
New plan!
Devil Zombie is weak to bright lights.
Perfect!
When she shows up,
Brown will turn the light on!
Too bright!
While she's blinded,
James makes his move!
Reset!
Hip hip hooray!
Brown, all good?
Come out wherever you are, Devil Zombie!
What?!
Her zombie wings grew even bigger!
Yikes!
Brown, go!
Brown, what's wrong?
Hurry up!
It's not working?!
Let's hide inside!
It's over!
Brown!
Thank you, Brown!
Cony!
What was I doing?
You're back to normal!
We're so glad you're back!
Four-leaf clovers really do
bring happiness!
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
I dreamt I was flying through the night sky
mahou no juutan ni notte
On a magic carpet
tondeku yozora no yume
And I just wanted you to see it
kimi ni mo
kimi ni mo misetakute
misetai
Oh, did I wake you? I'm so sorry
okoshichatta kana? gomen ne
I thought you sounded half-asleep
neboketa kotobatachi ni
And it made me swoon
nandaka
nandaka kyun to kita
kyun kyun
Just like the glittering scent of rose tea
kirameku kaori no roozu tii mitai ni
When my heart starts pounding, I lock up
dokidoki no sono shunkan
tojikomeru
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
Even though I could just type a <3 and send it to you
yubisaki haato wo nosete
tsutawattara ii no ni
It's hard to sum up the way I feel for you
kimi e no kono kimochi
hitokoto ja tarinai
It's like a millefeuille
egao mo namida mo zenbu
With all of my smiles and tears mixed in
tsumikasaneta mirufiiyu
I feel happy, I feel painful
ureshii setsunai itoshii
I feel longing — I'm in love
koishiteru
salsa
friend
Next time on Line Town...
Do you have any cool friends?
Mine is a really tiny old man!
He's always right by my pillow,
singing me lullabies!
salsa
friend
But not long ago, I rolled over
and crushed him...
I'm sorry, little old man!