A-B-C-D-E-F-G
H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P
Q-R-S-T-U-V-W
X-Y and Z
Now you know your ABCs
Isn't it bizarre, the way we string together
letters from A to Z?
Whether it be out loud or by text,
let's find something to talk about!
How will the world end? What's for dinner?
Let's share those moments of laughter and tears
I decide what I like and hate
But that too is a barrier I can break down
Don't you see? Our words make us who we are
There's something I want to talk about with you
Just thinking about that gets me all giddy
Whether you're right next to me or not
You always brighten up my day
Of all the things you've spoken to me
I cherish every last word
It feels good to think about somebody
And it feels good to put that into words
model
It's so beautiful!
I'm the happiest girl in the world!
Ma'am?!
Do you like this dress?
Yes, it's very beautiful!
Would you like to wear it for yourself?
Well, hopefully someday!
Why wait?
You could wear it right away!
Huh?
Moo-Moo-Moon!
Hey, guys! Let's do something fun!
Okay! How about we go to my place
and put on beauty masks?
Beauty what?
It feels very good! It'll make your skin smoother!
Makes your skin smoother, you say?
Yep! Smooth as a baby's bottom!
I think my skin is just smooth enough.
Got a big grin on my face!
Yup, Cony's grinning!
'Cuz she's just so happy!
Dang, she looks like she's in a good mood.
I got an idea! Guys, get on the ground!
Huh? Why?
We're gonna play a prank on Cony!
What...?
When she sees us lifeless on the ground,
she'll get worried about us!
Then we'll jump up like "boo!"
and give her a good scare!
I see...
Hurry up, James!
That's filthy!
I've got a grin 'cuz I'm just so happy!
Hey, get this!
Huh?!
You'll never believe this, Jessica!
What is it, Cony?
It's real big, so prepare yourself!
Hey, show some concern for us!
Tell me!
Well, you see, I...
I'm gonna be a bride!
Say what?!
D-Did you say a bride?!
Eeyup!
Y-You're getting married?!
Say what?
Cony's getting married?!
Please, I'm not getting married.
But I am gonna be a bride!
...What?
How exactly?
So there's this bridal shop nearby!
And I saw this wedding dress on display!
And then, get this...
We actually happen to be seeking a model
for a billboard advertising our shop.
Would you be willing to model for us?
You want me to?
Absolutely!
No way! I'm no model!
You certainly look like one to me!
Oh, my! How do I respond?
Oh, what's the big deal?
You're a model, not a bride.
You got that right. I'm gonna be a model.
Just an M-O-D-E-L.
That's impressive, Cony!
You're gonna be on a billboard!
Yeah, I am!
I'm not too keen on being in the spotlight,
so I actually said no at first...
But he practically begged me to take it on!
Why would he settle for someone like you?
Well, she's got a pretty face!
What?
Well, I guess I am kind of pretty.
But it's kind of embarrassing
when someone takes a liking to me!
You're so pretty!
And you'll look even moreso
in that wedding dress!
Naw, you're just saying that...
I'm not!
I want to see you all dressed up like a bride!
This is so much...
This is ridiculous. Bah.
Going home, Moon?
Count me out of this.
That's too bad.
You're missing out.
Huh?
It is a wedding shoot, after all!
So we'll need a model for the groom!
I was hoping I could get a professional model
to do more eye-catching promotion
and run TV commercials for the shop, but, well...
It's just not in the budget.
So I have to take the cheap route
and hire amateur models instead.
They need a male model too?
Yup, he told me to bring any guy I think fits best.
So I started wondering which one I should pick...
...I'm sorry?
I thought you were leaving.
Well, I felt like hanging around
you lovely ladies just a little longer.
Oh boy, I don't know!
I'd sure love to help you out, Cony!
Modeling's not really my forté,
but I'll do what I must!
You're not her only option, though...
Huh? I-I suppose, yes.
But I mean, if you're looking for
one of us to play a groom, well...
It seems clear-cut to me.
Oh yeah? How so?
What's that? You want to be the groom too, Moon?
D-Don't put words in my mouth!
I don't wanna be no stinking model.
Plus, as if I'd volunteer to be Cony's groom.
It's a good thing I didn't ask!
Well, maybe Brown can do it.
Nah, Brown's too shy for that.
See? Just thinking about it
has him trembling with anxiety!
He could never stand in front of a camera.
Alright!
Brown can't handle it,
and Moon doesn't want to,
so I'll be your model!
Now, it's not like I'm just doing it
because I have to.
I mean, I'd love to—
no, I'm not that into it.
But since I'm calmly taking this on,
it's all's well that ends well!
This hasn't ended well at all!
I mean, I sure don't wanna do any modeling.
I mean, imagine my face plastered on a billboard,
making all the girls in town go...
"Eek! Moon, please give me your autograph!
You're so handsome!"
and everyone in town knows my name!
I don't want any of that.
Then just leave it to me!
Hold your horses! Sure, I don't want to be a model.
And I definitely don't wanna be paired up with Cony.
But you get it, right? Y'know what I mean.
My friendships are serious business to me!
Cony needs a partner in this gig.
And James, you're forcing yourself to do that!
I can't just sit by and watch you
torture yourself like this!
Let me look out for you.
I get where you're coming from,
but I won't just make you!
I cherish my friendships too!
I could never wish such ill upon you.
So I'll do it—
I can't allow you, Jamellus!
You wish not to become a model either,
do you?
Who's "Jamellus"?
I apologize, Jamellus. I held you in high doubt.
I always assumed you had wanted
to become a model!
Jamellus, please strike at me!
No, please strike at me, Selimoontius!
I had assumed you wanted
to become a model as well!
Jamellus!
Selimoontius!
Squeeze.
Okay, out with it.
Both of you want to model, right?
Show of hands.
Me.
Et tu, Browntus?!
And so...
I thought it'd be best to let you choose between them.
So I brought all three.
I see...
I mean, any of them will do.
Huh?
Ah, no, I mean... since you brought all of them,
we should try taking photos of all three!
Then I can decide based on the photos.
That works too.
My assistants over this way
can help you out with your dress fitting.
I'm here!
Juby-julee!
Ready.
Boys, keep up those good looks!
Who might you be?
I'm Cony's escort.
Escort?
Do you want to be the bri—
I'm here!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
I-It's all fine.
Je t'aime!
You look quite fine, Jamellus.
Me? Look at you, you're positively dashing, Selimoontius!
Tu as well, Browntus.
Attention, please!
The bride is here!
Oh, beautiful!
It looks pretty good on you, I guess.
Time to begin the photoshoot!
Juby!
Julee!
Juby-julee!
James, you're blocking my shot!
Um, bridegroom?
What's it?
You're posing a lot like a martial artist
or a ramen shop owner.
What?!
Please just smile for the camera.
S-Sorry...
Fantastic!
You look like a pure new couple.
Hold those poses!
The billboard should be going up today!
I can't wait to see who made the cut!
I hope you guys won't hate me
if I get picked!
That's what I was gonna say!
Gosh, this is so exciting!
What?!
The heck happened here?
What's this supposed to be?!
Well, I gave it a lot of thought,
and this is what I came out with.
See, watch this.
I thought it would be best if customers could have some fun
and take beautiful pictures for themselves!
A good idea, if I do say so myself!
It ain't good to us!
Now it doesn't even matter
which one of us was the groom!
That's awful!
Well, uh...
We all wanted to see who got picked!
My apologies.
Your apology won't cut it!
Brown, yell at him with us!
Yeah! How could you do this, Mister?
Many apologies. I'm very sorry about this.
Why, you...!
Now nobody will see my beauty!
Oh, well.
hero
He defeats the evil forces
and preserves the peace.
Our neighborhood hero, Oldman!
Up I go!
Thank you for saving the day again, Oldman!
Oh my stars!
Oldman is the coolest guy ever!
I wanna be a hero like him!
Any good hero needs tights!
Hm, this feels... off.
Where was it...?
Found ya!
The badge that came with my
Full Moon Monthly magazine!
Lookin' good!
Your friendly neighborhood Hero!
I feel awesome!
Now all I gotta do is beat up some baddies
and I'll be a real hero!
Guess what?
Turns out polar bears' fur isn't white,
but transparent!
Hah!
Oh, Moon.
I am not this "Moon".
Huh?
I send baddies flying
to the dark side of the moon!
It's me, your friendly neighborhood Hero!
Hero?
Are you sure you're not Moon?
You sound just like him.
Juby...
I am, in fact, his cousin's second cousin's
cousin's second cousin.
No wonder you're just like him!
I'm on patrol to keep Line Town safe!
So if any baddies show up, fear not
for I will take them down!
How so?
Huh?
How will you beat them?
With my signature attacks, of course.
My very own Moonsault Scramble Punch!
My very own Full Moon Thunder Tornado Kick!
Bravo!
Line Town is safe in my hands!
Duty calls!
Hah!
I send baddies flying
to the dark side of the moon!
It's me, Hero!
Eek!
Huh? Uh, no, hey...
Calm down, Jessica!
This is our friendly neighborhood Hero!
He's a distant relative of Moon's!
Hero?
Yeah! Where's the baddie?
Well...
I spilled some of this chocolate shake
on my cardigan...
Dang, so nothing important.
Huh? You're just gonna ignore someone in trouble?
Huh...?
I really liked this cardigan...
Now I can never wear it around.
Sniffle.
I mean, she is in trouble, but...
Don't worry, Hero will find a way!
Really?
Huh? Uh, umm...
Thank you, Hero!
Knew we could count on you!
Good grief...
Why does a hero have to clean up a chocolate stain?
Wow, amazing!
It's just like new!
That reminds me, I have this sweater
with a ketchup stain on it!
Huh?
Just one moment.
Would you be able to—
I'm a hero, not a laundry cleaner!
Isn't there anything more big and epic
for a hero to take care of?
This must be my duty!
Are you alright?
Were you attacked by a baddie?
I'll take care of them!
Show yourself!
It's over there...
Huh?
Yuck, what is all this?
I haven't looked in that spot for ages,
and I caught a glance of it just now...
And it looks awful!
Who are you anyways?
Your friendly neighborhood Hero!
Oh?
Glad you're here!
Please clean up that ugly mess for me!
It's your fault for not keeping it clean!
But I stink at getting rid of dust!
Who doesn't?!
Blegh, I can't!
Someone, please help...!
Come on...
Heroes aren't supposed to be doing chores!
All done.
Duty?!
Ugh, what are you doing?
I got hungry and tried making pancakes,
but I messed up...
Oh, I know! Hero, can you—
Not happening!
You can't make a hero cook pancakes for you!
Wow, nice flip!
Please come visit me again, Hero!
Why would I do that?
Thank you so much!
Cooking and cleaning?
What does she think I am, a maid?
Hero, I need your help!
Does duty finally call?
It's an emergency! We have to go now!
You can count on me!
Where's the baddie?
That a-way!
I heard from my friend Jessica
you were good at removing chocolate stains!
If we don't make haste,
it'll become impossible to remove!
I'll leave it to you!
Why do I have to clean up
two chocolate stains in one day...?
It's good as new!
Thank you so much, Hero!
Right!
I should have some left.
Say whut?
Hero, please have one for your hard work!
These apples are very delicious!
Oh?
I'm done! I'm not taking on any more boring jobs.
I can't believe even Sally would
make me work like that.
What do those jerks think a hero is supposed to be?
Isn't there anything more disastrous happening?
If there were a big baddie,
I could fire up my signature attacks.
My very own Moonsault Scramble Punch!
My very own Full Moon Thunder Tornado Kick!
Hero!!
It's a disaster!
He's going on a rampage!
If no one stops him,
he might bring chaos to Line Town!
Hero, take him out with your signature attacks!
Huh?
Yikes...
Uh, Hero?
Y-You got it...
Then get out there!
Hey, you! I send baddies like you
flying to the dark side of the moon!
It's me, your friendly neighborhood Hero!
I can't do it! Nope, nope, nope!
What's wrong, Hero?
I didn't know he could breathe fire!
That would've been real helpful to know beforehand!
Come on, man!
I don't stand a chance against that monster!
If you fight him and keep our town safe,
you'll be a real hero!
Huh?
A... real hero?
Yeah! This is your ultimate chance
to become a real hero!
Wait, what?
Brown, I wasn't talking to you!
Don't push yourself, Brown!
Get back here, Brown! Brown!!
He fainted with his eyes open!!
Watch out, Brown!
Move!
Hero!!
Are you alright?
Watch where you point that thing!
Fighting is so scary!
Use your attacks, Hero!
A-Alright...
It's time for my ultimate attack!
I'll hear out your side of the story, start to finish.
Wait, what?
Is something upsetting you?
You know, rampaging won't solve anything!
If something's wrong, you gotta tell us!
You'll feel much better once you let it all out.
There's something stuck in there.
Got it!
Take care of yourself!
Looks like peace has returned to Line Town!
Thank you, Hero!
Huh? Hero, where'd you go?
I'm pooped.
I don't wanna be a hero.
I'm definitely not cut out for it.
What's that? You wanna be Hero's apprentice?
You should quit while you're ahead.
Moon, where's that relative of yours?
Gone, by now.
Don't expect him to show up again.
Aw, man!
Now, listen. Being a hero is nothin' but hard work.
Don't be a hero. Just watch them.
He's good at cleaning and doing laundry!
Not to mention cooking!
And he doesn't do it for a reward!
And I heard he saved Line Town
not with his fists, but his words!
What a dreamboat!
I wish I could marry someone like Hero!
Me too!
I hope we see him again.
Don't be a hero.
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
I dreamt I was flying through the night sky
mahou no juutan ni notte
On a magic carpet
tondeku yozora no yume
And I just wanted you to see it
kimi ni mo
kimi ni mo misetakute
misetai
Oh, did I wake you? I'm so sorry
okoshichatta kana? gomen ne
I thought you sounded half-asleep
neboketa kotobatachi ni
And it made me swoon
nandaka
nandaka kyun to kita
kyun kyun
Just like the glittering scent of rose tea
kirameku kaori no roozu tii mitai ni
When my heart starts pounding, I lock up
dokidoki no sono shunkan
tojikomeru
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
Even though I could just type a <3 and send it to you
yubisaki haato wo nosete
tsutawattara ii no ni
It's hard to sum up the way I feel for you
kimi e no kono kimochi
hitokoto ja tarinai
It's like a millefeuille
egao mo namida mo zenbu
With all of my smiles and tears mixed in
tsumikasaneta mirufiiyu
I feel happy, I feel painful
ureshii setsunai itoshii
I feel longing — I'm in love
koishiteru
faking sick
mud balls
Next time on Line Town...
Kneading mud balls!
Kneady-kneady-kneady-kneady-need!
Rolling mud balls!
Rolly-rolly-rolly-rolly-ball!
Muddy mud balls!
Muddy-muddy-muddy-muddy-dud!
faking sick
mud balls
Tumbling mud balls!
Tumble-tumble-tumble-tumble-dumb!
Moon, Brown, and their mud balls!