A-B-C-D-E-F-G
H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P
Q-R-S-T-U-V-W
X-Y and Z
Now you know your ABCs
Isn't it bizarre, the way we string together
letters from A to Z?
Whether it be out loud or by text,
let's find something to talk about!
How will the world end? What's for dinner?
Let's share those moments of laughter and tears
I decide what I like and hate
But that too is a barrier I can break down
Don't you see? Our words make us who we are
There's something I want to talk about with you
Just thinking about that gets me all giddy
Whether you're right next to me or not
You always brighten up my day
Of all the things you've spoken to me
I cherish every last word
It feels good to think about somebody
And it feels good to put that into words
fortunes
So good!
Hey, guys!
Gleeeam!
James, what's going on there?
You're looking more yellow
than a banana.
I sure hope not,
'cause this isn't banana yellow!
It's lemon yellow!
It's my lucky color for today!
Your lucky color?
Yeah! This always gets it just right.
Daily fortunes?
James, you believe in this fortune-telling stuff?
Forget about that.
Anyone else want donuts?
I heard a new place opened up on 3rd Street!
I heard it too!
People are saying they're very fancy and yummy!
I've been dying to try them!
Let's all go together!
Yeah, let's!
You not coming, James?
Well, 3rd Street is to the east.
The fortunes say bad things will happen
if you go east today!
So you can't come with?
I would if it weren't east...
Fine, let's go without him.
See ya, James!
Aren't there any good donuts
in the west maybe?
Surely, the north and south
have some!
I'm confident!
You don't have to pick
the dangerous path for this, right?
Are you actually gonna leave me here and go east?!
What do we do...?
See, I told you!
This is the same place we always go!
I wanted to go the new donut place!
Now, now. We can always go another time!
Congratulations!
Huh?
You are my store's 10,000th customer!
You can have any donuts you want, on the house!
What a score!
Good thing we came here instead.
You can thank the fortunes for that!
No way. It was just a coincidence.
I don't believe in those silly fortunes.
Moon, your lucky item for today
is a pair of heart-shaped glasses.
And if you change your hairstyle,
you'll have better luck with romance!
Huh?
Wh—
Hey, what's the big idea?!
A girl is staring my way!
Are my popular days finally upon me...?
I really am getting luckier!
It's from Sally!
"I made a cake!
Do you guys want to come over?"
Totally!
Wait, guys!
What's wrong?
Isn't Sally's home east from here?!
...Huh?
I told you, we can't go east!
How are we supposed to get anywhere like that?
I have an idea.
Let's start by heading northeast,
then go way down south
and make our way west.
That way, we should be able to make it to Sally's
without going east.
That's fantastic, Moon!
Why does Moon believe in James' fortunes now...?
Alright! Let's get going to Sally's place
using Moon's east-avoidance plan!
Aww, what?
I'm not taking that long detour.
Brown and I will take the normal route.
Come on, Brown.
What?! Don't tell me you're hooked
on those fortunes too?
The news?
"The fancy new donut store on 3rd Street...
"has a wait time of 10 hours?!"
Huh?! Isn't that the place we were supposed to be?
So if you had gone off to that
new shop on 3rd Street,
you would've had to wait 10 hours!
Close call...
Well, Cony, do you still feel like going east?
Are James' fortunes really all true?
Have they been wrong yet?
James, has anything good come
from you wearing that lucky yellow suit?
Not yellow, lemon yellow!
And nope, nothing!
Uh, nothing at all?
Tsk, tsk, tsk. So naïve.
Nothing happening is the lucky part!
Huh?
Ever since I started wearing my lucky lemon yellow,
nothing bad has happened to me!
My days of utter nothingness keep trucking on!
Nothing can get me now!
Nothing today, nothing to me,
nothing at all-all-all!
And I'm the luckier for it!
I'm in true bliss, la-la-la!
I can't tell if he's taking it positively or negatively.
Juby-jolly!
I spy Brown's lucky item!
Brown's lucky item of the day
is a red flower!
Fun.
But there's no way we can get it
from the top of that tree.
"If you hold on to a red flower,
someone might just give you a salmon!"
That's one weird fortune right there.
Aah, he's climbing for it!
Be careful, Brown!
Nice!
Watch out!!
If you weren't holding that red flower,
you could've been hurt much worse!
Wait, really?
Yep! Brown's lucky item protected him!
What a fine relief.
Hey! So what's my lucky item?
Will it help me with love? Dieting?
I'll take anything!
Your lucky item is...
Is? Tell me!
A stone!
Huh?
I don't suppose I have any other
lucky items, do I...?
"Holding a stone will make you
irresistible to the opposite gender,
"as well as boost your chances of
winning the lottery or losing weight!"
Says the fortune.
Oh, like one of those totem stones!
I've heard about this!
A-Are you sure...?
I mean, I'm sure it'll burn some calories...
So heavy...
Watch out!!
One, two, three...
Huh?
Everyone, take three steps back!
Why though?
A crow just flew past us, correct?
Umm, yeah?
If something black passes you and you
don't take three steps back, it's a bad omen!
Wow, really? Yikes...
One, two, three...
It's so heavy...
Phew, all clear.
What?!
How many was that?
How many steps back do we take?!
Just start walking!!
Easier said than done, here!
Move back, guys!
Ouchie...
Where are we?
My phone's dead!
Don't tell me we're lost!
What was that?!
What do we do...?
I don't wanna sleep out here!!
Everyone, stay calm!
Here, Cony.
Hold on to your lucky item!
Don't worry! Your luck is on the way, I promise!
Put a sock in it!
Huh?!
None of this is lucky at all!!
We wouldn't be lost if it weren't for your fortunes!!
It's my fault?!
Darn right!
This wouldn't have happened
if we just went straight to Sally's house!
Now, hold on!
I thought you believed in my fortunes, Moon?
Yeah, and I was an idiot for it!
Et tu, Brown...?
How could you?
I just wanted to help you guys!
Don't act all innocent!
What she said!
And that yellow suit looks ugly on you!
How many times do I have to say it?
It's lemon yellow!
Why, I oughta...!
Cut it out, guys!
I hate this...
We could've been eating cake
at Sally's house right now...
What's taking them so long?
What's that?
Hey, guys!
What are you doing way over there?
Sally!
Who would've thought your house
was so close by!
I saw something yellow shuffling around,
and I was wondering what it was.
And it was you, James!
Well, it's actually lemon yellow, but yeah...
You must be starving!
Have some cake!
It looks delicious!
Gotta get some forks.
Thank goodness we made it here in the end.
James' yellow suit really came in handy!
It's lemon...
Eh, I guess "yellow" is fine at this point.
Now that we're all chill on this...
Really, no matter how "lucky" it is,
lugging around that huge stone
is super weird, right?
You're not wrong.
So, guys! I've been getting
into fortune telling lately!
I'm going to read your fortunes!
Umm, well...
I think...
We'll pass for now.
Huh? Did something happen?
art
Beautiful.
It's fun to paint like this every now and then.
Art enriches the soul!
Not sure if it feels "enriching" or whatever,
but painting sure is fun!
I should've stayed home...
I stink at drawing...
Wow, that's amazing, Mister!
Y'think so?
It looks so lifelike!
This is marvelous!
It's so detailed, and the linework is very precise!
Are you a famous artist by any chance?
Oh, please. Me? I'm just an old man!
Wow! So humble, too!
Must be nice to have such talent.
Aah! Stop it!
Nooo, stay away from me!
Huh?
Cony, what is that thing?
Your art stinks!
I'm not even sure...
what it's supposed to be.
What's happening over here?
Master, take a look at Cony's awful painting!
M-My word!
It stinks, right?
I-It's marvelous!
This must be cubism!
Cucum...bism?
Cubism is a way of incorporating
different perspectives into a single piece.
In other words, even art that's crude from a glance
can have deep artistic character!
So that's cucumb...ism?
And you're expressing it unconsciously too!
You may just have a gift!
A gift?!
Cucumbism...?
It's "cubism!"
I'm gifted...?
Well, if a master artist like yourself thinks so...
No matter how much I look at this art,
it's just as breathtaking!
Aw, stop it.
He's right!
Your use of color is very unique!
You really are a gifted artist!
Absolutely! You're a diamond in the rough!
You're just finally starting to shine out.
You really think so?
So, Cony! When do you get ideas for your work?
That's a tough question!
I guess they just come naturally to me!
My, oh, my! Very deep.
So casual, yet within it lies
a principle of the universe.
Everyone, take notes!
You got it!
If you have any questions,
please raise your hand.
Me!
Jessica.
What's your favorite food?
Hmm... My favorite food?
C... Cu...
Cucumbers!
Cucumbers?
Naturally!
Cony, like any gifted cucumbism artist,
only eats cucumbers!
Didn't we eat burgers just yesterday...?
Oh, yeah! Cony!
Hold it!
Huh?!
Aren't you being a bit cheeky?
You're talking to the Cony!
The gifted cucumbism artist!
You ought to show her some respect!
You're amazing, Master!
Oh, please.
Well, if you insist on calling me Master,
I won't stop you.
Do you all get it now?
Yes, Master!
Master, would it please you to draw a portrait
of my beautiful face?
Excuse me? Master is awfully busy at the moment!
Now, Moon. It's fine!
I can spare a special drawing
for one of my close friends.
Thank you very much, Master!
Think nothin' of it!
Twing!
And voilà!
Is that... me?
Marvelous!
You've blessed our world with
yet another new masterpiece!
My face isn't anywhere near that green!
Easy fix!
Now you look just like it!
You're right! It's just like the drawing!
Thank you so much, Master Cony!
Ain't nothin'.
Master!
I've been wanting to decorate my room
with a cute vase.
I've tried making so many by myself,
but they never come out right!
Amateurs shouldn't be messing with vases, nope.
I'll make one for you!
Umm, it's very fascinating,
but there isn't any room to put flowers in it.
"What's the point of a vase with no flowers in it?"
Such a narrow-minded way of thinking.
What's wrong with having a flower-less vase?!
You're so right!
I had it all wrong!
I'm glad you get it.
What's up, Brown?
You want me to paint a salmon
to hang on your wall?
Sure, why not?
Hold it right there!
Aren't you asking Master Cony for too much?!
Huh?
She doesn't have all the time in the world
to keep drawing things for you!
I'm not that busy...
Master.
Y-Yeah?
Don't sell yourself short.
You'll get past this phase.
Phase...?
From now on, I'm not just your assistant,
but your manager as well.
So any and all requests will go through me.
Aah, so busy! Busy as a bee!
Master, we have a lot of offers to go over!
Ugh, who left trash just sitting here...?
Hey, Master!
Everywhere I go,
people are loving your works!
Oh, Moon!
You say something?
Just that everyone loves your works!
I see.
So what do you think of my new piece?
What new piece?
The one I finished earlier and left on the table.
On the table...?
I'm quite proud of it!
Oh, this new piece?
It's very marvelous!
Got that right.
It's the chaos of our world
represented by a cucumber.
Astounding!
You're one gifted artist, Master Cony!
Uh-huh?
If you like it so much,
it's all yours.
Huh, you're giving it to me?
Uhh, how do I put this...
Oh, yeah!
You can have the one
I'm working on right now, if you want it.
What is it?
It's rather big, but you can have it.
Umm... I, uhh...
Well, do you like it?!
Absolutely!
Do you want it?
Uhmm...
Oh, yeah!
I just thought of a great way to showcase your work
to people all around the world!
What is it?
Hello, everyone!
We'd like to thank you today for coming to
the grand opening of Cony Art Park!
The mic's all yours, Master Cony!
Thank you, thank you.
I call this piece "Scuplture of a Cucumber."
This right here is my life's work.
I hope when you all witness it,
you will feel its cucumbism!
A-Amazing!
It's beautiful!
What's going on?
Hey, Sally!
Master Cony is unveiling
her latest work!
It's breathtaking, isn't it?
That cucumber looks so tacky.
What?!
You take that back, Sally!!
Master Cony's art has been recognized
by this famous artist right here!
Pleasure doing business!
Huh?
I'm just here to sell picture frames.
What do you need?
You're kidding!!
It's even worse up close.
It's such a disturbance
to just leave it here in the park.
Y-You really don't get my art, Sally?
What part of this is "art" even?
Huh?!
Now that you mention it...
It's just a cucumber.
I thought the same thing.
Whaaat?!
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
I dreamt I was flying through the night sky
mahou no juutan ni notte
On a magic carpet
tondeku yozora no yume
And I just wanted you to see it
kimi ni mo
kimi ni mo misetakute
misetai
Oh, did I wake you? I'm so sorry
okoshichatta kana? gomen ne
I thought you sounded half-asleep
neboketa kotobatachi ni
And it made me swoon
nandaka
nandaka kyun to kita
kyun kyun
Just like the glittering scent of rose tea
kirameku kaori no roozu tii mitai ni
When my heart starts pounding, I lock up
dokidoki no sono shunkan
tojikomeru
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
Even though I could just type a <3 and send it to you
yubisaki haato wo nosete
tsutawattara ii no ni
It's hard to sum up the way I feel for you
kimi e no kono kimochi
hitokoto ja tarinai
It's like a millefeuille
egao mo namida mo zenbu
With all of my smiles and tears mixed in
tsumikasaneta mirufiiyu
I feel happy, I feel painful
ureshii setsunai itoshii
I feel longing — I'm in love
koishiteru
quiz
lottery
Next time on Line Town...
We're all on a quiz show!
Do I wanna go to the moon? Yeah!
Where are we going? The moon!
When's lunchtime? Noon!
What do you eat soup with? A spoon!
A word for a melody? Tune!
quiz
lottery
When does summer start? June!
Next episode of Line Town is coming soon!