A-B-C-D-E-F-G
H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P
Q-R-S-T-U-V-W
X-Y and Z
Now you know your ABCs
Isn't it bizarre, the way we string together
letters from A to Z?
Whether it be out loud or by text,
let's find something to talk about!
How will the world end? What's for dinner?
Let's share those moments of laughter and tears
I decide what I like and hate
But that too is a barrier I can break down
Don't you see? Our words make us who we are
There's something I want to talk about with you
Just thinking about that gets me all giddy
Whether you're right next to me or not
You always brighten up my day
Of all the things you've spoken to me
I cherish every last word
It feels good to think about somebody
And it feels good to put that into words
lottery
That's a consolation prize.
Another good day...
Last spin, give it everything you've got.
Huh? Is that Brown?
Another consolation prize!
If you want to try again, get more lottery tickets
by making purchases in the shopping district.
Here's your pocket ti—Huh?
Don't you want your tissues?
Brown looks so drained...
Hey, Miss! Want a spin?
No thanks! I don't got any tickets anyways!
That's a pity.
If you pull the special white ball,
you win a trip to Canada.
To Canada?
Moon, what'cha up to?
What do you want?
Oh, it's no big deal, but...
It's not? 'Kay, bye.
Wait, Moon!
What is it?! I'm in the middle of a video game!
I was gonna take a trip to the shopping district!
Need me to get you anything?
Do I need anything?
Yup!
Uh-huh, I'm sure.
Huh?
This is out of character for you.
You're planning something, aren't you?
Th-That's crazy!
Lemme guess. There's a sale going on,
and you wanna pocket the difference?
Of course not! There's no sale going on!
Okay. So you're try'na gain shopping points, right?
I-I wouldn't do that!!
True...
Oh, I know!
Gulp!
You've fallen in love with someone
at the shopping district.
Huh?
W-Well, yeah, maybe.
Aight, I'll leave my list to you.
Thanks! So, what do you want?
Let's see...
Curry and seafood cup noodles,
three each.
Three low-fat milks,
four cookies, six chocolates.
Also, I'm low on toilet paper,
so four rolls, please.
Here.
Uh, hold up.
What now?
Can you repeat?
Oh, come on!
Curry and seafood cup noodles,
three each;
three low-fat milks,
four cookies, six chocolates,
and four rolls of toilet paper!
Three low-fat milks, and, uhh...
Bye.
Curry and seafood cup noodles,
three each...
Three low-fat milks,
four cookies...
James, you there?
Curry and seafood cup noodles,
three each...
What brings you here, Cony?
I'm in the middle of tea time!
You're welcome to join me, if you'd like.
Thanks, James.
Three low-fat milks...
I can get you some low-fat milk tea!
Oh, no, not that.
I was thinking of swinging by
the shopping district!
Oh, are you? That's a pity.
Do you want anything from there?
Oh? You mean you'll shop for me?
Mhm.
Four rolls of toilet paper...
Huh? Four rolls?
Aah, ignore that!
You've always been so nice to me, James!
Is there anything I need?
Oh, but not too much,
my memory's no good.
Oh, right!
I'm starting to run dry on shampoo!
Could you get me some?
You got it! So one bottle of shampoo, correct?
That's good!
I'll be off, then!
One second, Cony!
What's up?
Please make sure the shampoo you get has
bis-aminopropyl dimethicone in it!
Bis...a...?
Bis-aminopropyl dimethicone!
Bis-aminopropyl dimethicone...
What's the matter, Cony?
I was about to head into the shower...
Bis-apinop...
Huh?
Aah, never mind!
I'm going to the shopping district!
Do you need anythicone while I'm out?
Hmm, let me think...
Oh, there is one thing!
Though, preferably nothing with
a really long name.
Name? I just want tea.
Tea? I've got you covered!
Thank you.
Though there's only one place in the district
that sells the tea that I like.
Can you get it there?
What store?
They just opened up!
When you enter the district, go through the light on the right,
and you should see a soda machine to your left,
take the street right past it,
turn right, then left,
then left, then right,
take a slight left, circle around, go right again,
and you should find the shop!
Take the street right past it...
Turn right, then left...
Then left, then right...
Take a slight left, circle around...
Left, circle around...
There it is!
I found you!
Cony?
Sally?
So this is your place?
It belongs to a friend of mine.
I'm just helping out.
I see.
So what are you here to buy?
Umm... uhh...
Low-fat curry shampoo...
Low-fat shampoo?
Uhh, no! I mean, bis-amino methicone...
"Methicone?"
Tea paper, toilet shampoo, uhh...
Calm down!
Cup noodles...
with shampoo...
Uhh... chocolate, take-a-right tea...
So have you decided what you want?
I'll take 100 kettles!
Looks like it's time to close up shop.
Hold it right there!!
Let me have a spin...!
Yeah, sure.
May I see your lottery tickets?
A hundred!
So, a hundred spins!
That Canada trip's all mine!
White ball, white ball, white ball...!
Red ball...?
Consolation prize!
I ain't done yet!
Consolation.
And another.
And another. And another.
And another, and another, and another,
and another, and another, and another.
That's 99 consolation prizes in a row.
You have one last chance.
Now, hold on a minute!
Is there even a white ball in this thing?
Of course there is!
Huh? That's a weird sound...
Well, there might only be one left now.
You mean the Canada trip?!
Well, it hasn't come out yet.
That means...
It's all mine!
What are you doing?!
You guys!
You never came back from your shopping trip,
so we got worried.
Oh, really? I'm sorry.
What are these lottery tickets?
You get them with purchases in the shopping district!
Ah-hah! Caught you red handed.
You were shopping for us
to get those lottery tickets, weren't you?
Uhh, not necessarily...
So where are the things we asked for?
Err, you see...
Did you get my tea?
Or my shampoo with
bis-aminopropyl dimethicone?
Or my curry and seafood cup ramen, three each,
three low-fat milks, and the other stuff?!
Well, you see...
You can have these kettles instead!
I don't need any stinkin' kettles!
Forget that. Let me spin the lottery!
You did my groceries for these tickets, no?
I-I mean...
The top prize is a Canada trip?
I'm going to Canada!
Me too! It's only fair!
I won't let you hog this to yourself.
Go on, let us spin it!
Nooo!!
G-Get back here!!
After it!!
Cony!
Uh-oh!
Juby-juby!!
Come back here, Canada trip!!
You won't get away!!
Cony?
You guys...!
Brown stopped us just in time!
What about the machine?
What the?
It's a dud...
Aww, no!
That's what you get for trying to
hog that trip to yourself!
Did you really want to go to Canada that badly?
Not really...
Then why?
I saw Brown doing the lottery earlier...
The Canada poster has a huge salmon on it,
so I assumed Brown must've really wanted to go.
Then I thought, if I won it for Brown,
it might make him really happy.
Brown seems fairly happy already!
You just wanted a bunch of those red balls
because they look like salmon roe?
Wow, no kidding! They really do!
No kidding!
quiz
Ta-dah!
It's the Line Town Quiz Show!
The winning team will receive
a most luxurious prize...
...a trip to the moon!
My day has come at last!!
I can hear the moon calling me!
I can't believe I get to go to the moon!
Do you want to go to the moon?!
Yeah!
Here's our competing teams!
Team Jessica!
And Team Brown!
Brown, get outta the way!!
We won't go easy on you!!
Neither will we!
Round 1: True-or-false quiz!
If you think the problem is correct,
go to the circle.
If not, go to the X.
Whichever team gets more right will win the round.
Is everyone ready?
Yeah!
No. 1:
It takes the light of the sun approximately
8 minutes and 20 seconds to reach Earth.
True or false?
Huh? I don't know!
Do you, Brown?
I know the light of the moon
takes 2 seconds to reach Earth.
Dunno 'bout the sun, though.
Everyone, stay calm.
I have just the solution!
Your shoes...?
Let's leave it up to Lady Luck!
If it we get heads, it's true—
and if tails, it's false!
Problem solved!
That won't solve the answer for us at all!!
Don't you wanna go to the moon?!
Wow, you're so clever, James!
A-Are you guys sure about this...?
You have 4 seconds left.
Hurry up, James!
You've got it! Hah!
It's tails! Let's get on false!
"It takes the light of the sun approximately
8 minutes and 20 seconds to reach Earth."
The answer is...
True!
Whaaat?!
Yay!
Good thing we studied for this!
Oh, no!
Clearly, trusting your shoe
to handle this was a mistake.
No. 2:
The average distance between the Earth and the sun
is 93,000,000 miles!
93,000,000 mi
True or false?
I don't know that either!
Between the Earth and the sun...?
283,148 mi
If only he asked the moon,
'cuz that's 283,418 miles!
Leave it to my shoe!
Hey!!
Hah!
It's false!
You expect me to believe that
after it steered us wrong last time?!
You don't even have a single drop of luck!!
Wait a minute!
Huh?
Why don't we just give the opposite of James' answer?
I get it! So we'll leave it up to James' lack of luck instead!
That might just work!
Hello?!
So let's go with true!
Huh?!
W-Wait for me!
93,000,000 mi
"The average distance between the Earth and the sun
is 93,000,000 miles!"
The answer is...
True!
Let's go!
What?!
No. 3:
I had toast for breakfast this morning!
True or false?
What kind of question is that?
How are we supposed to know?
Come on, James!
Hah...
I-It's true...
Which means it's false!
Off to false we go!
The answer is: False!
Hooray!
I had miso soup and rice for breakfast.
Also, the soup had seaweed!
We don't need to know that!!
Next question!
False!
True it is!
The answer is: True!
Yeah!!
True!!
The answer is: False!
False!!
True!
True...!
False!
Team Brown wins the first round!
Yeah, go us!
We wouldn't have done it without you, James!
Huh?
He's right! Thanks a ton, James!
O-Oh, no problem. Glad to help...
Round 2: Buzz-in quiz!
Whoever answers the question first wins!
Do we have to go all the way down there to answer?!
I-Is it even safe to cross this bridge...?
No. 1:
What is 3×5?
That's easy!
Moon, go answer it!
Are you crazy?!
Well, someone has to buzz-in first!
I'm afraid of heights...
So am I!!
Then you go, James!
James...?
He fainted with his eyes open!!
Snap out of it, James!
Dang it, and it's such an easy question, too!
Huh...?
Whoa!
Brown, that's amazing!!
Brown...!!
That's very cool and all,
but you gotta hurry up!
3×5=15.
Correct!
Whaaat?!
I'm not afraid of heights at all!
No. 2:
What is 6÷3?
6÷3=2.
Correct!
Team Jessica wins the second round!
Yay! Good going, Sally!
What was that?!
Those were simple math problems!!
If we never go to the moon,
I'm blaming it on you!!
What was that for?!
Cut it out, you guys!
What's the big idea?!
I'm back!
Now, now. Let's stop fighting, okay?
You want a piece of this?!
It's time for the final round!
The team that gets through the obstacles
and obtains the question
will be given the chance to answer!
Intelligence, strength, and luck!
All of it will be put to the test!
Oh, are you all okay?
Well, no matter...
Both teams are currently tied at 1–1!
Whichever wins this round
will be our champions!
Now, on your marks... get set... go!
Don't push me!
Move over!
No, you move over!
We have to climb all the way up there?!
I'm just thinking to myself, but...
We should probably stick behind Brown here,
since he's much better at this kinda thing.
Just IMO.
Humph! I'm not gonna follow you guys on this one.
Where's Moon?
Hurry up!
Shuddup! I'm gonna reach the end first!
Y'all won't beat me—
Brown...!
You guys!
Th-Thank you...
Let's go!
Aye-aye!
So we just need to take this?
Huh? How are we supposed to reach?
Brown, get on my shoulders!
Huh?!
C'mon, do it!
Moon...
You're almost there!
You've got it!
A-Are you okay, Brown?
Hooray!
You did it!
Good job, Brown!
Mine!
See you at the finish line!
That's just foul!
We gotta hurry!
Let's head to the moon together!
Yeah!!
There's the finish line!
Stop right there!
Sally, you help out too!
Wait!!
I have it!
The final round!
If Team Jessica gets this question right,
they will win the show!
Here it is!
The first manned spaceship
to go into space was...
What?!
Vostok 1!
However...
What was the first spaceship
to successfully land on the moon?
Apollo 11!
Correct!
Team Brown wins!
Congratulations!
We're going to the moon!
At last!
The winning team will get to go to the moon in 50 years!
Huh?!
In 50 years...?
Not now...?
Nope, in 50 years.
Congratulations!
Oh, the moon!
We don't get to go for 50 years, huh?
Moon'll be an old man by then.
Yeah, and you'll be an old woman!
I guess!
Let's all go there in 50 years!
Yeah, let's!
Wait for us!
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
I dreamt I was flying through the night sky
mahou no juutan ni notte
On a magic carpet
tondeku yozora no yume
And I just wanted you to see it
kimi ni mo
kimi ni mo misetakute
misetai
Oh, did I wake you? I'm so sorry
okoshichatta kana? gomen ne
I thought you sounded half-asleep
neboketa kotobatachi ni
And it made me swoon
nandaka
nandaka kyun to kita
kyun kyun
Just like the glittering scent of rose tea
kirameku kaori no roozu tii mitai ni
When my heart starts pounding, I lock up
dokidoki no sono shunkan
tojikomeru
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
Even though I could just type a <3 and send it to you
yubisaki haato wo nosete
tsutawattara ii no ni
It's hard to sum up the way I feel for you
kimi e no kono kimochi
hitokoto ja tarinai
It's like a millefeuille
egao mo namida mo zenbu
With all of my smiles and tears mixed in
tsumikasaneta mirufiiyu
I feel happy, I feel painful
ureshii setsunai itoshii
I feel longing — I'm in love
koishiteru
siblings
treasure
Next time on Line Town...
Brown is the father,
James is the big brother, Moon is the little brother?
Oh, no?
James is the big sister, Moon is the little sister,
Jessica is Cony's boyfriend, I'm the mother,
siblings
treasure
and the old man is the same old man?
What does that even mean?
What's going on next time?
Beats me!