A-B-C-D-E-F-G
H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P
Q-R-S-T-U-V-W
X-Y and Z
Now you know your ABCs
Isn't it bizarre, the way we string together
letters from A to Z?
Whether it be out loud or by text,
let's find something to talk about!
How will the world end? What's for dinner?
Let's share those moments of laughter and tears
I decide what I like and hate
But that too is a barrier I can break down
Don't you see? Our words make us who we are
There's something I want to talk about with you
Just thinking about that gets me all giddy
Whether you're right next to me or not
You always brighten up my day
Of all the things you've spoken to me
I cherish every last word
It feels good to think about somebody
And it feels good to put that into words
treasure
Yeah?
You've got mail.
I do? Who's it from?
I-Is this...?!
It's a treasure map!
Once I reach this big tree,
take three steps to the right...
Then take two steps left...
Make sure to avoid the pitfall...
Keep going straight?!
You don't gotta write down
pointless steps like that!
Who sent this thing to me anyways?
Here I am!
It's... Cony's house?
Cooomiiing...
What's up, Moon?
I see, that makes sense!
What does?
What's going on, dude?
This is the spot.
What spot?
Hold it!!
Oh, hey.
What are you doing here?
What d'ya think?!
This is my house!
Oh, right. Thunk.
Don't "Oh, right. Thunk." me!
What's your problem?!
Don't worry! Just pretend I'm not here!
How am I supposed to ignore someone
digging a hole in the floor of my house?!
Please, you're so fussy.
You're acting weird!
Think nothing of it.
How?!
What'cha got there, Moon?
A shovel!
Not that!
The suspicious piece of paper in your hand!
Oh, uhh, this? It's, well...
Lemme guess. A treasure map?
Nope! Wrongest answer!
"Wrongest?!"
Show me!
I can't!!
Oh, relax! Just show me!
That's the thing I can'test!
It really is a treasure map!
C-Crud...
Wait, it even says the treasure is in my house!
I suppose...
Get digging, I'll help you!
What's with the change of heart?
Think nuthin' of it.
Well, if you insist...
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
There it is!
We've found it at last!
Sure did! And the treasure...
...is all mine!
...is all for me!
Why should you have it?
Well, duh!
We found it with my map!
Are you kidding?!
It was in my floor, therefore it's mine!
I'm not playin' games.
Neither am I!
Alright, Moon.
How 'bout we split it?
Split it?
Since it was hidden so deep underground,
it must be worth a ton, even if we split it 50-50!
Well, maybe so...
Then let's do it, Bossman!
Bossman, huh?
I like the sound of that.
Well, whatever. We can think about the cuts later.
Let's see what's inside!
You got it, Bossman!
Huh?
"Take 259 steps east..."
"then 64 steps west..."
Who would've thought there'd be
another map in there, right, Bossman?
45, 46, 47, 48, 49, 50...
Besides, could you imagine trying to keep track
of all those steps, Bossman?
51, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56...
Not to mention, Bossman...
57, 58...
Stop talking! I'm gonna lose count!
Oh, sorry, Bossman. Just one thing...
What is it?!
I took a pedometer with me,
so there's no need to keep count!
Why didn't you say so?!
My bad, Bossman!
But y'know, a treasure hidden
as intricately as this
might be just as intricate
on the inside too!
Got that right!
Wait, isn't this...
James' house?
I'm coming!
Moon? Cony?
It must be that way!
Let's go!
Where are you guys going?
This's the place, Bossman!
Sure seems so!
What are you doing in my bathroom?!
Oh, hey! What brings you here, James?
I should be asking you that!
What's going on here?
Hey, Bossman?
It says take four steps southwest,
which means something must be behind this wall!
Aight, break it down!
On it!
Now, hold on a minute!
What's the big idea?!
We're smashing your walls! Why?
For what?
There's a treasure behind it!
Wait, Cony!
A treasure, you say? Behind my wall?
Nope. No treasure at all.
Then what is there?
Just somethin' not treasure-like.
You're lying! There is a treasure, isn't there?
Sure is! Now lemme get to smashing already!
For crying out loud!
Hold on. If there's a treasure in my bathroom...
then it must belong to me!
Wh-Wh-What are you talking about?!
I've already called dibs!
Then I can't let you break my walls, can I?
Oh, can it!
What's your house is mine,
and what's my house is mine!
I just wanna find the treasure!
Then we can split it between the three of us!
Again...?
Now, don't worry your itty bitty head.
There's still plenty'a riches, Bossman!
I mean, yeah, there might be...
But it's a pretty big split...
Pleasure doing business with you, Bossman!
Oh, fine.
So, will ya let us break your wall?
Be my guest!
It says, "take 999 more steps southwest."
15, 16, 17...
318, 319, 320, 321...
783, 784, 785...
996... Huh?
Isn't this...
So the treasure was buried here in the park?
997, 998, 999!
Here!
Sorry to interrupt your sleep, Brown,
but could you move over?
Why? Because, umm...
There's a treasure buried beneath you!
Don't tell him that!
Huh? You're too tired?
If you move over, we'll split the treasure with you!
Once you have those riches,
you can have all the salmon you can eat!
Hush, Cony!
What did I say about this?!
I ain't giving Brown any of that treasure.
What's the big deal?
He's just gonna buy a bunch of salmon.
Bossman, we won't have any treasure
if we don't get Brown to move over!
Ughhh, fine.
I got it!
Time to open it up!
What's this drawing of...?
I feel like I've seen it before.
Aah, I know!
Who knew you had a treasure
waiting back at home, Bossman?
It was right under your nose this whole time!
Let's go find that treasure!
Hold it.
Huh?
Good work, everybody.
You can go home now.
What do you mean?
Are you giving up on the hunt?
Why, of course not.
But you're not getting any treasure!
And why's that?
Well, duh!
I found the treasure map,
and the treasure's on my property!
Why should I have to split it with you three?
Because we all found it together!
Couldn't care less.
Really, Moon?
Guess it's time you all went home.
Don't bother, your anger won't work on me. Scram!
You're awful!
You're a monster!
Say whatever you want!
Alright, time to dig!
Should be right about here.
Whatever. We're leaving.
Yeah. You probably won't even find any treasure anyhow.
Found it!
Look what I found!
What is all this?
It's a bunch of trash...
I guess that's karma for trying to hog it to yourself.
No way...
Who buried this stuff anyways?
This is that time capsule we buried together!
Oh, yeah! We buried things that were precious to us!
Which means we buried this treasure!
Dang, I can't believe I buried this trash!
I was so dumb!
Huh?
This brings me back!
What an old picture!
Now that's a treasure!
Guys, go get some treasure from home!
We're gonna bury another capsule!
I'm down!
siblings
Please forgive me, my sister!
Dear brother!
My sister!
My dear brother!
Sibling love is so beautiful!
It's like they're bound together by fate!
I wish I had siblings like that!
I know!
You want to play siblings?
Yeah! Or put simply, imaginary siblings!
How is that simpler?
All of us, siblings?
Let's start with you, Moon!
You're my little brother, a bit rebellious but lovable,
and you love your sister!
Say what?
James, you're my kind older brother
who does absolutely everything that I ask!
I don't follow.
Brown, you're my dad!
You're the head of the family!
You're very strict but caring at heart!
Now we're a perfect family!
Perfect how?
We never agreed to play siblings with you!
No way!
Let's go, guys.
Sure, suit yourself.
I'm sure you don't want the gifts
you would've gotten for going along with it.
Krrk.
A ticket to a premium advance screening
of Katsudon Wars: The Final Battle.
Katsudon Wars?!
A meal ticket for a five-star hotel!
You'd get treated to
a fancy, luxurious dinner, all for free!
A fancy dinner?!
A salmon all-you-can-eat ticket
at a revolving sushi bar!
Woe is me!
Guess I'll have to toss these all away!
Slow down, sis! I can't keep up!
Happy happy Cony, dop dop whoo!
Why are you yelling? You're gonna cause a scene!
You can be a real handful sometimes, y'know?
Back me up here, James!
He's just happy, is all!
After all, our caring sister is more beautiful than ever!
You're such a charmer, big bro!
"It's no wonder a daughter of mine
would be so beautiful," he says!
Oh, stop it!
Alright! Today, I'm gonna spoil you all the best I can!
Huh?
Woohoo!
I was worried you'd ask for something bigger,
but a road trip is A-OK.
This is no road trip,
it's a shopping trip!
Wait, what?
Ooh, I like this one!
Can I get this one, James?
I have to buy it?!
Because if I don't become a beauty,
I might embarrass my fashionable big brother
when we're walking together in town!
I get it.
Happy happy Cony's goin' shopping!
I can't decide!
Which one looks better on me, big bro?
I think you'd look good in both!
Why don't you think it over
then buy it later?
I'll just buy both!
You might've bought a bit too much...
But doesn't it make you happy
to see your sister get even more beautiful?
Wait for me, sis!!
Keep running! You need the exercise!
Looks so good!
This one's for you, big bro!
This one's for you, Dad!
And the rest is for me!
What?!
I'm starving over here!
Hey! A good big brother would resist
so his sister can eat her fill.
Even Dad knows to always put his daughter first!
That's what I call beautiful sibling love—family love, even!
Down it goes!
So good!
I smell good eats!
Can I have some too, sis?
Moon, can you fetch me a juice?
Go do it yourself.
Hah! You heard what I asked, didn't you?
Then chop to it!
On it!!
I'm back!
Here, sis!
It's so warm...
Go fill it with ice.
On it!!
I'm back!
Here, sis!
Nah, never mind on the juice.
Can you get me some ice cream?
What?!
Oh, and some apple pie, some shiratama anmitsu,
and a chocolate crêpe!
My, my. Are you mad at me?
This is real smart coming from someone
who used to cry at me for things.
I even changed your diapers...
And this is how you repay me?
I'm so upset!
Oh, come on!
Dang it!
I'm so hungry...
That was delicious!
I'll have to top it off with that fruit Dad picked!
Oh?
Are you okay, Dad?
Big bro? Moon? Can you treat Dad?
What the heck, guys?
Who knew brothers were so unreliable.
This is so boring...
Oh, I know!
I'm your little sister, Catherine!
And I'm your big sister, Angelina!
Whew, so cute!
I knew having sisters would be a way better experience!
You're so pretty, Angel!
You're a real knockout yourself, Catherine!
But who's the fairest one of all?
You, Cony!
Hehe, I knew it!
I've been keeping a secret from you all...
I made a boyfriend!
Whaaat?!
He's a real nice guy! He even proposed to me!
H-H-He proposed?!
Bring him to us!
What she said! We have to see for ourselves
if he's the right one for you!
Thank you so much!
I'm so glad sisters can have my back
in times like this!
Here he is!
Love is my life
Dreams are what I have
La-la-la-la, dreams are my life
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I am Butler Jessica.
I've always wanted to do this!
You're just so handsome!
This is Catherine and Angelina!
My cute little sister and my beautiful older sister!
Why, this is just lovely!
Truly the sisters of my beloved fiancée!
Feel free to call me your big brother!
Right, big sister?
Oh, silly Butler! It's too early for that!
I don't like him.
Cony's happiness doesn't sit with me either.
Do we break them up?
I say so.
Hey, where's Dad?
He didn't want to see this boyfriend of yours.
I don't approve of this either, Cony.
Neither do I!
B-But why not?
I don't like your tastes!
Return that flashy boyfriend of yours at once!
He's hurting my eyes!
I expect my sisters to say nice things to me!!
We're just thinking of what's best for you!!
Yeah! We just want you to be happy!
Oh, please! You're just jealous of my happiness!
It's all over your faces!
I approve, sis!
So do I!
I think he's a great guy!
Aww, you guys!
You can come out now, Dad.
So that's where you were, Dad!
She's serious about this! Go meet him!
Why won't you accept them?
You don't even know how she feels!
You stubborn old man!!
D-D-Dad?!
Don't do it, Dad!
Huh?
He...
...accepted them?
Dad...
Thank you!
I love you so much, Dad!
Congratulations, Cony!
I knew this day would come!
Yeah...
Take good care of my sister, okay?
What a relief...
Thank you, big brother!
Thank you, little brother!
Having siblings is really great!
I love being in a family!
How about we remember this with a photo?
Let's do it!
Moon, you stand here.
Big bro, you stand here!
Wow, they look just like a family!
They must be very happy.
Hurry up, Dad!
Say cheese!
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
I dreamt I was flying through the night sky
mahou no juutan ni notte
On a magic carpet
tondeku yozora no yume
And I just wanted you to see it
kimi ni mo
kimi ni mo misetakute
misetai
Oh, did I wake you? I'm so sorry
okoshichatta kana? gomen ne
I thought you sounded half-asleep
neboketa kotobatachi ni
And it made me swoon
nandaka
nandaka kyun to kita
kyun kyun
Just like the glittering scent of rose tea
kirameku kaori no roozu tii mitai ni
When my heart starts pounding, I lock up
dokidoki no sono shunkan
tojikomeru
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete
imasugu aitai no
Even though I could just type a <3 and send it to you
yubisaki haato wo nosete
tsutawattara ii no ni
It's hard to sum up the way I feel for you
kimi e no kono kimochi
hitokoto ja tarinai
It's like a millefeuille
egao mo namida mo zenbu
With all of my smiles and tears mixed in
tsumikasaneta mirufiiyu
I feel happy, I feel painful
ureshii setsunai itoshii
I feel longing — I'm in love
koishiteru
diet
early bird
Next time on Line Town...
This is Sally! Yesterday, I ate 30 servings of tonkotsu ramen.
Actually, I lied.
Why would I lie about something like that?
diet
early bird
I don't really know.
In other news,
the next Line Town episode is "Diet!"
Moon becomes a big round ball! And that's no lie.
Be sure to tune in!