A-B-C-D-E-F-G
H-I-J-K-L-M-N-O-P
Q-R-S-T-U-V-W
X-Y and Z
Now you know your ABCs
Isn't it bizarre, the way we string together
letters from A to Z?
Whether it be out loud or by text,
let's find something to talk about!
How will the world end? What's for dinner?
Let's share those moments of laughter and tears
I decide what I like and hate
But that too is a barrier I can break down
Don't you see? Our words make us who we are
There's something I want to talk about with you
Just thinking about that gets me all giddy
Whether you're right next to me or not
You always brighten up my day
Of all the things you've spoken to me
I cherish every last word
It feels good to think about somebody
And it feels good to put that into words
salmmy
Huh? You made that, Brown?
His name is Salmmy, right?
And you love it so much that
you bring it with you wherever you go!
You love it that much?
Oh, yeah!
I got some donuts!
Huh, you want me to hold it
while you're in the bathroom?
This really is well-made!
You're kidding me.
I, uh, well...
I couldn't help but notice how nice this is!
Have some donuts!
Hey, Brown! What would you do if...
...I destroyed Mr. Salmon?
Rawr!
That's awful, Brown! I'm just kiddin' with ya.
Man, that's terrible!
You're kidding me.
Did I fix it...?
Crud!
Coming!
Hey, guys!
I just learned some yoga!
Yoga?
It's great outside!
You guys wanna do some yoga in the open with me?
Ooh! I wanna give it a go!
You guys in too?
Gah! Uh, yeah!
We're in. We're in!
Let's get started!
First is the eagle po... Huh?
Brown, you can't do yoga while holding Salmmy.
Alright, everyone! Do as I do!
This all-purpose super-ultra glue
should be able to stick Mr. Salmon's tail back on!
Eagle pose!
Tip-toe, tip-toe, tip-toe...
Next...
Camel pose!
Now, cobra pose!
And now...
Twisted triangle...
...pose!
Crud!
Finish off with a deep breath...
And done!
That felt amazing!
Hm? Moon, is something wrong?
I think I'll hold this pose a little longer!
You really love yoga that much?
Y-Yeah, yeah!
You can all head on back!
Doesn't your body feel
so refreshed after some yoga?
Yeah! Like I lost weight!
Think... Think, Moon!
That's it!
Didn't Brown say he made that himself?
If Brown can make something like that,
surely I can too, right?
I'll just make a duplicate
and swap it out when he's not looking!
Salmmy, Brown, you two are like peas in a pod!
Mind if I take some pics?
Random question...
Just how did you make Salmmy?
Mhm, I see...
Mhm, mhm, I see...
Mhm.
Climb the mountain to fetch some high-quality mud,
knead it for three days and three nights...
No way.
Hold on!
It's like I always told myself...
I can do anything if I try!
That's still true now!
M-Moon, you okay?
It's movie time.
A movie?
Oh, wow. This thing's 5 hours long.
Sure, it's long,
but it's a cinematic masterpiece that'll have you
laughing, crying, and feeling cozy.
It's a must-watch.
Ooh, really? Cozy sounds nice!
Slowly, slowly...
I can do it if I try!
I can't if I don't!
At least!!
Voilà!
Or not!
Wow, what a fun movie!
Moon, you look beat up. What's wrong?
Just brought me to tears is all.
Well, that was a very touching movie!
Look, a UFO!
Huh? Where?
Where is it? Where?
Heh, just an airplane.
Silly.
Oh, tomorrow's recycling day.
Brown, can you help me bring it out?
There's a lot though, so you'll need to put Salmmy down.
You're a lifesaver!
Lucky me!
I can go back to Plan A:
glue the tail back on!
Salmon roe?!
How much thought did he put into this?
Brown, we're not in a rush to get back...
Crud, what now?
Thanks for the help, Brown!
Salmmy seemed cold,
so I dressed him!
How is it, Salmmy? Feel warm?
"Yeah, very warm!"
"I love this sock!"
No good?
It's no good, is it?
Gotta get it back on somehow...
Oh, are you heading home, Brown?
Can I have my sock back, then?
Hey!
You realize how much you'll startle him
if you just yank the sock off?
Salmmy, time to take the sock off!
"Oh, okay!"
Here!
What's wrong?
It just pains me to have to say goodbye to Salmmy...
Brown, I beg of you!
Can I escort him home?
The stars out are beautiful, Salmmy!
Not to pat myself on the back,
but I'm a world-class swipe-his-tail-back-on-er!
What now?
At this rate...
I'll be stuck...
...sticking Mr. Salmon's tail back on
for the rest of my life.
I can't live with that...
Huh?
You're giving him to me?
As a symbol of our friendship?
Brown, the thing is...
Y-You knew...?
Whut?
You're telling me to be careful
since the tail comes off easily?
You could'a told me that earlier...
party
Huh?
Cony won a ticket to a cruise party from the lottery?
Wow!
It says it's on a luxury liner, too!
Hot dang!
Those parties are always full of fancy rich people!
Hm?
It says she can bring a plus one!
A cruise party on a luxury liner, huh?
A gorgeous ship...
A gorgeous buffet!
And in the middle of it all... gorgeous moi!
Moooi!
It sounds fabulous!
A cruise party, huh?
Yeah!
That'll tickle my fancy!
Then again, a party on a ship like that
might get a bit cold from all the strong winds.
A plus one ticket, eh?
Well, I get a little seasick,
so this kind of party isn't for me.
I hope Cony hasn't already decided who to go with...
Jeez louise, look at the time!
I gotta get back, my show's on!
Later!
Oh, I forgot!
I have a dentist appointment and a piano lesson today!
Busy as a bee!
Hard a-port!
Oh, James?
Hey, Cony!
Fancy seeing you here.
What are you doing?
I'm steering an imaginary cruise ship.
Imaginary?
So one day, I can make
my great great grandfather's wish a reality!
Huh?
What do you mean?
Long ago, when I was still a young lass...
The last thing my great great grandpa said to me...
"I want to see you partying
aboard a luxury cruise ship!"
Alas, getting on a cruise ship
isn't a chance you get every day...
So to make up for that,
I'm steering an imaginary one instead!
I believe that I can fulfill his wish someday!
Hoist the anchors!!
I had no idea!
Say, Cony...
If you ever got onto a cruise ship,
you would bring me along, right?
Absolutely!
Don't let him fool you!
Wh... Moon?
James' great great grandpa is still alive!
Just the other day, you were bragging to us about him
holding down third base in baseball, weren't you?
You mean he's completely fine?
James.
It's not nice to lie.
P-Please, I wasn't lying.
I never particularly said he was dead.
Cony?
Here, for you.
What is it?
The "Detective Katsudon" movie DVD box set?
I'll let you borrow it!
You told me you wanted to watch it, right?
You sure?
Didn't you say you'd never lend it to anyone though,
since the box would get dirty
and covered in fingerprints?
In exchange,
if you ever get to bring someone aboard a cruise ship,
take me with you!
Yeah, sure!
Say, Moon. Don't you have plans this Sunday?
Nope, totally free!
I have my entire schedule cleared,
but I bet you're super busy, James!
I'm super free!
Not only am I free this Sunday,
but I'm still wide open every day after that!
I'm way more free than you!
No, I'm free!
No, I am!
Um, hey, you guys...
What's gotten into you?
Brown?
Huh? They both want to go with me
to that cruise party I won?
What happened to boats being too cold?!
What happened to getting seasick?!
Please stop fighting!
I can't believe you two are fighting over me...
I'm such a sinful girl...
Nobody cares!
Just pick which one of us two gets to go!
You want to go to the party too...?
Alright! Take your pick, Cony!
Who's going with you to the party?
Wh... you can't just spring this on me...
Choose!
Uhh, just... give me some time to think!!
How did things get this bad...?
A party cruise can get really cold,
and I get seasick...
So I thought about giving my ticket to someone else...
And then...
Shine!
What's going on here...?
Brown, you're hilarious!
Aah, I'm getting real hungry...
I could go for a yummy dessert about now.
Juby, juby...!
I made you some pancakes!
Thank you!
Oh, my shoulders are so stiff...
Can someone take care of that, pretty please?
Who should I take with me this Sunday...?
I bet that gorgeous cruise ship party
is gonna be real fun!
Ohh, this feels great.
What's this? My feet are aching too!
I'm pooped...
Hey, you guys!
Are you all free this Sunday?
Huh?
Hmm... Maybe I should decide who to bring soon.
Coming!
Moon!
Excuse me.
He'll do.
So, hey, Moon!
You free this Sunday?
Oh, I'm taking this back.
Ack! It's got your fingerprints all over it!
This is why I don't let you borrow my stuff.
Whuh...?
And unfortunately, I'm busy Sunday.
Huh? I thought you really wanted to
go on that luxury cruise ship?
Sally's throwing a salmon party at her place on Sunday.
A salmon party?
She won one in the lottery!
Say what?!
But wait!
Surely a gorgeous party on a luxury cruise ship
sounds way more exciting, right?
Sorry, but I already told her I'd be there.
See ya.
What's his deal?
Oh, James!
Hey, about this Sunday!
Are you free this Sunday?
Huh?
Non non!
Cony's going to a gorgeous cruise party that day!
Oh, I see...
I was hoping you could come to
the salmon party at my place. Oh, well.
She's missing out! That salmon party is gonna be great!
ALL ABOUT
SALMON!
Brown! So, about this Sunday...
ALL ABOUT
SALMON!
"All About Salmon?"
ALL ABOUT
SALMON!
Ugh, what's the deal?
Fine! I'll just go all by myself!
This orange juice is great!
Oh, I've seen that guy on TV!
A gorgeous buffet, and tons of rich folk...
This party's definitely way more fun than theirs!
Those dummies are missing out!
So cold...
Sally's house is off that way...
They're probably in the middle of that lame salmon party.
Do it again, one more time!
Do that thing with the fresh salmon!
That's awesome, Brown!
Cony would laugh if she saw that!
Let's record it for her!
Oh, yeah! Good idea!
I caught it on the swim here.
Let's dig in!
So good, man!
Cony, how was the cruise party?
It was fun and all,
but next time, let's all go together, okay?
Definitely!
That'll be way more fun!
Yeah!
Gimme some!
Me too!
Aye-aye!
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
I dreamt I was flying through the night sky
On a magic carpet
And I just wanted you to see it
Oh, did I wake you? I'm so sorry
I thought you sounded half-asleep
And it made me swoon
Just like the glittering scent of rose tea
When my heart starts pounding, I lock up
I want to see you once a thousand nights have passed
Even though I could just type a <3 and send it to you
It's hard to sum up the way I feel for you
It's like a millefeuille
With all of my smiles and tears mixed in
I feel happy, I feel painful
I feel longing — I'm in love
smile
crisis
On the next Line Town...
James has gotten very depressed.
His beard is a mess, his room is a mess,
and he's so down,
all he wants to do is mope!
Like they say, it multiples insult by injury!
Wait, I did the math wrong. It adds to it!
Will we be able
to bring James' smile back?!