a i u e o ka ki ku ke ko
sa shi su se so ta chi tsu te to  na ni nu ne no
ha hi hu he ho ma mi mu me mo  ya yu yo
ra ri ru re ro  wa wo n
Then there's the dots and circles
ato ten to maru desu
It's a mystery wrapped in an enigma, putting together letters from A to Z
maka fushigi de  ara fushigi ne  "a" kara "n" kumi awase
What will we use our mouths and words to talk about today?
kuchi ni shitari  moji ni shitari  kyou wa nani wo hanasou
We can talk about how the world ends or just the plans for dinner today
sekai no hate  okiru koto mo  kyou no gohan no koto mo
If it means the chance to laugh or cry with you, I'll talk about anything
kimi to warai  toki ni naite  wakachi au tame hanasou
When I've shown I like this or I hate that
are suki de  kore kirai  kimeta no wa
It's just my opinion, so you can forget all about it
jibun jishin dakara  sore mo uchi kowashi teikeru darou
You see, the things we say make us unique, after all
hora ne  yappa kotoba ga bokura wo tsutsunderu
I've got something I want to talk about with you
kimi to hanashitai koto ga aru
I can't help but get all jittery thinking about it
sore wo omou to wakuwaku suru yo
So whether you're right next door or you live far away
kimi to chikaku ni itemo inakutemo
I'll always have the most wonderful days
sonna suteki na hibi desu
You've said a whole lot of things to me
kimi kara moratta kotoba no kazu
And I cherish every last word I hear
doremo taisetsu na takaramono
It feels good to think about someone else
dareka wo omou tte ii kanji
It feels good to put my thoughts into words
kotoba ni suru tte ii kanji
Cony's always very cheerful and stylish.
Her favorite thing to do is to diet.
Cony
Moon
Moon's moody but very lovable. His favorite satellite is the moon.
Brown is pure, quiet, and expressionless.
He gets really scary when he flips his lid.
Brown
James' favorite thing is his beautiful self,
and his least favorite thing is his ugly self.
James
Sally is a chick who loves karaoke.
She has a knack for nostalgic tunes.
Sally
Jessica is Cony's serious and beautiful best friend. Her favorite thing is to clean.
Jessica
These wonderful friends live in a town called...
LINE Town!
birthday
Oh- "Happy Birthday..."
Today is Brown's birthday!
So I'm gonna make his favorite salmon pie!
To have such a wonderful surprise like this up my sleeve...
I'm nothing short of a genius!
Moon, you doing good out there?
Yep, just a little more to go!
Brown's gonna love this!
[Cony humming]
I'm so happy they all remembered my birthday was today!
It's Jessica!
What's up?
Cony, do you want to go to the birthday party with me?
Sorry, I can't, I'm already on my way there.
Darn.
You guys are the greatest friends I could ever ask for, though!
I'm just so, so happy you're all throwing me a birthday party!
- Wait, for you? No, today's...
Well, see ya later! I'm psyched to see what you're getting me!
Cony? Cony?!
Oh...she hung up.
Dear, what do I do...today's Brown's birthday party!
Knock-knock, hello? Good ol' Cony has arrived!
Huh?
How dare they leave the guest of honor waiting? Have they no shame?
Oh, there you are, Moon! Whatcha doin'?
Can't you see? I'm putting up decorations!
- What about James?
- He's makin' a pie.
Aww, thank you!
Just what's making you all sappy?
What can I say, I'm happy!
Whatever. Decorations aren't gonna put themselves up!
I have to help too...?
What, not in the mood to help?
- Hurry up, Brown's gonna be here soon.
- But I...
Ahh, he's already here!
Happy birthday!
Thank you!
Come on in, you're the guest of honor!
You're making me blush.
Cony, I don't need you to interpret Brown for me just 'cuz he doesn't talk.
So, Brown, do you wanna help me put up decorations?
Why are you asking Brown to help you, ya numbskull?
Am I...not supposed to?
Oh, that's right! I won't have much time later, so is it alright if I give you your present now?
Oh, really? Thank you, of course!
This one's from me and James!
I'm so happy!
Happy birthday!
Whaaaaat?!
Why did he give Brown the present instead of me?!
Maybe this is just...
...a surprise!
Yeah, Brown's gonna collect all the presents, then wait for the perfect time and give them all to me!
Moon, you scamp!
Cony?
Hehe, I didn't see anything, I didn't hear anything!
Cony, where's your present?
What does the word "present" even mean?
I get it, you forgot to bring one so you're just playing dumb!
No idea what you mean!
Cony!!
You done yet?
Ugh, you're such a pain in the neck.
Whatever, just go help James make the pie.
Okay!
What's with her?
Oh, right! Sorry, Brown, mind lending a hand?
Hup-two...
Moon, did Cony get here?
Yeah, she's here. Not only did she forget her present but she's acting all high and mighty.
Oh, dear!
[Moon] Whaaaat?!
You're telling me Cony thinks this whole party is for her instead?!
That's right...I didn't even remember today was also Cony's birthday!
Augh...I had no idea...
Well, uh, I better go clear things up with Cony...
You mustn't! You do realize how she'll react, right?
No matter what, we can't let her find out we forgot.
Don't let her find out...?
So where's Cony right now?
I think...she's helping James make the pie.
- Pie?
- Yeah.
He's making this big salmon pie with "Happy Birthday Brown" written on it as a surprise.
Ack, didn't mean to spill that to Brown!
We can't let Cony see it!
Wow! Cony, the pie's ready! Wanna help bring it out to the party?
Sure thing!
- Cony, hold that side!
- Aye-aye!
Nooooo!!
Cony, as the guest of honor, you should be taking it easy!
But Moon told me to help out around here...
I never said anything like that!
But you said earlier...
...Jessica?
W-w-what's the m-matter?
- Isn't that...a bit hot?
- Huh?
Ow-ow-ow-ow-ow-ow-ow-ow!!
- Good job, Brown!
- Wait a minute...!
Whaaat, why'd you eat the whole thing?!
Brown must've been starving, hahaha!
Did you like it?
You think so? It was made for you with love!
- Made for Brown?
- Nothing, nothing at all!
Well, what do you guys say we start the party?
Mhm. Okay. I'll go set up the party grounds then.
Good, good, well then...AACK!
- You can't!
- Wha?
Where do you think you're going?
I said I'd set up the party grounds...
- You must not pass this point!
- Why not...?
If you wish to pass...
...You must get through Brown first!
Brown, don't let us down!
We're counting on you!
Uhh, what do we do about this?!
We just have to write Cony's name over it!
I'm on it!
I defeated him!
- Already?!
- That was fast...
Once I got serious about it, it was easy as pie!
What a wonderful sign! I just love it!
I was starting to think otherwise, but now I know this really is my birthday party!
What else would it be?
Hm? "Happy Birthday Brown!"?
Cony, we can explain...
How could yooooou?!
Happy bir--
...thday.
Cony, we're sorry.
The truth is, none of us actually knew your birthday was today.
I'm so sorry, Cony...
It's fine...don't worry about it.
If I'm being honest...I didn't know it was Brown's birthday either.
I wasn't any better.
I'm sorry, Brown...
Wasn't this present for you, Brown?
You don't mind?
Thank you so much!
We shouldn't let this dampen such a happy day.
Let's make this party even better by throwing it for the both of you!
Alright then, let's get the party train rolling again!
Yeah!
pit
[Cony humming]
It's so clear and fresh out today!
[Squish]
[Shrieks]
There's d-dog...
p-p-...
...all over my foot!!
[Sobbing]
[Sighs]
So much for clear and fresh...
[Moon laughing]
Moon?
[Cackling]
You saw that?!
Yup, savored the memory too.
Heheh, I'm sending this to everyone.
Y'all look at this, Cony stepped in dog...
Stop right there, you!!
Hey, what are you doi--OW-ow-ow-ow-ow!!
[Giggling]
Evidence, begone!
Noooo!
What was that for?!
You were being such a jerk!
What?!
It's what you get for mocking my misfortune!
But that was my phone...
Why, that Cony... the nerve of her...
Where's my phone...?
[Moon yelps]
Oh- there it is!
Ow-ow-ow...haah...
Where am I now...? Huh?
My goodness...
I can't believe there's a pit like this out here...
Hahaah, I'm such an idiot! I fell into a pit and now I'm stuck here!
Not the smartest decision...
Ahahahahaha!
For real?!
Heeeelp! Heeeelp!!
Anyone out there? Help meee!
Hellooo?!
A-a-a-ahh...I give up, this isn't funny anymore...
Hahaha. In times like this, there's always the blessings of society.
I'll just call for help in the group chat.
What a disaster. Stepping in dog... [munch]
...is bad enough, but then Moon of all people had to see it. It just gets worse and worse.
I'm such a failure.
[Phone notification]
What does that jerk want, SOS-ing me?
[Moon] Ooh, someone already sent back!
Darn, it's just Cony...
Tch. I wasn't asking you anyways.
I'm booored...
Hmm, well since I'm stuck here, I should take some pictures.
I can't take pictures in here...
I suppose I could do some exercises...
1...2...3...4...5...
[Laughing] Oh, you!
94...95...96...
Aww, man. And I was so close to 100...
...Wait, what do I think I'm doing?!
Why hasn't anyone responded yet?!
How 'bout I try calling...uhh, James...
♪ Jubi-juri... ♪ Huh?
[Phone ringing]
[Screaming]
I...can't...let...people...see!
My crawling...body...grab it!!
He didn't pick up...
Oh, right! I'll try Brown!
[Ringing tone]
No answer!
No, no, no, no, no...
I could never turn to that ungrateful Cony.
[Laughing] Oh, you!
[Quivering]
I have no choice...
[Video game sounds]
[Cony grunting]
[Phone ringing]
- Huh?
[Game over sound]
- Aaaagh!!
Moon?
What is it?
[Moon] Umm... uh, Cony?
What, you wanna apologize?
Huh? You should be the one apologizing! This whole mess is your fault!
Shut up!
Hello? Hellooo?!
Gah!
Darn it. As if anyone would ever apologize to you!
[Stomach grumbling]
I'm so hungry...
There's no use! I gotta be mature about this!
[Phone ringing]
I'm a lil' busy here, what's up?
[Moon] Please hear me out. I'm in a bit of a pickle right now.
A really big pickle if you ask me.
[Cony] Sounds like you got yourself tied up. You really had it coming, hahahaha!
I'm sorry for what I did, Cony.
Now get over here and help me.
Hello? You there?
Whut?
Eh?
Of all times...?
What was all that about...?
[Game over sound]
- Huh?
- Thanks a lot, Moon!
What do I do now...?
[Moon screams]
This is bad, this is bad, this is real bad! This is bad, this is bad, this is real bad! I'm in deep dirt!!
I'll have to rely on my own strength to get out of here.
[Moon roars]
[Panting]
[Yelps]
[Laughing]
[Moon] More like a big pickle if you ask me.
[Cony] Sounds like you got yourself tied up. You really had it coming, hahahaha!
[Cony sighs]
If I'm stuck here much longer, I may as well be...
[Coughs]
[Laughing]
[Choking up]
Goodbye, world...
[Cries]
Uh...huh?
[Exclaims]
[Screaming]
Huh?
B-Brown?!
How...?
[Moon stutters]
[Moon muttering]
I'm free...
Brown...?
Th-Thank you!
Why is this pit here anyhow...?
Whatevs. As long as I'm not in there.
Hm?
Cony!
Moon? What are you doing out here?
That's, uh, a bit of a long story...speaking of which.
What brings you out here, Cony?
Wait, don't tell me you were looking for me?
Uhh, for you? No, I...
I was just taking a walk.
In the middle of the night?
Because...
See, the moon's very pretty.
[Moon] It sure is.
When I see the full moon though...I can't help but think of your face and gag.
[Laughing]
- What's got you in a riot?
I feel like I can laugh about anything right now!
[Moon laughing]
What a nut.
[Both laughing]
I hope I can see you again once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete  imasugu  aitai no
I dreamt that I soared through the night sky on a magic carpet
mahou no juutan ni notte  tondeku yozora no yume
And I wanted you to see it too
kimi ni mo  misetakute
(kimi ni mo)
(I wanted you)
(misetai)
(See it too)
Did I just wake you? I'm very sorry. You sounded half-asleep
okoshichatta kana?  gomen ne  neboketa kotoba tachi ni
And it made my heart clench up a bit
nandaka  kyun to kita
(nandaka)
(It made my heart)
(kyun kyun)
(Clench, clench)
Sort of like a rose tea with a glittering aroma
kirameku kaori no  roozu tii mitai ni
The moment my heart starts pounding, I lock up
dokidoki no sono shunkan  tojikomeru
I hope I can see you again once a thousand nights have passed
sen no yoru wo koete  imasugu  aitai no
There I hope you will hold out your <3 and send it to me
yubisaki  haato wo nosete  tsutawattara ii no ni
The way I feel for you, I can't describe it so briefly
kimi-e no kono kimochi  hitokoto ja tarinai
It's like a mille-feuille made from all of my smiles and tears
egao mo  namida mo  zenbu  tsumikasaneta  mirufiiyu
It feels happy, it feels painful, it feels sweet - I'm in love
ureshii  setsunai  itoshii  koishiteru
party
mr. salmon
[Sally] Next time on LINE Town...
Moon gets in trouble when he breaks Brown's adored Mr. Salmon!
Somehow, without letting Brown found out, he must fix it - at all costs!
...What is "Mr. Salmon" anyway?