Hey, stop, Ricochet!
E-Excuse me...
Hahaha, she's so friendly.
What's her name?
It's Ricochet.
So what are you seeking consultation for?
Well...
My dog...
keeps spinning.
We ran after our adjacent shadows
I'll always be with you
Just how much light can you bring me
Like that which shines through the trees into my dark room
My soul was covered in sand, and you were a raincloud in the desert
That was when we first met
I forgot all about your mischievous smile
I just love you so much with every passing moment
Every path takes us back to our first encounter
I've always loved you, as childish as it sounds
I'll always be with you
Let's walk to the ends of the earth
Spinning Dog
She keeps spinning?
Whenever any vehicle on
the road passes by on a walk,
she suddenly starts spinning
around in place trying to go after it.
I worry she could get run over
if I don't stop her somehow...
I see now.
Is she acting up otherwise?
Not as far as I'm concerned.
Now, how do I stop her...
Okay, okay, slow down! I hear ya!
Ricochet! Knock it o—
Huh?
I-I'm terribly sorry...
Oh, d-don't worry about it!
She's too cute.
Feel free to sit back down.
M-M-My apologies.
How long of a walk
does she get every day?
About half an hour...
15 minutes in the morning, 15 at dusk.
That's not enough.
She needs at least double that amount.
Will walking her for longer
stop her from spinning?
Yes, as long as it's done properly.
But I work during the day.
I can only walk her for so long.
Um, do you have any family members?
I live with my husband
and teenage daughter.
Then if you all take turns walking her,
you can triple the amount she's getting!
If only that was a possibility...
Do your other family members
not like Ricochet-chan?
No, I wouldn't necessarily say that...
They've gotten burnt and turned red
from her saliva.
Don't let her lick her paws.
It's not good conduct.
I'm sorry... I usually tell her off...
This goes beyond just spinning.
What?
Next time, please bring your family
along for a counseling session.
Then we'll continue.
Reservations are always open.
Um, we have a hard time
lining up our schedules, though...
Then make them line up.
We'll see you again this Sunday at 10 A.M.!
Okay...
Goodbye, Ricochet-chan!
Excuse me...
I really think it'd be best
for me to come alone.
Can you still fit her in for a session?
I'm free right now.
Not without the rest
of the family being there.
In exchange, how about I send in an assistant?
Samura.
Go with her and try to persuade the family.
Huh, me?!
If she starts spinning on the way home,
get it on video.
Then...
Sorry for all the trouble.
It's fine.
Though I have a bad feeling about this...
Umm, do you want me to walk her?
I'm not much better at handing a leash,
but I'm stronger, at least...
That's quite alright.
R-Rico!
She's staring...
Don't!
Stop it, Ricochet!!
So that's how she spins?
This is really bad...
She could get seriously hurt.
I'm home.
S-Sorry to intrude.
Come in.
Do you not wipe her paws?
No, but this house is filthy anyways.
Here, use these.
Oh, thank you.
Okay, I get it, Rico!
You're gonna make me spill my tea!
Oh, do you want my snack?
I just can't say no to you!
Just don't tell mommy, okay?
Darling! You know I told you
not to give her any human food!
Oh, cut me some slack.
A little bit ain't gonna kill her!
I'm starting to see...
That doesn't matter,
you can't give her any!
Alright. Well, as they say,
many a little makes a prickle.
Mommy's so sensitive.
Would you shut up?
Isn't it just awful, Rico~?
I think I can see now why Miyake-san
didn't want to bring her family with her.
You made me send a message
to the wrong group chat!
Huh?
And who are you?
Shit, I forgot to greet them!
Sorry to interrupt. I'm Samura
from Proud Dog's Dog Training.
No way, you're the trainer?
I didn't think you'd be so young!
I'm still more of an errand boy if anything.
The trainer asked me to come over with a favor.
Would you all be open to doing
a session together next Sunday?
Please. She doesn't need any sort of training.
Dogs are meant to be a bit rowdy!
That's what makes them cute.
Ain't that right, Rico?
Can't. I'm hanging out with
my friends over the weekend.
Besides, she sleeps with me at night,
and I'm very nice to her.
You should at least consider taking her on walks.
The missus can handle that by herself.
Oh, right. Y'think Rico might be
gettin' hungry about now?
Why don't you...
I'm doing it!!
Would it kill you to feed her yourself sometimes?!
Yikes, so scary! You shouldn't act up in front of a guest.
You have plenty of time to handle it yourself.
I'm getting a really bad feeling about this!!
Dinner's ready, Ricochet!
Can they at least get her to sit?
Did she just drop it for her...?
Y'know, you're pretty handsome, Samura-kun.
Huh?
What's your name?
How old are you?
Are you single?
My name's Kanon!
Can I have your number?
If the family doesn't cooperate,
then convince them by any means necessary.
Sure thing.
You will?
On one condition...
I need you to do something for me.
Miyu-kun!
Kanon-chan!
I got what you asked for.
It's just stuff we shot inside the house, though.
That'll do just fine.
Thank you! Later.
Wait, you're leaving already?!
Lame...
I'm on the clock.
Do you want Ricochet to be happy?
Why wouldn't I? She's family.
Anyways, can we have tea again sometime?
If you go with your mom to training!
She considers her family...
Aww, I don't wanna...
Niwa-san might just be able to help!
I'll start the playback.
Darling, get Ricochet off the couch!
She'll shed all over it!
Aw, come on.
We can just clean her fur off later.
Sit! Sit down!
You don't get a treat if you don't sit!
Just forget about it, okay?
Rico, come here!
Be quiet, Ricochet!
Shut up, Ricochet!
She gets mad at everything, Rico!
She's so scary... It's okay!
Kanon, stop scattering around your slippers!
Yikes...
When you take them off, line them up!
Here's the slippers Mom lined up.
Rico, stop!
Mom will snap at you again!
I said stop! Give it back!
So they're always like this?
Yeah.
Only Mrs. Miyake seems to get angry all the time.
Oh, and this...
Is that...?
Mhm. It's clearly a stress-related behavior.
Stress...
Mom says no to this.
Dad says "it's fine."
The girl sees her getting scolded
and comforts her.
The family's instructions are all over the place,
leaving her in a state of anxiety and confusion.
And since they don't walk her much,
she doesn't get enough exercise.
Border Collies, and other sheepdogs,
need far more exercise than other breeds,
and have a higher tendency
to run after moving objects.
Barking and spinning
in reaction to vehicles
is a common stress-related
behavior in sheepdogs.
And there's one more thing.
The mother is afraid of her.
Huh?
I-I noticed that too!!
I wasn't sure why,
but something felt off...
Even though she's so worried about her
shedding on the couch and chewing up the slippers,
she didn't wipe her feet
when they entered the house,
and at dinner time,
she dropped her food bowl on the ground.
Shinichiro...
This is bad...
We have to intervene
or it could get much worse.
Miyake Kanon
It's their daughter.
Kanon-chan, what's the—Huh?
Miyu-kun, Rico just...
Ricochet...bit your mother...?
Miyake-san!
Miyu-kun!
Rico bit Mom's hand...
That's a lotta blood...
Are you alright?!
She was barking at a motorcycle that passed by
and Mom threw this at her!
So Rico acted out...
Why would you have something like this?
I read about a form of scolding called
"divine punishment" in a book...
where if you threw something loud nearby,
it would startle them into being quiet...
I didn't mean to hit her directly,
I just missed my aim...
No way, you did it on purpose
because you were mad!
I didn't, I swear! I was just trying...
Don't yell so loudly. It'll set off the dog.
Ricochet isn't going to calm down
while you're here.
Go to the hospital now.
Huh...?
Samura.
On it.
There's a cab waiting outside.
Let's go.
But I...
Let's leave Niwa-san to handle this, okay?
Alright...
Don't touch her.
She might bite you too!
Stay back.
He turned his back to her...
Will he be alright...?
Come with me.
Everything's okay.
That's a good girl.
Amazing...
When Miyake-san and I
got back from the hospital,
Ricochet had calmed down
in a crate we bought from the store.
She received five stitches,
but despite the blood loss,
the wound was shallow.
She wasn't like this before...
She was. You just didn't notice.
Huh?
This isn't the first time this has happened.
Ricochet has bitten you several times before,
hasn't she, Miyake-san?
Huh?
Wh-What do you mean?
You know what I mean.
During our counseling session...
when Ricochet quickly turned around,
Miyake-san got panicked,
stood up and raised her hands.
That's the behavior of someone
who either got bit
or nearly got bit by a dog.
She didn't wipe her feet,
and she dropped her food bowl on the ground...
The things you told me earlier
convinced me all the same.
Those are all situations
where the dog could easily bite her.
I-Is that true? This whole time?
You should've spoken up about that!
Why did you hide it from us?!
How could I tell you...?
Being bitten by my own dog
is just too shameful!
Ricochet's been a rowdy girl
ever since she was a puppy.
Besides, all the two of you ever do
is dote on her.
You never help train her
or look after her!
So I started picking up books
and trying every training method in them.
When one day...
I try so hard to discipline her,
but she's only gotten worse...
Learning from books isn't a bad idea.
But even though she repeats the same actions,
sometimes you ignore her,
or throw things at her,
and the other family members
praise her for it,
which makes the dog confused
on if what she's doing is right or not.
Ricochet's problematic behavior
is thanks to stress from that confusion.
She's not really sure what to do anymore.
She's not getting enough exercise either.
As a sheepdog, she needs a lot of exercise
to relieve stress.
Only walking her for 30 minutes a day
built up her stress over time.
She's sensitive, so she tends to show
signs of aggression when threatened.
If you want her to grow healthily,
you need to put in a lot of effort.
But I read that Border Collies
had high training potential.
Shouldn't that make them
easier to train...?
A supreme dog can't do everything
if you don't teach it anything.
The same is true for Labrador Retrievers,
which are used as guide dogs,
and German Shepherds,
which are used as police dogs.
They're specialized in training,
but if you don't teach them properly,
they tend to grow up to be violent
beyond control.
They're also very intelligent,
so they cannot reset
soured relationships with humans.
In many cases, people simply have to leave them.
Leave...
Rico?
I know someone who runs a ranch.
There, she can operate the way
a sheepdog is meant to,
and she'd certainly be happier
than she is here.
But it's your choice.
Our choice, huh?
No... Please no. I refuse.
I don't want to lose her...
She's family.
She's my little sister...
I won't make Mom do all the work anymore...
I'll walk you and train you the best I can.
So please don't give her away...
I want... to stay with Rico...
Kanon-chan.
She's right.
I'm really sorry for forcing you
to take care of her, honey.
Her husband too...
Sensei, we'd like to stay with Rico.
We want everyone in the family
to be happy.
Please teach us the best you can.
And so, the entire Miyake family
began training together.
They took turns walking her,
tripling her exercise.
Niwa-san trained them on
holding a leash, walking a dog,
Hook the loop on your thumb.
and giving proper instruction.
Relax your shoulders.
Okay!!
Watching the family come together
for the sake of their dog
with resolve and kindness
was heartwarming.
The family built a uniform attitude towards the dog,
used the same commands...
You're doing great, Dad!
And after a month, Ricochet's behavior
had improved massively.
Though Mrs. Miyake's still acting a bit uneasy...
She's traumatized,
so it's naturally harder for her.
She still has to conquer her internal fear
that the dog might bite her again.
Miyake-san, don't back out.
O-Okay!
Stand up straight.
Okay!
Straighter!
Okay!!
You've got this!!
More dignity, even if you have to fake it!
You used to play the violin, right?
I'm sorry?
From the photos and sheet music in your house.
Ricochet's the name of
a violin-playing technique, right?
Oh my, you know about that, Niwa-sensei?
I used to do a very good staccato
bow bounce when I was still playing!
That's why I named her that!
Isn't it just adorable?
Then I want you to treat the dog and leash
like a violin and bow.
You are a violinist who's about to step out
onto a packed stage.
You stride onto the stage, chest puffed out,
your precious violin in hand.
Now walk just like that.
I am a violinist.
Ricochet is my violin.
The audience is waiting
to hear my Ricochet.
It's time to take the stage!
Mom!
She did it!
Niwa-saaan!
How did you do that?
You made her practically transform!
What magic spell was that?
Where there's a will,
there's a way.
Now get off me.
I'm heading back.
You go confirm their next appointment.
Get back here!
You're not leaving
until you praise Mrs. Miyake!
You're crazy.
Any owner would put in effort
for their dog.
People and dogs are one in the same!
Neither can go on
if you don't encourage them!
Niwa-san, owners need praise
to make their dogs happy too!
To make their dogs happy...
Sensei?
Am I slouching again...?
Oh, uhh, no.
You...
Yes?
Y-You did... very well... today.
Th-That's all. Take care.
If people change, dogs will too.
And when dogs change, people do too.
Being a dog trainer really is amazing.
Today, we're at a disc dog tournament.
After their adventures in training,
Miyu-kun!
You're late! Gimme my beer!
Miyake-san and Ricochet
began playing disc dog.
Sorry, I had trouble finding a store.
Where's Ricochet and Miyake-san?
Over there in the beginner's area.
The third throw!
It skewed off-course again!
As they're just starting out,
the two of them aren't doing too hot.
You've got this, Rico!
Go for it!
Ricochet falls over yet again.
Sorry, Rico!
Rico, come back here!
Uh-oh, and she comes back,
but without the disc!
You're supposed to bring the disc back, silly!
And that's just fine.
Even if they stink,
they're having fun.
And the whole family is smiling.
Let's head back, Ourson, Singe.
What?! Come on, let's stay longer!
I'm taking the car.
Ey! You want us to walk home just 'cuz
you hate beer and crowds?
Hey, long time no see.
Looks like you're doin' well.
Right, Shin?
Didn't we take your shop's car here, Izumi-san?
Damn right! He has some nerve acting like that
when he can't even afford one for his own store.
Now, you listen here, Shinichi—
Oh, hey, Ritsu!
Let's get out of here, Shinichiro.
You too, Miyu-kun!
What's going on?
Do you know that guy?
No, he's got us mixed up.
W-Wait, slow down!
A mix-up?
He's strange.
Giving a name to chance
Or giving love to fate
If I'm being honest
It's all the same either way
The things that you love
Are what make me happy
It's hilarious
Just how simple I am
Your heartbeat, stuck in my head
It brings back memories
To when we rushed home, laughing along the way
I hate being alone
It makes the night feel so slow
So come on, fall for me already
Sugarspot
You make my days even sweeter
With brown freckles just like your spots
I can get through a scratch or a rough patch
Just like that, the day's over
And in the deepest depths of my heart
Somewhere I feel lonely
Or maybe I miss you
Or a mix of both?
I don't know
Next Time:
Farewell Ceremony