Well look at what we have here!
Is a certain someone finally working
their way back into society?
Nosuke-sensei!
Chill out, Singe.
You got time to kill or something?
Was just making a house call in the area, s'all.
I'm glad to see this little guy's doing well!
Guess that memory isn't all
too distant for you, huh?
Oh! Are you perhaps Sin-chan's vet?
That's correct!
I'm Kubo Suzunosuke from Nosuke Clinic!
Thanks for coming, Nosuke-sensei,
though this may not be a good time.
After this, we have a counseling session
with a new client scheduled.
Very intriguing!
Perhaps I should peek in on Shinichiro's job.
Whatever floats your boat.
We ran after our adjacent shadows
I'll always be with you
Just how much light can you bring me
Like that which shines through the trees into my dark room
My soul was covered in sand, and you were a raincloud in the desert
That was when we first met
I forgot all about your mischievous smile
I just love you so much with every passing moment
Every path takes us back to our first encounter
I've always loved you, as childish as it sounds
I'll always be with you
Let's walk to the ends of the earth
Farewell Ceremony
Little by little, Proud Dog continued
to get more customers.
As for the customer seeking guidance today...
My dog can't stay home alone,
and it's worrying.
I read online that it might be
something called "separation anxiety..."
Is there any way I can help her...?
First, can you put her on the floor
while holding her leash?
O-Okay...
Down, Coco.
No, you have to sit down.
Coco...
I'm sorry. Can I keep her like this?
She's very spoiled...
Hey, Niwa-san.
What's separation anxiety?
Must I have to explain everything for you?
Here, Miyu-kun! I'll tell you!
Separation anxiety makes a dog
anxious when they're apart from their owner.
It goes beyond just being spoiled
or easily getting lonely,
and can lead to many problematic behaviors
that inflict stress on a dog's mind and body.
Huh? That sounds serious...
I've never heard about it before.
There are four main symptoms
of separation anxiety.
YAP YAP YAP
No. 1: Excessive barking.
They'll bark very loudly when
they can't see their owner.
YAP YAP YAP
No. 2: Destructive behavior.
They'll destroy everything in the house—
from the walls to the pillars to the furniture.
No. 3: Accidental excretion.
No matter how potty-trained they are,
they'll go everywhere else instead.
No. 4: Self-harm.
They'll hurt themselves in anxious fits,
and lick and bite their tails and paws
until they bleed.
If it gets worse, it could lead to symptoms
similar to those of human anxiety disorders,
such as diarrhea, lack of appetite,
and fainting from panic attacks.
You may need supplements or medication
to relieve their anxiety.
Ask your vet for more info!
Thank you, Nosuke-sensei!
You're a legend!
Aw, man. I got called in.
Just when it was getting good.
See you again.
It was "getting good...?"
Separation anxiety, huh?
Come to think of it, she's been clinging to her owner
since the moment she walked in.
Go get her name and make her chart.
It's one of the few jobs you have.
Oh, right!
Hey, rude!
Excuse me, what's her name?
Abe...
Abe-san? What kanji?
Oh, sorry, it's Kozuka.
She's Kozuka Coco, a miniature dachshund.
Female, five years old.
I got into a divorce lately,
so I had to move with Coco two weeks ago.
I found a job nearby and managed
to start working last week,
but as soon as I left the house,
she made this loud, heartbroken bay
I've never heard from her before...
It made me worried,
so I went home for a bit during my lunch break...
Coco?!
Coco!!
Was it that hard for you?!
If only I hadn't gotten divorced...
I'm so sorry!
She barked at me again
when I left to go back to work,
as well as in the evening
when I got back home.
And her voice was so hoarse,
I felt awful...
Did she manage staying alone
before the divorce?
Well...
Thank you.
I was a stay-at-home wife, and she would
come with us when we both went out.
So she's never been left home alone before.
But I can't live a stable life now
if I don't work.
So while it hurts to leave her alone,
I need to get her to manage it.
Always all about how it "hurts."
Can she be trained to
handle being home by herself...?
I'd like to witness how she's reacting currently.
We'll lend you a pet camera
and have you set it up in your place.
The thing is...
I can't do that... I felt so bad for her,
I ended up quitting my job.
So there's no reason for her
to be alone right now.
Huh...?
Then find a reason for her to
have to stay home alone.
I'm not sure about that...
I'd feel terrible if she lost her voice again
or got sick from the constant barking...
Then leave.
Huh?
Hey, Niwa-sa—
In the unlikely event
your dog has pathological separation anxiety,
you will need to work
together with a veterinarian.
I cannot give accurate instructions
based on biased stories alone.
It's not my problem your dog can't stay home alone.
Go find someone else.
Th-That's so ru...
You're being very rude, Niwa-san!!
She came to you for guidance!
You can't just turn her away!
What? You gotta be...
Even if her anxiety is pathological,
we have Nosuke-sensei to help out,
so would you just relax?
Besides, if you turn her down,
what'll become of your debt to Izumi-san...?
Apologies for that.
He can be somewhat...
well, generally ill-tempered.
But I can assure you he's a skilled trainer!
Oh, if you're not good at setting
up cameras and such, I can come with you!
I-If it's not too much trouble,
would you like to go out somewhere
while we record your dog?
L-Like on a shopping trip
in the afternoon, perhaps!
How do you feel, Coco-chan?
Haha, really?
Y-You don't mind doing that for me?
Of course not!
You're down too, right, Niwa-san?
Just get going already.
You've got it!
I think here should do.
I'll try to connect it to the shop.
Niwa-saaan, can you see me?
Hi-hooo!
Looks like it's all good to go!
Let's head on out.
Coco gets worked up
when she stands up.
She clings to Kozuka-san's legs
and starts sniffling.
Sorry, Coco. You can't come with me.
Be a good girl, okay?
I'll be home soon.
Mommy doesn't want to go either,
so please listen to me.
I'm doing this for you.
You understand, right?
Kozuka-san's farewell ceremony
lasted 3 minutes with her shoes on.
Oh, I left something back at home.
Can I go fetch it?
Sure. I'll wait here.
One second.
She wouldn't come back for another 20 minutes.
Then at the supermarket,
Kozuka-san was spacing out for the entire time.
I'm sorry, I need the restroom.
Oh, okay. I'll be here.
...Or so she said.
Samura
Niwa-saaan! Kozuka-san still hasn't
come back from the bathroom!
Pipe down!
She left the shop earlier.
Huh? Where'd she go?
Straight back home.
Damn it!!
That confirms it.
Go get her and come back here at once.
O-Okay!
I can now verify based on her behavior at home—
it's very much separation anxiety.
I knew it...
So can you train her...
You're the one who needs training.
Huh?
She's not the only one with separation anxiety.
Her owner does—you do.
I need something from you
before you start treating her.
From... me?
B-But Niwa-san,
Coco really does bark when she leaves!
Of course Coco's anxious.
What else would you expect?
For one thing, her owners were overprotective,
so she didn't get to stay home alone until age 5.
For another, thanks to her owners' divorce,
there's less family members,
resulting in a change in environment.
And lastly, she's in a different home too.
You couldn't ask her not to be anxious.
Moving may be completely normal for humans,
but for a dog, it feels like being brought
into a strange house.
Until she gets used to it,
she won't recognize it as her own home.
So making her stay by herself makes her feel
like she's being left behind somewhere strange.
But the major issue here is that her owner's actions
are only heightening her anxiety.
Huh?!
You performed two actions characteristic
of anxious pet owners.
And I imagine you do them on a daily basis.
First, the "leaving ceremony."
I'm so sorry...
I don't want to leave you here,
but I can't take you with me!
Please be a good girl
until I get back at 8:00, okay?
Don't bark while I'm gone, please!
Dogs cannot understand what we're saying,
so if their owner is acting anxious or unnatural,
it only serves to make them more anxious.
Trying to level with your dog
is counterproductive to getting her to behave.
You also keep getting worried
and going home to check on her.
Don't bark, you're making me worried!
When you come home early,
it can give her the idea that
her barking made you come back.
Once you leave, she gets restless,
hoping you'll come back soon.
Maybe she was barking from anxiety the first day.
But because you kept
dragging it out further and further,
your anxiety only fueled Coco's anxiety,
rendering it impossible
for her to get used to being alone.
For example, when you opened the door
and called out right after leaving.
Coco was just about to give up
and walk away from the door.
After you left, she barked for more
than twice as long as the first time.
Huh...?
Your behavior planted the expectation in Coco
that barking might make you come back.
Now look at this.
After all that barking
and restless fidgeting,
Coco got tired and started digging in her bed.
If you had waited longer,
she might've given up and slept.
But then she notices something.
Presumably, your footsteps hurrying home
after ditching Samura at the supermarket.
So Coco starts barking again.
I thought Coco just kept barking the whole time...
She stopped...
Dogs are beings that follow a set program,
but that doesn't mean they can't adapt to change.
But it's rare for a domestic dog to be able
to make that change in an instant.
Through trial and error,
dogs find a way to deal with their anxiety,
then grow to understand
and learn from the situation.
Mommy left me!
I'm sad... I'm scared...!
I'll try barking for her!
She didn't come home...
I guess I'll just go to sleep...
Coco, are you hungry?
She came home when I slept!
I'm off to work, Coco!
I know you'll come back,
so I'm not worried anymore! Go ahead.
As her owner, you should have been
overseeing the process,
but instead you kept
interfering with her learning.
You even quit your job
so she could cling to you all day.
I felt so bad for her,
I ended up quitting my job.
Thanks to that, Coco learned the wrong lesson.
"If I make a fuss, she'll come back."
"If I cause trouble, she won't leave me."
I...was interfering Coco?
If you really can't afford to leave her at home,
you need to recreate the
environment she had before.
But if that's out of the question,
then you simply need to be strong for her.
Coddling her out of pity
will only hinder her growth.
Dogs will believe if their owners believe.
What should I do...?
In addition to improving her surroundings,
you must train yourself to leave her alone.
Train herself how?
Start by closing the front door
and coming back in.
1 minute
Wimper whimper
Then stand in front of the door for a minute,
then three minutes.
Wimper whimper
3 minutes
5 minutes
Bark
Then away from the building
for five minutes, then ten.
Bark
10 minutes
Then extend it to match
how long you would be out for work.
Keep training until you're both able to stay calm
and not worry about each other.
Some dogs may get used to it in days,
while others may take weeks or even months.
And given you're unusually anxious
about being separated from your dog,
I'm sure it'll be tough for you too.
But if you can't overcome this,
neither can Coco.
I want you to understand that happiness
for both you and Coco lies at the end of this training.
I want both of us to be happy...
I'll do it.
First, we must put together an environment
where she can comfortably stay by herself.
Let's make her a kennel.
Ah, I'd feel really bad putting her
in such a tight, enclosed space...
That's the human in you talking.
Dogs evolved from cave-dwellers,
so they feel safer in tight places
where their bodies make contact.
They do?!
Letting her roam free
exposes her to danger.
My dog would start eating human food, plants,
and other weird things. It was a mess...
But what if she needs to go
while she's crated up?
I'd be at work for a really long time...
Then we'll make her a kennel like this
to accommodate those needs!
Water
Crate
Bed
Potty
There's two places to sleep,
so she can rest easily!
And she can drink and use the bathroom!
Start taking her on walks to relieve stress
before you go out to work.
That'll tire her out and she'll get sleepy.
And lastly, no more dramatic
goodbyes or greetings.
You could pay her no mind whatsoever
when you go through the door,
though really, anything goes as long as
you don't rile her up.
We spent the first week
training Coco to use the kennel.
Looks like she's accustomed to it now.
Yes. I tried giving her food and treats
inside the kennel like you said,
and she likes it so much, she brought her
favorite plush in and started sleeping with it...
Which means it's time to train you to leave her.
Kozuka-san?
O-Oh, yeah. I'll do what I can!
Do you bathe with Coco too?
Huh?
H-How do you ask a lady something like that?!
So straight, too!
I-I don't, really.
I just give her a shout to let her know,
and she waits quietly in the living room...
In severe cases of separation anxiety,
a dog will start acting out if they can't see their owner,
even if they're both in the same house.
That's to say, as long as you're not anxious,
Coco will simply wait for you.
Just leave the house with the same peace-of-mind
as when you go take a bath.
He's right!
Coco's had it in her this whole time!
Right, Kozuka-san?!
As for you, you'll be helping her train
on a daily basis starting tomorrow.
What?
She's much less anxious with someone by her side.
Besides, not like you work much around the shop.
Wouldn't kill you to help out.
Watch your tone!
If it weren't for me,
your storage room would still be a junkpile!
Though he's not totally wrong...
Kozuka-san.
Yes?
Want me to help out?
The smile of an idol!
Hmm?
Umm... I... I'd appreciate that.
How does he do that?
The next day, both Kozuka-san and Coco
began training to overcome their anxiety.
Coco, will you go in?
Good girl!
Here's your treat! Eat up.
She started by going outside
then coming right back in.
Do you like it?
Then, she stood outside for one minute.
No barking.
Then for three minutes.
Hang in there...!
Then for five minutes.
There she goes!
What now? Did she figure it out?
She's not stopping...!
She's calling for me, but I can't go back in now...
This song's about five minutes long.
Wanna listen to it together?
It's only one song,
so it'll be over quickly.
She stopped!
At last, after two weeks,
it's time for the final test:
Staying home alone
for the length of her shift.
Hello, Samura-kun!
Good to see you.
Five barks...
And she's done.
Looks like she'll be okay.
Then off we go.
Niwa-san arranged a day out for the two of us
from 9:00 to 5:00.
Do you think Coco's resting easy?
That's the first time you've mentioned her today.
Oh, you're right!
I was just having so much fun.
That's very good to hear.
Niwa-san would probably say something like...
"You pass."
You sound just like him...
You even got his smug look down.
I also got really anxious for my dog
the day he had to get neutered.
I'd never had a dog before,
so doing anesthesia and surgery was so scary...
I was worried I could lose him.
But then, Niwa-san told me
the same thing he told you.
Dogs will believe if their owners believe.
He's not gonna die.
And I got to see Singe again after all.
So I'm sure if you believe in her,
Coco can do positively anything!
I know this is part of your job,
but I'm sorry for taking up your whole day.
Y-You don't have to apologize for that!
I had a lot of fun,
and I'm glad to help out either way!
Aah, my hat!
Thank you. You're so kind.
By the way, I have a job interview tomorrow!
Huh?
I better get back to work.
Not just for me, but for Coco too!
When Kozuka-san turned around to say that,
her face was radiant,
like a totally new person.
Now I can rest easy.
Because the two of them
will be much happier from now on.
You pass.
Giving a name to chance
Or giving love to fate
If I'm being honest
It's all the same either way
The things that you love
Are what make me happy
It's hilarious
Just how simple I am
Your heartbeat, stuck in my head
It brings back memories
To when we rushed home, laughing along the way
I hate being alone
It makes the night feel so slow
So come on, fall for me already
Sugarspot
You make my days even sweeter
With brown freckles just like your spots
I can get through a scratch or a rough patch
Just like that, the day's over
And in the deepest depths of my heart
Somewhere I feel lonely
Or maybe I miss you
Or a mix of both?
I don't know
Today's BenchBARK Advice
The way you should take care of a dog varies
depending on its breed, personality,
and the environment it's kept in.
Just be aware, not every dog should be treated
or thought about
the same as the doggos from today's episode!
Today's BenchBARK Advice
Next Time:
Niwa's Teacher