We ran after our adjacent shadows
I'll always be with you
Just how much light can you bring me
Like that which shines through the trees into my dark room
My soul was covered in sand, and you were a raincloud in the desert
That was when we first met
I forgot all about your mischievous smile
I just love you so much with every passing moment
Every path takes us back to our first encounter
I've always loved you, as childish as it sounds
I'll always be with you
Let's walk to the ends of the earth
My name is Izumi Ritsuka.
I'm a landlady and a dog groomer!
Your New Name
I run a dog salon two doors down!
Oh, you're his landlady! That makes sense.
Wait, are you his girlfriend too...?
Perish the thought.
S-Sorry!
I'm surprised that anyone would
want to work for Shinichiro, though.
Everyone's pretty much afraid of him.
That doesn't surprise me...
He's actually a sweetheart, you know.
Just experienced a lot
in the past, that's all.
Huh?
And he's a damn good dog trainer too!
But he's wasting those talents of his.
Ah, I know what you mean!
My dog got loose from his leash
and he saved him from getting run over!
He just went snap!
It was so dang cool!
Almost like magic!
Miyu-kun, was it?
You're looking to get paid, right?
W-Well, yeah.
Then you oughta get him movin'!
You can do it!
Me? Do what? What should I do?
Just think about it!
Hold on!
Get... Niwa-san moving?
How...?
I know...
Crap, it's already past 11:00!
Sorry. I ended up taking longer than I meant to.
You little...
Where the hell did you run off to
while you made me watch your un-potty-trained dog?
I-I'm sorry, I had to sort something out.
But, anyway, you said you'd train us
whenever you had no customers, right? Right?
I'll quickly clear this mess up
and then how about we head to the park?
So, what do you wanna tackle?
Hmm, I dunno.
Any minute now...
How about you demonstrate something for me?
Like some cool trick!
That'll surely get me motivated to learn!
Looks like he's fed up of this already.
What's that?
A long leash.
It allows a dog to train more freely
in places that mandate leashes.
But keep in mind, some parks
forbid the use of long leashes.
Ourson, heel.
Go!
So cool!
Stop!
He's signaling him by hand alone...
Even though they're so far apart!
This is the last one.
Over!
Izumi-san was right...
It's such a waste...
to keep all of this awesomeness to yourself!
That was amazing!
He's so talented!
Did you enjoy the show, everyone?
That was only an ounce
of what Niwa,
representative and trainer of Proud Dog,
can accomplish!
Huh? Hold on...!
Dog Trainer Niwa-sensei presents
A dog training demonstration
+
Free consultation
Today at noon
by the clock in Central Park
Dog Trainer Niwa-sensei presents
A dog training demonstration
+
Free consultation
Today at noon
by the clock in Central Park
Is this what you were up to earlier?
How could you...
To get customers!
You're not gonna get any by
hiding away in your room!
You're behind on rent, right?
And I need a salary to live, too!
Excuse me...
My name is Eguchi.
My boy is very aggressive
and I don't know what to do...
He's always acting like this...
"Aggressive..."
Can you elaborate?
Whenever he sees other dogs on a walk,
he'll start barking and trying to pick a fight.
I thought it'd be nice to make new friends,
but I can't even walk past them,
much less talk to them.
Why does he have to be like this...?
First of all, please set your dog down.
I can't! He'll lash out at the other dogs.
Just do it!
O-Okay...
Please be careful, doggies...
He's really...
Stop!
No.
Wow...
That's a good boy.
I can't believe it...
I want you to try walking around my dog next.
Bring Ourson over.
Got it.
Wait a minute!
He's even worse with bigger dogs...
He's really hopeless...
That's only because you don't believe in him.
Any dog can still be trained.
Let me have him.
What's his name?
L-Leo...
Leo.
Just now, he looked at me when I said his name.
That's called eye contact.
Today's BenchBARK Lesson
I'm going to teach you how and when
to initiate eye contact.
First are the "hows"
on initiating eye contact with your dog.
Saying its name.
Guiding their gaze with hand gestures.
Guiding them with the smell of a treat.
Getting their attention with
a toy that makes noise, etc.
This will attract the dog's interest to you,
giving you their awareness,
not just their gaze.
That, itself, is fundamental to dog training.
Today's BenchBARK Lesson
And now, the "whens."
If something happens
to distract your dog during a walk,
then just before they get riled up...
Leo!
And praise them once you have their attention.
Good boy, Leo! You're doing great!
Praise them like there's no tomorrow!
You're amazing, Leo! You're a superstar!
You can also give them a treat
whenever they make eye contact.
Practice this patiently.
Being on-and-off about praise
only serves to confuse your dog.
If your dog is already riled up,
then it's too late to initiate.
Leo! Stop it, Leo!
Not listening
Today's BenchBARK Lesson
Lastly, picking him up the way you did
won't make him calm down, but the opposite.
Hey! You have to stop barking.
When you pick him up to try and stop him,
he gets the idea that you're hugging him
for barking, and takes it as praise.
As a result...
He starts to think,
"Barking is a good thing! If I bark, she'll praise me!"
Cut it out, boy!
YAP
He gets the wrong end of the stick from it.
Right now, notice how he's looking at Ourson.
But if you look closely,
his ear is pointing this way.
It's a sign he's still paying attention to me.
Which means...
Leo.
I can immediately get him to focus on me.
Good boy.
And then Leo-kun walked all the way
around Ourson-senpai without barking even once!
An owner's emotions play a
major role in a dog's behavior.
When you get nervous that he might start barking,
Leo gets further on edge.
"She's too freaked out to handle this,
so I have to take the initiative."
Which created a habit of trying to intimidate others
by going on the offense.
When he's really timid, and doesn't want to fight.
Leo...
I'm so sorry, Leo...
How can I help him...?
As long as he can rely on his owner,
he'll feel safe.
He'll know he doesn't have to fight alone.
Correcting a dog's behavior
starts with their owner.
You need to get to know him better,
and believe in him.
If the owner changes, their dog will with them.
Heck yeah!
We got two trials booked, including Leo-kun's!
We'll be flooded with customers
in no time!
What about me?
Do I get a reward for bringing in customers?
I don't have any jerky for humans.
No, not jerky!
Teach me that magic snap you do!
This guy won't even so much as
look at me when I try...
Ourson, wait.
You won't pull off that snap in a million years.
Aw, what? What am I doing wrong?
So, do you have a name?
How many times do I have to tell you?
It's Samura Miy—
For the dog, not you.
No clue. I'm kinda shocked.
I'm the one who should be shocked...
Y'know, I never asked.
I'll have to call Yuko—
...Right, she won't pick up.
To a dog, a name is a special word
their owner says to them.
Calling him by a name will bring you closer together,
and build your trust.
It doesn't have to be the same as his old name.
You're his current owner.
Give him a name that's easy to understand,
easy to remember,
and that you'll want to call him over and over.
Only after that can you begin training.
Though, whenever you call his name,
you need to know...
Right, gotta move quick!
See you later!
A name... Hmm...
Dog Names
· Koro
· Shiro
Dog Names
· Koro
· Shiro
Koro? Nah, that's too cliché...
Shiro...?
He's not even white.
Dog Names
· Koro
· Shiro
Dog Names
· Koro
· Shiro
Kuro?
He's not even black!
Agh, coming up with a name is so hard!
Niwa-saaan!
Good mooorniiing!
It's time for work, Niwa-saaan!
Why are you banging on my door this early...?
What do you mean "this early?"
It's opening hours!
Gotta get the shutters open and clean up!
We have clients coming for trials
in just three days!
Get a move on!
I-I'm scared...
It's probably just as cluttered as his room upstairs...
This is the training room.
There's nothing even in here!
Where's the spirit?!
It's a training room.
It's supposed to be empty.
Wait, really?
How else will the dogs have room
to walk and run around?
If we need something,
we grab it from the back.
Sh-Shouldn't there at least be something
for the owners to sit on?
They can stand just fine.
God, he's hopeless...
He's very considerate about dogs,
but not in the slightest about humans.
Is that the back?
Yeah.
This is the staff room.
There's a toilet, shower, and kitchenette over here.
Just what I expected!!
Wait, where's the kitchenette?
It's behind that, I think.
You think?
Oh, what's that?
The dog training equipment.
Don't touch it without permission.
He really cares more about the dogs...
Human area
Dog area
Looks like I'll have to be the one
that cares for the humans!
Human area
All of the sake of bringing in customers!
First, I'll need to buy chairs...
If I check this website for unneeded furniture
being sold for cheap or given away...
"Set of 8 chairs for café renovation, ¥1,000!"
Umm, hi! I wanted to ask about
that eight-chair listing...
Oh, you have them?
Can I pick them up today?
Thank you very much!
Hi, I'm calling about that free listing...
Yeah.
The ones paying for our services
are the humans, not the dogs.
So if you want more customers, we'll have to make it
comfortable for them too, Niwa-san!
Uh-huh...
I made a risotto with
some canned foods from the kitchen!
Dig in.
Since I saved you money on lunch,
you can cover the cost of the chairs, right?
Oh, not a fan of tomatos and tuna?
Do you not want it?
No, it's fine.
It's so good...
So, have you decided yet?
Decided on what?
His name.
I'm still, uhh, working on it.
I just need a bit longer.
It's no problem with me,
but I'm not training you until you name him.
I get it!
See you tomorrow!
Man, what am I gonna do...?
Thank you!
See you next month, Sara-chan!
Izumi-san...
Ack, Mi-Miyu-kun!
Struggling with his name, huh?
Yeah...
I can't come up with something that fits him...
I see.
Well, that customer before was named Sara-chan,
and she had a little boy named Riku-kun.
Riku... Hmm.
For male dogs, there's Marcy, Ack, Lila, Max...
Oh, and Japanese names too.
Yakumo-kun, Kamui-kun, Kotetsu...
They can be Japanese too?!
There's so many options!!
It's an endless hell full of names!!
Guess I only added to his confusion.
My head's gonna explode...
There's no other choice...
100 Dog Names
For those who
just can't decide!
I'll just have to search for one!
Kotaro, Ivy, Luke...
I think those would fit a smarter dog, not him...
Ritsu, Rocky, Zero...
He's not nearly that cool...
100 Dog Names
For those who
just can't decide!
Choco / Chappy / Roy
Fuuta / Iroha / Nick / Tarosuke
Maya / Nika / Taku / Lily
Matthew / Maron / Momo
Nioji / Santa / Robby
Santa...?
That's the one!
Why are you here so late...?
Miyu-kun messaged me to come over.
Why don't we add each other too?
Why, so you can nag me about my tab?
You got me.
Sorry for the wait!
I come with an announcement!
A-An announcement of what?
He brought a scroll?
Santa
Naming!
My dog's new name is Santa!
Hey, stop that, Santa!
Oh, I see. Wow.
Why did he write it out with a brush...?
Aw, shucks. I gave it a lot of thought,
and this just fit the best!
He gave me a present I never expected:
a future as a dog trainer!
So I thought, he's like a year-round Santa Claus!
He's pissing on my floor.
Anyhoo, I know I worried both of you
about this,
so I wanted to let you know ASAP!
That's all. Right, Santa?
What?
Come on, let's go, Santa!
See you tomorrow!
G'night!
Took him all of 3 minutes...
Well... he seemed very happy.
Don't tell me that he...
After that, it finally feels official!
Alright, Santa! Let's walk on home!
Santa! Wait up, Santa!
Slow down, Santa!
Santa! Hello, Santa?
Weird, he's not responding to his name.
Santa? Hey!
Stop it, Santa!
Why won't he respond?
I put a lot of thought into it...
Cut it out, Santa!
Don't run from me, Santa!
Shut up, Santa! Are you listening to me?
Santa!!
He tried to run away when you called his name?
Why?
No idea...
And after all it took to come up with it...
Santa! I told you yesterday,
you can't eat tissues!
Hold it.
Were you scolding him like that
last night too?
Well, yeah. He was acting up.
That about explains it.
Huh?
You don't say a dog's name when you scold them.
You might just be trying to reprimand him,
but from the dog's point of view,
you're furiously yelling the word "Santa" over and over.
Santa!!
You gave him a bad impression
of the word "Santa" overnight.
No way...
Don't we usually hear our names when we're scolded?
Yes, because as humans,
we understand how names work.
Dogs, on the other hand, don't.
"My owner's always smiling
when they say this word."
"If I turn around when they say this,
I'll be praised."
To dogs, names are nothing more than "special" words.
If that word is followed by something they hate,
they hate the word too.
If you keep calling his name when you scold him,
then he'll start to hate hearing it.
Santa.
That name's too far gone now.
Aw man, I had no idea!
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I tried to, but you left before I could say anything.
Oh, yeah, back then...
What you keep calling "magic"
takes a lot of experience to put to work.
This is part of that training.
Today's BenchBARK Lesson
I'm going to go over some precautions
for calling your dog's name.
If you say their name while you scold them,
it'll plant a bad idea of that name in their mind.
They'll start to ignore you
or run away when they hear it.
You'll want to call their name during situations
a dog takes positively.
Say it when you give treats,
or whenever you praise them,
and they'll begin to think of
hearing their name as a good thing,
and turn to look at you when they do.
You don't want to overdo it, though.
They might start to find it annoying
and ignore you.
So what do I do when I scold him?
"Hey," "no," "don't."
As long as it's consistent, anything goes.
Just say a short word in a deep voice.
A short word...
"Hey" sounds embarrassing...
Okay, I'll go with "Don't."
– Don...
– Wait.
If you don't catch him in the act,
he won't understand later
when you show him what he did wrong.
He'll see your random reprimanding
as based on your whims.
Instead of understanding that
what he's doing is wrong,
he'll just think you're annoying and quick to snap.
So annoying.
What do I do...? Everything is so hard
for newcomers like me...
But I can't just give up!
Alright, let's deal with his name!
I can't have him hating his name, right?
How do I fix that?
Pick something else. Simple as that.
Won't it be confusing to change it on a spur?
You don't want to change a dog's name
after they've memorized it, no,
but your dog's already made it a word he hates
before he's had that opportunity.
There shouldn't be any problem
making a name from a completely different word.
You just have to use that word
in a way that he'll like.
But what do I do about "Santa?"
As long as you don't use that word regularly,
he should forget about it with time.
Even though you don't know it, your ex-girlfriend
must've called him something different.
Oh, yeah. He's right...
Then that means...
I have to go back to the drawing board!!
Leave him be, Ourson.
Come to think of it...
Where does Ourson-senpai's name come from?
Ourson...
...means "bear cub" in French.
Bear cub? That's oddly fancy coming from you.
No!
He used to look like one!
Y-You're right!!
And I went with a French name
because France is where poodles came from.
I wasn't just following trends!
Oh, wow. I never knew poodles were a French breed!
French fits him so well...
"Singe."
How is it? It's French.
Singe... Singe? Singe.
I like it!
It sounds very cool!
Say it gently.
Singe.
He looked at me!
Praise him.
Good dog, Singe.
I'll be sure to say it more carefully
so you'll like it this time!
So he settled on "Singe," huh?
You like it?
Why are you here...?
I was free, so I'm tenant-watching.
So what does "Singe" mean?
I wanna know too!
What's it mean?
Singe...
Yeah?
...is French...
Go on?
...for monkey.
Huh?
It's a male monkey. Didn't think you'd like it.
Monkey...
Monkey?!
I thought it would mean something cooler!!
But it fits him... uncannily.
...Monkey.
Singe.
It's cute.
It's good to meet you again, Singe.
You're a good boy.
You've done it again, Shinichiro.
Good boy.
Giving a name to chance
Or giving love to fate
If I'm being honest
It's all the same either way
The things that you love
Are what make me happy
It's hilarious
Just how simple I am
Your heartbeat, stuck in my head
It brings back memories
To when we rushed home, laughing along the way
I hate being alone
It makes the night feel so slow
So come on, fall for me already
Sugarspot
You make my days even sweeter
With brown freckles just like your spots
I can get through a scratch or a rough patch
Just like that, the day's over
And in the deepest depths of my heart
Somewhere I feel lonely
Or maybe I miss you
Or a mix of both?
I don't know
Next Time:
Living in Bliss