Coming up on Punirunes...
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
The show is squishing!
Let's play, Punirunes!
Punirunes.
Before we knew it, these creatures
began to inhabit the human world.
They're squishsterious and soft to the touch!
They all love to be squished.
There's also fun, adorable puni-pals aplenty.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Kachi-Freezy Jewelrune is
Come-Come-Comin' to Town♪
What should be our next new bread pastry?
How about a hard, crispy baguette?
Aww, what?
Squishy, springy bread is way better!
The bakery is closed today.
Yuka and her family are relaxing on their day off.
As for the Punirunes...
They're full of spunk, and about to head
to Kachikochiland in search of a Punistal fragment.
"Now, off to Kachikochiland!"
Oh my! This isn't Kachikochiland at all.
They ended up in Puniland instead!
Jewelrune's in freezy form.
But Airune's in its usual squishy form.
Looks like only Jewelrune ended up here
in its freezy form.
"What do I do?" it worries.
"It's all fine!" says Enerune.
And then...
Nazorune appears.
Everyone's started to notice Jewelrune.
"My gosh! This texture is just brilliant!"
"So hard!"
"So smooth!"
"So shiny! So amazing!"
Jewelrune's novel, stiff texture
has swept Puniland.
They're having... not a handshake event,
but a freezy squish contact event.
Jewelrune's become a squish-fluencer,
and everyone's begun exercising
to become rock-hard like Jewelrune.
Can exercise even do that?
Jewelrune's a hit all over.
It's super busy giving autographs.
Over here, handmade fan merch
are making the rounds.
Yes, please calm down.
Wait, what?!
This is making it difficult
to get around.
Coolrune has a plan!
Rocking out an incognito disguise
courtesy of Coolrune!
This'll keep it safe alright.
Oh no, Airune's house fell over.
Much better.
Jewelrune?
Something's off about you.
What's the matter, Jewelrune?
"Everyone in Puniland is so caught up
with being kachi-freezy. It's too much!"
"What am I to do?" it says.
That sounds tough.
Huh, you're not squishy?
What on earth is this texture?
Squishy textures are really good,
but so are hard textures too!
Got that right!
Hard and soft both have their quali-teas!
I think the day you recognize
the greatness of baguettes is nigh!
I see!
Y'know, Jewelrune.
How about you tell everyone
how you feel about it?
I'm sure they'll hear you out.
See you later!
Jewelrune boldly proclaims...
"Both squishy and freezy textures
are brilliant alike!"
"Please don't treat being freezy
as the gold standard!"
Looks like Puniland has moved on
to the next big thing: jumping Enerune.
The trends change so quickly, don't they?
Jewelrune's freezy trip to Puniland
turned into one real adventure.
The Puni-Puni Squestion!
I will present a question
based on the events of the episode.
Try your best to remember!
Puniland fell in love with kachi-freezy Jewelrune.
It became a big craze, many responding,
"Being hard is cool! I want to be hard!"
It even got chased down by a horde of fans.
Squestion time!
What did the Punirunes do
to try to become like Jewelrune?
Give your frozen brain a squish
to find the answer!
Here's the answer!
Here's the answer...
They exercised!
And miraculously failed at it, clearly!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Red Light, Punin Light.
A game passed down generations in Puniland,
with an annual tournament
soon to be held again.
Next Time
Now run, win the qualifiers
and become champion,
Airune!
Jewelrune!
Claim victory!
Next Time
Next time: "Red Light, Punin Light♪"
Red Light, Punin Light♪
"Puni" in next time.