Coming up on Punirunes...
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
The show is squishing!
Let's play, Punirunes!
Punirunes.
Before we knew it, these creatures
began to inhabit the human world.
They're squishsterious and soft to the touch!
They all love to be squished.
There's also fun, adorable puni-pals aplenty.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
A Midsummer's Trip by the Seas♪
"A Midsummer's Trip by the Seas♪"
The Punirunes are on vacation
to make some summer memories.
Isn't this just the best?
Come on, take a dip, Jewelrune!
Feels great, doesn't it?
Jewelrune's never been to the sea before,
and it's loving it.
What's a perfect tropical game?
Watermelon splitting!
Go right!
Wait, left, go left!
"Watermelon Ultra Hyper Max Blade!"
Airun has the spirit,
but not the strength.
Yum, yum, in my tum!
I heard we're gonna have barbecue tonight!
I really wish Aoi could've come with...
If it weren't for...
I wish I could go, I swear!
But I'm taking care of a glass catfish
for a school research project,
so I can't really be away for long.
Enerune, go have fun for me, okay?
You remember that, Enerune?
Hey, Yuka!
Why don't you go check out the coral reefs?
Wow, sounds amazing!
Thought you might enjoy going snorkeling too.
Who knows, you could run into a manta ray!
You sure know your stuff.
Well, it's all book smarts.
But listen to this.
There's a legend the books don't have.
Huh? What kind of legend?
You see...
They say there's a secret spot here
which only appears during special occasions, arr!
A secret spot?
Whoa! Sounds epic!
I picked it up from some folks living nearby.
Yuka, time to go!
Oh! Coming!
I'm gonna go pick out a souvenir for Aoi.
Good call.
Don't run off now, you hear?
I'll prepare the barbecue while you're away!
A-Are you sure you'll manage?
Abso-dang-lutely!
I won't end up making pastries like I usually do!
Loverune, Ururune, and Coolrune
help out with the prep work.
Barbecue, barbecue...
As for the others...
They're fooling around over here.
Seems like Jewelrune is fixed
on the secret spot Dad told them about earlier.
Oh my! The Punirunes are rowing out to sea
in search of the secret spot!
Their epic adventure will now begin...
uh, soon, right?
They've started rowing in sync
and are finally moving forward.
"There's a shark! We're swimming
straight into danger!" it says.
Airune looks very chill compared to everyone else.
"Airune!"
Wait, a dolphin?!
Looks like Airune knew it was
a dolphin the whole time.
They're progressing quicker than before.
The Punirunes are surprisingly good swimmers.
"This must be the secret spot
Dad was talking about!"
What an amazing spot!
It's a beach created from coral
building up over a long time.
Loverune and Coolrune
are taking an elegant sunbath.
These few are taking a sand bath.
Everyone's truly enjoying themselves.
The beach is getting smaller and smaller!
The others have finally caught on.
This isn't looking good for them!
How will they get out of this one?
Are you kiddin' me?!
Why did I start kneading dough?!
On the bright side,
I finally perfected my new recipe!
We're back!
Glad you decided on a good souvenir!
Yeah.
This seashell bracelet is perfect for Aoi!
Oh? Something smells good!
Time for a barbe—wait, it's bread? Seriously?
I knew you'd go baking again.
You're an open book!
Wait, where are the Punirunes?
Huh? They were right over there...
Airune! You guys!
The seagull gave them a ride back.
Jewelrune starts to tell the story
of their epic adventure.
Wow! So Dad's story was true after all!
Dinner time!
Ooh!
Aah!
Everyone made very wonderful
summer memories.
The Puni-Puni Squestion!
I will present a question
based on the events of the episode.
Try your best to remember!
The Punirunes went on vacation
to make some summer memories.
Jewelrune had a lot of fun too,
for its first time by the sea.
And they had a tropical game
of watermelon splitting.
Airune showed a lot of spirit.
Squestion time!
What did Airune shout here?
Give your frozen brain a squish
to find the answer!
Here's the answer...
Here's the answer!
"Watermelon Ultra Hyper Max Blade!"
The answer is
"Watermelon Ultra Hyper Max Blade."
Try to split it for real
next time, Airune!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Jewelrune, guess what?!
Something amazing happened
to me and Airune!
I became Airune,
and Airune became me!
Next Time
Woohoo!
Now I can get all the squishes,
and do squish contact every day!
Alright! I'm gonna savor this to the end!
Next Time
Bye, I'm off to play!
Yuka and Airune's
Squishy Body Swap♪
Next time: "Yuka and Airune's Squishy Body Swap♪"
"Puni" in next time!