Coming up on Punirunes...
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
The show is squishing!
Let's play, Punirunes!
Punirunes.
Before we knew it, these creatures
began to inhabit the human world.
They're squishsterious and soft to the touch!
They all love to be squished.
There's also fun, adorable puni-pals aplenty.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
The Squishy Photo Contest♪
"The Squishy Photo Contest♪"
Lookin' good! Great squish!
You're squishing magnificently as ever!
Feast your eyes!
Aww, so adorable!
For that, I'll treat you to
some of my other shots.
This is from this morning.
This is from last night!
And this is that from a slightly different angle.
And another, and another,
and another!
Even just a single millimeter of a difference
changes your impression of them entirely!
Okay, maybe I just went overboard.
But I can't help it.
My finger has a mind of its own!
I know just what you mean!
I want to take tons of pictures
of noctiluca blooming,
but the water tempature and other things
make it hard to catch it in action.
But if I ever saw it,
gosh knows I'd be snapping photos like crazy!
Oh yeah, Aoi, you enter
the marine photo contest every year, right?
Yeah! And I'm planning to win this year!
Huh? Airune, you wanna take photos too?
It says it wants to hold
the 1st Squishy Photo Contest.
Everyone's on board.
Sounds fun!
How about Aoi and I be the judges?
We should probably think of
a prize for the winner.
Hold it right there!
I'm on it! I'll make you
a special, wonderful gummy!
Yuka's mom is very much on board too.
The Punirunes are getting
even more excited.
I can't wait to see all the cute photos you take!
Have fun!
Get some good photos!
Puniland
This is Puniland.
Where everything...
even the rocks...
are squishy.
It's Jewelrune's first time here,
and it's starstruck.
They drew lots to decide
what pairs take photos together.
How will this turn out?
Sushirune
These three are called Sushirune.
Maguro, salmon, and shiromi—
altogether, they make the Sushirunes.
They're playing pretend as sushi.
They're asking if they can take a photo
with the Sushirunes.
It's a seafood bowl!
This'll make a great photo.
Photography fail: unfocused shot.
Meanwhile...
Nyarurune
This is Nyarurune.
It's sunbathing, when...
Looks like they're doing a photo shoot
with Loverune as the director.
Oh my goodness!
It's rolling over like a cat
showing trust to its owner!
Perfect photo op!
Can't let this chance slip away!
Followed by a stretch!
Perfect photo op!
So how did their photos come out?
Photography fail:
jumpy photographer, shaky photos.
And over here...
Airune's stumped on what to get photos of.
Oh? Where did Jewelrune go?
Found it.
It's so starstruck by Puniland,
it keeps taking pictures of rocks.
Hikarune
This is Hikarune.
It can turn into a full moon
and shine brilliantly.
Airune wants to take a photo
of full moon Hikarune.
How unfortunate!
Hikarune's real bashful,
and responded by hiding in the clouds.
It's asking if Hikarune
would like to take a photo with them.
Jewelrune's cuteness won Hikarune's heart.
Say cheese!
How'd it come out?
Photography fail:
blinking during the shot.
Did you see that...?
Later...
Everyone's tuckered out
from all the photos they took.
Jewelrune wants to take
one last photo all together.
Naturally, everyone's in.
Airune has an idea.
What could it be?
Puni-Friend Bell
O-Oh wow!
With Jewelrune's help, Airune called in
a ton of its puni-pals!
Jewelrune seems real happy too.
Time for the results.
The winner of the 1st Squishy Photo Contest is...
everyone!
Here is your prize!
Mama's specially-made mega gummy!
You won't be able to fit it
in one day!
Alright, let's do this!
Yeah!
The Puni-Puni Squestion!
I will present a question
based on the events of the episode.
Try your best to remember!
The Punirunes gained an interest in photography
thanks to Yuka and Aoi.
They decide to hold the 1st Squishy Photo Contest,
and get lots of photos with their puni-pals.
It wasn't without a few mishaps,
but they made for good memories.
Squestion time!
Can you name all the Punirunes
in the final photo they took?
Give your frozen brain a squish
to find the answer!
Here's the answer...
Here's the answer!
Airune, Jewelrune, Loverune, Enerune,
Coolrune, Ururune, the Sushirunes,
Nyarurune, Hikarune, Babyrune, Cuprune,
Pikarune, Utarune, Bakerune, Happyrune, and Angelrune.
How many did you get?
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Huh? Airune, Jewelrune,
where are you off to?
To Kachikochiland to search for
the second Punistal fragment?
Next Time
What? It's in a terrifying dungeon?
Are you sure about this?
Next Time
Airune, you're trembling like crazy!
Next time: "Kachi-Freezy Dungeon Quest♪"
Kachi-Freezy Dungeon Quest♪
"Puni" in next time!