Coming up on Punirunes...
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
The show is squishing!
Let's play, Punirunes!
Punirunes.
Before we knew it, these creatures
began to inhabit the human world.
They're squishsterious and soft to the touch!
They all love to be squished.
There's also fun, adorable puni-pals aplenty.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Oshirune the Super-Fan♪
"Oshirune the Super-Fan♪"
The Punirunes are here to play
with Airune as always.
Looks like Airune has something to say.
Let's see. "I love how squishy Airune's cheeks are!"
"Don't you agree?"
"Its squishy ears are another one
of its best traits!"
Now why on earth is Airune
talking itself up?
You sure ate your fill of breakfast, Airune!
Oh, the gang's all here!
Good morning!
Huh? What's Airune doing here and there?
Airune, didn't you just eat
five squishy buns?
Huh? What the? Wha?
But you just came in, right?
Airune, you are Airune, right?!
Calm down, Yuka.
Then who's that Airune?
Who are you?
Oshirune
Oshirune, is it? Nice to meet you!
Why are you dressed like Airune?
It feels shy seeing its oshi Airune up close.
Wait, are you a fan of Airune?
Oshirune made all of its Airune merch itself.
Airune mask!
Airune fan!
Airune photo cards!
Oh wow!
You really do like Airune a whole lot!
But what sparked this interest?
"You see..."
Oshirune is a shy Punirune.
It wants the teddy bear,
but it can't bring itself to speak up.
"I want it so bad..."
Just as it boldly reaches out for it...
it is graced with an encounter.
Airune gave it the teddy bear
and spoke up to get the clerk's attention.
Oshirune knew right then
that it had fallen for Airune.
From then on, Oshirune began spreading
the good word of Airune.
Aww! What a nice story!
But Airune's not sure what to do.
No one's ever cheered it on like this.
Why don't you ask Loverune?
Loverune says that it's important
to live up to the support of one's fans.
Airune made up its mind.
If it wants to uphold this fandom,
it must become a better Punirune:
a superstar Punirune!
Airune, it's lunchti—wha?!
What the?!
The first step to stardom
is looking the part.
Next up is a concert.
It's doing a guest performance
in Loverune's concert.
The Babyrunes aren't sure how to feel
about Airune's rapping.
Stardom is no easy feat,
but Airune continues working towards it.
It must exercise every day
to maintain its perfect body.
Being a fashion leader means creating
fits with brand new accessories.
Become a squish-fluencer,
always stealing the spot...light?
Are you alright, Airune?
Airune's not sure what it means
to be a star anymore.
"How am I supposed to hold a fandom now?"
Airune ponders.
Oshirune answers...
"You don't have to worry!
You're already..."
Oshirune?
Uhh, allow me to translate.
"Seeing a whole new side of you when you
tried to be a star was so hype!"
"But you don't have to be a star,
because you're already amazing!"
"You treat everyone with the same kindness,
and you have a bright smile,"
"and you make food look so yummy,
and have such cute ears and cheeks..."
"on top of so many other qualities
I couldn't begin to describe!"
...it said.
Basically: "I like you just the way you are."
Well said.
You're great because you're you!
Don't you agree, Oshirune?
What's wrong?
It loves Airune so much,
it's having a hard time speaking face-to-face.
Really, after that big tangent before?
Oshirune will keep cheering Airune on.
The Puni-Puni Squestion!
I will present a question
based on the events of the episode.
Try your best to remember!
Oshirune is a Punirune
who loves Airune.
It made its own Airune merch
and cheers Airune on.
Oshirune's fandom of Airune
was sparked on by a certain event.
Squestion time!
What item did Airune and Oshirune
touch at the same time?
Give your frozen brain a squish
to find the answer!
Here's the answer...
Here's the answer!
The answer is a teddy bear!
Did you get it puni-right?
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Airune, Jewelrune, look over here!
Say cheese!
I got a squishy photo!
Next Time
You think photography sounds fun
and want to take photos yourself?
A squishy photo contest?
That sounds awesome!
Next Time
I wonder what kind of photos you'll get!
The Squishy Photo Contest♪
Next time: "The Squishy Photo Contest♪"
"Puni" in next time!