Coming up on Punirunes...
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
The show is squishing!
Let's play, Punirunes!
Punirunes.
Before we knew it, these creatures
began to inhabit the human world.
They're squishsterious and soft to the touch!
They all love to be squished.
There's also fun, adorable puni-pals aplenty.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Jewelrune Gets Flustered♪
"Jewelrune Gets Flustered♪"
This isn't getting anywhere!
I got carried away having fun...
and haven't touched my homework one bit.
Jewelrune here is lamenting
over hardly getting any Punistal fragments.
"Once we get all twelve Punistal fragments,"
Jewelrune responds, "I can make something even cooler!"
But it hasn't gotten anywhere
close to twelve yet.
"Okay! Then let's go to Kachikochiland now!"
All hands on deck,
and it's time to set off!
Jewelrune is awfully flustered.
"Let's look for them together!"
Everyone begins searching
on Airune's order.
Have they found one already?
They were just fooling around.
Airune instinctively calls them out.
Naturally, Enerune slides
with much enthusiasm.
Perhaps a bit too much enthusiasm.
Calm down, punis.
What is Enerune's fate?
Shocked that both ramming itself and using its sword
did not work, Jewelrune starts to lose confidence.
Airune has some sort of idea.
"You should craft again,
like that one time!"
"Craft what? Another baseball bat?"
Jewelrune begins crafting.
Jewelrune took the sword and saber
and crafted a large board out of them.
It took cues from Enerune's star
and Loverune's heart boards.
Now they have four Punistal fragments in all.
"Let's look for all twelve together, okay?"
The two swear on it.
And so they shall continue
their search for the fragments.
On the other hand...
This isn't getting anywhere!
Ugh, I'm done for! I'll be stuck doing homework
for the rest of my days!
Yuka failed to get even one
bit of homework done.
The Puni-Puni Squestion!
I will present a question
based on the events of the episode.
Try your best to remember!
"Once we get all twelve Punistal fragments,"
Jewelrune responds, "I can make something even cooler!"
With that, the Punirunes set off to adventure
in search of a fragment.
Squestion time!
How many Punistal fragments
does Jewelrune have as of this adventure?
Give your frozen brain a squish
to find the answer!
Here's the answer!
Here's the answer...
The answer is four!
Did you get it puni-right?
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Whoa, what's with the new look, Airune?
You're all kachi-freezy!
Aw, you look down. What's up?
Next Time
"I've got this?" What do you mean, Coolrune?
Wait, where are you going
with all those costumes?!
Next Time
Next time: "Coolrune and Kachi-Freezy Airune♪"
Coolrune and
Kachi-Freezy Airune♪
"Puni" in next time!