Coming up on Punirunes...
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
The show is squishing!
Let's play, Punirunes!
Punirunes.
Before we knew it, these creatures
began to inhabit the human world.
They're squishsterious and soft to the touch!
They all love to be squished.
There's also fun, adorable puni-pals aplenty.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
The Punirunes’
Grandest Adventure Ever♪
"The Punirunes' Grandest Adventure Ever♪"
Two Punistal fragments remain.
"Everyone, will you all help me?"
Off they go!
Tomorune the warrior
joins the party of Airune the hero!
The party sets off on an adventure
to find the Punistal fragments.
After Tomorune left our heroes,
it asked around about the Punistal
fragments on its journeys.
"We'll be sure you build your crown!"
"We will! To replace the one you lost!"
Ururune does a
squishsterious dance!
At last, Jewelrune has obtained
twelve Punistal fragments.
Or so it thought...
"Do it!"
Tomorune leaves one last hope
in its party...
Sorry, not you.
"Ouch!"
"Thank you, Airune!"
"You really are the hero
I've sought for!"
"Now you can build
the crown you lost!"
"But you didn't lose the crown,
did you, Jewelrune?"
"Tell them the truth."
Jewelrune is the prince of Kachikochiland.
And even in royalty,
it found a puni-pal in Tomorune.
Jewelrune loved chatting with Tomorune
under the great kachi-freezy tree.
However...
One day, they found strangely overgrown
kachi-freezy fruits on the tree.
If these all fell off at once,
they'd bring ruin to the city.
"We don't have time to search
for Punistal fragments."
"Isn't your crown super valuable?!"
"I have to keep the citizens
of Kachikochiland safe!"
"Don't tell anyone I used my crown, okay?"
Then, some time later...
"I found this old legend."
"'When the crown is lost,
seek aid from the hero.'"
"Where would I find a hero...?"
"I know someone heroic!
A very perky puni-pal of mine!"
"You used your crown to save everyone?
That's so cool!"
"So is Airune being a hero!"
"Then we have to make your crown now!"
The cave is about to collapse!
"Get out of here!"
"Tomorune, take these."
"Now!"
How will Airune get out of this?
The Puni-Puni Squestion!
I will present a question
based on the events of the episode.
Try your best to remember!
Jewelrune found strangely overgrown
kachi-freezy fruits on the kachi-freezy tree.
Squestion time!
Jewelrune used an item to make a giant axe
to save the citizens of Kachikochiland.
What did it use to make it?
Give your frozen brain a squish
to find the answer!
Here's the answer!
Here's the answer...
"We don't have time to search
for Punistal fragments."
It was its crown!
Did you all get it puni-right?
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Huh?! Airune got trapped in a cave
in Kachikochiland?
Are you okay, Airune?
Next Time
Jewelrune, you have to save Airune! Please!
Wait, Jewelrune, what are you doing?
Don't tell me...
Next Time
Next time: "Airune the Hero
& Jewelrune the Prince"
Airune the Hero
& Jewelrune the Prince
"Puni" in next time!