Last Time
The Punirunes head to Kachikochiland
in search of the final two Punistal fragments.
After many perils,
they stand before the fragments at last.
Last Time
Then Tomorune begins to tell
Jewelrune's secret.
Jewelrune didn't lose
its crown at all—
Last Time
as it turns out, it used the crown
to save the citizens of Kachikochiland.
Afterwards, they acquire
the fragments, but then...
Last Time
Airune the Hero
& Jewelrune the Prince
"Airune the Hero & Jewelrune the Prince"
Airune and Jewelrune will slash through
with both their swords at the same time!
Listen here.
Those are the Punistal fragments.
"Do you have a plan, Jewelrune?"
"I think we should use these
to craft a stronger sword."
"Didn't we go through all of this
so you could build your crown?"
"It's fine. I already have a crown."
That crown...
"Airune put itself in danger to save me."
"Not only is it a true hero...
"but it's the best puni-pal
one could ask for."
"Even if it means no crown...
"I want to use these Punistal fragments
to save Airune!"
It's Fairune!
"Thank you!"
"But how did you save me?"
"Jewelrune used the fragments
to build a super big sword!"
"What matters most
is that you're safe and sound."
"I'm sorry. If it weren't for me,
you could have made your crown."
"Don't worry."
"There's still plenty more Punistal fragments
across Kachikochiland!"
"So we can still find more
to make the crown!"
"Alright! Let's do it!"
"But I'm pretty hungry,
"so let's stop for now."
Welcome back!
How'd it go?
Wow. Sounds like a real doozy.
Okey-dokey! Ultra-delicious energizing pastries...
coming right up!
It's what you've all been waiting for!
Here we go!
Let's get squ-ooking!
Give it some of the
squishsterious squishence...
Stir it up...
Knead it...
Give it a squishy kneading
so it'll be nice and fluffy!
Appuni pie, ready to serve!
Appuni pie
Bon appétit!
Eat up, okay?
Food always tastes better
then when we all eat together!
There's plenty more to eat,
so doughn't hold back,
pump all that food kin!
Yuka, your cooking is so good!
Please, you flatter me.
I'm getting inspiration
for new recipes!
Your ideas always take the cake!
They're all having a good time.
The puni-squishy days
of the Punirunes...
will squish onwards.
Okay! Have a safe trip!
See you!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!