Coming up on Punirunes...
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
The show is squishing!
Let's play, Punirunes!
Punirunes.
Before we knew it, these creatures
began to inhabit the human world.
They're squishsterious and soft to the touch!
They all love to be squished.
There's also fun, adorable puni-pals aplenty.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Welcome Back, Tomorune♪
"Welcome Back, Tomorune♪"
Looks like they're playing hide and seek!
Tomorune
This is Tomorune, a very perky Punirune
with lots of puni-pals.
Naturally, Tomorune's
even puni-pals with Jewelrune!
We missed you, Tomorune!
Yuka and Aoi are also happy
to see Tomorune again.
The time you lived in Airune's home
feels so long ago now.
Tomorune, what kind of places
did you see on your trip?
Tomorune says...
"I went to faraway mountains,
"a faraway town,
"and a hilltop where I saw
beautiful shooting stars!"
Jealous!
Seems like Tomorune traveled
a good distance in Puniland.
"How is Unirune?"
Unirune is a legendary Punirune
seldom seen by others.
It's puni-pals with Airune and the rest.
Seems like Unirune's living happily still
in the squishsterious forest.
Tomorune, we heard you're back!
So glad we're "apple"
to see you again!
Alright! Let's throw a party
to welcome Tomorune back!
Yay!
Let's toast to Tomorune's return! Cheers!
Kanpai! Appuni pie!
Appuni pie!
Delicious!
Jewelrune and Tomorune
are happy to reunite.
"Where did you two meet?"
"Why, in Kachikochiland!"
"Have you gotten all the Punistal fragments?"
"We've got a long way to go."
So Tomorune even knows about Jewelrune's
goal to collect the Punistal fragments.
"Airune's been helping me out!"
"But Jewelrune, are you sure you can be here?"
"After all, you're..."
"Let's just move on from the bread,"
says Jewelrune.
However...
"Don't worry! I did a lot of
mountain climbing on my trip!"
Tomorune never changes.
Tomorune is leaving on a trip once again.
Yeah! You're welcome back here
anytime, Tomorune!
Jewelrune thanks Tomorune for the bread
with its favorite food—a puni burger.
Goodbye!
I hope you two meet again, Jewelrune.
The Puni-Puni Squestion!
I will present a question
based on the events of the episode.
Try your best to remember!
Tomorune is a friendly Punirune
with lots of puni-pals,
as well as a traveler.
Tomorune, what kind of places
did you see on your trip?
Tomorune says...
"I went to faraway mountains,
"a faraway town,
"and a hilltop where I saw
beautiful shooting stars!"
Squestion time!
Where did this traveling Tomorune
meet Jewelrune?
Give your frozen brain a squish
to find the answer!
Here's the answer!
Here's the answer...
The answer is Kachikochiland!
Did you get it puni-right?
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
What's wrong, Jewelrune?
Wait, Jewelrune,
why aren't you squishy?
It's freezy Jewelrune!
Next Time
Wait, so you took this form to Puniland
by mistake and it turned into a whole kerfuffle?!
Freezy Jewelrune's getting swarmed
by Punirunes! This is no good!
Next Time
Next time: "Kachi-Freezy Jewelrune is
Kachi-Freezy Jewelrune is
Come-Come-Comin' to Town♪
Come-Come-Comin' to Town♪"
"Puni" in next time!