Coming up on Punirunes...
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
The show is squishing!
Let's play, Punirunes!
Punirunes.
Before we knew it, these creatures
began to inhabit the human world.
They're squishsterious and soft to the touch!
They all love to be squished.
There's also fun, adorable puni-pals aplenty.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Coolrune and
Kachi-Freezy Airune♪
"Coolrune and Kachi-Freezy Airune♪"
The Punirunes are about to head to Kachikochiland
in search of a Punistal fragment.
They got left behind.
My, Airune's still in kachi-freezy form!
This is quite the predicament.
"Hold up! I could become a star!"
...it says.
It heads straight off
in its kachi-freezy form.
Oh! It's Oshirune, Airune's fan.
It's never seen Airune kachi-freezy before.
What will it think?
Oshirune's made up its mind:
it's a fan of kachi-freezy Airune too!
This has filled Airune with confidence.
Airune's ready to become a star!
"How do I look? Awesome, right?"
It didn't go the way it hoped.
It's taken a real shock.
Airune's fallen into despair.
"I'll bring back your confidence
and make you smile!" it says.
"Coolrune presents a show
bringing out Airune's good looks. It's called..."
"The Kachikochi Collection! A.k.a..."
"Kachi-Colle for short!"
Coolrune fashion takes more than a tiara and cloak—
the sunglasses bring together the elegant look.
Strutting with a grand impact—
we are witnessing the rebirth of fashion.
It's certainly characteristic.
Hello world, meet fashion!
Coolrune's eye for fashion
may be a bit too far ahead of its time.
Its confidence is draining harder and harder.
Crows love shiny objects. Surely...
Oh no! It went after Airune!
This is Pikarune, a very wise Punirune.
It seems to have an idea.
"Crows love nuts.
Walnuts, for example."
"So let's swap one with Airune," it says.
Cool!
Coolrune's normally very cool.
Who knew it could be so relieved.
"That was a crow nutcracker!"
"It's how they crack walnut shells."
Way to go, Coolrune.
You're all tidied up now!
Jewelrune and the others
are back from Kachikochiland.
They have successfully acquired a Punistal fragmgent.
Now they have five Punistal fragments in total.
I'm back!
Airune?!
Y-You're kachi-freezy now!
C-Can I... touch?
This feels different
from when you were squishy...
It must be... It must be...
a new texture! Oh my!
I'm a fan of kachi too!
I can't get enough of this sensation!
You two look so cool!
The Puni-Puni Squestion!
I will present a question
based on the events of the episode.
Try your best to remember!
Airune and Coolrune got left behind
on a trip into Kachikochiland
to search for a Punistal fragment.
While they waited for their return,
Airune tried to use its kachi-freezy form to become a star.
Unfortunately, it was all for naught,
and Airune's confidence sunk.
In order to bring back Airune's confidence
and make it smile,
Coolrune put on a show
to bring out its good looks.
Squestion time!
What was the short name
for Coolrune's show, The Kachikochi Collection?
Give your frozen brain a squish
to find the answer!
Here's the answer...
Here's the answer!
It was "Kachi-Colle!"
Coolrune is a world-class producer!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Airune, who's this little guy?
Why hello, Gaorune!
It's nice to meet you!
Huh, your roar turns anything squishy?
That's so cool!
Next Time
Must be fun to be squishy!
What?! Everything and the kitchen sink
has turned squishy!
Next Time
Gaorune
Makes Everything Squishy♪
Next time: "Gaorune Makes Everything Squishy"
"Puni" in next time!