Coming up on Punirunes...
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
The show is squishing!
Let's play, Punirunes!
Punirunes.
Before we knew it, these creatures
began to inhabit the human world.
They're squishsterious and soft to the touch!
They all love to be squished.
There's also fun, adorable puni-pals aplenty.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Red Light, Punin Light♪
"Red Light, Punin Light♪"
Airune!
I made some appuni pie
for you and your... friends?
Oh, down it goes.
I see! So you're training
to get better at Red Light, Green Light.
Oh, it's Red Light, Punin Light?
And there's a tournament coming up
in Puniland?
Wow! I'm sure you'll all have
lots of fun together.
What do you mean
it's not that simple?
You have to get through the qualifiers
to make it to the finals?
And of all those that enter,
only five people make it to the finals?
No... five punis.
Wow, sounds like some competition!
Go for the finals, you all!
And so, the Red Light, Punin Light
tournament begins.
Qualifiers begin taking place
in various locations in Puniland each day.
If the caller sees you move,
you get disqualified.
The first one to touch the caller
while it's turned away reaches the finals.
Airune wins the qualifier
during the Sushirunes' panic!
Nyarurune's swift feline speed
wins it the qualifier!
On a close look...
they're moving.
Bakerune, Angelrune, and Happyrune
are disqualified!
That wraps the qualifiers.
Airune and Jewelrune
have won the qualifiers.
And touch!
And now they train harder
for the finals.
At last, the day of the finals
has come upon them.
Having lost the qualifiers,
Airune and Enerune's friends
give their all into cheering them on.
Good luck, you two!
Now, onwards to the finals!
The winners of the qualifiers are...
Airune,
Jewelrune,
Nyarurune,
Hikarune,
and Cuprune.
The victor's prize is...
a giant gummy with
five times the squishiness!
The Punirune who touches the caller
first is the victor!
The Red Light, Punin Light
finals start now!
Oh no, it moved!
All the Punirunes watching it
made it feel bashful!
Hikarune, disqualified!
Oh no, Nyarurune's washing its face!
Now it's rolling over!
Its belly is exposed!
It won't stop moving!
Nyarurune's just too fickle!
As cute as that is!
You've probably figured,
but Nyarurune is disqualified!
Oh no! Where's Cuprune?
Cuprune got hungry and let its
stomach take the lead! It's disqualified!
Only Airune and Jewelrune remain.
Who will be the winner?
Oh no! What's going on here?
They're bringing out the tickles!
Hang in there, Airune!
Don't give in, Jewelrune!
Safe! They endured it!
Can they fight the urge
to take the delicious gummies?
They're feeling the pain!
But they cannot afford to move now!
You're doing amazing, Airune and Jewelrune!
Behold the power of the Punirunes
who have made it this far in the finals!
Believe in yourself and keep onwards!
Victory is in the palm of your hands!
Airune touched the caller first and won!
"The winner is actually Jewelrune,"
it says.
Jewelrune actually touched the caller
before Airune could.
"I may have lost,
"but I had fun."
Congratulations, Jewelrune!
Cheers to Airune too,
for sticking strong until the end!
There were many puni-smiles,
and many puni-tears.
And so, the 100th annual
Red Light, Punin Light tournament...
comes...
"END"
to an end.
The Puni-Puni Squestion!
I will present a question
based on the events of the episode.
Try your best to remember!
A Red Light, Punin Light tournament
was held in Puniland.
An intense face-off between
many Punirunes played out,
and the winners of the qualifiers
moved on to the finals.
The winners of the qualifiers are...
Airune,
Jewelrune,
Nyarurune,
Hikarune,
and Cuprune.
Squestion time!
How did Cuprune get disqualified
from the finals?
Give your frozen brain a squish
to find the answer!
Here's the answer!
Here's the answer...
Oh no! Where's Cuprune?
It moved to fill its hungry stomach!
Did you get it puni-right?
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Jewelrune, what's got you so flustered?
You're falling behind on getting Punistal fragments?
That sounds bad!
Next Time
Jewelrune, no! You shouldn't rush out there!
Next time: "Jewelrune Gets Flustered♪"
Jewelrune Gets Flustered♪
"Puni" in next time!