Coming up on Punirunes...
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
The show is squishing!
Let's play, Punirunes!
Punirunes.
Before we knew it, these creatures
began to inhabit the human world.
They're squishsterious and soft to the touch!
They all love to be squished.
There's also fun, adorable puni-pals aplenty.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Yuka and Aoi
Turn Mini-Mini♪
"Yuka and Aoi Turn Mini-Mini♪"
"Small-a-kazam!"
"Ice cream-a-kazam!"
"Birdy-kazam!"
Looks like Airune's pretending
to be a wizard.
"Birdy-kazam!"
Hey guys!
I made appuni pie!
Did you like it?
Now you're all nice and full!
They fell asleep.
Must be tired from playing.
Oh, you're awake!
Good morning.
Oh yeah, Airune.
You left this on the table.
What a cute wand!
"Small-a-kazam!"
Oh, you're a wizard!
Sounds fun!
W-We actually shrunk!
This is b-b-b-b-bad!
Or y'know what,
I can work with this.
I've always wanted to go in Airune's house.
Me too!
So this is what it feels like, huh?
Looks so yummy!
Thank you!
So squishy, so yummy!
Th-This can't be...
I expected squishiness from this...
But I couldn't have imagined this level of it.
What on earth is happening here?
Squishiness...
still has many hidden secrets
we've yet to uncover!
You all want some?
It says they want to spoil Yuka and Aoi today.
Huh? What's after dinner?
This is amazing...
After dinner, they take a relaxing bath.
This is amazing!
Top-of-the-line squishes for their guests.
Thanks. I'm having so much fun!
Next? I'm not sure.
I wanna go to Puniland!
Good idea! We can't miss out on that, right?
I want to go too!
Don't worry. We'll make sure we don't get lost.
We won't leave your sides!
Please take us!
Please? Pretty please? With a cherry on top?
I'm stoked!
We got separated from the others.
Yup...
Oh hey, it's Utarune.
What's this poster for?
Looks like Utarune, the superstar
who loves to sing, is holding a concert.
Utarune's holding a concert?
Sounds like fun!
They've found Yuka and Aoi!
Now they can rest assured...
or not!
A pack of Utarune fans
are swarming towards the concert!
They've lost Yuka and Aoi.
I wanna go see Utarune's concert!
Me too. But let's look for Enerune
and the rest first.
Yuka, look!
You think they'll let us ride?
We can look for the others on the move.
Let's ask!
Hey! Over here!
Nyarurune, Nazorune, Angelrune!
Where are you all headed?
"We're going to Utarune's concert!"
We're looking for our friends!
Can we get a ride on your carriage?
You'll give us a ride?
Thank you!
There's Yuka and Aoi!
Hurry up or you'll lose them again!
Thanks for the ride!
Enjoy the concert!
We couldn't find the others anywhere.
Yeah...
It's Cuprune!
That looks yummy!
Let's go eat some!
Cuprune!
Can we have some?
There's the carriage!
Thank goodness.
Now you'll finally meet up with Yuka and Aoi...
There they are!
Yuka!
Airune!
Yuka, the bat!
Oh no!
Airune and Yuka meet again at last.
And now, it's time for Utarune's concert!
Let's raise the roof! Woo!
Utarune!
Airune's smiling!
Must be having a nice dream.
The Puni-Puni Squestion!
I will present a question
based on the events of the episode.
Try your best to remember!
In a squishsterious turn of events,
Yuka and Aoi shrunk.
They enjoyed spoils from their Punirune friends
and a trip to Puniland.
But they were separated from the Punirunes.
Squestion time!
What Punirunes were on the carriage
that Yuka and Aoi hitched a ride on?
Give your frozen brain a squish
to find the answer!
Here's the answer...
Here's the answer!
Hey! Over here!
Nyarurune, Nazorune, and Angelrune.
I'm glad you made a fun memory, Airune.
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
You're all reading a picture book?
Lemme see!
I see, it's about a sparkly Punirune named Fairune!
It's a kind-hearted Punirunes
who spreads happiness!
Next Time
Huh, you wish Fairune was real?
Maybe it's out there somewhere!
Who knows, it could be close by,
watching over you!
Next Time
Next time: "Fairune and the Spark♪"
Fairune and the Spark♪
"Puni" in next time!