Cap Revolution Bottleman DX: Side Story!
Kaori's Bottleman Cooking
Kaori's Bottleman Cooking!
Hello, I'm Hakase Kaori!
Today, I'm going to take my cute little Bottleman
Append fast
shooting
and append the ability to shoot at fast speeds.
Today, I have a high-quality Bottleman
that is well-maintained with well functioning joints!
First, I will give it a nice cleaning. While I do so,
Brush
I view research data from other Bottlemen
and compare it against mine.
Recommended: Equip trigger
So in today's episode, I will create a trigger!
In order to implement fast-shooting, I'll be shortening
the speed of reloading and firing to a fraction of a second.
The key is to shorten the time it takes for the trigger to return
from firing, which relies on the repulsion of the spring.
So I get straight to designing the trigger
then send it to the 3D printer and wait overnight!
And voilà, here it is!
My top-tier efficient Hook Trigger is complete!
Ohh! So smooth and refreshing to the touch...
Smooth like a baby's bottom!
Now I can positively shorten the time
from firing to reloading!
Right after this, I'm gonna have my first Bottle Battle with Colamaru!
After I make him more purdy!
That concludes today's "Kaori's Bottleman Cooking!"
No ergonomics, no life!
The End
Produced & Distributed by
Cooking Committee
Kaori's Bottleman Cooking!
Kaori's Bottleman Cooking
Hello, I'm Hakase Kaori!
Wouldn't every battle be just a breeze
if you had both rapid and fast shots?
Our dish today will be a unique Bottleman
that combines both of those!
Let's make a one-hand reload Bottleman!
When it comes to reloading,
Gifted Bottle Battler
Ryo
Aquasports DX
Caps
I have to mention the gifted Bottle Battler Hocari Ryo.
While his Aquasports DX specializes in rapid-firing,
his reload is the fruit of his gifted swift speed.
Gifted Bottle Battler
Ryo
Aquasports DX
Caps
"Aw, he's just 'gifted?' That's no fair!"
That's what you're thinking, aren't you? Worry not!
Technology will solve everything!
Gifted Bottle Battler
Ryo
Aquasports DX
Caps
This is the Hook Trigger we made in the last episode!
Our goal was to shorten the time of the trigger return,
but guess what...? Feast your eyes!
You can hold it with one hand!!
So in today's episode,
we're going to prepare a Bottleman
with both rapid and fast fires, and one-hand reloads!
First off, I'll go over the results of my research
on Aquasports I set aside three days ago!
We want to have a solid idea
of what kind of Bottleman we're making!
Then we'll boot up our 3D program
and build a model of the core!
You'll want about 100 TB of memory for this!
Be sure to boot up your BMA-approved
3D printer, which you should have at the ready.
But if you don't, a personal 3D printer will do.
As long as it has laser etching and powder sintering!
With its framework and functionalities finished,
we must give it shape.
We'll decide on the color in this stage as well!
Writing and laying down as much as you can
is important for bringing your dish to perfection!
Build upon rejections...
Finalize the design...
Done! Here's what I settled on!
Now I can program the print around this sketch,
and behold the output!
Ahaa, I love this color!
The mold came out great too!
And just like that...
He's done!
How are these joints with that top-notch trigger?
In a world of decimals, reality comes down to
a difference of 1-10 centimeters...
The job of an engineer is never over!
I rate this brand new Bottleman...!
A splendid dish! 3 stars!!!
Mhm, it was great. You could really taste the ingredients.
There really is more to Bottleman than shooting!
That's what I'm sayin'!
Like, the standing trigger is neat,
but this form is amazing!
Aah, you're perfect!!
Right, you need a name!
Hmm, since you're purple...
Docpepion DX!
I'm so happy to see you, Docpepion!
I'm finally holding you in the real world!
Hehehehe...
*gasp*
*clears throat* I've prepared the ultimate Bottleman!
That's coming from me, the talented techy Bottle Battler!
But you should custom-make one to your enjoyment!
(Please don't try this at home.)
No ergonomics, no life!
The End
Produced & Distributed by
Cooking Committee