"Cap Revolution Bottleman DX: Side Story!"
Gwehehe...!
BMA
Bottleman
Museum
Its strong body built with the impression of a beast...
The two magazines that are both practical
and look super cool...
It's the real thing...! I need you~
Kaori Excitement Rate
Oh C.C. Leon~!
Ah.
Kaori Excitement Rate
Hello there!
Welcome to Dr. Kaori's Full-View! Bottleman!
Today, I'm here at the Bottleman Museum
and I'm gonna look at every nook and cranny
Kaori Excitement Rate
of C.C. Leon until there's not one bit left!
Dr. Kaori's
BOTTLEMAN
Full-View!
— C.C. Leon DX —
C.C. Leon is the Bottleman of one of the Champions,
About C.C. Leon DX
A reward for ranking up to Gold!
A personal one-of-a-kind Bottleman
Tons of features!!!!!!
Kinshasa Ari... Wait, what?
That's not it... Kindo Nichi?
Huh... What was it...? Shishimai Leon?
About C.C. Leon DX
A reward for ranking up to Gold!
A personal one-of-a-kind Bottleman
Tons of features!!!!!!
It's on the tip of my tongue...
Champion
Kinjishi Leo
Kinjishi Leo!
That's it! Kinjishi Leo!
Ah, thank goodness it came back to me.
Take 2!
C.C. Leon is the Bottleman of one of the Champions,
About C.C. Leon DX
A reward for ranking up to Gold!
A personal one-of-a-kind Bottleman
Tons of features!!!!!!
Kinjishi Leo, made to reward him for ranking up to Gold,
a one-of-a-kind model invented for him.
Leo dreamt of fighting the then-Bottle King Citrus,
but just as he had became Gold Rank,
Citrus had went missing!
In the depths of regret that he missed his chance,
Leo began to want speed more than
they had provided before.
One could say that this machine is the output
of his own feelings.
Without a doubt, the greatest feature it has to offer
is the two quick-loader magazines
that allow for 10 rapid shots!
The motive to develop this came when Leo said...
"I'm always lookin' for thrill!
"I want you guys to make a Bottleman
that pushes rapid-firing to its limits!
Rapid
Fire
"I'm the king of a hundred beasts,
so make it 100 shots!
"If that were a good idea, so...
"I'll live with just 10 rapid shots!
"If you can't do it, I'll devour you!"
Rapid
Fire
Oh, because "ten" and "beast"
are both "juu" in Japanese!
That's unexpectedly comedic of you!
What an unreasonable demand,
even if it is a reward.
There's no way you'd get away with that
by modern standards!
But BMA's researchers gave it a serious thought.
In order to implement 10 rapid shots,
you'll need to make a magazine that can hold 10 caps.
Which led to their very first prototype... Take a look!
The Super-Duper Long Magazine!
Ahaha, this is just so good!
Kaori Excitement Rate
Really feels like an early design,
it's so rough and heavy-handed!
It's so amazing just to get to see
the development process...
Kaori Excitement Rate
Such a rare machine to behold!
Aaaah, gosh!
I need every single one of these parts
carved into the creases of my brain...
Kaori Excitement Rate
Ack!
Crap!
Kaori Excitement Rate
P'haah!
Leo's reaction to this prototype was...
"It's so long! Too long!
"It's too hard to manuever like this,
"and it'll take dang too long to reload!
"Isn't that against the point
of using a rapid-fire type?!"
You just don't get what's good about it, do you?
The meetings were chaotic.
The researchers would sometimes yell at each other,
and dance with each other, but never got anywhere.
The development team inched towards
the brink of dissolving.
Until one person saved them from their predicament...!
"A lion leaves a rabbit at the bottom of a deep valley,
"and saves it if it doesn't make it back!
"Eat this and revitalize!
"Rawr!"
"Wow, so sour! I'm full of energy!
"And my head feels clear too!"
"Y-Yeah!
"The citric acid in the lemon
must've helped with our fatigue!
"Thanks, Kinjishi Leo!"
The researchers, as if they were new people entirely,
resumed development at a furious pace.
Many prototypes were built, then destroyed,
built, then destroyed, repeating trial and error...
until they finally came out with...!
Equipped with two magazines on its back
holding four caps each!
Additionally, holding one cap on its back and one inside!
At last, they've realized then 10 rapid-fire!
Now, even with heavy movement,
the magazines won't get in the way,
and reloading is quick and easy!
And just you look at this!
PROTOTYPE
OFFICIAL
The joint on the magazine and body!
At first, they envisioned putting a lid on the magazine
so the caps wouldn't fall out,
PROTOTYPE
OFFICIAL
as well as the idea of
putting a lock on it,
but they were both scrapped
in order to shorten the reload time!
Instead, it uses a stopper
to prevent caps from falling out
that only releases when the magazine
is jointed to Leon's body!
PROTOTYPE
OFFICIAL
Kaori Excitement Rate
Aaaahahaha, it's marvelous!
This structure is the best one yet,
Kaori Excitement Rate
so well thought-out without losing sight
of the development concept!
Kaori Excitement Rate
No piece of jewelry or artwork
holds a candle to this!
Kaori Excitement Rate
Isn't it just radiating with perfect beauty?!
Even Sir Leo was very pleased with this machine!
So he sought to think of a name for it.
"Let's see...
"It has two magazines that fit four (shi) caps each...
"And I'll take the 'Leo' from my name to make...
"C.C. Leon!"
"His new name is C.C. Leon DX!"
This caused a storm across the battling world.
Fanservice Please
Little C.C. Leon was born!
Happy birthday, C.C. Leon!
Fanservice Please
Welcome to life, C.C. Leon!
Also, in a request from Leo,
Kaori Excitement Rate
they made some color variants
of it as well!
How do you come up with
such good color palattes?!
Gwehehehehe!
Kaori Excitement Rate
I can't hold back any more...!
A little bit won't hurt, rght?
Kaori Excitement Rate
A little research won't hurt, right?!
Research, research, research, research, research...
Kaori Excitement Rate
There she is! It's Dr. Kaori! Get her!
Bruh?!
Kaori Excitement Rate
Aw, come on! It's okay!
I was just gonna research...
I mean, study it from a view!
You should've been banned from here a long time ago!
For trying to disassemble machines on display!
Good thing we saw this coming
and installed an excitement meter!
Whaaaaat?!
Isn't that the final Champion,
Kurenai Haku's R Greno DX?!
You already have that on display?!
I wanna see it, I wanna see it so badlyyyy!!
You still have those?! I'm confiscating them!!
Come on, just for a little bit? Meanie!
Anyways. That concludes Dr. Kaori's Bottleman Report!
Tune in next time!