Cap Revolution Bottleman DX: Side Story.
The Black Suits Know!
Skyscraper,
Top Floor
Hocari
Residence
You haven't been in any Bottle Battles as of late.
What have you been up to?
None of your business.
Well, that's cold.
I happen to be very eager
to see you climb a rank.
Would you be a dear
and Bottle Battle for me?
When I feel like it.
Machiko's been acting very kind to Ryo.
Has Io talked to Ryo lately?
Not really, come to think of it.
They aren't having issues, are they?
Maybe the reason Machiko's
been chatting with Ryo...
A Result of the Inheritance?
Ryo Bids Farewell to Io
On the Hocari Successor
Hocari Machiko to
Adopt Nephew Ryo?!
Who Will Gain Custody?
The Future of the Hocari Family
Hocari Machiko Goes Forward
With Bottle Battler Adoption
We're not prepared for this!!
What's for dinner tonight?
Yes!
As always, we will be ordering a full course
from a five-star restaurant.
There will be purin for dessert!
We'll summon you at approximately 7 P.M.
Numbskull.
The Next
Morning
Hocari
Residence
Living
Room
Machiko, regarding a matter we discussed
at yesterday's meeting.
My, you're here. What a surprise.
Were we not to finish this topic next week?
I see you're just as sharp about work matters,
but laid-back when it comes to the family.
I actually ran into him yesterday.
Came home pretty late, I think.
Can only imagine what he's been doing.
Let him do what he wants.
Are you sure? He hasn't been in
any Bottle Battles as of late...
You don't suppose he gave up
on it entirely?
Hocari Ryo's New Career?!
Becoming an Intellectual Shogi Player...
Gifted Bottle Battler
Hocari Ryo Announces Retirement
Hocari Io's Son Ryo Shocks the
Bottle-sphere with News of Retirement
Hocari Ryo, Youngest Shogi Title Owner:
Making Plays for the History Books
Demonstrating True Talent Through the
Intellectual Game of Shogi
BMA will lose its credibility!!
What are you two dawdling for?!
Get back to work!!
Sorry!
Do you think Ryo will be late again?
Maybe Machiko is right to question
his whereabouts...
You don't suppose...
he's going through
his rebellious phase?
Kids his age are like that...
Now that you mention it...
When Io was young, he got
super into **Daman,
and often didn't come home
because of it.
I wonder what Machiko
was like when she was young.
I heard she studied abroad.
Did she really?
Unsurprisingly, she was a very free spirit,
and would go cruising with her boyfriend.
You're enjoying yourselves.
Machiko!!
I presume you're finished
tidying things up.
N-No, ma'am!
We apologize!
Just a bit longer!
Oh dear, she heard us,
didn't she?
She must've heard us talking,
but not what we said...
Since you have time to kill,
perhaps you can go clean up the caps.
Instead of discussing me
cruising with my boyfriend.
Eeek!
She heard everything!!
The Black Suits Mess Up Big Time!
New Uniform Will Be White
The Days of Black Suits Are Over
"Black Suits are Worthless,"
Hocari Machiko Coldly Responds
According to Hocari Machiko,
All of the Hocari Family's Black Suits Will Be Replaced?!
Next, need to clean the trash in this field...
Um. You two. Why are you frozen solid?
Get back to work!!
S-Sorry...