Deadline: 1 Away!
My deadline's in an hour.
I want beef bowl...
Beef bowl?
Beef Bowl
BAM
You're so cute when you're
craving beef bowl!
But it's going to take an act of god
to wrap this up on time!
Where's the rest of the manga?
Oh hey, it's me.
Tapping time!
Are you the god of manga?
Are you the Gureco here?
We swore we would use this manga
to make a world full of maidens!
#MAIDENIFYTHEWORLDProject
But we're running out of time!
Please help us finish this!
Okay, fine. I'll help.
Kuromi.
I'll help too.
A monster came out of a hole...
Aha! I'll add this detail...
There!
M-M-My goodness!!
That's the work of a god of manga!
I'm exploding with inspiration!
All done!
Now get that manuscript in!
I'm on it!
You look like you had fun, Kuromi.
Oh? Of course I did!
No matter the world,
I only do what I wanna do!
What you want to do, huh?
Universe!
Beeef booowl...
Kuromi!
Your manga's finished up!
Huh?!
Ain't easy
being popular!
Artist: Kuromi
Now, now.
Don't fight over me.
Artist: Nico
Don't fall for me now!
Artist: Gureco
What on earth is this manuscript?!
Who drew these?
The god of manga!
Kuromi's keyword!
"Warp gate!"
I become a warp gate?