Another taker, eh?
See ya later!
They grabbed Kuromi again...
Well, we are new characters.
Not me!
Huh? What world am I in now?
Oh no! I'm in trouble, aren't I?!
Kuromi!
Nico! C'mon and help me!
Your Universe Patrol rescue
is on the way!
Hey!
That's no fair, Kuromi!
What's your problem?
I'm in a bit of a jam here!
Beg someone else to grab you!
Huh?
Are you new Kuromi merch?
So cute!
Of course only Miss Kuromi
gets new merch...
Well, that's what stinks
about being new characters.
We're just not popular enough
to have variants.
I already told you,
I'm not new!
Nico, you're crushing my face!
Really? A video told me
this was the way to grab you.
I won't let you get ahead!
Hey, cut it out!
Jealous!
Wh-Who a-are you?!
Kuromi!
Ignore me and get out of here!
Dunno who you are, but thanks!
I did it!
Now we can tap your plush
and move out!
Universe!
Someone buy us...
Kuromi's keyword!
"The dark side!"
Am I destined to succumb
to the darkness...?
As if!