Oh, it's the Kuromi from this world!
I-I'm so cute, even as a zombie!
Thanks for comin'!
Want a candy, hun?
Now you can be part'a
the ZOMBIfy the World Project too!
ZOMBIfy the World Project?
Got that right! Zombies don't gotta
think about anythin'!
#ZOMBIFYTHEWORLDProject
The world's way happier like this!
I'm happy bein' a zombie!
We make more zombies
through this scallion cola!
Scallion for life!
What?! I already drank it!
You should get zombified
real soon!
I can feel it...
Nothing.
I suppose since you forget
your troubles overnight,
it won't work on you.
It won't?!
Of course not!
Besides, life's no fun
without a few challenges!
Ugh, you sure are difficult.
Get rid of that eyesore!
Welp, I can't interfere,
but I can cheer you on!
You have one job, dude!
Oh, right!
So spicy!!
Heat! It's every zombie's weakness!
Kuromi, take MM!
Tap it against zombie-you!
Boop.
Universe!
Huh?! What just happened?
I am the Multiverse Mobile,
or MM for short.
An equipment used by
Universe Patrol.
Tapping me against a key
opens the door between dimensions.
Wait, so I'm the key?
It just happens to look like you!
Funny coincidence, right?
Freaky.
So if I step through this door...?
You'll go back to your home world!
And my mission will be complete.
Have a safe trip!
Kuromi's keyword!
"A villainess!"
I look totally cute like this!