What do you mean "arrested?"
Have you not seen the chaos
she turned this world to?
We have to keep her under watch
to prevent any further evil.
I'll pay for my crimes.
How could you say that?
You ain't thinking about her at all!
You can't take her home
over your stupid rules!
But there's nothing left
we can do about this world.
Oni!
Mom, Dad.
Nico!
I'll turn back time!
What?!
But that technique is for emergencies,
it will deplete your power!
We can't assure you'll ever come back
to Universe Patrol!
Nico...
It's fine, Kuromi.
Because now...
when I see someone suffering,
I want to come to their rescue!
Launching full-power mode!
You've made a brave decision, Nico.
Mom, Dad...
We'll join you.
Nico!
You better not give up, ya hear?
You're gonna be Universe Patrol, right?
Don't stop pushing towards your goals!
Now or ever, got it?!
Oh, Kuromi.
Your selfishness made me brave
enough to push forward.
I'll be an outsanding member
of Universe Patrol!
You better, Nico!
I'll be back!
October 31st
Kuromi's keyword!
"October 31st!"
Next one's the season finale!
Don't stop now!