The villainess is a role in a tragedy work:
a character born into villainy,
fated to punishment.
But I'm gonna show that
Count Baku who's boss,
and save this world's me!
Have you finished cleaning?
All done!
It's empty!!
I made the room sparkling clean!
Oh, and prepared your
takoyaki lunch!
Looks delish!
Oh no! Gotta test for poison.
Oh, I better clean the paintings too!
You're ripping them!!
Let's open up the windows!
You're smashing them!!
How about I open the doors too?
Oh my, so sorry!
That's enough!!
Cut it out!!
You two are twins...?
You don't want anymore, do ya?
Then promise you won't
pick on Kuromi no more!
I promise, Kuromi!
I apologize for everything!
That's Miss Kuromi!
Miss Kuromi!!
Welp, that's that!
Time to tap you
and go back to my own... world?
I cannot allow you to leave.
What?! But I saved your butt!
Maybe so, but your actions
were truly heinous!
She's right...
Don't listen to her!!
You taught me that I can change my fate.
So I must work harder as a villain!
#VILLAINIFYTHEWORLDProject
Huh?
Villainy is justice here!
I'm going to become a villainess queen!
S-Say what?!
Oh, Miss Kuromi!
I challenge you to see which one of us
is more fit to be this world's villainess queen!
Kuromi's keyword!
"Infinity tempest crossover!"
The heck?