Your Mom and Dad?
Are we finally gonna learn
who Nico is?
This Kuromi kidnapped my parents.
Wait, don't!
The reason I tagged along with you
was so I could ambush Dark Kuromi when the time came.
So it had nothing to do with getting me home?!
I was doing that too,
but this was my plan!
When did you plan that?!
Ugh, you're getting on my nerves.
Could you stop rambling about your home world?
Aah! Kuromi, stop her!
How? I can't see nothin' as a gate!
You stop her!
But I'm not supposed
to interfere with this world!
That's not true! You're just a fraidy-cat!
I am not!
If I'm going to become an upstanding
member of Universe Patrol, I must...!
Your Universe Patrol powers
will soon run out.
You will now switch
to your provisional state.
Now I run out of power?!
Oni...
Off to my brand new life I go!
Wait, don't go!
Give me back my parents!
Oh no! Kuromi's still behind!
I'm back to normal!
You alright, Nico?
Wait, huh?
Where'd you go?
Come out, now!
He abandoned me!!
I don't need to celebrate my birthday,
I just wanna see my friends!
One Year Later...
I guess I could see why anybody else
would feel awful here.
Nico!
Oh, Nico!
What's that?
I'm sure Nico is okay...
Who are they...?
Kuromi's keyword!
"Fluffy!"
This man seems to know Nico.