Ugh, ow-ow-ow...
What the heck just happened?
Baku! Guys!
Where'd you go?!
Eek! It's Kuromi!
You're back!!
Wait, it's just you, Collimo!
Why'd you shriek like that?!
Huh? You're not our Kuromi.
What do you mean?
Zom... zom...
Oh! Baku, Gureco! Hey, guys!
Zo...
Zombie!
Collimo?!
Zom...bie!
What the heck, guys!
Wh-What's happened to you?!
Zombies? You guys turned into zombies?
Ey, how's it goin'? Alright!
What's da matter, Kuromi?
Lookin' like you saw a ghost!
You need a refreshment!
Have some scallion cola!
Huh? Scallion cola?
Doesn't sound bad, actually.
'Sup, Kuromi! You look
as charmin' as ever! Alright!
Kuromi, girl, you're the life of the party! Alright!
Alright! Alright! Alright!
Now that hits!
Wait, forget that.
What's goin' on here?
You're gonna be a zombie, gurl!
Wait, I'm not getting out of this, am I?
Kuromi!
Over here!
A hot prince?
Kuromi's keyword!
"Zombie Kuromi."
Oh no, am I gonna become a zombie?!