Everything has sucked
for me since I was born.
Then they showed up.
Your presence is bad for this entire world!
I envied watching another me having
so much fun while I was suffering.
I have a worse life than anyone else,
so I have the right to take
the place of the me who's most happy.
Don't mess this up for me!
Are you kidding?
I can't just leave you be!
You see, it hit me when I met myself
across a bunch of different worlds.
Whether I'm a zombie or a villainess,
I'm always me—Kuromi!
You're always... you?
Hey, looks like we're in my mind! Alright!
Dark me, your feelings are most understood!
Do I know it.
But we make do!
Although I kinda took out
my birthday woes on my friends...
I think you gotta start by
celebrating yourself.
Huh?
Happy birthday, me!
Happy birthday!
Happy... birthday... me...
Welp, it's all in the past now.
Now what do I do...?
Hmm...
Have you finally calmed?
Dark Kuromi, you're under arrest!
What?!
Kuromi's keyword!
"Final technique!"
Nico, what are you gonna do?!