Why are My Melody and I
acting all chummy?!
Is she not your friend?
Of course not!
We're rivals!
Oh? When did you get over here?
M-M-M-My Melody?!
Wanna play?
What do you think?!
I ain't your world's Kuro—hey!
Hey! You can't tell strangers
about the extended universe!
I-I mean, sure, let's play!
Wait up, little butterfly!
Wait up!
There!
Bah-hah.
Kuromi, say "ahh!"
Bah...
Kuromi?
Is it yummy?
Mhm!
Could this be kawaii chaos?
I'm actually having a lot of fun.
But I really should get home soon.
I made everyone really mad.
Wanna play with me?
Baw, if I have to, sure.
You're such a sweetheart, Kuromi.
I... am?
I don't think so.
I'm only running for myself,
not for anyone else.
It's all so selfish.
But I have lots more fun when you're here!
Huh?
I guess... I should go home!
Okay!
I'm on my way, guys.
Universe!
Kuromi's keyword!
"Final boss."
Oh no! I gotta get back quick!