Watch with
the lights on and
at a distance
from the screen!
Watch TV with the lights on and
at a distance from the screen!
My name's Burton.
I'm a ninja and an ace scientist at
the WNA, the World Ninja Association.
My research is on—
Hang on a minute, it's not
"your" research, it's our research!
Right, yeah. Sorry, Berecca.
Our team is tasked with the research
and development of Ninja-Gum.
What's Ninja-Gum, you ask?
It's an unbelievable item that draws
out a ninja's hidden strengths
granting them all sorts of
amazing new abilities!
And we finally perfected it!
But right as we did...
Our colleague Ron turned his sword on us!
To make things worse, the gum
turned the two of us into kids!
Look at us!
Now what are we supposed to do?
Maybe Baby, here we go! Something special just for us
Maybe Baby Lovin’ Beats Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, always makes my heart skip a beat
Maybe Baby
In this breathless city of the future
I invite you to take it all in
Accelerating at the speed of light
We'll change the world
Boomy Boomy Life
Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, here we go! Something special just for us
Maybe Baby Lovin’ Beats Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, always makes my heart skip a beat
Maybe Baby
Ugh, how are we ever going to undo this?
The super powers are great,
but why did we become children?
What a mess.
Huh? Wait!
What?
We turned into kids because of
special Ninja-Gum, right?
Yeah, I guess.
So maybe normal chewing gum
can reverse the effect!
Huh?
Yeah! Let's buy some!
How? We have no money.
Oh, yeah. I forgot.
Wow!
Hey! Were you hiding that?
No! It was just there!
Berecca, it must be destiny!
Maybe we can undo this!
I'll be back!
Sheesh.
Ready?
Yeah.
How is it?
Tastes good and normal.
Wonderful.
What happened to destiny?
Oh! What if...
Let's see.
Maybe a gum smoothie—
Bad idea.
You're right.
Let's be rational.
I see. They're children now.
And?
Oh, umm, it was just quite unexpected.
May I continue surveillance?
Do as you wish.
He knows too much.
Sir!
Take care of him.
Burton and Berecca too.
Yes, sir!
Bad news!
What is it?
The prototype was stolen.
Was it him?
Most likely.
Awaken, Young Van!
Nice!
Way to go, Van!
Ha! Piece of cake!
We can't lose with Van on our team!
Yeah! We better do our part too.
Let's practice more!
OK!
Hey, Mom.
Hm?
It's about Dad.
Huh? What about him?
Do you think he'd come to my next match?
I don't know. I haven't seen him in so long.
His job in trade keeps him busy traveling the world.
Right.
I just wish I could see him.
Will we ever live together again?
Van...
Thanks, that was delicious!
Dad?
Oh, no!
Watch out!
It was just a dream.
Right?
Van!
Huh? Oh!
Van, what's the deal?
Sorry.
You're acting strange.
I have a bad feeling.
I'll go find Dad!
I see.
The form of a child?
Yes!
We're actually adults. Is this a curse?
Berecca, didn’t you say to be rational?
This is unscientific!
So what? It's free.
It can't hurt to try.
This was definitely caused by Ninja—
Evil spirits have latched onto you!
Spirits?
Yes. Evil spirits. This is the work of evil spirits.
Huh? Evil spirits?
Uh-huh.
However, there is a way to break free
from their curse.
Take these jet-black precious stones.
Wear them until tomorrow and all will be well.
Here.
What is this? A marble?
It's not a marble!
Those miraculous stones steer the fate—
OK, uh-huh. Thank you.
Berecca, let's go.
Wait. Well?
Huh?
Umm...
The fee.
What? It says free!
For the stones.
Give this to your parents.
Huh?! It's a scam!
This is no scam!
Listen here. Those miraculous stones—
Then keep them!
I don't accept returns!
So it's a scam!
This is no scam!
Listen here. Those miraculous stones—
Then keep them!
I don't accept returns!
So it's a scam!
This is no scam!
Listen here. Those miraculous stones—
Then keep them!
I don't accept returns!
So it's a scam!
This is no—
Thanks, everyone!
Did you like it?
Is he not here?
It hasn't changed.
Oh? Ha, ha, nice job!
Here.
OK! Yes, that's it.
Here we go!
Dad...
I miss you.
Huh? What was that?
What?! No way!
Dad!
Van? Why are you here?!
Who is that guy?
A ninja?!
Van!
Help!
Van! Where are you?
Dad!
Van! Watch out!
Van, quick, you have to run.
Why? I can't leave you!
Quick. Save yourself.
But...
Is this fate?
Then we'll face our destiny together.
Gum?! At a time like this?
Not just gum. Ninja-Gum!
Ninja-Gum?
Yes. Eating it will awaken the power
of the Shinobi within you.
Power of the Shinobi?
Van, I'm a ninja.
You're a ninja?!
That's right. And you can be one too.
Use your power!
But I—whoa!
If I don't do something, we'll both...
Am I too late?
Could it be...?
Van!
Dad!
Good job. That's the power of the Shinobi.
Dad! Dad!
I want you to choose your own path.
Wh-Who are you?!
You must be Van.
What?
We'll talk later. We must save your father.
Really? So Dad will be OK?
Yes. He's still unconscious.
But he'll get better with some rest.
Dad! Isn't that great?
Van, we need to talk.
So Dad really is a ninja?
Yes. We wanted to tell you when you turned 12.
It was going to be up to you what to do next.
But I hoped you would...
Are you OK?
Thanks for helping!
Are you a friend of Dad's?
I'm Genryusai.
I'm from the World Ninja Association.
Like you, I have Shinobi blood.
World Ninja Association?
You can relax. We will protect Max.
Van.
Do you want answers
about your father and yourself?
Huh?
It's up to you.
Up to me?
Why was another ninja attacking Dad?
There are those who use the power of
the Shinobi for evil.
It was probably their doing.
So that was an evil ninja?
Come, let's go.
OK.
This is it.
What? This is...
"To descendants of the ninja bloodline...
I leave this record of our past."
Outcasts after the shogunate fell,
we ninjas fled overseas.
We ended up in a dry, vast wilderness.
Fending off vicious attacks from
strange weapons...
we mounted an iron beast that raced
over stone paths...
and headed west together.
We happened to find gold on the way.
With room to breathe, our long journey of escape...
turned into one of exploring strange new lands.
We met tribesmen who taught us...
how to integrate into the diverse culture.
Before we knew it, this was our home.
We sealed away our power of the Shinobi
to avoid conflict...
and hid the truth.
Until the power of the Shinobi is needed again...
each of us must decide how to use our own power.
It is up to you to protect the power
of the Shinobi and our bloodline.
Dad...
Dad has always been fighting against evil ninjas.
That's right.
I can be a ninja too.
I want to be a ninja like Dad!
I've decided!
Training to be a ninja is tough.
Are you sure you're ready?
I'm ready!
I'll become a great ninja like Dad and fight evil!
Flame Strike!
Jeez, sleeping in a place like this.
You'll catch a cold!
Ahh, thank goodness they caught her.
Yeah.
I'm telling you, those kids said they were in trouble.
Uh-huh. Keep walking.
You just don't learn.
She was a repeat offender scam artist.
Of course a fortune teller can't fix us.
Sorry for the strange idea.
It was a nice distraction.
Back to smoothies?
Forget that, we need money!
We're totally broke.
Sure are.
Oh, I know!
I have an idea!
You do? Is it something weird again?
No, this one will work!
I'm exhausted.
What is this?
Ninja-like
Ninja!
Nin! Sinking underground with the sun
(Showtime! Our time! Da-dan-dan!)
Now! We seek our men along the thread
(Looking bright! Through the night! Ba-ban-ban!)
Just like the heavy winds (whoo-whoo!)
Just like the calm, quiet woods (ring-ring!)
Like the aliens primed to invade (meep-meep!)
Getting shot down like a crush (bump-bump!)
You only live once
Every encounter has its parting
Our world may burn in war with itself
But the Shinobi Night will protect it
In a flash of the glittering moonlight
We hear blades clashing around us
Through flames, through earth, our lives
They keep going, keep repeating
Life of a ninja! (Nin!)
Ninpo strike, to this day we're
just scraping our way thorugh the war
Until a day comes we can achieve glory
Until I reach your heart on the other side
Nin nin nin!
All sold out
Thank you!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
Concentrate and
succeed!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
“Now I shall take my leave... in smoke!”
Next Episode
Hey! Van here!
Training to be a ninja like Dad is hard,
but I won't give up!
What?! Who is that?! I'm scared!
Next time on Ninjala,
"Lucy and the Mysterious Eye."
Lucy and the Mysterious Eye
Don't miss it!