Watch with
the lights on and
at a distance
from the screen!
Watch TV with the lights on and
at a distance from the screen!
After me and Berecca got turned
into kids by the Ninja-Gum,
we decided to join the WNA Academy.
There we met...
Van,
Lucy,
Emma,
Kappei,
and now Ron and Jane, too!
Wait, hang on a second!
Is that the same Ron that vanished
after he betrayed us?
No way, it can't be.
But if it is...
What are we gonna do?
Maybe Baby, here we go! Something special just for us
Maybe Baby Lovin’ Beats Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, always makes my heart skip a beat
Maybe Baby
In this breathless city of the future
I invite you to take it all in
Accelerating at the speed of light
We'll change the world
Boomy Boomy Life
Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, here we go! Something special just for us
Maybe Baby Lovin’ Beats Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, always makes my heart skip a beat
Maybe Baby
Presenting... Space Ninjas!
Cadets! Nighty-night...
A weird melon with a hat on...?
I bet it's a present from the kids!
Bwah! You're that creature
from the other day!
Hiyah!
That there's full of our
treasured Ninja-Gum! Give it back!
Gonna put up a fight? Foolish creature.
I acted as bait to save the kids last time,
but a little slime-ball like you
won't beat me now
when nothing's holding me back!
Everything's gone dark!
No way! You can use ninja tricks?
You little! Where'd you go!
You're not gonna beat me! Not today!
Rgh... You got the jump on me...
Intruder! Intruder! Halt! Stop right there!
Resistance is futile. Engage battle mode!
Intruder!
Intruder! Intruder! Intruder!
What?! Fine. I'm on my way.
My apologies. This was the situation
when we got in this morning.
Were the doors locked?
Of course.
But someone got them open.
A friend of that unknown creature?
We figured that was a possibility,
so we checked the security footage...
But someone deleted the video feed.
I'll send out the Oniwabanshu.
I want every hand available on this.
Yessir!
Is something amiss?
Mr. Chief...
My goodness, that strange lifeform!
I'm afraid it has escaped.
Pardon this...
Yes? And...?
Very well, then.
Now what?
An academy instructor was attacked
on campus last night
and we lost the Ninja-Gum left in their care.
Lost to whom?
For some reason, the security cameras
in the academy remained operational
and that unknown lifeform was
caught on camera.
Our aids are on it now.
We should hold an emergency meeting
to discuss our analysis of it
and devise a plan to
deal with it moving forward.
You'll want me to call on the other leaders, then?
If you would.
Bruce had a little accident and hit his head,
so he won't be in today.
Meaning...?
Today will be self-study.
Sweet!
That's no way to react to our
teacher being injured.
I'm worried.
You really care about that guy?
We might never get to hear
those amazing jokes of his again!
That's what you're worried about?!
Hmph...
They weren't amazing to begin with.
I don't know about his jokes,
but he should be back tomorrow.
Thank goodness.
Now please use this time
to actually do some studying.
Yes, ma'am.
If we can go anywhere,
I say we go to the hideout.
Was thinking the same thing.
What's the plan?
If we're really after the same thing,
it would make more sense
for us to work together.
If we're worried about efficiency,
we're better off on our own.
Come on.
Right.
So he thinks we're holding him back?
Seems like it.
If that's even how he really feels.
I guess there's no denying that
they're better ninjas, though.
We should get going, anyway.
Going where?
I want to soup up the
equipment at our hideout.
We're going shopping! Sounds fun!
Mind if we do it on your card?
Why...?
Whaddya wanna do?
We don't have any gum,
but we could still battle!
Yeah, count me in!
This is a neat sorta weapon.
It's not exactly a weapon.
It's a "shinai," we use it to practice.
Yeah? All right, how about
whoever lands the first hit wins?
'Kay!
Men!
Men! Men! Men!
Yeowch!
Hey! That's not fair, Van!
What isn't?
This is a shinai-only battle,
you can't just throw stuff at me.
I didn't do anything!
Playing dumb, huh?
Wait though, doesn't that
slime look kinda familiar?
Yeah, yeah, sure. Time for another go! Men!
Wagh! Wait!
What happened?
We've got company!
That's one of those things!
What's a Space Ninja doing here?
Wait, what?
Never seen anything like 'em before,
so they gotta be from outer space.
Name really says it all, huh? "Space Ninja."
Not really creative though, huh?
You gotta try harder.
Names are only good if
they're easy to understand.
I wish we had some Gum Weapons!
These shinai are all we need.
Let's double-team 'em!
You got it!
Huh?
Ninja-Gum?!
What are you doing with this?
Uh-oh! Why you...!
Wha?
Agh!
Shoot!
Yikes!
They just keep multiplying!
Ngh?! Over here!
Oh, no you don't!
Over there!
After analyzing the creature's
genetic code, chromosomes, and DNA
we found no match among
any other lifeforms on Earth.
We believe that proof enough
these creatures come from space.
Goodness...
They also exhibited strong reactions
to the ingredients in Ninja-Gum.
Given their actions within the
academy this morning,
we believe they are seeking
out our Ninja-Gum reserves.
Might we take that to mean it was
Ninja-Gum which drew them here?
We have no reason to believe otherwise.
Would that not also mean
if we hadn't mass produced the gum,
we wouldn't have this problem?
That's...
And perhaps those responsible for
its development should be held at fault?
How can we jump to such rash conclusions?
Ninja-Gum has been nothing
but a boon for the WNA.
With that I agree.
It is the plain and clear truth.
I much agree myself.
Plus, we can't undo what is done.
What's important are the
steps we take next.
Meaning...?
We must halt all use
and production of Ninja-Gum
and destroy all our current supply.
Perhaps doing so might spare Earth
from any future celestial visitors.
But that's...
Or, the WNA could take responsibility
and eliminate these creatures.
They're arrival here is the
result of our actions, after all.
Very well. Let us form an extermination squad.
I'd ask that you use only our
best ninjas to ensure our success.
Of course. The Oniwabanshu will
give this mission all it has.
That's reassuring.
Hang on, now.
If you've come out this far,
we oughta play!
There's four of you, now!
Is this payback for last time?
Guess that's enough for today.
Come on then, I'm right here.
Huh?
Hey! It's those green guys again!
They're here to see me. You stay outta this.
Fine, but this place is gonna
get awfully slimy if you fight here.
Oh. Eww. Don't want that.
Lucky us, they took off on their own!
Sure you're okay without any gum?
You can't get away from me!
Kept you waiting, huh?
They're faster than before!
But not as fast as me!
Ninja-Gum?
These things stole it?
Lucky us!
Emma!
Thank you!
Here goes!
They're tougher than last time!
Agh!
Shoot!
Emma!
Lucy!
Let me go!
That's how you wanna play?
Then take this!
That's all you got? How boring...
Lucy...
Understood. I'll let him know. Thank you.
It seems Emma and Lucy have
won back our missing you-know-what.
Wow, really? That's great news!
You-know-what, now?
Oh, well, uhh...
You-know-what. You-know-who.
Actually, pee-ew!
See, he's a comedic genius!
Seriously...?
Ninja-like
Ninja!
Nin! Sinking underground with the sun
(Showtime! Our time! Da-dan-dan!)
Now! We seek our men along the thread
(Looking bright! Through the night! Ba-ban-ban!)
Just like the heavy winds (whoo-whoo!)
Just like the calm, quiet woods (ring-ring!)
Like the aliens primed to invade (meep-meep!)
Getting shot down like a crush (bump-bump!)
You only live once
Every encounter has its parting
Our world may burn in war with itself
But the Shinobi Night will protect it
In a flash of the glittering moonlight
We hear blades clashing around us
Through flames, through earth, our lives
They keep going, keep repeating
Life of a ninja! (Nin!)
Ninpo strike, to this day we're
just scraping our way thorugh the war
Until a day comes we can achieve glory
Until I reach your heart on the other side
Nin nin nin!
All sold out
Thank you!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
Concentrate and
succeed!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
“Now I shall take my leave... in smoke!”
Burton's Gum Weapon Lessons
Hey, Gumchi! How's it hanging?
Gum-Gum!
Today we're taking a look at this
Gum Weapon here!
"Ninja Yo-Yo!"
Ninja Yo-Yo
This Gum Weapon is highly effective
at attacking from a distance.
Gum!
Its Gum Shoot, "Gum Balloon"
will chase after enemies.
And its special "Yo-Yo Leap"
can teleport you to where you throw it!
Ninja Yo-Yo
Gum-Gumchi!
Master this and you can
fight from a distance.
Now you're all ready
to score your own IPPON!
Gum!
Next Episode
It's finally time for our very first mission.
Better keep an eye on Lucy so
she doesn't go AWOL!
Definitely wanna find out more
about her crazy powers, too.
Next time on Ninjala,
"Ninja Duty."
Ninja Duty
Stay tuned!