Watch with
the lights on and
at a distance
from the screen!
Watch TV with the lights on and
at a distance from the screen!
Maybe Baby, here we go! Something special just for us
Maybe Baby Lovin’ Beats Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, always makes my heart skip a beat
Maybe Baby
In this breathless city of the future
I invite you to take it all in
Accelerating at the speed of light
We'll change the world
Boomy Boomy Life
Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, here we go! Something special just for us
Maybe Baby Lovin’ Beats Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, always makes my heart skip a beat
Maybe Baby
A long time ago, meteorites
fell upon a certain country.
Fire escape
Before long, people with special gifts emerged there.
Water escape
Art of hiding
Ninjas
And they were called ninjas.
In a lawless age, ninjas served feudal lords.
They undertook various missions
centered around intelligence.
But over time, as a new age arrived...
Ninjas were needed no longer.
Expelled, they crossed the sea and
were scattered all over the world.
It is now the present.
And some of those Ninjas' offspring
can be found today.
Ninja-Gum Perfected!
There you are.
Ms. Peggy, you waiting for someone?
Cut it. You've been making a ruckus every night.
Oh, no. Don't look so sour.
You do have such a beautiful smile.
Don't change the topic.
Smiles make you happy.
Start your day with a smile.
Have a nice day!
He keeps getting away...
Ms. Peggy was so upset.
I should bring her some pie.
Today's the day our experiment succeeds!
Right, guys?
Burton, what time did you...
Berecca, I know what you want to say.
But we're two hours behind schedule.
No time to waste.
We must perfect Ninja-Gum.
Let's get to work!
Hmm... It's been three years since
we started these experiments.
What number is it?
Experiment number 2502.
Thanks, Ron.
We keep setting our failure record.
Who knows when we'll finish?
You don't get it, do you.
Thomas Edison once said...
"I have not failed.
I've just found 10,000 ways that won't work."
...Wait.
You better not be telling me you're actually going to try 10,000 times!
Based on yesterday's error,
I'll put this and this.
We're all set.
Berecca.
Power on!
Lookin' good!
Burton.
Right.
Another failure.
But we learned one thing.
That taste is important.
Nobody's gonna chew something this awful.
Duh.
I compiled our error data.
Thanks, Ron.
He works out at 11 A.M. sharp,
always keeping his routine.
Let's take a break till Ron comes back.
What? A break? We just got started!
I haven't had breakfast, and I wanna analyze this.
Just in my head.
Oh, and potato chips, please.
This is how it goes.
Don't be uptight.
Research is not just working in labs.
People buzzing, and new products
in shop windows...
are all sources of
ideas found in town.
Whatever.
Three years' worth of data.
Oh?
This error...
That's when we ate the gum and...
I'm so sorry, you guys!
I keep screwing up...
I'm such a dumb and clumsy scientist...
I'm a burden to you guys!
Burton.
Berecca! What's up with your face?
Huh?
The trouble I caused you...
It must've turned you ugly!
I'm so sorry, Berecca!
This is how I look normally...
I forgot about that one.
And also...
The page corner's curled up!
There're crumbs all over!
Like that.
Meow!
And that.
But we've come this far step-by-step.
Three years.
Do you remember when Ron
first showed up?
Yeah?
Soon after the Ninja-Gum research started.
Who is it?
Are you the scientist sent from WNA?
I thought it was tomorrow.
He's our scientist!
Oh?
Being born a ninja offspring...
doesn't mean I can use
Ninjutsu like you do.
He seemed very
unapproachable at first.
Was it at our 1000th error?
We were quite discouraged.
"The most certain way to succeed is
always to try just one more time."
I'm set anytime.
Ron...
Even when WNA kept pressing us
about when it would be ready.
Leave WNA to me.
You two just focus on the research.
Without Ron our research
could've been terminated.
Yeah.
Here you are.
Fibonacci Sequence!
Huh?
This shell.
It's my favorite formula,
the most beautiful one!
Fibonacci Sequence is...
a series of added numbers.
You add the last two numbers.
In recurrence formula...
where n is greater than 1.
In figures...
Once he starts this,
he keeps on going.
Place a square of side two...
Wow! Ninjas are the best!
All right. I'm gonna try.
Ninpo, Flame Strike!
Kappei!
I'm so sorry!
Emma! Emma! Emma!
Let's pump it up!
Oh? Where is she?
Help me.
Watch out!
Whoops.
Amazing reflex.
Wanna play basketball?
Basketball? Heck yeah!
I'm John!
I'm Van!
Lucy, time for dinner!
Hi, Ron.
Perfect timing. We're about to begin our 2502nd...
I mean, our 2503rd experiment.
Thanks, Ron.
The error data you compiled taught me...
It's no use thinking.
Come on, guys.
Let's get going with our 2503rd failure.
Berecca.
Power on!
Huh?
Why did it stop?
Goro, are you OK?
Oh, dear. My goodness.
Hm? Where's his bell?
What's happening?
It's about to explode.
Guys! We did it!
Are you kidding me?
It's the same old gum.
Tastes great!
The flavor is all right.
But still, we failed again.
Uh, Burton?
I'm up here!
Huh?
Burton?
There you go! Whoopee!
What's this sensation? There!
Here I go!
Look at me! I can run on walls!
Yippee!
Yahoo!
Here we go.
This is so cool! Is it the effects of Ninja-Gum?
When ninja offspring chew on them,
it taps into our potential.
It draws out the power of the shinobi.
You told me about that, but dang, this is crazy!
I know, right?
Yippee!
Awesome!
That's it.
I totally got carried away.
Let me see something.
Huh?
What's up?
Whoa. Be careful!
Hey, cut it out!
Show me the true power of Ninja-Gum!
True power?
What? What's going on?
Burton!
What?
I've seen all that I need. Now, you die!
Burton!
Just as I expected from a descendant of Hanzo.
There you have it.
OK, Burton, you owe me an...
Hey!
Come on, explain.
A bomb!
Mom, they fell from the sky!
A bomb? Now that's just overkill.
Alright, Burton. Your turn.
Explain.
Explain what?
The Ninja-Gum turning into a weapon!
Surprising, wasn't it?
Burton!
I honestly had no idea!
A Ninja combined with the gum
unleashes shinobi power.
It produces powerful
weapons and Ninjutsu.
And it seems Ron knew about it.
Then WNA must too.
Are they gonna start a war?
Burton?
Have you gotten younger?!
Really? Maybe the gum has
esthetic effect.
I'm young too?!
Berecca, the gum turned us into children!
Understood. Continue surveillance.
The experiment was a failure after all.
Not necessarily.
Probably the side effects of the gum.
Listen, Berecca.
Thomas Edison once said...
"It's not failure..."
I get it, enough with the Edison shmuck.
We'll have to go back to the lab
and find a way to undo this.
Hopefully there is.
Is that right?
We will see some changes in our future.
It's cordoned.
No entry.
What's wrong?
It's empty...
Empty?
Ninja-like
Ninja!
Nin! Sinking underground with the sun
(Showtime! Our time! Da-dan-dan!)
Now! We seek our men along the thread
(Looking bright! Through the night! Ba-ban-ban!)
Just like the heavy winds (whoo-whoo!)
Just like the calm, quiet woods (ring-ring!)
Like the aliens primed to invade (meep-meep!)
Getting shot down like a crush (bump-bump!)
You only live once
Every encounter has its parting
Our world may burn in war with itself
But the Shinobi Night will protect it
In a flash of the glittering moonlight
We hear blades clashing around us
Through flames, through earth, our lives
They keep going, keep repeating
Life of a ninja! (Nin!)
Ninpo strike, to this day we're
just scraping our way thorugh the war
Until a day comes we can achieve glory
Until I reach your heart on the other side
Nin nin nin!
All sold out
Thank you!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
Concentrate and
succeed!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
“Now I shall take my leave... in smoke!”
Next Episode
Berecca, what do you think?
Y'know, about the Ninja-Gum turning us into kids?
Is it finally finished?
Berecca, wait up!
A Long Day for Burton and Berecca
Next on Ninjala,
"A Long Day for Burton and Berecca."
A Long Day for Burton and Berecca
Don't miss it!