Watch with
the lights on and
at a distance
from the screen!
Watch TV with the lights on and
at a distance from the screen!
My name's Burton.
Our completed version of Ninja Gum
left me and Berecca as kids,
and now we have ninjas after us
for some reason.
We had no other choice but
to hide away inside the WNA Academy.
And that's where we met...
Van,
Lucy,
Emma,
and Kappei.
No way!
They're mass producing Ninja-Gum?!
What's going on?
We really need to get
our grown-up bodies back!
And the best way to do that is with
some ultra-nutritious smoothies!
Ugh, could you quit playing around?!
Maybe Baby, here we go! Something special just for us
Maybe Baby Lovin’ Beats Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, always makes my heart skip a beat
Maybe Baby
In this breathless city of the future
I invite you to take it all in
Accelerating at the speed of light
We'll change the world
Boomy Boomy Life
Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, here we go! Something special just for us
Maybe Baby Lovin’ Beats Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, always makes my heart skip a beat
Maybe Baby
That's the WNA for you.
They've got some serious security.
I had a feeling this wasn't going to be easy.
Hope you're not about to give up on me.
Not after we've made it this far.
Still though...
Do we have to sneak in like this?
This is our best shot
now that we've got Ninja-Gum.
Using it outside class might be against the rules,
but sometimes rules need to be broken.
Now's our chance!
Go on, do your worst!
Coming right up!
Phew...
Wha?!
H-Hey!
Burton! Burton!
Ugh!
Why do you always have to be such a pain?
Sheesh, what am I going to do with you?
Do-or-Die — Infiltrating WNA HQ!
If the server rooms are underground,
why'd we have to start from the roof?
This is our quickest route in.
But bump into one of those fan blades
down here, and we're out for good.
The fans are supposed to stop
for 10 seconds of maintenance, right?
Yup. We gotta get down there
before they start back up.
Let's do this, Berecca.
Right.
They're way behind schedule.
Can we even still make it... Huh?
What?! Ahh!
Could you not?! Ahh!
We're done for!
Huh?
We're...safe?
It's almost time.
We've gotta get through
before they come back online.
We've got 10 whole seconds.
We'll be fine.
– Ack!
– Huh?
This is the only hall
that leads underground.
Here's where things get tough, huh?
Well actually, I think I know just
how we can slip in.
We good?
Yup. All clear.
Huh? What was that?
Huh? What the heck?
What are these doing out here?
Hrngh! Jeez!
These are heavier than they look!
Well? You find anything?
Looks like someone left these out.
People need to learn
to clean up after themselves.
Phew, that was close.
All right, the server room's just ahead.
Hmm?
A fire?
I swear it's on this floor somewhere...
Then why haven't we found it yet?
Ugh...
Wait, what?
Whoa!
The server room!
All our old records have been wiped.
So that's why...
It all makes sense now.
What about Ron's data?
Got it!
The Intelligence Division...?
Aced the entrance exams with flying colors,
and then joined the Oniwabanshu.
Should have known.
So if Ron stole our data on Ninja Gum, then...
It might have been under orders
from Allen, Director of Intelligence.
Huh? There's more...
It says, "Whereabouts currently unknown."
What's that supposed to mean?
No clue. Doesn't say why.
It's no good. Our research
is locked in top secret files.
There's something about Ninja-Gum that
someone really wants to keep secret.
It's a real reminder...
that we were researching some
seriously sketchy stuff.
Intruder alert! Intruder alert!
All hands report to the lower level!
Shoot! Did they spot us?
Oh, Goro!
– What?
– What are you doing here?
S-So by intruder, did they mean...?
They went this way!
Let's get back inside!
Search every nook and cranny!
Think they went in here?
Master Genryusai!
Do forgive the poor feline.
Seems he ran off and tripped the alarm.
Really? But...
Sorry for all the trouble!
What the heck is going on here?
Not like I know!
Sneaking into headquarters
takes a certain kind of crazy.
Now tell me, who are you two?
Ever since you first joined the academy,
there's been something
strangely off about you both.
And now I find you here like this.
Well, we were out for a stroll
and got lost, see?
And before we knew it,
we were here...I guess?
Is that so?
Now, tell me what you were looking up.
Now now, settle down.
Well, that would explain things.
Ninja-Gum has its side effects then, does it?
It's perfectly safe for kids though,
and the way it draws out the power
of the Shinobi sure is something, right?
Seriously, Burton?!
However, it seems someone is trying
to make use of that very power.
Allen, you mean.
You think he's using the gum to
toughen up these kids for something?
I can't say what it is he's after,
but he's working to secure control
of the WNA for sure.
Even Luke, our chief, has his hands full with him.
So there's more to the story...
It might look like any old power grab,
but something just doesn't sit right.
Master Genryusai, what are you
going to do with the two of us?
Are we going to be expelled?
No, you're going to stick around.
Huh?
Allen is out for you both.
But not even he can lay a hand on
our students here so easily.
I want you to think, now.
Say you get your old bodies back. What then?
Do you spend the rest of your lives
with targets on your back?
If you truly wish for your old lives back,
you'll need to purge this
wicked scourge from WNA.
And I for one think it wise
for you to remain as you are now,
and work together with me.
Morning, recruits!
Today, we're gonna pair you up in
different one-on-one Ninjala battles.
Sweet, sounds fun!
Every opponent is different,
and so is every battle.
This practice will make you
all more versatile.
These battles will be solos.
But make sure your scores aren't "so low."
Uh...
I don't get it.
One-on-one means we're fighting solo
and not on teams, right?
It was supposed to be a joke about
"solo" sounding like "so low."
Ooh, now I get it!
Make sense. Good ear, Berecca!
I'm impressed!
Oh come on, it was nothing.
No, that was seriously cool!
You've got brains, Berecca!
You think?
So? Made up your mind?
About last night?
I'm still thinking.
You are?
I'm pretty sure we should do exactly
what Master Genryusai said
and stick around here
till the moment's right.
Aww, man!
That's enough. Next up!
All right! Time for some fun!
Sure, the academy might be safe,
but as long as Allen's sitting
near the top, he'll keep coming for us.
Burton! Hurry up already!
Sheesh, I really don't have time
to play around like this.
Let's make this quick!
You're kidding!
Piece of cake!
Next! Let's keep up the pace!
I think it's time to give this a whirl.
I was just caught off guard last round.
These are just a bunch of kids.
As long as I don't hold back...
That's enough for today!
You're all free to go.
They sure got you good.
I made up my mind.
Huh?
I'll play along with Master Genryusai.
Today I learned the hard way
my ninja skills aren't up to par.
If I can't even beat a bunch of kids,
then I don't stand a chance against
the Oniwabanshu, grown-up body or not.
My best shot is to train hard
while I've got the body to do so.
I like that mentality.
Wonderful. Just the answer I hoped for.
From here on, we three are a team.
Yes, Master!
Huh, there's a fireworks festival
in Eagle City today?
Wonder if I can see it from here?
Huh? What do we have here?
We've got a hit!
"I eagerly await the day you lead the WNA."
"You have my utmost support."
Well that doesn't sound nice, hmm?
To think these two were in cahoots.
Huh?
Does this mean...?
There must be some mistake.
I'm sure I didn't have
any dates planned for today.
You've snooped too deep, Jane.
I'll take that as a compliment.
What?!
Is this what you're after?
Hand it over!
Do I look like the sort of girl
who does as she's told?
Ron!
Trying to play the hero with
a flashy entrance like that?
If only...
Wonderful...
These go off all night long, you know.
This is my favorite day of the summer every year.
We have firework festivals back in Oedo, too.
It's awesome. You can get shaved ice
and yakisoba and stuff, too.
You got that Bon-odori dance, right?
Always wanted to give it a try!
Komerika's President Harold?
Yup. I've got a secret message
he sent to Allen.
So the Oniwabanshu are after you
because they found out?
Seems so.
But why are they after you?
Beats me...
Really, now?
What's the matter?
It's too quiet.
We probably lost them.
They're the Oniwabanshu.
They won't give up that—
Did they lead us here?
Huh? Why would they bring us here?
They wouldn't...!
Wouldn't what?
Mission complete.
Excellent.
Make sure you overwrite their data.
Hmph.
Ninja-like
Ninja!
Nin! Sinking underground with the sun
(Showtime! Our time! Da-dan-dan!)
Now! We seek our men along the thread
(Looking bright! Through the night! Ba-ban-ban!)
Just like the heavy winds (whoo-whoo!)
Just like the calm, quiet woods (ring-ring!)
Like the aliens primed to invade (meep-meep!)
Getting shot down like a crush (bump-bump!)
You only live once
Every encounter has its parting
Our world may burn in war with itself
But the Shinobi Night will protect it
In a flash of the glittering moonlight
We hear blades clashing around us
Through flames, through earth, our lives
They keep going, keep repeating
Life of a ninja! (Nin!)
Ninpo strike, to this day we're
just scraping our way thorugh the war
Until a day comes we can achieve glory
Until I reach your heart on the other side
Nin nin nin!
All sold out
Thank you!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
Concentrate and
succeed!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
“Now I shall take my leave... in smoke!”
Burton's Gum Weapon Lessons
Hey, Gumchi! How's it hanging?
Gum-Gum!
Today we're taking a look at this
Gum Weapon here!
The Trick Ball here looks
just like a basketball!
Trick Ball
Gum-mm-gum!
It's a yo-yo-type weapon
perfect for ranged attacks.
Gum-Gum-Gum!
Trick Ball
And if you use its special move
Beyond the Gum,
you can transform and
neutralize your opponent!
Gum-Gum-Gum!
Now you're all ready
to score your own IPPON!
Gum!
Next Episode
Stealthy plans? Busted. Battles?
Busted up. Is Burton good for anything?
Everyone's headed off for break.
Me? I'm gonna sleep through it!
Next time on Ninjala,
"Emma and Lucy's Fun-Sized Adventure."
Emma and Lucy's Fun-Sized Adventure
Oh, to be young again!