Watch with
the lights on and
at a distance
from the screen!
Watch TV with the lights on and
at a distance from the screen!
Maybe Baby, here we go! Something special just for us
Maybe Baby Lovin’ Beats Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, always makes my heart skip a beat
Maybe Baby
In this breathless city of the future
I invite you to take it all in
Accelerating at the speed of light
We'll change the world
Boomy Boomy Life
Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, here we go! Something special just for us
Maybe Baby Lovin’ Beats Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, always makes my heart skip a beat
Maybe Baby
We are facing
unprecedented circumstances.
These extra-terrestrial lifeforms
and their Ninja-Gum-focused attacks
leave not only the WNA,
but the academy and
its students in danger.
Indeed.
Director Alan, what is the status of
our extermination squad?
Well, now.
To think we'd see this team...
Seemed fitting given the situation.
They're the very best the WNA has.
I doubt any would disagree.
They'll lead the squads,
each of which will be dispatched
to areas with reported
sightings of these lifeforms.
No objections here.
The situation is safe in their hands.
Find and eliminate your targets.
That's an order!
Yessir!
We are counting on you.
Ninja Duty
As Shinobi, our duty is to fulfill our missions.
This won't be like our usual classes.
This is an important mission given
to you all directly by the WNA.
One which can only be handled
by ninjas like ourselves.
A true ninja mission.
And one just for us...
Ever since the WNA was founded,
in fact, even long before that,
the ninjas of the world have carried out
their missions for the greater good.
To become great ninjas yourselves,
you will need to do the same.
This is so cool!
We're gonna be real-deal ninjas!
I can do this, you'll see, Dad!
Your very first ninja mission is...
Is...?
A recon mission.
Recon?
There are growing sightings of these
seemingly extra-terrestrial creatures.
You have been tasked with gathering
intel and drawing them out.
How?
These creatures appear to be drawn
towards Ninja-Gum.
Ah, and since we've all been trained to use it...
We're going to be the bait.
Wait, really?
That's so lame!
If I find any,
I'm gonna beat 'em to a pulp!
There's no need to go looking for a fight.
Huh?
The extermination squad was
put together to handle that.
Exactly.
The extermination squad
is en route as we speak.
We'll drop in ahead of them
to scout the area.
If you encounter the creatures,
you're to retreat immediately.
Leave them to the extermination squad.
Rest assured, you won't be in danger.
Hey Van, let's see which one of us
can find a Space Ninja fastest!
You're on!
What's this about “Space Ninjas?”
Those extraterrestrials you mentioned.
That's what we call 'em.
Hmm, Space Ninjas, huh?
Let's go with that!
Sure we don't need a second opinion?
It's straightforward enough,
what's the problem?
A trekker out exploring this cave
reported seeing floating lights
deep inside recently.
What sort of lights?
Your job today is to find that out.
Roger!
Keep your wits about you in there!
Huh?
Hey, there.
Who's this guy?
Beats me.
This is Chris.
He's another teacher assigned
to our mission today.
Nice to meet you all.
Wow, we have another teacher, now?
He seems pretty nice.
Hey, teach! What's your best Ninjutsu?
What's your favorite food?
How old are you?
Settle down now, one at a time.
I feel replaced already...
We'll be splitting up into teams today.
Team Bruce.
Team Chris.
And Team Amy.
Teams Bruce and Chris will be our recon teams.
We'll split up and head through the caves.
Team Amy will be in charge of communications
and remain outside the cave
relaying orders to the other teams.
How are we supposed to do that?
With this here.
This device here is called a MakiPhone.
You'll be using these whenever
your out on ninja missions.
It can do video calls, give you GPS data,
send texts, perform calculations,
keep track of your health...
Wow, this will come in handy.
So Lucy, about the other day...
Huh?
Y'know, when those
Space Ninjas attacked us.
You seemed sorta different.
Wasn't sure if I should be worried.
That's just how I always am.
You sure?
Haven't gone all out like that
for a while, though!
It was pretty cool!
But don't overdo it, 'kay?
Wha...?
What's wrong?
What? No, nothing.
Hmm?
You're our comms team, huh?
We'll be counting on you.
Leave it to us!
Just keep a cool head
and everything will be fine.
Ready, recruits?
Operation Space Ninja Recon
is now underway!
Ease up now,
no need to be frozen with fear.
Keep your wits about you, though.
Hey! Space Ninjas!
Come out and show yourselves!
Oh, Lucy.
Why do I feel like I'm not getting
the respect a teacher deserves...?
All right, listen up.
Huh?
Wanna hear a tip on how to stay
on your toes on these missions?
What sort of tip?
Tell us! Tell us!
The trick is, no matter
what trouble comes your way,
you need to remain calm and collected.
H-Hey! Gimme that light back!
Agh! Lucy, where'd you go?!
Argh! I can't see a thing!
Bruce!
Did you see that?
Cut that out.
Leave the poor guy alone.
That was, uhh, just me
pretending to be afraid! Yeah!
I needed to see how
you would handle the situation.
Huh?!
What's the matter?
Nothing, I guess.
All right, back to work, then!
'Kay!
We should be near the location
where those lights were reported.
Berecca, can you pull up our map?
Sure, just a sec.
These extra-terrestrial lifeforms...
“Space Ninjas,” as you call them, right?
If we suppose they're trying
to remain out of sight...
Then they're probably hiding
somewhere along this route.
Exactly.
Where are you stinkin' Space Ninjas?!
Here?
Or here?
Maybe here!
No, here!
I'll find 'em first!
Nuh-uh, I will!
Come on, you two...
Don't forget, if we do
stumble on any Space Ninjas,
we're to retreat to safety immediately.
Yessir!
Come on, we're headed up there next.
Whoa!
Look at that!
Whoa-ho-ho!
That was awesome!
Ninja-Gum might draw those things out,
but that doesn't mean you can't
use it when necessary!
For this?
This is nothing!
See ya at the top!
I'll be there first!
Phew...
That was close.
Boys...
This is no game. One wrong move
can cost your life on these missions.
Or worse, your rash behavior
can put your friends in danger.
Understood...
But, if you work on these mistakes,
one day you will save many lives.
Perhaps even the entire world.
Chris!
You're our leader for life!
Gimme a break.
What is it?
Nothing to report?
Nothing on our end.
Nothing at all?
Huh?
Not right now, at least.
I hope I'm just being overly cautious.
Well, that was weird.
What?
Nothing, you just seemed really concerned there.
It never hurts to be too prepared.
Huh?
Right, yes... Copy that.
The extermination squad will
be here soon. No trouble so far.
Huh?!
The Shadow Ninjas!
You outcast ninja wannabes.
You dare raise your blades to us again?
All right, now listen up!
The most important thing on
these missions is cooperation!
We really have our hands full with you!
Sorry...
Finally...
Do you think that's...?
Bruce!
It's dangerous to go any further.
Wait here for the extermination squad.
Lucy!
Stop! You have orders!
Jane! Follow us!
Seriously? Sheesh...
You've spotted the Space Ninjas?
What?!
Sounds like Lucy is trying to engage.
I'm sorry, what?!
Huh?
The extermination squad is
caught battling Shadow Ninjas.
That's the situation.
Gah, of course the Space Ninjas
had to be on their side.
I bet Lucy was planning this from the get-go.
– Look out!
– Agh!
That was close!
You okay over there?
We're fine!
We'll get out of here ourselves.
You two head off to help Team Bruce!
There's no time to waste!
You got it!
Was it a good idea to send them off?
Yup.
Oh, right. Better contact Burton and...
Wait, what...?
Looking for this, are you?
Huh?
What?!
Chris...?!
Lucy, get back here!
Come down and face me!
Welcome to your new grave!
What is this thing?
Never seen anything like it.
It's definitely a Space Ninja, though!
What's going on here?
I really hope I'm wrong, but maybe
they were the ones baiting us?
Fine by me.
Gah, no choice left but to fight, huh?
What's the meaning of this?
There's really no point in asking.
You're not getting out of here alive.
You caused that cave-in, didn't you?
Did you use explosives or something?
Like I said, there's no point asking.
Time to say goodbye.
Burton! Ron!
You okay, Berecca?
Yeah!
You're one of Alan's assassins, aren't you?
I knew something was off
when we shook hands.
Those were no teacher's hands,
they'd been honed for combat.
Could'a said something, you know!
I couldn't be sure.
Kappei and Van were with you, too.
Figured he wouldn't pull anything.
Your MakiPhone suddenly going
offline was the proof we needed.
According to Ron, at least!
You had no clue, did you?
Ron, you're quite the talented recruit.
It's hard to believe you're really a child.
Quit boring me with all these weak attacks!
Why'd they stop?
What's going on?
I'll take 'em all out!
You okay?!
That's more like it!
We had a bit of a mess
to clean before we got here!
What?!
No way!
These things are stronger than ever before.
The only way to explain it is...
So much for the great extermination
squad. I'll do this myself!
Lucy, stop!
Remember how we're supposed
to handle these missions?
Huh? Like I care.
Lucy.
Fine, fine. Stay calm and work together, was it?
Yes!
Bruce, I have an idea.
Huh?
They're stronger than we thought.
Do you have a moment?
Hmm?
Now's your chance!
It got away!
Get back here!
Wait, Lucy!
The area up ahead is too dangerous.
We can't follow them in
any further than this.
We'll pursue them from here.
One of those orange balls got away, huh.
Because someone slipped up.
Hrngh!
Get ready, Space Ninjas!
'Cause here we come!
The fight's over already.
What?! Ugh...
Something up?
These Space Ninjas behaved
much differently than before.
Still seemed like wimps to me.
The one commanding them was
clearly more intelligent.
Hmm?
Those moves are familiar...
There you are! Is everyone all right?
Are you hurt?
Uhh, well...
Amy! Great timing.
I've just been called away for
an urgent mission I need to be off to.
Farewell!
What? Wait, Chris!
Burton, Ron, I know we were in
an emergency situation,
but I cannot excuse you for
abandoning your assigned posts.
Sorry...
I'm glad you're unharmed, though.
I can't just tell them Chris was after us...
Nice work, recruits.
It got hectic, but you pulled through.
This is only the first of many
difficult ninja missions, however.
So don't relax and vegetate!
Or you'll wind up as vegetation!
You don't need to be that mad.
I'm not happy about this either.
My cover as a teacher is blown.
I sort of liked it, you know.
Acting as this “Chris.”
Your disguises never fail to impress.
I did confirm one thing today, however.
And that would be?
That boy in the academy is
the very same Ron.
Is that so?
Ninja-like
Ninja!
Nin! Sinking underground with the sun
(Showtime! Our time! Da-dan-dan!)
Now! We seek our men along the thread
(Looking bright! Through the night! Ba-ban-ban!)
Just like the heavy winds (whoo-whoo!)
Just like the calm, quiet woods (ring-ring!)
Like the aliens primed to invade (meep-meep!)
Getting shot down like a crush (bump-bump!)
You only live once
Every encounter has its parting
Our world may burn in war with itself
But the Shinobi Night will protect it
In a flash of the glittering moonlight
We hear blades clashing around us
Through flames, through earth, our lives
They keep going, keep repeating
Life of a ninja! (Nin!)
Ninpo strike, to this day we're
just scraping our way thorugh the war
Until a day comes we can achieve glory
Until I reach your heart on the other side
Nin nin nin!
All sold out
Thank you!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
Concentrate and
succeed!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
“Now I shall take my leave... in smoke!”
Burton's Gum Weapon Lessons
Hey, Gumchi! How's it hanging?
M'chi-chi!
Today we're taking a look at this
Gum Weapon here!
Scrap Saber
The katana-type Scrap Saber!
Gum-mm-Gum!
It's an extra-long weapon made from
a bunch of road signs.
You can attack with a
wide reach with this weapon.
Scrap Saber
Plus, it can draw your foes in
so they don't slip away from you.
Wherever you go is
a Dead End for your foes!
Gum!
Now you're all ready
to score your own IPPON!
Gum!
Next Episode
Our teacher Chris was an assassin?
Can't judge a book by its cover, huh.
We'll have to keep our wits
about us next time.
Wait, Ron and Jane are gone?
Next time on Ninjala,
“Ron and Jane's Infiltration Mission.”
Ron and Jane's Infiltration Mission
You can't miss this one!