Watch with
the lights on and
at a distance
from the screen!
Watch TV with the lights on and
at a distance from the screen!
After me and Berecca got turned
into kids by the Ninja-Gum,
we decided to join the WNA Academy.
There we met...
Van,
Lucy,
Emma,
Kappei,
and now Ron and Jane, too!
Wait, hang on a second!
Is that the same Ron that vanished
after he betrayed us?
No way, it can't be.
But if it is...
What are we gonna do?
Maybe Baby, here we go! Something special just for us
Maybe Baby Lovin’ Beats Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, always makes my heart skip a beat
Maybe Baby
In this breathless city of the future
I invite you to take it all in
Accelerating at the speed of light
We'll change the world
Boomy Boomy Life
Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, here we go! Something special just for us
Maybe Baby Lovin’ Beats Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, always makes my heart skip a beat
Maybe Baby
Careful out there.
Good luck!
Seriously?
They just left us here...
Hellish Survival Mission
Let's recap your mission, Team Coyote.
This is your first outdoor training.
Proceed with caution.
"Team Coyote?"
The name is a tradition
for this survival mission.
You'll drop down on the starting point
and will need to make your way
back to the academy.
By ourselves...?
Do we get any Ninja-Gum?
No gum.
Amy's Team Jaguar will also work on
their own to reach their goal.
We have something "special" prepared
for whoever loses!
Special how?!
Great...
Sounds fun to me!
We're almost at the drop point.
Seems like a good point
to drop this conversation.
Mhmm...
Ugh...
I guess the Academy is that way.
Ridiculously far away, though.
I'm kinda excited.
Don't go keeling over halfway there.
Same goes for you.
Hey now, let's play nice.
Yeah, yeah.
You'll wind up hurt out in the wild
if you aren't careful.
You sure know your stuff.
Are you sure we're even the same age?
You both just don't act your age.
Lucy could teach you a lesson...huh?
What are you doing?
Going down.
I just want to get out of here.
What's her deal?
See ya down there!
Hmph.
Wait up, Kappei!
Ninpo, Rock Climbing!
Horse around and you'll wind up hurt!
We'll be fine.
What's the big idea?!
It wasn't on purpose!
Grr, see? Huh?
Tough playing mom, huh?
I'd rather be the older sister here...
Definitely not a fan of places like this.
It's hard to tell what sort of trouble awaits.
You think?
You don't find being out in the
wilderness makes you feel truly alive?
I think I kinda like it.
Specially with cuties
like this around!
Really?
See?
We should pick a leader.
What for?
It's the law of the wild.
If we don't all work as a group
we could get lost out here.
Owww...
I vote for Burton, then.
Me?
Him?
He might not seem dependable,
but he's got a sixth sense for danger
and how to avoid it.
He's quick to run away, then?
If you wanna put it badly...
Sorry. I'm fine following you, too.
There you have it, leader.
Uhh...huh...
Why'd you go and offer me up as leader?
Would you rather we let Ron lead?
That's probably just what he wants.
You think he'll come after us
now that we're outside the academy?
Do we have any reason
to think otherwise?
Guess not.
– Eek!
– Whoa!
Give us some orders, leader.
– Hrrrgh!
– Ngggh!
Still a long ways to go!
Take it slow or you'll regret it!
You heard her. Slow down.
You first!
No, you!
No, you!!
I'm... beat...
I-It's water!
Water! Water!
Wait, you can't just drink up
any puddle of water!
That's what our Ninja Straws are for!
Huh?
Hmm?
What are you two doing?
Fishing with our Ninja Rods.
Not gettin' any bites, though.
Gramps always said you'll never
catch anything if you aren't patient.
The key to fishing is to keep
your mind clear and serene.
"Seer and queen...?"
"Keep calm and flat as a mirrors surface,
and keep your mind clear as the water itself."
Sounds like the essence of
ninjutsu itself.
Indeed.
Indeed...
Clear and serene. Clear and serene...
You have fun, then.
C'mon already you stinkin' fish!
Couldn't even last a minute, huh?
Wagh!
W-Whoa!
Here comes a biggun!
Talk about steep.
Guess there's no way but up, though.
I'll climb up and scout things out.
It's too dangerous to go up together.
Why?
If we got attacked here, we'd all be wiped out.
What? But this is just training, right?
If you're a real ninja,
you always need to be prepared.
Ron's really something.
Dependable as a grownup, really.
What about me?
Even younger than you look, I guess?
Berecca, is that a good thing...?
Definitely not.
I secured the rope up here.
Climb up one at a time.
Ron...
If he cuts this rope...
No way!
Wha?!
Thought I was done for...
Does this mean...?
This fish I caught is de-lish!
I dunno, I bet mine's better!
Oh, yeah?!
Come on now, they're both delish.
How's yours, Lucy?
Say, leader?
Wha?
Are these really edible?
They could taste a little better, but...
Don't worry, I found them in here.
"Jungle citrus." Doesn't taste great,
but it's full of vitamins.
Hmm...
Hey Ron, why don't you join us here?
It's safer to stay spread out.
Because you never know
who might attack?
Exactly.
Not much we can do if the attacker
is one of us though, eh?
Berecca, drop it.
Someone cut that rope with a blade.
Were they after me, or...?
Wow!
You're really good!
I've been practicing
ever since I was a kid.
"Ever since?"
Err, I mean, since I was really little.
Back then it was really popular.
There was this TV show about a high
school girl who fought evil with one.
I don't remember any show like that.
My gramps was pretty good with a yo-yo.
He'd be all woosh! Then zoom! And bam!
Your grandfather is
Master Genryusai's brother, right?
Yup! He's part of a long line
that protects Iga Village.
The one where ninja come from?
I wanna go there someday with my dad...
I'll take you all there!
Bet Gramps would love it.
Sweet!
Lucy, do you... Huh?
What are you—
Up for some ghost stories?
Ghost stories?
Camping's all about scary
stories around the fire!
Hang on, now!
I got something even better
for camping!
Ta-da!
Marshmallows?
I snuck these in.
Nicely done.
On Christmas my family always
roasts them by the fireplace
as we tell spooky stories.
So, who's going first?
Guess I'll start.
This was back when I was eighteen...
Eighteen?
Summer vacation when I was eight.
I was asleep in my room
when I heard a sound from the hall...
Creak. Creak.
These were no human footsteps.
Without a doubt, it was...
definitely a grey alien!
The only scary part was your face.
Look at this place.
Makes me miss spending my days
with my experiments.
Can't say I hate this excitement.
Are you serious?
Just a bit.
Now that I think about it,
things weren't so peaceful back then.
We just never noticed.
The professor...
Your father, Sean, supposedly lost his
life in a research accident, but...
I wonder...
Wonder what?
He was with his partner, right?
With Leonard, I think he said.
I kind of want to talk to him.
To hear about what happened.
I heard he passed away.
He was hospitalized, but didn't last.
Yeah, huh...
You don't think it was
an accident, then?
Can't say.
Nothing surprises me anymore, though.
Mommy... Daddy...
The old man stared at me and said...
"Van! That's no cookie! That's clay!"
Uh-huh. Next!
Back in my village there was
a house were strange things happened.
Lights left on for days.
Items going missing day by day.
And then there was the dark shadow
in the bedroom...
A shadow that slowly turned...
And it turned out to be a ghost!
There was once a campsite by a lake...
One which people said any who camp there
would never return again.
And that summer, a group of
new victims paid a visit...
"It's only an urban legend!" one said,
before being the first among them to vanish.
But wait, he came back,
only now with a chainsaw...
Brum-brum-brum-brrr!
"You'll never escape! Never!"
"I've got you!!"
This was the tale of camp death.
And there's someone behind you now...
That scared, huh?
No! Behind you!
Behind me?
Come on.
Trying to scare me with
the oldest trick in the book?
Gum...
Gum... Gum!!
Gum-Gum-Gum-Gum-Gum-Gua!
What's gotten into you, Gumchi?
I've been expecting you, Hanzo.
Hattori Hanzo...
More dreams about my ancestors, huh?
Ron?
What's he doing?
Who's there?!
I wanted to ask you about earlier.
Are you the one who cut...
Don't move!
What?!
The Oniwabanshu...
So they're after you.
Me?
Get 'em!
Ron!
Never thought I'd have you
covering my back.
That's definitely my line!
Here!
Th-Thanks.
What's going on?
Ron's coffee's pretty great!
Want a cup?
What's gotten into all of you?
Where's Lucy?
She was gone when I woke up.
Really not a team player, huh?
Things are tough for girls her age.
Quit dillydallying, Kappei.
Says the guy who just woke up.
Who was so afraid of ghosts.
Wha?! So were you!
Ghosts don't exist. Only kappa!
Nah, kappa are definitely fake.
They're real! I've seen 'em!
Doubt it!
They're real!
Maybe Ron's right.
Better not get these kids involved.
Is something up between Ron and Burton?
What makes you think that?
I mean, just look at them.
Guess that's true.
It's so hot!
Lucy?
Thought you took off without us.
What's her deal?
Like I said, just at that age.
We made it!
We win!
Welcome back.
We lost...
Now we're in for it...
I can't take it!
There's nothing "special" about this!
Hey, now! I want silence!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
Nin! Sinking underground with the sun
(Showtime! Our time! Da-dan-dan!)
Now! We seek our men along the thread
(Looking bright! Through the night! Ba-ban-ban!)
Just like the heavy winds (whoo-whoo!)
Just like the calm, quiet woods (ring-ring!)
Like the aliens primed to invade (meep-meep!)
Getting shot down like a crush (bump-bump!)
You only live once
Every encounter has its parting
Our world may burn in war with itself
But the Shinobi Night will protect it
In a flash of the glittering moonlight
We hear blades clashing around us
Through flames, through earth, our lives
They keep going, keep repeating
Life of a ninja! (Nin!)
Ninpo strike, to this day we're
just scraping our way thorugh the war
Until a day comes we can achieve glory
Until I reach your heart on the other side
Nin nin nin!
All sold out
Thank you!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
Concentrate and
succeed!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
“Now I shall take my leave... in smoke!”
Burton's Gum Weapon Lessons
Hey, Gumchi! How's it hanging?
M'chi-chi!
Today we're taking a look at this
Gum Weapon here!
Pop Eye
"Pop Eye!" Can't miss those eyes and teeth!
Gummm...!
It shoots a straight Gum Laser
that taps targets in a Gum Bind.
Pop Eye
Gummm!
And its Gum Ninjutsu
"Baiting Shark" is ultra powerful!
When someone gets close enough to
the trap, a big shark will pop out!
Chomp...chi!
Now you're all ready
to score your own IPPON!
Gum!
Next Episode
How does Lucy come up with
such scary stories?
And now we're training in
a ghost town?!
There aren't really ghosts, right?
Right?! Please say no!
Next time on Ninjala,
"Hide and Seek with the Unknown."
Hide and Seek with the Unknown
Th-Th-They're really real!