Watch with
the lights on and
at a distance
from the screen!
Watch TV with the lights on and
at a distance from the screen!
Maybe Baby, here we go! Something special just for us
Maybe Baby Lovin’ Beats Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, always makes my heart skip a beat
Maybe Baby
In this breathless city of the future
I invite you to take it all in
Accelerating at the speed of light
We'll change the world
Boomy Boomy Life
Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, here we go! Something special just for us
Maybe Baby Lovin’ Beats Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, always makes my heart skip a beat
Maybe Baby
That oughta be the train for the WNA Academy.
I hope you're ready for this!
Why would they target such young children?
I sense these lot are up to no good.
You let them get away?
WNA Academy – Let the Battles Begin!
Greetings, aspiring young entrants.
I am the academy's principal.
Seems like we're as good as in!
Let's not waste any time and see who among you
has true ninja potential.
Wait, what?!
Uh-oh, wasn't expecting that...
Those of you lacking such potential
will be asked to leave us immediately.
Those eyes of yours are the
striking image of a ninja.
You are free to enter.
This could be bad.
If he finds out who we really are...
We're not gonna get anywhere
fussing around out here.
You are...free to enter.
No, wait one moment.
You are ninjas, that much I'm certain.
But where are you two from?
Huh?! Uhh...
Th-That-a-ways!
Oh? And which way might that be?
Those two will be no problem.
Master Genryusai!
It seems clear to me that
the two are both true ninja indeed.
Yes, but...
Or perhaps...
you wish to claim old age clouds my gaze?
No master, I would never.
You are free to enter.
Thank you!
That was close!
So that was the real Master Genryusai.
Gathering biometric data.
Please don't let this call up our old files...
Nutritional levels are...perfect!
No way!
Those smoothies really did the trick!
Oh, I'll give you my fingerprints!
Be more gentle!
The name's Kappei! That's Kappei, 'kay?
Unable to retrieve voice pattern.
Please refrain from screaming.
Ugh, is there anything worse
than getting weighed in public?
Please tell me I've lost some weight.
Wow, I'm light as a feather!
Or not, since I'm a kid now...
Old gramps said there'd be some
other old guy to look out for.
Now where is he?
Gumchi, Gumchi!
Hey! I told you to settle down in there!
Wait, gramps?
Heya, gramps!
Hrm? Well I'll be. Kappei!
You're sure a long way from home.
Wow, he wasn't kidding!
You look exactly like ol' Genunsai!
Twins tend to work that way.
I wouldn't know the difference if
it weren't for your weird hat.
Gumchi, Gumchi!
So there's that Gumchi I've heard so much about.
Genunsai has told me all about you.
Gumchi!
Come, I'll look after them now.
That should do it.
Master Genryusai!
Well, well! I see you've made it, too.
I'm here to learn all you will teach me.
You'll face truly demanding training,
will you cut it, Van?
Yessir!
Your name's Cuttit Van?
No, you dolt, it's just Van.
Oh, guess that makes sense.
Who are you?
The name's Kappei! Nice to meetcha.
So uhh...what was your name again?
V... Vomit Man!
It's just Van! Got it?
Ah, right, right.
You new to the ninja "macadamia," too?
It's the ninja "academy," you doofus!
Wanna say that to my face?!
That's enough, both of you!
We got through those checks somehow,
but something's definitely off.
Our data should be on record at headquarters.
True, but at least we're in.
Definitely beats sleeping on
rooftops and park benches.
You got a point...
Everyday is a day for sword practice 'round here!
Hey, you're that kid from earlier!
Well look at you, practicing your
lame little sword sport.
Oh yeah? Like you're one to talk,
running 'round with your little ball.
Kendo is way cooler!
What?! This ball's no toy, okay?
Or what, never heard of basketball?
You wanna mess?
Bring it on!
Time to see which one of us is best!
I'm not about to lose to you!
So uhh, how are we doing this?
Our Ninja-Gum research has to be
stored in headquarters somewhere.
I wish we could just waltz right in there.
But we're gonna need to
scope things out carefully.
Greetings, and congratulations on
your placement in the academy.
My name is Luke, and I am chief
of the World Ninja Association.
The academy is fortunate enough to
welcome 100 new entrants this time.
My hope is that you all grow to be
excellent ninjas yourselves
and use your powers to aid humanity
in drawing closer to peace.
Now then, we will start off with a
display of what talents you bring.
It's time to test your mettle
in a Ninjala battle.
"Ninjala battle?"
Allow me to explain!
In these battles you will use
gum weapons and combat one another.
Here are your weapons!
What?
What is this?
But this... It can't be!
How'd they get it here?
This is Ninja-Gum!
It is indeed.
Chew on that and the power of the Shinobi
that slumbers inside you will awaken!
For real?
Oooh...
So this here's gonna turn me into the
ninja I've always wanted to be?!
Is it even safe for kids to chew?
You okay?
Oh... It's great!
Can't beat that taste, right?
It took a lot of hard work to—
Now's no time to gloat!
Wait, what is this?
Huh?
I feel all pepped up!
Check out what I can do!
Looks like there aren't any side effects.
How are we supposed to fight
like this, though?
Hah! How 'bout I show ya?
Like this!
That's so cool!
You lookin' for a fight?
That kid already knows how to use it?!
Yes! Follow the boy's lead and use
your Gum Weapons!
Okay!
We just gotta blow 'em up ourselves, yeah?
Wow! That's so cool!
Oooh, now this looks fun.
Seems like we won't have time
to stand around.
Alright, now's my turn!
Could you be any lamer?
Jeez, it's hard to watch the lot of you.
What's his deal?
Listen up. You gotta think about the physics of it.
If you want to blow a bubble,
you need to seal your tongue tight in
gum so no air leaks out.
Phys-wha...?
What are you talking about?
Basically, you gotta use your tongue
like you're making a silly face,
and that should seal it off
so you can blow a bubble.
I don't really get it,
but silly faces I can do.
Like this here!
You don't actually need to make
a dumb face, though!
Sweet! It worked!
It seems you're all ready.
Let's not forget good sportsmanship.
It's time for our Ninjala Battle
exhibition match! Ready? Go!
Here goes!
Booyah!
Guess it's time for a little fun!
I've got your back covered.
I'm counting on you!
That you, Jane?
Those gum weapons sure are something.
I never knew that's what you
were working on.
Didn't realize there was
anything you didn't know.
Did you really think I'd hacked
into every last secret database?
It's them!
Come on, gimme your worst!
Hah! Hiyah!
Whoa, outta my way!
Seriously?
What happened to watching my back?
You're busy spacing out,
but I'm coming over to play!
Wow, not even scared? I'm impressed!
Nice one!
I'll show you what all my
sword training has been for!
Bring it on!
Hiyah! Hiyah! Hiyah!
So our swordsman Kappei is up against
our aerial combatant Van, hmm?
This should be interesting.
You're never gonna get me!
There's my opening!
Oh, yeah! You see that?
Oof... Shoot...
Gumchi?
If we keep treating these kids
like any normal brats,
we're not gonna last long here.
Talking to yourself, are we?
You're starting to sound
like some old lady.
Old...?
Did you just call me old?!
Jane, does anything seem off lately?
Such as?
No, never mind.
Take that!
This is getting fun.
It's hard to believe they're using
Ninja-Gum for the first time.
Well! That young girl sure
seems to have a knack for defense.
She may well be of help to her allies.
You've left your back wide open!
Take this!
Hiyah!
Time to finish you off!
What's the matter? Give up already?
I've already seen right through your attack!
What?!
I'll stop this blade...
with my bare hands!
Practice makes perfect, young Kappei...
Wh-What the heck are you?
Gumchi!
An unidentified life form, huh?
This is quite the discovery.
Gumchi!
Hey, wait!
That'll show you! I'm stronger than you think.
Where'd that thing run off to?
Hmm? Oh! There's a cafeteria here.
Yeowch!
This is for that last one!
That'll teach ya!
You'll pay for that, you little...!
Those two are going to be quite
the headache for us...
Take that... You...!
Quit twirling around like that and
just fight me already!
This ain't all I'm good at, y'know!
I feel dizzy just watching!
What's with all that spinning?
Your fight's over here!
Goodness!
That's enough!
Where the heck were you?
I worked my butt off down here, you know!
Sorry 'bout that.
That was excellent for your very first
Ninjala Battle.
We hope to see more from all of you!
Ninjala Battles, huh?
That was crazy fun.
Next time I'm going to
stomp out every last one of them.
Hey! Guess we'll say I won today, eh?
Yeah right, I definitely won out there.
Well, lemme tell you, I was only using
about half of my real strength.
And I was only using 20%!
Oh, yeah?!
You wanna mess?
Definitely going to be
feeling that tomorrow.
Unlike a certain someone
who was down after a single hit.
Sure, but I found something to make up for it.
Like what?
Berecca, over here!
Here's what I was talking about.
Whoa!
Whaddya think?
With this much stuff to work with,
I can fix up a new
smoothie attempt every day!
Uh, I'm pretty sure
we can't just use this stuff!
No need to worry.
You're still growing.
You should eat as much as you need.
This is awful!
I rather like it.
S-Seriously?
I'll take another.
Just as I'd expect from a great master.
A man of more refined taste!
If Burton and Berecca are
enrolled in the academy,
then that means they'll be
under constant surveillance.
That could actually work in my favor.
Ninja-like
Ninja!
Nin! Sinking underground with the sun
(Showtime! Our time! Da-dan-dan!)
Now! We seek our men along the thread
(Looking bright! Through the night! Ba-ban-ban!)
Just like the heavy winds (whoo-whoo!)
Just like the calm, quiet woods (ring-ring!)
Like the aliens primed to invade (meep-meep!)
Getting shot down like a crush (bump-bump!)
You only live once
Every encounter has its parting
Our world may burn in war with itself
But the Shinobi Night will protect it
In a flash of the glittering moonlight
We hear blades clashing around us
Through flames, through earth, our lives
They keep going, keep repeating
Life of a ninja! (Nin!)
Ninpo strike, to this day we're
just scraping our way thorugh the war
Until a day comes we can achieve glory
Until I reach your heart on the other side
Nin nin nin!
All sold out
Thank you!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
Concentrate and
succeed!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
“Now I shall take my leave... in smoke!”
Burton's Gum Weapon Lessons
Hey, Gumchi!
Today I'm gonna talk about Gum Weapons!
Gum, Gum!
Let's get started, then.
IPPON Katana
The IPPON Katana.
A katana-type weapon with
great mobility and rushing power.
Gum-mm!
Use the Gum Launcher to catch
far away opponents,
then use a Charging Slash
to strike right at them!
IPPON Katana
Gum, Gum!
Then there's the powerful Gum Ninjutsu.
With the Ninja Tornado you can
round up all your opponents at once!
Gum!
Now you're all ready
to score your own IPPON!
Gum!
Next Episode
We managed to sneak our way
into the academy,
but how are they already
mass-producing Ninja-Gum?
We don't have any time to waste.
I need to fix us up a smoothie
to turn us back into adults, fast!
Next time on Ninjala,
"Kappei of the Shinobi Village."
Kappei of the Shinobi Village
Don't miss it!