Watch with
the lights on and
at a distance
from the screen!
Watch TV with the lights on and
at a distance from the screen!
My name's Burton.
Our completed version of Ninja Gum
left me and Berecca as kids,
and now we have ninjas after us
for some reason.
We had no other choice but
to hide away inside the WNA Academy.
And that's where we met...
Van,
Lucy,
Emma,
and Kappei.
No way!
They're mass producing Ninja-Gum?!
What's going on?
We really need to get
our grown-up bodies back!
And the best way to do that is with
some ultra-nutritious smoothies!
Ugh, could you quit playing around?!
Maybe Baby, here we go! Something special just for us
Maybe Baby Lovin’ Beats Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, always makes my heart skip a beat
Maybe Baby
In this breathless city of the future
I invite you to take it all in
Accelerating at the speed of light
We'll change the world
Boomy Boomy Life
Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, here we go! Something special just for us
Maybe Baby Lovin’ Beats Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, always makes my heart skip a beat
Maybe Baby
Good morning! Time to wake!
Today is your long awaited day off.
Go on out and have some fun.
But remember! Use of Ninja-Gum
is forbidden outside the academy!
What am I gonna do
with a whole day off?
Maybe I should pay everyone a visit.
I guess I could visit Mom and Dad.
Or I could bust a move.
They're so far away, though...
Ugh...
Huh?
Are you going somewhere?
Yup.
Where?
Nowhere in particular.
Yeah...?
Hey.
What?
Nah, never mind.
'Kay.
Hey.
Huh?
Nah, nothing.
Emma and Lucy's Fun-Sized Adventure
Sure feels a lot healthier to be
on a more natural sort of schedule, huh?
It's unbelievable, really.
Who could have guessed
the key to being energized
was exercise, a full belly,
and a good night's rest?
How are you feeling?
I could use some more sleep.
Things have been non-stop since the
Ninja-Gum first turned us into kids.
I'm going to eat as much as I can
and head right back to bed.
Not a bad idea.
Huh?
Goro!
Wanna join me for a nap?
Napchi, napchi!
Hey, it's Gumchi!
Bertchi, Bertchi!
Huh? Are you trying to say my name?
Can you say Berecca, too?
Berechi, Berechi!
Glad you're here, there's a lot
I still wanna figure out about you...
But I guess it'd be rude to get
straight to running tests.
Whaddya say I treat you to a
tasty smoothie first?
Gum?!
Smoochi, smoochi!
All finished! Here you go.
Gulpchi!
Yuckchi!
You're kidding!
Could'a told you.
Oh, heya, Gumchi!
Dolchi!
Still can't say my name, huh? It's Kappei.
Sounds to me like he's calling you
a dolt, and I sure agree!
Oh, shut up.
What'cha up to with Gumchi here?
I whipped up one of my
special smoothies for him,
but I don't think he was much of a fan.
Yeah? Looks pretty good to me.
Fix me up one, too!
I wouldn't do that if I were you.
Mhmchi.
That just makes me
want to try it even more.
Here you are!
Blrgh! Delish...!
Bet you couldn't handle
one of these, Kappei.
I want one, too!
Here!
Blrgh!
Don't see what the problem is!
I'll take another!
Me too!
Wow, I never thought my
smoothies would be in such high demand!
Gumchi might not like it, but maybe
he just has different taste buds.
Those two are just trying to
one up each other.
Emma!
Warren?
Well? Enjoying life at the academy?
It's all right.
Make any new friends?
Don't need any.
You're off today, right? Any plans?
Just dancing.
Don't forget that—
That I can't use Ninja-Gum
outside the academy?
Yeah.
Just so you know...
I'm done with the whole
vigilante hero thing for now.
Probably for the best.
Is that what you were here to tell me?
N-No, of course not!
It's no big deal, y'know.
Isn't there anything fun
to do around here?
Huh?
Kappei!
Van!
What are you doing here?
What's it to ya?
Whatever. Later.
Uh-huh.
Why do you keep following me?
I should ask you the same!
I was headed this way already!
So was I!
Hmph!
Quit acting like some little kid!
You first!
Idiots.
Go boost it for me.
It's the pickup truck.
Bring it on over to the warehouse by the
electronic store when you're done.
Whaddya need it for?
I lifted the key to the warehouse.
We'll slip in and get the goods,
then you guys will wheel it all out.
Gotcha.
That'll do it for today.
Thanks for dropping by to watch.
Guess I'll just head back,
this is so boring.
Huh?
Well, well! Maybe things are about
to get interesting after all!
Come out and play!
Bwah?! What the heck?!
The jig's up, baddies!
Huh?
What do you want, punk?
You should'a brought that lost key
back to its rightful owner.
Using it to steal just makes
you a bunch of thugs.
You that vigilante hero
that went viral?
What if I am?
Yeowch!
Grr, where's that truck I asked for?!
No word from 'em.
There they are!
Are we done already?
Wha?!
Huh?
Oh my!
What are you doing here?
Was about to ask you the same!
Don't tell me you're with these thugs.
Yeah, right!
They're some real baddies.
Oh, yeah?
Then maybe it's time for some fun!
Stay real still.
That was cool!
What's with these kids?
Come on, gimme your best shot.
The fun and games are over!
Warren?!
Emma...
Huh?
Wouldn't want this lady to get hurt, eh?
Not like I care.
Wait!
You might not know her,
but she's with the academy.
Really?
What "academy?"
You're better off not asking.
Who asked you, hostage lady?
I'm sorry I lied about
giving this hero thing up.
No, no, it's fine.
Sorry for getting in the way.
Enough chit-chat,
let's take care of these guys!
Wait.
Please, not now.
What?!
Hmph. Fine, I guess.
You okay?
Yup. This is nothing.
Sorry for dragging you into all of this.
No biggie. I was bored anyway.
You're not afraid after
getting captured by this thugs?
Why would I be? This is fun!
True, nothing feels too scary
now that I have you here.
I have a name, you know. It's Lucy.
Right. And I'm Emma.
I'd heard people talk about a
vigilante hero around here
but was it you the whole time, Emma?
Yeah.
Why do you do this stuff, though?
No reason. I just...
Just?
I just wanna put a smile
on people's faces. Simple as that.
Yeah? That's pretty cool.
Smiling faces, huh...
You monster!
Lucy?
You ready to get going?
Going where?
Where else?
To go beat up some baddies!
That was amazing!
That was nothing.
You could do that all along?
Yup. But if I did...
we'd miss out on all the fun, right?
Are you hurt?
I'm fine. And I heard you two talking.
I was thinking the same thing as Lucy.
Guns or not, they never had
the upper hand on me.
I just wanted to see how
you two handled the situation.
Really?
Why?
Because I have faith in you!
Hmm...
Never thought we'd sell off all that
loot and the stolen pickup to boot.
With the right connections
you can pawn off just about anything.
What do we do about those kids?
They could ID us.
No choice but to finish 'em off.
How do you plan on doing that?
How'd you get out?
You can't keep me down
with anything like this.
I'll spare you a lecture,
just turn yourselves in.
That way you won't need to get hurt.
Big talk, little lady.
Y-Yo...
Dude...
You didn't say they could fight...
I warned you.
Nice moves.
You two can handle the rest.
You could still help out, y'know.
Enough of this.
I'll have all the fun myself!
Two of us will make it faster.
Grr...
Listen up! They might look small
but give 'em your worst!
Aight!
These are no ordinary lil' brats!
C'mon already!
What is this, a staring contest?
Get 'em!
Gotcha!
You little...!
Eat this!
Hiyah!
Rrgh...
You're mine!
You gotta be kidding me...
You're all that's left.
And I'm barely getting started!
If you're the leader,
I bet that means you're strong.
Hah! Sure, I'm the strongest,
and the fastest off the scene!
What?!
No way their little legs can keep up.
Is this as fast as you can go?
You'd be the slowest one
at the academy.
Seriously, what the heck
is this "academy?"
Here goes!
Say...
Hmm?
This seems like a great opportunity.
Why don't you two become friends?
You mean me and...
me should be...
friends?
Mhmm! The academy's full of people from
different countries and backgrounds.
And you all got tossed into life
together with a bunch of strangers.
You're surrounded by people, but feel
all alone with no one you know.
I know I'd feel exhausted in your shoes.
But I bet things would be much easier
if you at least had a friend.
I think I'd rather duke it out
with Emma instead.
You what?
Fine by me.
I was thinking the same thing.
What?! What's gotten into you both?
Whaaa?
Bwah!
I was just kidding.
Same. Just joking.
We'll have plenty of time to
fight it out at the academy.
Let's save all the fun for then.
Sure. I won't go easy on you, though.
Sounds good to me!
Can't wait!
Phew...
How long are you gonna keep doing this?
How long are you?
Can you just stop already?
Let's stop together, then.
Fine. At the same time.
Three, two, one...
No, wait! Do we stop at zero?
Duh.
And you really will?
Yup.
For really real?
Really really real!
Dunno if I buy it.
Figures... But why the heck not?!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
Nin! Sinking underground with the sun
(Showtime! Our time! Da-dan-dan!)
Now! We seek our men along the thread
(Looking bright! Through the night! Ba-ban-ban!)
Just like the heavy winds (whoo-whoo!)
Just like the calm, quiet woods (ring-ring!)
Like the aliens primed to invade (meep-meep!)
Getting shot down like a crush (bump-bump!)
You only live once
Every encounter has its parting
Our world may burn in war with itself
But the Shinobi Night will protect it
In a flash of the glittering moonlight
We hear blades clashing around us
Through flames, through earth, our lives
They keep going, keep repeating
Life of a ninja! (Nin!)
Ninpo strike, to this day we're
just scraping our way thorugh the war
Until a day comes we can achieve glory
Until I reach your heart on the other side
Nin nin nin!
All sold out
Thank you!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
Concentrate and
succeed!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
“Now I shall take my leave... in smoke!”
Burton's Gum Weapon Lessons
Hey, Gumchi! How's it hanging?
Gum-Gum!
Today we're taking a look at this
Gum Weapon here!
Matsuri Board
It's the board-type Matsuri Board.
'Mchi-mchi!
With Sweet Ride, you can cruise around on
this gum weapon like a real skateboard.
It's crazy fast, too!
Gum-mm!
Matsuri Board
Roll right up to your opponent
and pull off some stylish tricks
before you hit them with a
super powerful kick!
I've never been good
on a skateboard, though...
Gum!
Now you're all ready
to score your own IPPON!
Gum!
Next Episode
Even the bad guys around here
are too wimpy to be any fun.
Huh? We're getting new classmates?
They better learn not to mess with me!
Next time on Ninjala,
"New Friends? – Ron & Jane."
New Friends? — Ron & Jane
Now who's ready to play?