Watch with
the lights on and
at a distance
from the screen!
Watch TV with the lights on and
at a distance from the screen!
Maybe Baby, here we go! Something special just for us
Maybe Baby Lovin’ Beats Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, always makes my heart skip a beat
Maybe Baby
In this breathless city of the future
I invite you to take it all in
Accelerating at the speed of light
We'll change the world
Boomy Boomy Life
Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, here we go! Something special just for us
Maybe Baby Lovin’ Beats Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, always makes my heart skip a beat
Maybe Baby
Rain, oh rain, hits the sea.
The fish and me.
Hmm?
Whuzzat, now?
Strange lifeforms have been sighted
on the shores of Aubett Village.
An old man was attacked
just two days ago.
The WNA ordered us to investigate under
the assumption it was by Space Ninjas.
We are to investigate under the
guise of a school field trip.
So basically, we're the decoys again?
The extermination squad will
handle all the dangerous work!
Hard to get excited 'bout that.
How can you not see?
As a teacher I want nothing more
than to keep my students safe!
Yeah, yeah.
So, who's this?
Sorry for the reduction of an introduction.
Amy is away on vacation,
so instead today we have...
Ms. Daisy.
That's me.
Sea of Oranje
You'll be working two to a team
as a safety precaution.
Regroup here in five hours
and report your findings.
He said we shouldn't, but I'm
thinking we battle if we find 'em.
Count me in.
Show yourselves, Space Ninjas!
Have you seen any floating lights?
– You really wanna know?
– We do!
Three days ago, after docking
my boat here at the pier,
staring off at nothin' in particular,
I spotted orbs of light headed for me.
I thought, "What in the world?"
As I got a better look, I saw these
big ol' jack-o-lanterns spinning round!
We found ourselves a storyteller.
I had to take my umbrella out on my walk.
Can you even imagine seven
straight days of rain?
Everything was all soggy and awful.
And then?
My eyes caught this
strange thing off by the cape.
A wriggly, jelly body with a face on it.
Jiggling all around.
It was terrifying!
Whoa, personal space!
You mean the old man
who got spooked by ghosts?
Old fella's a bit goofy,
prolly just saw a fire lure.
There are old tales of people snatched up
by ghosts 'round here, though.
Have you noticed anything
else odd recently?
Well, there was that guy
out in the woods the other day.
All worn out, like a zombie.
But he took off once he got an eyeful of this!
That's probably not what we're after.
What's the situation with
Burton and Berecca?
Our plan is in motion.
Luke seems to be up to something,
so I want all loose ends tied up.
We have Tsukikage on the matter.
Do we, now?
You think those Space Ninjas
are really out here?
We'll sure look like idiots
if this turns out to be nothing.
What's got your attention?
Our new teacher, Daisy.
After what happened with Chris,
I'm not sure how I feel...
Think she's another one of Allen's assassins?
Sure seems pretty sketch.
Let's make a run for it!
Huh? Uhh...
Burton!
You won't get away from me this time,
you stinky Space Ninjas!
Did we lose her?
Seems like.
Seriously, how long do
we have to live like this?
Think this is the place?
Where the old man was attacked?
Someone's over there...
No, don't!
I'm glad we made it in time!
You can't go throwing your life away like that.
I just felt a bit dizzy...
My name's Burton.
And I'm Berecca.
We're here on a school trip.
I'm Eliza.
Nice to meet you.
You should be more careful.
There have been accidents here lately.
You mean my grandpa...
Wha?
After my parents were lost at sea,
Grandpa raised me all alone.
And now he's...
How is he fairing?
He's still unconscious.
People say the Sea Terror stole his soul away.
"Sea Terror?"
It's an old legend around here.
When the moon shines bright,
the Sea Terror comes to feast on souls.
Sounds rather un-scientific to me.
Especially considering that
mind-body dualism has now been—
– Burton!
If we pray to the Sea Terror,
we can call on it to give back
a lost soul in exchange for our own.
That's just some superstition.
Truth is, it's just—
You should stay at
your grandfather's side.
Bet he'd be worried if
you weren't there when he came to.
Maybe you're right.
We'll walk you back.
Thank you. But I can make it alone.
I feel almost responsible for this.
How so?
If the Space Ninjas did this,
that makes it our fault, too.
How do you figure?
They only showed up
in response to Ninja-Gum.
Ninja-Gum that we created.
Which means we're the ones who
brought them here in the first place.
Maybe you're right.
Huh?
Wonder if this is Eliza's.
Should we bring it to her?
Hellooo!
Is anybody home?
I'm sure this is the place.
– Hey.
– Hi!
Who are you?
Gregory?
You can call me Greg.
You're quite the artist, Greg.
Because I paint every day.
It's a nice hobby.
I've been in the village a week now.
Doctor said the air would do me good.
But there's nothing to do here but draw.
Here to recuperate, then?
Yeah...
Mind showing us your paintings?
Sure.
Are these...?!
I saw them floating over there.
Thought they were balloons or something.
That matches the reports on the Space Ninjas!
"Space Ninjas?"
Oh, uhh, never mind that.
Watch that mouth!
– Hey.
– Huh?
There's a girl over there.
Huh?
I don't see anyone.
I saw her earlier, too.
A girl in a white dress who looked
about ready to stumble off the cliff.
He means Eliza!
I hope she hasn't got any bad ideas...
I'm going to check on her.
Is something wrong?
Could be.
But say, could you tell me more
about those floating lights?
The first showed up from over there.
Okay, then.
Emma! Lucy!
You were almost done for there!
Was it the Space Ninjas?
I dunno, it all happened so fast.
Greg!
Sorry for running off like that.
You made the right move!
Glad you're okay.
No sign of anyone.
Guess they got away.
It's time to head back.
I should go, too.
I'll walk you.
Thanks.
Eliza!
Burton?
Ron! Jane!
Did you see Eliza?
Who?
So, unfortunately we didn't find any
Space Ninjas out there,
but we did uncover bits and pieces of intel.
There are multiple reports of strange
lights around here this past week.
Tomorrow we get back to it.
For now, there's plenty of curry to go around.
Bet you'll be s-curry-ing for seconds!
The granddaughter of the man
who was attacked, huh?
Where could she have gone?
I bet she's fine. She's from around here.
Can't help feel she's suffering
because of the WNA.
Give me a break.
Huh?
If this town's legends are true,
that means the Space Ninjas might
have been here since long ago.
We just never knew till now.
Welcome back, Berecca.
Hey, how's Greg?
I told I'm I'd walk him home, but...
Thanks, this is good enough, you know.
But...
I'm not that much of a scaredy-cat.
All right.
Berecca.
Huh?
Thanks for saving me.
It made me really happy.
To know I had a friend.
Greg...
I'm starting to feel responsible, too.
He was almost in danger because of me.
That's exactly it.
Don't overthink this.
A ninja must focus on their mission.
Cast their feelings aside.
And...
And?
Your faces give away
everything you're thinking.
You should learn to be more suspicious.
What?!
Trust me, we are.
Eliza!
You came to see us?
I felt bad for not
thanking you for saving me.
Where did you go?
We dropped by your house
but nobody was home.
Sorry, I thought I should visit my
grandpa in the hospital like you said.
Here, you dropped this.
Oh, thank you!
I was looking all over.
So, uhh... You don't really believe
in that Sea Terror stuff, right?
I'd be happy to find it's just superstition.
Oh, it's getting late. I'd best be going.
I'll walk you.
No need. I know the way well,
and the moon is nice and bright tonight.
The Sea Terror, huh...
Berecca! Burton!
Greg!
What? You're headed home tomorrow?
The doctor said I'm in good enough
shape to go back, now.
That's good to hear!
Yeah, but we just became
friends and everything...
We'll meet again.
For sure.
Thanks.
I'm gonna head back. Sticking around
too long would just make me sad.
Friends, huh...
That kid's going to be
a great painter one day.
Should have asked for
a sketch or something.
Could be worth a fortune someday.
Art is worth more than the
price you can put on it.
"I want to thank you by painting your
portrait by the moonlit sea."
"If it's no bother, please come by 8."
"It will be a beautiful portrait.
But come alone, please. In private."
What should I do?
What's up?
N-Nothing!
I don't mind the idea of being
a future star's model!
Someone pulled a joker!
I can see it in your face.
Ninjas need to perfect their poker face...
I know the way well,
and the moon is nice and bright tonight.
On nights when the moon shines bright
the Sea Terror will give back
a lost soul in exchange for our own.
Eliza!
What was that about?
Greg?
Maybe I'm too early?
Eliza! Don't!
A boomerang?!
Eliza! Run for it!
Burton!
Miss Daisy!
– Behind you!
– Huh?
Eliza?! Why?
That old man has no grandchildren.
What?
And he's quite well.
Intel is a ninja's strongest weapon.
Why have you gathered none?
Who ever that is, they lied to get close to you.
She's gone...
Here's some more unfortunate news.
There is no sick child here
undergoing treatment.
Berecca's in trouble!
They have us surrounded.
We were too careless!
Check out our big catch!
There's no time to call in
the extermination squad.
We need to handle this ourselves.
Bring it on, then!
I'm ready, too!
Figured me out, did you?
I'm here to turn you down.
Your paintings are nothing but fakes.
Came here a week ago, did you?
Sure have drawn lots of sunny pictures.
Weird, since it's been raining for a week.
Perhaps they needed some finishing touches.
Eliza?!
There's gotta be one giving out
orders 'round here somewhere!
Jane, these things are all yours!
Got it!
All were but phantoms in the moonlight...
Who are you?!
I sometimes ask myself the same.
Tsukikage.
I've heard of a member of the
Oniwabanshu by that name.
Eliza and Greg were
the same person all along.
Shoot, guess I'm busted!
Chris, too?!
What are these two to you?
They stopped!
Now's our chance!
Payback time!
He got away...
How did you know he was a fake?
No matter the disguise,
his eyes, nose, and mouth were the same.
Seeing them in succession was all it took.
I'm starved...
Seriously?!
We were real suckers, huh?
Guess we still got a lot to learn.
Are you okay?
Berecca...
Huh?
Leonard...?
Ninja-like
Ninja!
Nin! Sinking underground with the sun
(Showtime! Our time! Da-dan-dan!)
Now! We seek our men along the thread
(Looking bright! Through the night! Ba-ban-ban!)
Just like the heavy winds (whoo-whoo!)
Just like the calm, quiet woods (ring-ring!)
Like the aliens primed to invade (meep-meep!)
Getting shot down like a crush (bump-bump!)
You only live once
Every encounter has its parting
Our world may burn in war with itself
But the Shinobi Night will protect it
In a flash of the glittering moonlight
We hear blades clashing around us
Through flames, through earth, our lives
They keep going, keep repeating
Life of a ninja! (Nin!)
Ninpo strike, to this day we're
just scraping our way thorugh the war
Until a day comes we can achieve glory
Until I reach your heart on the other side
Nin nin nin!
All sold out
Thank you!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
Concentrate and
succeed!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
“Now I shall take my leave... in smoke!”
Burton's Gum Weapon Lessons
Hey, Gumchi! How's it hanging?
Gum-Gum!
Today we're taking a look at this
Gum Weapon here!
The ASAKUSA Wheel!
ASAKUSA Wheel
M'chi!
It stands out with its twin faces
on the left and right sides.
It's a yo-yo-type weapon
perfect for ranged attacks.
Gum!
And its Gum Ninjutsu,
Shinobi Beast, is super powerful.
ASAKUSA Wheel
With it you can transform
and use a powerful beast attack!
Awaychi!
Now you're all ready
to score your own IPPON!
Gum!
Next Episode
We've got a long way to go if
disguises like that can fool us.
Wait, is that man Leonard?
But, he and my father were both...
Next time on Ninjala,
"Leonard the Runaway."
Leonard the Runaway
You can't miss it!