Watch with
the lights on and
at a distance
from the screen!
Watch TV with the lights on and
at a distance from the screen!
My name's Burton.
I'm a ninja and an ace scientist at
the WNA, the World Ninja Association.
My research is on—
Hang on a minute, it's not
"your" research, it's our research!
Right, yeah. Sorry, Berecca.
Our team is tasked with the research
and development of Ninja-Gum.
What's Ninja-Gum, you ask?
It's an unbelievable item that draws
out a ninja's hidden strengths
granting them all sorts of
amazing new abilities!
And we finally perfected it!
But right as we did...
Our colleague Ron turned his sword on us!
To make things worse, the gum
turned the two of us into kids!
Look at us!
Now what are we supposed to do?
Maybe Baby, here we go! Something special just for us
Maybe Baby Lovin’ Beats Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, always makes my heart skip a beat
Maybe Baby
In this breathless city of the future
I invite you to take it all in
Accelerating at the speed of light
We'll change the world
Boomy Boomy Life
Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, here we go! Something special just for us
Maybe Baby Lovin’ Beats Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, always makes my heart skip a beat
Maybe Baby
Huh?
Agh!
What the heck is this thing?
Is it trying to talk?!
Grubchi, grubchi!
Lucy and the Mysterious Eye
Isn't this ice cream amazing?
I get why people are always lined up!
Definitely worth the wait.
I was a little scared, though.
About what?
A kid tried to cut in line, remember?
You really showed him what-for, Lucy.
Oh, that kid.
He's a real troublemaker from
the class next to ours, you know.
Aren't you afraid he might come for revenge?
Nope. He'll be in for a whooping if he tries!
You're so brave!
I'm still a bit worried, though…
Don't be! I'll look out for
you both if anything happens.
Thanks, Lucy!
You're the best!
Huh?
Agh!
Hey! I'm walkin' over here!
What's the big idea?!
Can it!
Ya gone and ruined my dude's threads.
Who do you think you are?
W-we're really sorry!
Please forgive us!
Come on now, sorry ain't gonna cut it.
You brats need to be taught a lesson.
It's for your own good.
Somebody help!
Leave them alone, you big jerk!
Wuzzat? Who you callin' a jerk, now?
How's about we make sure you can't
run that mouth any more?
I say we start with these two here.
Get up!
I said stop!
I banish you... into darkness!
Huh?
What's going on...?
Lucy...
Are you girls okay?
– Stop!
Stay away from us!
Why? What's wrong?
What was that? What are you?
I...
I don't know...
I wish I did, honest!
Y-You're a monster!
What? No!
I'm no monster, just me!
Wait!
But I... I...
That girl's a monster!
Run for your lives!
Did she really do all this?
Someone had better call the police.
Anyone get that on video?
Mommy, I'm scared!
Maybe my eye's just a little dry.
Bet we have eyedrops somewhere...
Did this eye do all that?
I banish you... into darkness!
What "darkness?" What was all that?
Lucy, you okay in there?
I'm fine!
Why is the door locked, then?
Are you sure you don't want to talk?
I said I'm fine!
Lucy!
Y-You're a monster!
Here you are.
Can I use your restroom?
Everything will be fine again by tomorrow.
I know it will...
It has to!
If you don't hurry down for breakfast
you're going to be late!
I'm not hungry.
Still wearing that eyepatch?
I thought you'd be better by now.
It's a fashion statement!
My favorite band wears them, okay?
Good morning!
Better not get too close.
Lucy.
What's the matter?
Are you being bullied?
Did you have a little fight with your friends?
My friends...
I wanna change schools.
What?
I wanna go to a different school!
Are you sure about this?
She says it's what she wants.
Maybe she's just being fussy, though.
Even still...
Wait, you don't think...
What if she has that power too?!
What power?
Surely you don't mean that Shinobi one?
Okay class, everyone say hi to
your new classmate, Lucy.
Hi, I'm Lucy.
Where did you transfer from?
Do you play any sports?
Where do you live?
I'll show you around the school!
We should sit together at lunch!
What's that eyepatch for?
Wow, you're a real artist, huh?
My name's Chloe. What's yours?
Lucy...
You just transferred here too, right?
Well, yeah, but...
We oughta be friends, then!
It'll be fun!
Lucy! Let's walk home together!
Okay.
C'mon!
So I ran back 'cause I forgot my purse, see?
But then I forgot my phone, too!
Sometimes I can hardly believe myself!
It's good to see a smile on her face again.
I take it she's finally enjoying herself.
Guess we won't be needing this after all.
Feast your eyes!
Behold the incredible skill of Samurai Girl! Have at!
Thank you!
Thanks kindly!
Thanks so much!
Much appreciated!
How was that?
We got quite the haul.
This was a great idea, Berecca!
It's the perfect way to get the money
we need as fast as we need it.
I could put on an even better show
if you'd let me use more gum powers.
We don't want to draw
more attention than we need.
Already done that, I'm afraid.
Think you kids could show me
some fancier tricks?
Wow! You'd give us that much?
I'd like a closer look at
that sword of yours, though.
Sure thing. Go on and show him, Berecca.
Oh, I'll show you all right.
A ninja?!
Why is he after us?
C'mon, Burton!
Right!
Keep up, Goro!
The Oniwabanshu?
What are they after me for?
So the Ninja Gum is ready and
being mass produced as we speak?
That's music to my ears.
Hrmm? You've got some bad news, too?
Mhm? Hmm...
Be sure you take 'em out.
Yes, yes.
I'm sure you've heard as much already.
But rest assured,
there is no need for concern.
The future appears bright indeed.
I was pretty worried when
I transferred here,
but I'm starting to like this place.
Why's that?
Isn't it obvious?
Because I have a new friend now!
I'm glad we met, Lucy!
You are?
You're my very best friend of all.
I am...?
Oh, you know what?
There's a great ice cream shop nearby.
Whaddya say we go
and get a scoop together?
You want to get ice cream...?
It's just two blocks from here.
Is something wrong?
Oh, no, I just have plans today...
That's too bad.
Maybe some other time, then!
Yeah, maybe.
Okay, well I'm off this way.
See you tomorrow!
Yeah, see you!
We're best friends...?
Chloe! Look out!
Chloe!
We oughta be friends!
You're my very best friend of all.
I... I'm...
I'm not a monster!
Chloe...
Do you think it's that monster again?
I'm...
I really am...
I...
I am a monster!
Lucy.
Want to come join us at the dinner table?
You both know already, don't you?
Whenever I try and help my friends...
The lampposts get all warped and creepy
and crash into the ground and stuff...
Am I...
some sort of monster?
You're nothing of the sort, Lucy. I promise.
You just have a special power most people don't.
What kind of power?
When I was your age I could
use the power of the Shinobi, too.
"Power of the Shinobi?"
Your mom here comes from
a long line of ninjas.
Ninjas?
Which means you have ninja blood, too.
We're thinking of sending you to
the World Ninja Association academy.
Why?! Because I'm a scary monster?!
No, no.
The academy is full of young kids
with powers just like yours.
It's not just me...?
When I was around your age,
I'd accidentally used my powers, too.
I had a really hard time.
You did?
Yup. So I spent my whole life
trying to hide my powers.
But sometimes,
you just have no choice
but to use them, right?
That's what happened today.
I stopped using my powers
even in times like those.
I did whatever I could to hide them.
Always looking away.
Swearing to never get involved
with anything or anyone.
But when I got older, I started to think
that maybe living like that
had cost me something precious.
So that's why we thought,
maybe if you joined the academy,
you might find some real friends.
"Real" friends?
Lucy, your mom and dad
love you so very, very much.
Even if the whole world flipped upside down,
we'd still love you.
We want you to live your life
just the way you are.
The way I am...?
"Just the way I am..."
But I don't even know the real me.
I used to be cheerful and energetic,
always saying what was on my mind.
I never even worried about making friends.
I didn't need to, I always had them.
If anyone ever wanted to be friends,
I was always ready to oblige.
It was always my choice.
That's what the real me was like.
I don't need to close my eyes
and ask the darkness under
my eyepatch to be my friend.
Still, if that dark power is no monster,
then what is it?
Is it a part of me? Or is it me entirely?
Cut it out!
Would you both shut up?
You wanna mess, twerp?
Could you even be any more lame?
Hey! You can't just knock someone
over like that! You made me look bad!
Oooh, the girl's got guts.
Well, well. Maybe we'll let you be
friends with us if you wanna join up.
You'll "let me?"
I... I...!
Get out of my way.
Oh yeah?!
If you lay a hand on me,
you're in for a world of hurt!
Maybe I'll let you be my friends if you ask nice!
What the heck?!
You some sorta monster?!
Sounds good to me!
We're sorry! We won't do it again!
Just let us go!
I'm just me!
Whoever wants to play, come get a piece!
Not again!
Let's all have some fun!
Now about our deal...
Ninja-like
Ninja!
Nin! Sinking underground with the sun
(Showtime! Our time! Da-dan-dan!)
Now! We seek our men along the thread
(Looking bright! Through the night! Ba-ban-ban!)
Just like the heavy winds (whoo-whoo!)
Just like the calm, quiet woods (ring-ring!)
Like the aliens primed to invade (meep-meep!)
Getting shot down like a crush (bump-bump!)
You only live once
Every encounter has its parting
Our world may burn in war with itself
But the Shinobi Night will protect it
In a flash of the glittering moonlight
We hear blades clashing around us
Through flames, through earth, our lives
They keep going, keep repeating
Life of a ninja! (Nin!)
Ninpo strike, to this day we're
just scraping our way thorugh the war
Until a day comes we can achieve glory
Until I reach your heart on the other side
Nin nin nin!
All sold out
Thank you!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
Concentrate and
succeed!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
“Now I shall take my leave... in smoke!”
Next Episode
The name's Lucy!
Get too close and you're in for it!
Check out our little dancer there.
I hope they're ready to play!
Next time on Ninjala,
"Ninja Dancer Emma."
Ninja Dancer Emma
Let's have some fun!