Watch with
the lights on and
at a distance
from the screen!
Watch TV with the lights on and
at a distance from the screen!
My name's Burton.
I'm a ninja and an ace scientist at
the WNA, the World Ninja Association.
My research is on—
Hang on a minute, it's not
"your" research, it's our research!
Right, yeah. Sorry, Berecca.
Our team is tasked with the research
and development of Ninja-Gum.
What's Ninja-Gum, you ask?
It's an unbelievable item that draws
out a ninja's hidden strengths
granting them all sorts of
amazing new abilities!
And we finally perfected it!
But right as we did...
Our colleague Ron turned his sword on us!
To make things worse, the gum
turned the two of us into kids!
Look at us!
Now what are we supposed to do?
Maybe Baby, here we go! Something special just for us
Maybe Baby Lovin’ Beats Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, always makes my heart skip a beat
Maybe Baby
In this breathless city of the future
I invite you to take it all in
Accelerating at the speed of light
We'll change the world
Boomy Boomy Life
Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, here we go! Something special just for us
Maybe Baby Lovin’ Beats Maybe Baby
Maybe Baby, always makes my heart skip a beat
Maybe Baby
Got the goods?
Yep.
Got my cash?
Who's there?!
You're gonna wish you hadn't seen that.
Today's not your lucky day.
Freeze!
The jig's up, baddies!
Who are you?!
A masked vigilante fought off
the crooks, seeking nothing in return.
According to the witness,
the fight played out like a dance.
Those moves...
Yes?
Oh! Mr. Chief!
Found us some promising
young talent, have you?
Yes sir.
No confirmation just yet, of course.
That's good news.
Not long now until the academy's
opening ceremony.
I'd like us to have as many young
ninja descendants as we can find.
I'll get right to work making contact.
Very well.
Ninja Dancer Emma
That whole incident took place
somewhere around here...
Emma, slow down!
This is tag! You just gotta keep up!
You know, there is something that
troubles me...
It seems that Emma...
has been dancing out on the street corner.
She'll be fine, she's growing up so fast.
I love the way you dance!
Thanks for always coming to watch!
Quit dancing on the sidewalk.
Who does she think she is?
Some sort of dancer.
Don't make me laugh!
I gotta do my homework.
I'm so hungry.
Call that dancing?
I'm hardly impressed.
The heck is her deal?
Hasn't anyone told her she's awful?
Give it up already.
So lame.
Are you done yet?
Leaving already?
Not really in the mood today.
She's quite the dancer, isn't she?
Yeah! Emma's amazing!
But...
She gets this sort of stage fright or something.
She's still a great dancer!
But she just gets up and leaves like that.
She probably just wasn't feeling good.
It's one of the Oniwabanshu's ninja stars.
Oh?
It was thrown directly at me.
Was it?
Did you not order as much yourself?
Why would I target you?
If you'll excuse me, then...
Ron!
Jane...
What's with that grim face of yours?
The director toss something
troublesome your way?
What about you?
Oh, you know...
None of my business of course,
but try not to get in too deep.
Might say the same to you.
That lady's back again.
She looks pretty out of place out here.
I've been waiting for two hours already!
I'm getting lonely...
It'll go down at midnight on the dot.
On the northern dock G18.
I trust you've got the goods?
Emma?
Oh, don't mind me.
If it's not too much a bother,
can we talk a moment?
Whaddya want me for?
You've got some incredible talent.
Thanks, I guess.
Oh, right...
Here.
Where did you get this?
In the northern warehouse district.
Don't worry, I—
Goodbye!
Wait!
I'm famished...
We don't have another penny to our name now...
The street performer life sure isn't easy.
We can't just spend the rest of our days like this.
What's our next plan?
Hard to plan anything with
the Oniwabanshu out for our heads.
True...
Why, though?
Not like I know.
Are we even sure they're after us?
Maybe it's all just a misunderstanding.
I mean, look at us.
Is something going down at WNA?
Maybe that's why—
The Oniwabanshu!
They're getting on my nerves!
Berecca, use your Ninja-Gum.
I'm fresh out.
What?!
You chewed through it all already?!
Please tell me you still have some!
Mommy...
Mommy!
Mommy!!
Right on time.
You got the goods?
You're packing real power with this.
Must be sitting on quite the turf.
That's none of your business.
You got the stuff?
The jig's up, baddies!
I'll give you one chance to turn yourselves in!
You're that rotten do-gooder, eh?
Had a feeling you'd show up.
We're quick on the uptake, y'know.
Bring all your friends, I've still got you beat.
Why you little!
And so the tables turn.
You're in for it now.
Now that was a close one!
Who are you?
You brought backup?!
What's the big idea?
Now you're the ones in for it.
Now we finally have some time for ourselves, Emma.
You know who I am?
I had a feeling you were spying on me.
I just wanted to chat.
About what?
Your incredible talents.
My talents?
I knew you were something special
the moment I saw you.
I looked into your history.
I know you came here from
far away and lost your parents.
It must have been so tough.
I'm okay!
All I need in life is dancing!
You don't need anything to dance,
and it makes everyone happy!
I'm one with all the people
once we're on the same rhythm.
I heard you're hoping to make it big.
Everyone will really flip once I'm a star!
I want to put smiles on all their faces.
Talk about dreaming, huh?
Your feet get tied up once
you take the big stage, though.
I wasn't joking when I said I did my research.
I always hear these voices on big days
like dance contests and stuff...
What's her deal?
Talk about a failure.
This is hard to watch.
But I know the truth.
I know that it's twisted
people causing everyone pain.
They're mean, absolutely cruel...
Sounds like you've got quite the ears.
So good they pick up even things
people say under their breath.
I think you should give it another shot,
for everyone's sake.
And more importantly, for your own.
"Stars of Tomorrow?"
It's a contest to find the
greatest dancer in all of Eagle City.
I'd never win.
If you just learn how to control
your powers, you'll be a shoe-in.
Control what, now?
Those excellent ears of yours.
It's not like I'm trying to hear all that stuff.
I can't stop what I didn't even start.
You just need to learn to concentrate.
Concentrate?
By focusing on just the path ahead
you can learn to block out the noise.
You'll be free from all those pesky
voices that seem to bother you.
Easy for you to say...
You already know how to control it, though.
Out of all the things people say,
you pick up just the bad bits.
Sounds controlled to me, don't you think?
You listen for the voices that bring
pain instead of happiness.
Those that bring sadness instead of joy.
But think for a moment.
Surely you've heard the voices
of those who support you, too.
Huh?
She'll be fine.
There are voices out there
that are always on your side.
All you need to do is lend them your ear.
Who are you?
Why did you come looking for me?
I'm Warren.
Warren...
Hang in there.
You're bound to be a star!
A star, huh...
Huh?
As you've all been informed,
we've managed to perfect the Ninja Gum.
Our hope now is to distribute the gum
to the incoming academy recruits.
I am in agreement.
It will surely become an invaluable tool
to bring out our students' potential.
I am afraid I must disagree.
It seems rash to supply our students
with such a new and untested invention.
Should the safety of our young ones
not be our top priority?
Fair point.
Still, though...
Forgive me, Mr. Chief,
but we have full confirmation that
Ninja-Gum is entirely safe.
I would argue that this is exactly
what the future of the WNA requires.
Welcome back to
the Stars of Tomorrow Contest!
Things are getting as heated as ever!
We've got the greatest bunch of dancers
you'll ever feast your eyes on!
Next up is entry number three,
the fairy of the streets, Emma!
Go on, Emma!
Show us what you're made of!
Go get 'em, Emma!
Emma!
What's her problem?
Why won't she start?
Must be nervous.
She's frozen with fear.
Here she goes again...
I can't dance like this!
Emma... Emma!
I'm here for you.
Warren!
Just focus your ears.
Listen for the voices here for you.
The voices of my friends...
Concentrate...
You can do this, Emma!
This girl is adorable!
I think I'm in love!
Emma looks so good!
She really does.
Come on, you've got this!
Even strangers are cheering for me...
All right, let's kick things off!
Yeah!
Excellent, Emma!
Congratulations, Emma!
You're a real star now!
All thanks to you.
There's something I should
apologize for, though.
Huh?
Sorry for not telling you sooner.
But I actually work for the WNA.
The what?
The World Ninja Association.
We work to protect the descendants of
ninja who spread across the globe,
teaching them the powers of
their ancestors.
I'm a ninja myself.
You are?
After seeing you fight like that,
I figured you were no ordinary lady.
You're a ninja, too.
I am?
Whether you're dancing or fighting,
the way you hold yourself, that finesse,
It's your ninja heritage at work!
I'm a ninja...?
I hope that doesn't bother you.
There are lots of people who work
to hide their ninja abilities.
I imagine your parents did the same.
This is so cool!
Huh?
Who wouldn't want to be a ninja?
That's the best news ever!
Oh thank goodness. Now, Emma.
I'd like to invite you to the
WNA academy. What do you say?
Count me in!
What's this academy for, though?
It's a school where you and lots of new
friends will all study the ninja way!
I'll meet new friends?
Other ninja boys and girls.
You're telling me there are
tons of ninja kids?
Mhm!
That's awesome!
I never imagined you had
special powers like that.
How wonderful!
You're leaving us, then?
Yup.
There's a new world out there to see.
I'm certain you'll make plenty of new friends.
It's only a quick train ride away.
I'll still come visit.
Thanks everyone.
Coast looks clear...
Good grief.
We're never gonna get anywhere
if we're always on the run like this.
You got any better ideas?
What if we snuck into the academy?
The new school year should be just
about to kick off.
We could slip in as some new students.
The Oniwabanshu would never think to
look for us there.
"You never see what's
below your nose," eh?
I'm going to some academy?
To study the ways of the ninja in greater depth.
Gumchi, Gumchi!
It is time you and Gumchi headed off.
Alrighty!
I'm off then, Dad.
Promise you won't get yourself in a mess, Van.
Yeah...
Don't worry!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
Nin! Sinking underground with the sun
(Showtime! Our time! Da-dan-dan!)
Now! We seek our men along the thread
(Looking bright! Through the night! Ba-ban-ban!)
Just like the heavy winds (whoo-whoo!)
Just like the calm, quiet woods (ring-ring!)
Like the aliens primed to invade (meep-meep!)
Getting shot down like a crush (bump-bump!)
You only live once
Every encounter has its parting
Our world may burn in war with itself
But the Shinobi Night will protect it
In a flash of the glittering moonlight
We hear blades clashing around us
Through flames, through earth, our lives
They keep going, keep repeating
Life of a ninja! (Nin!)
Ninpo strike, to this day we're
just scraping our way thorugh the war
Until a day comes we can achieve glory
Until I reach your heart on the other side
Nin nin nin!
All sold out
Thank you!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
Concentrate and
succeed!
Ninja-like
Ninja!
“Now I shall take my leave... in smoke!”
Next Episode
Unbelievable!
The WNA academy is so exciting
and full of all sorts of kids!
Whoa now! We're jumping right into Ninjala battles?!
Next time on Ninjala,
"WNA Academy – Let the Battles Begin!"
WNA Academy – Let the Battles Begin!
Stay tuned!