Have you ever heard
the tale of the Jewelpets?
Allow me to tell you a secret tale
no one has ever heard before.
Chapter 1: The Road to Jewelland
It all began when I found a jewelry box
by chance in an antique shop.
Before I knew it, a strange town
appeared before my eyes.
I was in the magical
jewel kingdom, Jewelland.
Chapter 2: Meeting the Princess
This kingdom thrives off magic.
But our magic has been
weakening as of late.
If it continues, our kingdom will crumble.
You must raise the Jewelpets
to strengthen our magic.
Please raise them
to become grown magicians.
My fun, strange life with
the Jewelpets had just begun.
I'm Ruby, a Jewelpet!
My eyes are made of jewels,
and I can do magic
based on the effect of my gemstone!
But I'm still training, so I can be
a bit of a handful to my master.
Practicing magic is important,
but I also gotta stay fashionable!
How does this hair accessory look?
Ooh, cute!
I also go to magic school!
There I have thirty-three friends
with different eye colors.
We study, we play,
and all sorts of fun things happen!
We still have homework, though...
And with every passing day, we all
aim to become fully-grown magicians!
We know we've made it once
we graduate and receive Jewel Cloaks.
It's a lot of work to get there,
but we promised the princess we would
keep Jewelland safe in troubled times!
The tale of Jewelpet will continue!
Jewelland is a truly wonderful, fun place.
Come listen to my tale again, okay?
See you again!