Slow and steady...
In the Bears' School, there's...
One, two, three, four... twelve little cubs in all.
And all of them get along very well.
And of those twelve bears, eleven of them are boys.
In we go.
They look so good!
We did it!
How much longer?
They're gone! The cupcakes are gone!
What? Where are they?
Over there!
The last of these twelve bears...
...is the only girl of the bunch. Her name is...
Down the hatch!
...none other than Jackie!
Why, you!
Here I go! See you later!
\ One, two... Jackie! \
Yeah!
\ Whenever Jackie smiles, even the sky grins back \
\ Whenever Jackie smiles, the flowers grin back too \
\ Whenever Jackie smiles... \
What?
\ Jackie, oh, Jackie, she's \
\ quite like the sun, don't you think? \
The Bears' School
Jackie the Pastry Chef and the Sunny Sweets
MOVIE
Thank you!
Why, my big brothers, they can't blame me for eating those cupcakes!
I wonder if there's a place I can eat all the sweets I want without being scolded...
Okay... Next on the list...
Ow-ow-ow...
Huh? Where...
Where'd it go...?
How could this happen?
Wait!
Do you know anything about a place where I can eat all the sweets I want?
Huh?
...Can't say that I do.
That look on your face! You do know!
I really don't.
You're lying!
After all, I smell some tempting goods you have with you!
What?
Come on.
Is that smell coming from
some yummy sweets?
No, of course not.
I'm Jackie! It's nice to meet you!
I'm Mindy, and I ask that you stop following me.
I'm following 'cuz there's gotta be
some yummy sweets wherever you're going!
– No, there aren't.
– Of course there are!
– Are not.
– Are too!
– There really aren't!
– There are too!
– There really aren't!!
– There are too!!
There really aren't!!!
Boo!
I want to eat until I'm all full!
And I'll get to do it if I follow Mindy!
Yummy sweets, you say?
Thanks, down the hatch!
Wooow!
What's this place? It's so cool!
"Sweets Land?"
And just who are you?
My name's Jackie. Is this a place where I can eat all the sweets I...
If you really believe you can eat for free here because you're a child, you're sorely mistaken.
Is this girl a friend of yours?
We met a little while ago...
If you want to buy food, you'll have to work for it. Take a look...
Those dishes need washing and those utensils need polishing.
There's tons of work to be done.
Now, what would you like to do first?
Well?
Steady... steady...
Mindy, could you please fetch another tray?
On it!
O-kay! My job as a pastry chef... begins!
Huff huff huff huff huff...
Stirry-stirry-stirry...
Trickle-trickle...
Steady... steady!
Are you trying to burn my business to the ground?
Excuse me!
Coming!
Granny...
Tch... Tell me it's not the mayor again.
This place is so irritating...
Oh, Sue! Is this where you've been?
Grandpa, why are you here?
I'm here on business.
Fiiine...
Well, then...
Miss, don't you think it's time for you to step aside?
Sell us Sweets Land.
Can't you see Sweets Land has gotten all dirty and worn-out?
If you let me handle it, I can turn this heap of junk into an elegant hotel.
So, what do ya think? We on the same page?
You're only into this to make cash, aren't you?
My, my, don't slander me like that.
Sweets Land is a place for anyone to freely enjoy themselves.
I'm not going to sell it.
Hey, you!
Meeeeh!
Grr, that's just rude!
So, how 'bout a deal?
Huh?
This year's Frappe Village Sweets Contest is upon us.
I'll enter the contest with my own pastry chef.
If my chef wins, you'll have to transfer Sweets Land to me.
That's not fair....
And what if you lose?
I'll do whatever it is you ask me to.
Oh, of course – you'll never have to see me in here again.
It's a deal.
Granny...
Get back here!
You have my word.
Of course! Good, that's that.
Alright, come on, Sue, let's go home!
Oh, Sue, you're always such a lively little one!
Tch... I can't stand walking around this place.
What's with that geezer? He's as creepy as they come.
Not to mention that little brat...
Granny... Are you alright?
Mhm...
Just peachy.
Oh, is this Dicky?
I'm becoming a pastry chef!
Yeah! Why, how come?
I dunno, that's just how things turned out for me.
Okay, I'll do my best! Talk to you later!
I kinda want to talk to my brothers in person...
Jackie, are you lonely?
Yeah...
Granny!
Don't tell me you were up all night!
Huh?!
Granny!
I'm sorry...
I let you down...
Granny... don't give up yet!
Mindy, please listen to me.
As you can see, I'm in a very bad condition.
I just can't push myself to make sweets.
I'm going to have to withdraw from the contest.
It's just too bad...
– Granny!
– Chackie!
I'll enter the contest in your place!
Mindy, what are you thinking?
You're not ready for that yet.
I am!
Sweets Land is very precious to you.
So I want to protect it!
That's why I'm gonna win the contest!
Mark my words!
Mindy...
My, this is delicious...
You're so cool, Mindy!
What do I do?
I could never live up to what I just said...
Huh?
There's no way I could enter on Granny's behalf!
I don't even know what kind of sweets to make for it...
Hey, Mindy, wanna go on a little walk?
– What?!
– Just come with me!
Times like this call for a walk!
We're here!
Wow, a sunflower field!
This is where I like to rest under the sun.
When I'm here, I can't help but have a huge smile on my face.
The sun sure is wonderful.
Mindy, why don't you relax?
O-Okay...
Feels good, right?
Yeah!
Hey, Mindy?
Yeah?
Why do you want to become a pastry chef?
The first time I ever made a sweet...
My granny ate it and said it was "delicious!"
And when she finished, she drew a great big sunflower to reward me.
Granny's smile back then made me really ecstatic!
Ever since then, I've wanted to become a pastry chef!
I get it!
Man, I just wish I could see Granny's smile again!
That's it, Mindy!
What is?
A sweet that can make your granny...
No... a sweet that can make anyone who eats it smile!
The "Sunny Sweets!"
Sunny Sweets?
You see, no one can resist smiling when the sun's out!
So let's work together to make...
...Sunny Sweets!
Yeah!
Yippee! Mindy, we did it!
Yippee, hooray!
But Jackie, we still have to actually make the dessert!
Oh, you're right.
Heave-ho...
Jackie! There you are!
Jackie, everything's okay.
You're in good hands now!
'Cause we're here!
– Brothers!
– Huh?
Oh, yeah. These are my brothers!
Nice to meet you, I'm Mindy!
Hey, this again?
You sure are quick to fall for others...
What ever happened to the last girl?
Brothers, I need your help!
Huh?
We need all of you to bring utensils and ingredients for making desserts to the sunflower field!
Sunny Sweets need to be made in the sunlight!
Right, Mindy?
Yeah!
– Well, get to it!
– Roger!
Let's get to work!
Granny!
Hm?
We made a sweet to enter in the contest!
And I couldn't have done it without Jackie.
It's called... a Sunny Sweet!
A sweet that will make everyone smile!
Aww, that's nice.
It's as angelic as you two are.
Go enter the contest.
I'm counting on you.
Of course!
Let's go, Mindy!
Okay!
Granny, we're gonna head out, alright?
My girl really has...
...grown before I knew it.
I can't wait to have a slice soon!
Same!
So much for getting to eat Sunny Sweets...
Yeah...
And so, let this year's Frappe Village Sweets Contest commence!
Just whose sweets will make them champion this year?
Here's my sweet.
I borrowed it from a cake shop in ze next village and just decorated it.
Well done, just what I expected from a bogus pastry chef.
But can we really beat zat lady with this?
Don't you worry. I'll have them disqualified.
Just watch. I'm gonna make a killing with a hotel in that spot.
Thank you for waiting!
What do you say we get right into it?
Our judges here are Frappe Village's mayor and other special people you may know!
First onto the stage is...
A chef from pastry shop Dandota who has people lining up to taste his sweets!
Give it up for Tuile!
Our second entry...
From Amatino's, a western confectionery shop with history in the business for over 300 years...
...Give it up for Souffle!
Next, our third contestant!
All the way from Paris, the city of flowers...
Give it up for the famous pastry chef, Jean Pierre!
I am Jean Pierre!
Go on, have a bite...
Well, judges, how does it taste?
Yum!! Very delish!!
It must taste amazing!
Jean Pierre's already on track to win by a landslide!
Zas so? My mother back home will be real proud!
Coming up now are our final contestants!
The young pastry chefs from Sweets Land!
Give it up for Mindy and her pal Jackie!
One and two and...
Making everyone in this village smile!
It's Sunny Sweets!
Go on, dig in!
Oopsy!
Well, this sure is rough!
And I was so looking forward to tasting your dessert too!
How will it be judged now?
Well, with their dish splattered all over the floor...
...I'm afraid we have no choice but to disqualify them.
Disqualify us?
Please let us make it over again!
Too late for that.
Unless you'd like to defy the decision of the judge chairman?
But that's not fair...
After we worked so hard to make it...
M-Moving on, just who will claim victory today...?
Chairman judge, would you like to announce...?
The winner of the 5th annual Frappe Village Sweets Contest is...
Ba-da-ba-da-ba-da-ba-da...
The famous pastry chef from Paris, the city of flowers, Jean Pierre!
Oh my, I actually won? I'm zo happy!
I'm overjoyed!
Wait just a minute!
Huh?
Sue, what are you doin' up there?
I've snitched food from tons of top-class restaurants,
so I'm way more of a gourmet than my grandpa.
That said, I've been snitching from all the desserts in this contest.
This whole time?!
The winning dish... must be the Sunny Sweets!
What on Earth?
It's a million times better than Jean Pierre's sloppy dish.
Sue, please, don't cause such a fuss during this event...
Then, why don't you check it out for yourself?
It's the Sunny Sweets!
Go on, dig in!
Sue, you didn't...
Brothers...?
Darn all of this...
All I have to do is say it tastes awful and bam, it's over.
Where am I...?
Grandpa...
Grandpa, I love you!
Sue...
Su-u-u-ue!!
It was like a slice of heaven!
So... in conclusion...
The winner of the 5th annual Sweets Contest is...!
The pair of friends, Mindy and Jackie!
Hooray, hooray!
We won, we won!
You see now? It brought out a smile in you too!
Yet another failed attempt to eat... a Sunny Sweet.
Uh-huh...
Thanks so much, Sue!
Grr, she really is just rude!
Sue sure is something!
– We won!
Granny?
Mindy, look!
Huh?
Oh, it's the flower!
It's the same sunflower she'd draw when I was little!
Yeah!
It's Granny's flower!
That means she must have eaten it with a big smile!
That's right!
Your sweet made your granny smile!
Yeah!
Thank you!
You did great out there!
Grannyyy!
Hey now, I haven't recovered just yet!
Granny really loves this merry-go-round!
My grandpa, who was a carpenter, made this for their wedding anniversary.
Does that mean he built all of Sweets Land, too?
Uh-huh! A-a-all of this was the work of my grandpa!
Your grandpa was amazing!
We made so many memories with Grandpa here,
and that's why Granny could never stand to see this taken away from her.
I could imagine.
Thank you, Jackie.
I couldn't have saved Sweets Land without you.
I had to do something. I mean, we're pals, right?
Of course!
Oh, Mindy.
Sue, isn't this a little cruel...?
This is what you get for being cruel!
Fiiine...
Come on, come on, come on...
Don't you dare!
In the Bears' School, there's...
One, two, three, four... twelve little cubs in all.
Brothers, wait!
Wait for me!
And all of them get along very well.
I think if life
were a person...
They'd be restless and rash sometimes,
and wouldn't like to tell jokes
Why don't you show me
your best smile?
It has a wonderful magic to it
that brightens things up
Goodbye, mister...
I see you're already
on your way
Out in search of an extraordinary
thing called "happiness"
But that's not such a bad way
to spend your days after all
Your heart knows
the reason why, so
Turn that frown upside down!
Mister...
Mister... mister!
Everyone's unique, and you won't
always be able to understand
But expressing our flaws and differences
is what makes things fun!
Goodbye, mister...
You've begun spilling tears
And you're the only one who knows why,
but you don't need to say it
But you shouldn't look back,
you're already lovely as you are
It's up to you to seek out
what you hope for
Sadness doesn't just disappear,
so you need to let the joy overtake you
So when the right day comes
around, be kind and gentle
And someone out there will
love you very much for it
Goodbye, mister...
When I encountered you
I feel like I learned a little
about "happiness"
If we give it a name,
sing this feeling to life
No, I can't do this...
I'm going to cry
If we keep saying our
greetings and farewells,
You'll eventually be an adult too
But don't get too used to it
It's all just a brand new
chapter in your life
It'll all be okay,
you can walk away
All the way through the wind,
all the way through the wind
Goodbye, mister...
I see you're already
on your way
You were always born
to be happy
If you ever get lonely and tremble,
don't stop in the midst of the wind
I want you to remember something
I'm always thinking of you
Mister...
Mister!
THE END