In the Bears' School, there's...
One, two, three, four...
Twelve little cubs in all.
And all of them get along very well.
And of those twelve bears,
eleven of them are boys.
The last of these twelve bears...
...is the only girl of the bunch. Her name is...
...none other than Jackie!
The Bears' School
Jackie and Katie
It's morning! Wakey wakey!
It's morning! It's great out there today!
Wake up already, you guys!
Rise and shine!
So annoying...
Man.
A bakery!
All done!
Dear my sleepyhead brothers,
I'm off to buy brek
breakfast.
B
From Jackie
I'm off to buy breakfast.
From Jackie.
Maple jam bread, milk bread!
Waffles, bagles, croissants!
A butterfly!
Yay!
Of course! We'll have
pumpkin bread for breakfast!
I'm usually better at sliding!
I just didn't think it would be that steep.
Sorry. You're right,
that really is a steep hill.
I'm actually really good at sliding!
Oh, really?
Did you scrape yourself?
It sure looks like you did.
Just one second.
Don't you cry.
See? All better!
Yay!
This is cute!
I'm Katie!
I'm Jackie!
Are you hungry?
The bakery!
The one I saw from my window!
We just moved in here.
So cool!
Jackie!
Jackie?
Jackie, where are you?
Well, that's new.
Are you a friend of Katie's?
This is my father.
Dad, this is Jackie.
We became friends earlier!
Neat. Nice to meet you, Jackie!
Should I fetch some firewood?
Don't worry, I'm good.
Hey, Dad?
Can I go to the flower garden tomorrow?
You can't go to the mountain. It's too dangerous a trip.
What about the one by the riverside?
Ohh. Yes, you can go there.
Thank you.
He says I can go.
Almost done...
That looks like fun.
More to the right!
What's going on?
I'm heading out!
I really love these flowers.
What do you love about them?
The way they bloom straight to the sky.
They do, don't they?
I'm soaking wet!
Much better!
Katie?
Are you back, Katie?
Katie!
She has a bad fever...
Katie's always been physically weak.
So we came to the forest for fresher air.
You're the first friend
Katie's ever brought home.
She must've been so happy she pushed herself too hard...
I'll keep visiting!
Huh?
I'll come visit everyday
until she's healthy again!
She's my friend, after all!
Until the end!
We can just eat without her.
Peter, move out of the way! I can't see!
Jackie's home!
Where were you?
We were waiting for ages!
We've been waiting!
Since you took so long,
we went ahead and had stew.
No carrots, small potatoes,
it even had hot dogs in it.
I like hot dogs.
You can use the TV too if you want.
There's also parsley in it.
What's her deal?
She must really hate parsley.
Is anyone using this red marker?
We're using crayons, not markers!
Herman, stop drawing!
Done!
"Meeting Regarding Jackie's Strange Behavior!"
Meeting Regarding Jackie's Strange Behavior
What's that?
– A rocket.
– I see a crow!
Meeting Regarding Jackie's Strange Behavior
It's a hawk!
How long has she been acting up?
Since yesterday, I think.
When we were having stew.
What happened?
The potatoes were too big!
There weren't enough hot dogs!
Why was there parsley in it?
The stew isn't the problem!
Jackie didn't even eat it!
Anton and Roy are heading out
to investigate.
Hi, good to see you.
Katie's sleeping soundly.
Got it!
Who is he?
I wonder...
She's pretty!
Calm down, Roy, you'll get us caught!
Jackie?
Katie, look at me!
I'm going to visit you everyday
until you're feeling better!
You're just like one of those flowers
blooming straight up...
Roy!
We should see the flower garden again.
Katie!
I'll bring you tons of those flowers!
Jackie, are you heading home?
Excuse us!
Is that why she's acting up?
Jackie's been feeling bad
because Katie isn't feeling good.
Exactly.
Jackie's basically been
going there to nurse her.
So what do we do?
Yeah, what do we do?
Do we make stew?
More?
With smaller potatoes!
Put hot dogs in it!
Why not just use sausage?
Don't bother with the parsley!
I hate that stuff.
Katie was so pretty...
Roy!
The flowers are gone...
Jackie.
There were flowers here
and now they're gone!
The rain yesterday must
have washed it away.
Oh, well. Time to give up.
No!
Jackie?
You found her?
Not over there.
Where on earth did she go?
Maybe she went home?
I found her! Look, she's over here!
What kind of store is that?
It's a florist.
But what is she doing there?
Hmm...
"I'd like flowers, please!"
"Sorry, we don't have any."
"Even though you're a florist?"
"That way?"
"That's a mountain."
Jackie!
Let her be, Roy!
It's just like her to drop all these flowers...
I bet there won't be any left
when she gets to Katie's house.
Jackie!
Up here!
Katie!
You feeling better?
Yeah.
Yay, I'm happy for you, Katie!
Oh, yeah!
For you!
Did you put up all these decorations?
Yeah! I wanted to surprise you
when you got better.
One more thing!
Be careful, Peter!
Katie looks better now!
Yeah!
Back it up, back it up, back it up!
How did you get this thing in the air?
Whoa...
He filled the blimp with helium gas.
Wow, you know your stuff.
Time for Phase 2!
Come in!
This pipe is just a toy.
You don't seem very well.
Miss, it's time for the party.
Hah! Don't think, just feel!
Jackie! Come back!
I'm Chief Tiny!
Brrr! This thing's got a straight-six engine
with 120 horsepower!
This has a V4 engine!
Bartholomew's treasure is that-a-way!
Blub blub blub blub...
I mean, this-a-way!
Badabadabada... Ta-dah!
This is for you!
We've been secretly
putting this together for you two!
You're invited to a party
now that you're feeling better!
Hold that.
Roy...
The party's tonight!
Yeah!
Where's the fire?
Spitfire!
Don't stand behind me!
In the Bears' School, there's...
One, two, three, four...
Twelve little cubs in all.
And all of them get along very well.
And of those twelve bears,
eleven of them are boys.
The last of these twelve bears...
...is the only girl of the bunch. Her name is...
...none other than Jackie!
Fa-la-la-la-la
\ Born underneath the blue sky \
\ I always waited for one strange encounter \
\ I want to see the smiles of my favorite people \
\ So I'll do my very best to bring them out! \
\ Please smile! \
\ We've grown so close, I'm always thinking about you \
\ Fa-la-la-fa-la \
\ I'll write you a letter \
\ Fa-la-fa-fa-la \
\ There's a party tonight \
\ Fa-la-la-fa-la \
\ I'll decorate it with your favorite flowers \
\ Fa-la-fa-fa-la \
\ Just waiting on the sun \
\ What will I bring you today? \
\ I love you, so I want to surprise you \
\ Baked bread, donuts \
\ A mischievous frog, and an air blimp \
\ I have so many photos of our memories! \
\ I hope we grow even closer together tomorrow \
\ Fa-la-la-fa-la \
\ On the count of three, we all sing \
\ Fa-la-fa-fa-la \
\ Make it a happy song \
\ Fa-la-la-fa-la \
\ Lots of your favorite sweets on the table \
\ Fa-la-fa-fa-la \
\ Underneath the light of the moon \
Fa-la-la-fa-la
La-la-la
\ Fa-la-la-fa-la \
\ I'll write you a letter \
\ Fa-la-fa-fa-la \
\ There's a party tonight \
\ Fa-la-la-fa-la \
\ I'll decorate it with your favorite flowers \
\ Fa-la-fa-fa-la \
\ Now let's dance! \
Fa-la-la-fa-la
\ Fa-la-fa-fa-la \
\ Make it a happy song \
\ Fa-la-la-fa-la \
\ Lots of your favorite sweets on the table \
\ Fa-la-fa-fa-la \
\ Underneath the light of the moon \
Fa-la-la-fa-la
La-la-la
\ Let's wait for the sun \
Fa-la-la-fa-la