This Episode's Squishyyyy Highlights
Squishy
Punirunes. Before we knew it,
these creatures began to inhabit the human world.
They're very squishsterious creatures!
They all love to be squished.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Coolrune Gets Stylish♪
Coolrune is a cool beauty who loves being stylish.
Looks like Airune wants to try it on.
I'm home!
What happened here?
I see, Coolrune lent it to you!
Do you want to be stylish like it, Airune?
Huh? You two were just about to head out?
Coolrune really likes keeping tidy.
Have a safe trip!
This is the Punirunes' world.
Where could these two be heading?
They've arrived at the market!
This is a store where
they can remodel their room.
Here's a place where they can buy
clothes and other stylish accessories.
Welcome back!
How'd it go?
You seem mighty confident!
It's about to show us
what it bought at the market!
You okay?
I mean, I know you're happy getting all dressed up...
Coolrune has an idea!
Komugi's over there, Coolrune.
You're going to train it to act cool?
Coolrune seems to think that what Airune's style
is lacking is coolness.
But where does Komugi come in then?
Umm... So you want it to play with Komugi?
S-Such cool poise...
I see! You want it to master this!
Wanna give it a shot, Airune?
You've got this!
Airune...
Airune has fallen into deep despair.
Now there's nothing stylish left.
Airune!
You gave it a good try!
Being squished has cheered it up!
Not only that...
It's motivated, too!
You look ready to take this on, Airune!
Alrighty!
Your training is back on!
First off: Play it cool and walk
without breaking any plates!
Next: Play it cool and resist the urge
to dig in on your favorite appuni pie!
Next: Do a cool spin without getting flustered!
And at last...
You did it, Airune!
Thanks for having me!
Come to think of it,
Enerune's been acting strange lately.
It doesn't seem very cheerful...
Is it feeling down?
It was, but then...
It suddenly started trying to be stylish.
How did you know?
Well...
They've all started training because
they want to be stylish like Coolrune!
Oh, I see!
You all look wonderful!
Happy for you!
So cute!
It says arrangement is key in fashion!
Airune's finally exploring its own style.
This may be the way to true fashion.
Hey, don't overdo it, now.
Coolrune's already getting to work
on a cool new training plan.
Punirunes Guide
Today on the Punirunes Guide...
Coolrune
Coolrune is a fashion leader
who loves being stylish.
It's always visiting the market to see what's trending.
It dreams of owning its own brand.
The squestion!
It's time for the squestion!
Which of these did Coolrune rock today?
1. Wings
2. Swim Ring
3. Scarf
The answer is...
The scarf!
Seasonality is also key to fashion!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Hello, we're Pekopa!
"Pekopa" is a comedy duo that appears in
advertisements for the Punirunes toyline.
We're Pekopuni!
Pekopa? Pekopuni?!
Huh? Wha?! Which one is it?!
Next time: "Pekopa Becomes Punirunes♪"
Next Time
Pekopa Becomes Punirunes♪
"Puni" in next time!