This Episode's Squishyyyy Highlights
Squishy
Punirunes. Before we knew it,
these creatures began to inhabit the human world.
They're very squishsterious creatures!
They all love to be squished.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Thanks for waiting, viewers at home!
I'm Taiyuu Shouinji!
And over here is...
Hey there! I'm Shuupei!
Hey, you're covering me up!
Good thing I can move over.
We're Pekopa!
Glad to be here!
Here we are!
Squishy-squishy-squishy-squish!
What's gotten into you, Shuupei?
I wish I could be a Punirune and get squished!
What are you gonna do if that wish comes true?!
I sure hope it does! I wanna be squished!
If you wanna be squished that bad, I'll do it! Take this!
Squish! Squish! Squish! Squish!
Now you've done it! Squish!
Squishy-squish! Squish squish!
Squish squishy squish!
Squish? Huh? What?
What? Huh? What the?!
Huh?
Where are we?
Pekopa Becomes Punirunes♪
Hold on...
You're Shuupei, aren't you?
We actually got ourselves turned into Punirunes!
Is that all you can say now?
No, I can talk.
Oh, thank goodness. You can talk.
Yippee, we're really Punirunes!
Why are you so hap...
Well, we are cute.
Guess it's not that bad.
I'm Peirune!
Peirune
And this is...
Thanks for waiting!
Shourune
I'm Shourune!
Nailed it.
Together...
We're Pekopuni!
Pekopuni
Alright! What should we play first?
P-Peirune!
There's people waiting for us, you know!
We have to hurry up and transform back!
But just how do we do that?
Who's that?
Let's go see!
– Hup!
– Peirune!
I'm Peirune!
Sorry, didn't mean to startle you.
Wow, they warmed up to you fast!
But no worries. Squishing will save the world!
I see!
Squishing was what turned us into Punirunes.
So maybe squishing will be what turns us back too!
What is this feeling...?
I can't stop squishing!
But it didn't turn them back.
We'll need more squishpower.
Squishpower?
What's that supposed to be?
Oh! Maybe that is what we need!
We need more squishing!
Please give us more squish!
There's no way they understand what you're saying.
They understood!
Oh, thank goodness! Please give us more squish!
Gummies?
They don't understand! Or maybe they do.
Maybe we really were hungry.
Thank you for helping us realize something we didn't.
Time to eat!
So good and squishy!
Alright, now that our stomachs are full,
let's go find more friends to squish with!
You two should come along too...
Looks like they've fallen asleep from their meals.
Excuse me!
We're...
Peirune!
And Shourune!
We need to ask you a favor.
Right, it won't understand.
How do I tell it...?
Interesting, you want a dance-off?
If I win, you squish me!
Time for a very sudden dance-off!
I'm Shourune!
Not bad.
However...
Are you okay?
Of course not! Though I have to be
to say it out loud like this.
Did it enjoy it?
I sure hope so.
Maybe it's not laughing, but it's about to cry.
Is something making it sad?
Ururune is scared seeing strangers
and it's making it cry.
Sorry. We're not scary!
Look at me! I'm like an eggplant!
Doesn't look like it's drying up.
I'm Peirune!
Its tears have been stopped.
Good work, Peirune.
I have a favor for you guys!
Do you understand what "favor" means?
Nope, they don't...
There's a bunch of them coming!
They must have a whole bunch of squishpower!
Excuse me!
Please be our friend!
Yes, we must start with friendship!
We must take the first step
before asking favors from them!
Please be our friend!
Peirune?
Are you alright?
We're okay the way we are, right?
Shuupei, snap out of it!
We said we would try to turn back to normal, right?
I'm gonna stay around as Pekopuni!
I don't wanna go back!
What are you saying? Come back with me!
We're Pekopa!
We're best when we're together!
We have to go back!
Thank goodness.
I'm home!
Oh, do we have visitors?
A human girl! We're saved!
We're called Pekopa.
We want to turn back to normal!
Can you squish us?
Okay!
Okay! Though I don't understand
anything you're saying.
Unfortunately, Yuka can't understand Pekopuni.
You only can't understand us
because we've turned into this.
We shouldn't be pointing fingers anymore.
Nice to meet you, I'm Yuka!
Anyways, we have to beg her for squishes!
Do you wanna be squished? Alright!
Th-This is it!
This feels so good-puni!
Feels so real... She gives such a good squish...
She's a pro-squisher...
What's a "pro-squisher"...?
Huh?
After all that, they still haven't turned back.
You don't suppose we were off-track about
squishing turning us back to normal, do you?
What are we supposed to do now?
Hey, maybe this is fine?
What?!
We can't turn back time.
We must live in the present!
Hey, what?!
You were the one that said we needed to turn back!
Shourune, come back with me!
Shourune...
Oh, whatever.
Will Pekopuni turn back after this?
Or will they continue to live as Punirunes?
Next time...
The brand-new series "Pekopunirunes" begins!
Tune in next time!
Knock it off!
Glad you put an end to that.
Today on the Punirunes Guide...
Punirunes Guide
Pekopuni
The always cheerful, airheaded Peirune...
And the harmless straight man Shourune.
The squestion!
It's time for the squestion!
Silhouette quiz!
Which numbers are Pekopuni?
Easy peasy! Number one!
And number three!
Too bad, that's an eggplant!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
The Punirunes are doing a Sports Day?
Just as I thought, Enerune's the star of this one!
Huh?!
Next Time
Next time: "Enerune's Sports Day♪"
Enerune's Sports Day♪
"Puni" in next time!