This Episode's Squishyyyy Highlights
Squishy
Punirunes. Before we knew it,
these creatures began to inhabit the human world.
They're very squishsterious creatures!
They all love to be squished.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
What am I doing?
There's a choir at school during music class!
But I'm not really a great singer...
You'll cheer me on?
Thank you! I'll do my best!
See you later!
Airune wants to know what school is like.
According to Aoi,
they study...
play...
and eat lunch, says Enerune.
Airune still wants to know more.
Pikarune
The Punirunes have called their friend Pikarune.
Airune asked it to teach them
what school is like.
Pikarune is very wise.
Everything is written down
in its book.
Pikarune has agreed to be their teacher
and teach them about school!
Pikarune's Elementary School♪
Class is in session at Teacher Pikarune's
Punirunes Elementary School!
First period is Math.
Be quiet during class!
What is 3+2?
That's very wrong, Enerune.
I'm not sure how this works,
but these hearts are spreading all over!
The answer is 5.
Second period is Science.
When you mix red and yellow,
you get orange!
If you mix yellow and blue,
whose color do you get?
They think it will turn the color of Coolrune.
Where have they seen this color before?
It's the color of Togerune!
Now they're mixing Airune and Ururune's colors...
And it turned Coolrune's color!
How would they make Loverune's color?
Third period is Music!
Airune asked Pikarune to sing with them...
But it's not very good at exercise or singing.
I'm home!
Choir went well!
Oh, you brought a friend over to play?
Pikarune, huh?
I'm Yuka! Nice to meet you!
I heard you guys earlier, what were you up to?
A choir?!
Let me sing with you guys!
Wanna sing too?
Don't worry!
My teacher told me this...
Just be cheerful and have fun singing!
Alright!
Start the music!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
Pikarune's joining in as a rapper?!
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious! (Puni!)
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Punirunes Elementary School
is a fun, lively school.
Would you like to go here too?
Punirunes Guide
Today on the Punirunes Guide...
Pikarune
Pikarune is very wise.
Everything is written in its book.
The squestion!
It's time for the squestion!
1. Cooking
2. Dancing
3. Drawing
Which of these is Pikarune not good at?
The answer is...
All of them!
Hang in there, Pikarune!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Uh-oh!
That crow took your hat!
The trick to getting it back is... jumping?!
Next Time
Next time: "Doing Our Best in Squish'n Jump♪"
Doing Our Best in
Squish'n Jump♪
"Puni" in next time!