This Episode's Squishyyyy Highlights
Squishy
Punirunes. Before we knew it,
these creatures began to inhabit the human world.
They're very squishsterious creatures!
They all love to be squished.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
That was amazing!
They're putting on a performance for a Halloween party.
Bakerune's Halloween Scare♪
Those pumpkin costumes are so cute!
You really wowed me with that dance too!
Do you know what Halloween is?
You don't?!
It's a celebration of the autumn harvest
which is held every October 31st!
It's also the day when the spirits of our ancestors
return to their families.
That's right!
She actually just learned that in class today.
Why do people dress up as monsters, you ask?
Because...
I dunno!
You don't?!
The spirits of our ancestors bring back
evil demons and witches with them,
so dressing up as monsters
is to make them all feel welcomed.
That's right!
There's one more fun thing about Halloween!
You dress up as monsters and scare grown-ups
by saying "trick-or-treat!"
And they give you treats!
All done!
Oh, pumpkin cakes!
They look so good! I'll give it a taste...
– No you don't!
– Ow!
This is for Yuka and the Punirunes.
Boo-hoo...
Trick-or-treat!
M-M-Monsters!!
Please let me off the hook!
Neither of them are very great actors.
Give us treats, or we'll play a trick on you!
Darling, get some treats!
We should have some gummies...
W-Will this do?
H-Help yourself to some pumpkin cakes!
Honey, we have to get out of here!
Okay!
We scored big!
These pumpkin cakes look so good...
Let's make use of this pumpkin cake!
Let's get squ-ooking!
Give it some of the squishsterious squishence...
Stir it...
Knead it...
Give it a squishy kneading so it'll be nice and fluffy!
Pumpunin cake
Pumpunin Cake, ready to serve!
Dig in!
Do you like it?
Who's sneaking around up here?
I'll start giving out gummies!
Here.
Your gummies disappeared?
What are Ururune's gummies doing over there?
Huh? Airune took them?
They're starting to get suspicious of Airune.
Now, hold on. Why would Airune
take Ururune's gummies?
What's wrong, Airune?
Airune...
"It was floating around...
"went see-through...
"and passed through the door?"
It wasn't a ghost!
None of them believed Airune.
You were hungry, right?
But you can't take Enerune's gummies.
Huh?
Trick-or-treat!
Looks like the shock knocked it unconscious!
Who is he?
Oh! It's squishy!
Are you alright?
I guess we gave you too big a scare.
We're sorry.
Its name is Bakerune!
Bakerune
You're a bit of a scaredy cat for a ghost, though.
Why did you take their gummies?
I see. You wanted to be friends with them,
but couldn't speak out and tried to get their attention.
Airune, sorry for doubting you.
Have some pumpunin cake!
Trick-or-treat!
You look weird!
But we worked hard on these costumes...
They're not very great at costumes either.
Bakerune really is easily frightened for a ghost.
Today on the Punirunes Guide...
Punirunes Guide
Bakerune
Bakerune loves scaring people,
but it's easily scared itself.
The squestion!
It's time for the squestion!
1. Monsters
2. Dark Spaces
3. Komugi
Which of these is Bakerune most scared of?
1. Monsters?
2. Dark Spaces?
Or 3. Komugi?
The answer is...
All three!
Hang in there, Bakerune!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Airune wants to be stylish!
You're going to help it, Coolrune?
What do you have planned?
Next time: "Coolrune Gets Stylish♪"
Next Time
Coolrune Gets Stylish♪
"Puni" in next time!