This Episode's Squishyyyy Highlights
Squishy
Punirunes. Before we knew it,
these creatures began to inhabit the human world.
They're very squishsterious creatures!
They all love to be squished.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
with Happyrune♪
A Merry Squishmas
It's Christmas day!
We're going to throw a party
and have a huge feast!
You might even get presents!
I can't think of anything!!
Mom and Dad are trying to think up
a special dish for the party.
I better give them a hand.
The Punirunes are going to
get ready for the party.
Oh?
I just thought of something!
Oh, my! This is a surprise!
It's the Punirune that loves making everybody happy...
Happyrune!
Happyrune
Happyrune is a professional
who makes people around it happy
without anyone seeing it.
Airune is making a Christmas tree out of building blocks.
Loverune is trying to come up with
a special variant of its hearts.
Coolrune is figuring out a special outfit for the party.
Ururune is drawing a Christmas tree.
Enerune is training to make itself hungry
for the feast...
Looks like it worked too well.
Aha, found you!
Huh?
Where'd the star go?
Huh? It's gone...
What now...?
We can't have a Christmas tree without a star!
Happyrune is set on making Yuka happy
by finding the tree star!
Yuka, did you find it?
Yeah!
Coming!
Airune is going to ask Yuka
to make food for Enerune.
Airune spotted Happyrune like nothing!
Happyrune is too busy looking for the star
to be bothered by Airune.
Happyrune's rule is to make people happy
without anyone seeing it.
Shooting stars!
It's finished its special Christmas hearts!
And Coolrune found the finishing touch for its outfit!
Ururune and Enerune are also very happy now!
Oh, there's the star!
Huh?
Togerune, did you bring this to me?
Thanks a ton, Togerune!
What's up?
So soothing!
That's it!
How about a matcha warabimochi pastry?
That sounds great!
Then we can add red raisins
to give it a Christmas color palette!
Absolutely perfecto!
Thanks again, Togerune.
Merry Christmas!
Those presents are from me!
Happyrune has to go soon.
What's up, Airune?
Hm? You want a squish?
Sure, no problem!
Squishy-squish!
It's very cold outside.
I'm so glad I got to have a party with you all...
It was so fun!
Huh? That felt like a completely new texture...
So pretty!
What do you think is shining up there?
Airune got to meet Happyrune
and had a very merry Christmas.
Maybe Happyrune will come to your place next!
Punirunes Guide
Today on the Punirunes Guide...
Happyrune
Happyrune is a Punirune that loves making people happy!
The squestion!
It's time for the squestion!
Where's Happyrune?
Look for it!
The answer is...
Here!
If you found it, tomorrow will be a very happy day!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Oh, no!
Airune changed colors!
Everyone's acting weird!
What's going on here?!
Next Time
Next time: "Punirunes Swap Colors♪"
The Punirunes Swap Colors♪
"Puni" in next time!