This Episode's Squishyyyy Highlights
Squishy
Punirunes. Before we knew it,
these creatures began to inhabit the human world.
They're very squishsterious creatures!
They all love to be squished.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Yuka and Airune♪
How long ago was this?
Must be around
three or four years ago.
This is from the first time you made apple pie!
Didn't come out very good, though.
We were so young back then.
Are we not still?
Oh, right!
I hadn't met Airune yet back then!
See, Airune's house isn't there!
Huh?
You want to know when we met?
Me too!
Have I never told you?
Nope!
Ahh, the day we met...
Really brings me back.
Komugi, over here!
Hey, wait!
What the...? The swing's moving on its own!
Whaaat? What's that thing?
It's running!
What in the world is that?
Komugi!
Don't pick on it...
A-Are you okay?
I'm Yuka! What about you?
Ai...
...rune?
Airune, huh?
Such a cutie!
What is this texture?
It's soft like freshly-baked bread,
but rubbery like fresh gummies!
This must be... the squishest of the squish,
the pinnacle of squishiness!
I present you with the Squishy Award!
And that's how Airune and I met.
So it was so squishy you wanted to give it an award?
You want to know how we got closer after that?
You see...
Airune!
Were you napping?
Aw, you got all dirty.
Don't worry!
You feel better?
I'll help rinse you by squishing.
Airune, stay still!
Airune, where are you?
Airune?
Found ya, Airune!
Are you hungry?
Wanna eat with me?
Here! A pastry made by my dad.
You don't want it?
What food do you usually eat anyways?
Squishy things?
Oh! Then you might like this.
They're gummies!
My mom made them!
Here!
It's very squishy just like you!
You like it?
I'm glad!
See ya, Airune!
Oh, wow!
So both of you started getting more excited
to spend time with each other.
Huh, what about Airune's house?
Think it wants to know when it appeared.
What's wrong?
Just trying to remember.
The day Airune's house showed up...
You alright, Airune?
Hey, Airune!
Wanna come home with me?
I'm home, Airune!
Huh? Airune?
Huh? What's that thing?
I see!
So that was the day Airune moved in!
It really brings me back!
Oh, Airune!
You getting hungry soon?
Wow! You really know everything about Airune!
We've been together for ages, after all!
Looks like everyone's hungry!
Alright, then!
I'll make you some of this!
Let's get squ-ooking!
Give it some of the squishsterious squishence...
Stir it...
Knead it...
Give it a squishy kneading so it'll be nice and fluffy!
Appuni pie, ready to serve!
Punibone
...Wait, what?
What on earth is that?
When you use the wrong squishence combo,
you get a punibone!
Why the smug look...?
Though they seem to like it.
Really?
Guess there's a lot I still have to learn about Punirunes.
There's a lot I still want to learn about Airune.
And I can't wait!
Airune and Yuka's squishy lives...
...will continue on squishingly!
Today on the Punirunes Guide...
Punirunes Guide
Squishence
Squishence comes in three colors:
red, blue, and yellow.
When mixed in with food,
you can make it squishy and delicious.
The squestion!
It's time for the squestion!
Which combo do you need for appuni pie?
1. Red & Blue
2. Red & Yellow
3. Blue & Yellow
4. Blue & Blue
The answer is...
Red and yellow!
Appuni pie
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Agents. Aoi's birthday is almost upon us.
We must search for the secret ingredient for her cake.
Next Time
Next time: "Squishon: Impossible♪"
SQUISHON: IMPOSSIBLE♪
Don't squiss it.