This Episode's Squishyyyy Highlights
Squishy
Punirunes. Before we knew it,
these creatures began to inhabit the human world.
They're very squishsterious creatures!
They all love to be squished.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Enerune's Sports Day♪
Sports Day is coming up
this Sunday!
I can't wait to see
what will be for lunch!
Will it be fried chicken?
Hamburg steak sounds good too!
Aoi, what's wrong? You look sad.
I'm not very athletic...
I see.
Must not like Sports Days, do you?
It's not fun if I can't win!
I want to be a winner!
Aoi is surprisingly competitive.
Y-You want to win, I see.
I wish I were as athletic as Enerune.
What are the Punirunes up to?
Looks like not a bread-eating race,
but a gummy-eating race.
It jumped too high!
Come on in, Aoi!
W-What the?
What's going on here?
Huh? Sports Day?
The Punirunes found out about "Sports Day"
and wanted to do their own!
So what are you doing next?
What's this...?
Oh! It's a fan!
A gymnastic formation!
Amazing!
Looks like they're about finished!
Aw, and after you just finished the formation!
What's the next event?
The spoon race!
They must get to the finish line
without dropping the squishence!
Good luck, Enerune!
Ready, set...!
Loverune, winking at the squishence
won't make it do as you say!
Look at you go!
Amazing, Ururune! You got first place!
Enerune...
Looks like tug of war is up next!
You can do this, Enerune!
Oh! Are Enerune and Airune at the advantage?
Loverune and Coolrune have made
a lovely turnaround victory!
Enerune...
So cute, Enerune!
Looks like you're having fun, though.
What's up next?
A scavenger hunt?
Whoever finds the item drawn on the paper
and brings it to the finish line first wins.
A cat toy!
A measuring cup!
Dad's weird mask!
The ribbon from earlier!
What's that?
Enerune!
I wonder what that's supposed to be.
Did you figure it out?
A... A crow?!
So the black circle was a game piece!
Aoi!
What's wrong? You look sad...
Enerune found the ribbon,
but a crow came in and took it away...
A crow?!
It finally had a chance to come in first...
I see...
So where is Enerune?
Huh? It was just right here...
Huh?!
Wait...
Airune claims first place!
In second, Coolrune!
In third, Loverune!
In fourth, Ururune!
No Enerune...
Yuka, you don't think Enerune went
to get the ribbon back from that crow...?
Enerune?!
Huh?
Enerune!
Enerune! That was amazing! Amazing!!
Whether you win or lose,
what matters most is you come out with a smile!
Alright!
I'll participate in Sports Day too!
What's this?
Not a spoon race,
but a spuni race!
Enerune, stay still!
Catch ya later!
I'm gonna win!
Let's go, Enerune!
Aoi is certainly competitive.
Punirunes Guide
Today on the Punirunes Guide...
Enerune
Enerune is mischievous and an amazing athlete!
The squestion!
It's time for the squestion!
How many meters high did it jump today?
The answer is...
1 meter!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
It's finally time to tell the story...
of the day Airune and I met!
Next Time
Next time: "Yuka and Airune♪"
Yuka and Airune♪
"Puni" in next time!