This Episode's Squishyyyy Highlights
Squishy
Punirunes. Before we knew it,
these creatures began to inhabit the human world.
They're very squishsterious creatures!
They all love to be squished.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Something's Cooking
on Valentine's Day♪
Yuka is hanging out with Aoi at her house.
So cute!
These two are having plenty of fun as well!
It's over!
What d'ya wanna watch next?
How about a manta ray video?
A what?
The biggest ray in the world!
It grows to be as wide as 6 meters!
Ever heard of it?
C-Can't say that I...
How about...
...the broadfin shark?
Or the cryptic bearded goby?
So cute, right?
I-I guess...
Fine, what do you want to watch?
Umm... I usually watch cooking videos.
Like, good temporing methods
to avoid blooming.
Huh? What does that even mean?
I'm not good at cooking like you are anyways...
Fine, watch your maple ray video then.
It's a "manta" ray!
And I don't care. Watch your temper videos.
It's tempering! Don't just call it whatever you want.
Why does it matter?
You went first, didn't you?
No, I didn't.
Yeah, Airune?
You think I took it too far?
Airune and Enerune ask the group for advice.
Ururune draws without thinking...
then gets even more shocked
upon seeing it.
Coolrune says to let things be,
let the wind take its course.
February winds are very chilly.
Loverune takes a walk around,
looking for ideas.
All set!
Why, hello, Loverune!
Hello!
This is a Valentine's Day sign!
Valentine's Day is when you
give someone special a gift
to tell them how you feel!
Which means people start buying
chocolate in swarms,
so we've gotta work real hard!
We're gonna boost our sales ten-fold!
Yeah!
It's a director?!
Loverune's Valentine's Day operation
is underway!
Hmm? "Valentine's Day is wonderful"?
If I make chocolates for her,
I should be able to easily make up with her?
Huh? What the?
Give her something on Valentine's Day?
Huh? What do you mean?
It would be a good idea
to make up with her on Valentine's Day...
But I don't know...
I can't really get myself to cook right now...
Loverune?
Huh? What is it?
What is it?
As part of the operation,
chocolate-making is already underway
in the kitchen!
Airune!
Are you okay?
That's not a chocolate!
That's chocolate fondue Airune!
You can melt it in the microwave,
but to make really good chocolate...
...there's something extra you can do!
They call this "tempering!"
By adjusting the temperature like this,
we can make the chocolate smooth
and melt in your mouth!
Take a look!
I made chocolate gummies!
Give them a taste!
Oh my!
This is bliss!
The theobromine in chocolate
is said to aid the brain substance serotonin,
which boosts our motivation and happiness.
That's to say, delicious foods
bring us happiness.
Why did I take things so far...?
Airune...
I...
want to apologize to Aoi.
How do I make my feelings clear?
I think that cooking is fun, and I like doing it.
If I make something that Aoi likes too...
That's it!
Aoi, I, uh...
I'm sorry!
Me too, I might've come on a bit too strong.
What's this?
Go ahead and open it!
A dolphin!
An orca too!
I thought, whatever my precious friend likes
is very precious to me too!
Yuka...
I almost don't want to eat them...
It tastes so good!
You're amazing, Yuka! Thank you!
I'm glad they made you happy!
I actually made you some Valentine's sweets too!
Huh? You did?
Here!
Thank you!
Are these chocolate daifuku?
Yeah!
Enerune and Coolrune
helped me come up with it!
They said since you liked squishy things,
that it might make you happy!
Really?
Thank you, Aoi!
And you, Enerune, Coolrune!
Like you said, what's precious to my friend
is precious to me too!
Making sweets is fun, but really hard!
So I thought I'd give it a shot!
You must be working really hard.
Aoi...
I'm sure it won't be as good as your cooking.
Delicious!
Thank goodness!
Mmm, it's a whole new texture!
Huh?
It's a brand new squish!
The syrupy chocolate melting in my mouth,
combined with the soft, doughy texture!
I never thought of this before!
I have to study it at once!
You really do like cooking and squishy things, huh?
Yeah...
Their friendship is rekindled,
thanks to the hard work of the Punirunes!
Oh, right! Here!
Valentines for all of you too!
Thanks for everything!
Happuni Valentine's Day!
Punirunes Guide
Today on the Punirunes Guide...
Loverune's Hearts ❤
Loverune
Loverune's hearts are free like the wind.
Today, they're Valentine's hearts!
The squestion!
It's time for the squestion!
Which one is the chocolate heart?
And begin!
The answer is...
This one!
If you found it,
have a happuni Valentine's day!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Leave Airune to your father — I'll take care of it!
Umm... Yuka?! What's Airune saying?!
Next Time
Next time: "Dad Watches Airune♪"
Dad Watches Airune♪
"Puni" in next time!