This Episode's Squishyyyy Highlights
Squishy
Punirunes. Before we knew it,
these creatures began to inhabit the human world.
They're very squishsterious creatures!
They all love to be squished.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Next, I'll bring this...
Meltyrunes Panic♪
Come in!
Yuka, are you all packed for tomorrow?
Yep, just finished!
We'll be leaving early tomorrow,
so don't stay up too late, okay?
Okay!
There's a baker's convention
happening in a faraway town,
so Yuka's family will be staying there overnight.
Hey, Airune!
I wonder what pastries there'll be in that town!
Mom told me it's by the beach too!
Man, I can't wait!
Let's explore together, okay?
We'll be leaving early, so let's get to sleep now.
But don't worry, I'll bring your house with me.
Good night, Airune!
Airune is so excited for the trip that it can't sleep.
It's swimming in the sea...
in its mind.
Taking a cool photo...
Relaxing in a hot spring...
yep, in its mind.
It ended up passing the time by imagining the trip.
We'll be leaving early, so let's get to sleep now.
But don't worry, I'll bring your house with me.
Airune melted from sadness
after being left behind.
I mean, you brought this on yourself...
In order to turn it back,
they'll have to squish it in Yuka's place.
Getting squished by other Punirunes
isn't going to turn it back, it looks.
Enerune has melted!
Not being able to play with Airune made it sad.
What will you do, Punirunes?
Good work, Coolrune!
Playing it cool and analyzing the situation...
it thought that showing them food
would cheer them up.
And now Loverune and Ururune have melted!
I see!
They're trying to get Komugi to come and squish them!
Coolrune, the last one standing,
has finally melted...
Now they're not Punirunes, but Meltyrunes.
When suddenly, Togerune shows up!
Looks like it's scheming up a prank.
Airune, are you okay?
Huh? It's not here...
Huh? Where is it?
Oh, no! Airune!
You guys!
I'm sorry for leaving you behind...
I was so sure you were sleeping away in your house...
I'm sorry to you all too.
You must have felt really lonely.
I was too, Airune.
Airune...
I'm so sorry!
Thank goodness.
What's going on here?
After melting and being stuck in place for a while,
their energy appears to have pent up.
Yuka!
Is everything alright?
Yeah! Uhh...
I think so.
Sure looks like it.
After everything, Airune still loves
Yuka's squishing the best.
Punirunes Guide
Today on the Punirunes Guide...
Meltyrunes
Punirunes melt when they're not taken good care of.
When they melt, they're not able to do anything.
The squestion!
It's time for the squestion!
How far do you think Enerune can move
in three seconds while melted?
The answer is...
3 millimeters!
So slow...
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
It's Christmas!
The Punirunes have been waiting so long for this!
Huh? Airune, who's that?
A secret? Aww, tell me!
Next Time
Next time: "A Merry Squishmas with Happyrune♪"
A Merry Squishmas
with Happyrune♪
"Puni" in next time!