Coming up on Punirunes...
The show is squishing!
Punirunes.
They're squishsterious creatures
you might find just nearby.
They all love to be squished.
When the Squishsterious Antenna glows,
a new puni-pal might come to hang out!
Nyarurune's Squishy Paws♪
"Nyarurune's Squishy Paws♪"
Tomorune wants to squish Komugi's paws.
Komugi seemed to be in a bad mood
and hurried off.
Tomorune feels dejected not getting
to squish Komugi's paws.
In response to Tomorune's desire
to squish paws,
Nyarurune
its puni-pal Nyarurune has arrived.
Tomorune got to squish paws at last.
Nyarurune is a cat-like Punirune.
Cat trivia #1:
Cats have good reflexes,
and are able to land safely
from a big fall.
Cat trivia #2:
Cats are cute.
Komugi has his eye on
this popular new friend.
Cat trivia #3:
Cats are very cool-headed,
but are actually prone to jealousy.
Nyarurune has never met a cat before.
Cat trivia #4:
Cats are very cautious,
especially around fresh faces.
Look! They're posing like
beckoning cats!
Cat trivia #5:
Cats are quite territorial,
and try to intimidate new cats
that enter their territory.
Airune and Enerune try to stop them...
Coolrune is helpless against them.
Now it's Loverune's turn!
They brought out their cat punches!
Ururune is next.
Will Ururune's tears
save the world?
Cat trivia #6: Cats are fickle.
Tomorune breakdances!
Cat trivia #7:
Cats are quick to react
to fast-moving things.
Nyarurune and Komugi
have chased Tomorune into the park.
Its hopes to make good friends
out of Nyarurune and Komugi
have quickly turned into a game of tag.
Look! They're going on the slide next!
Tomorune's trapped!
Komugi's paw...
and Nyarurune's paw...
have touched one another.
Cat trivia #8:
Cats' paws feel really good to squish.
You actually managed to get
those two to get along!
Astounding work, Tomorune!
Sorry. You did great too, Airune.
Tomorune got to squish
Komugi's paws at last.
Tomorune trivia #1:
Tomorune can make good friends
with just about anyone.
And now everyone is great friends.
The end!
Cat trivia #9:
Cats sleep often.
They're quite fickle after all.
The Puni Channel!
And squish.
Today, I'll be introducing Nyarurune.
Nyarurune
It's a cat-like Punirune.
It has good reflexes like a cat,
is cautious around new faces
like a cat,
and reacts quickly to fast moving things
like a cat.
It's fickle,
but very, very cute.
Time for the question.
What is the squishiest part
of Nyarurune's body?
Here's the answer!
Here's the answer...
The answer is...its paws!
Komugi seemed to like
squishing them too.
That's all for today!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
We're throwing a Christmas party today!
Oh yeah, Tomorune, you don't
know what Christmas is, huh?
When you think Christmas,
you think cake, feasts, and presents!
Next Time
It's just such a fun holiday!
B-But, um, Tomorune...
Next Time
You don't have to call so many puni-pals!
Next time: "Tomorune's First Merry Squishmas♪"
Tomorune's First
Merry Squishmas♪
"Puni" in next time!