Coming up on Punirunes...
The show is squishing!
Punirunes.
They're squishsterious creatures
you might find just nearby.
They all love to be squished.
When the Squishsterious Antenna glows,
a new puni-pal might come to hang out!
The Intense Face-Off
in Puniland♪
"The Intense Face-Off in Puniland♪"
Puniland
The battlefield: Puniland.
The opposing teams: Team Airune
and Team Tomorune.
A friend yesterday, an enemy today.
Will Team Tomorune...
manage to capture everyone
within this puni-cage?
Or will Team Airune escape their clutches
and manage to capture the flag?
It's an intense face-off
with everyone's pride on the line...
and it's underway.
Team Airune splits up,
evading the sunglasses-puni.
How will Team Tomorune catch them?
Leader Tomorune has something in mind.
Ururune finds a sketchbook,
now of all times.
It's been found.
Ururune is captured
Tomorune loves Ururune,
and knows well how much
it loves to draw.
Word of Ururune's capture
spreads in an instant.
Team Airune worries.
But they can still win
if they capture the flag.
Tidy Coolrune cannot ignore speckles of dust.
Team Airune won't crumble that easily.
Coolrune hides quickly
by playing a mannequin.
Meanwhile, Loverune's been found.
A concert begins,
here of all places.
Loverune starts performing mid-battle.
It cannot let down an audience.
Even the sunglasses-puni
has fallen for its charm.
Team Airune displays determination.
But Tomorune has cooked up
a terrifying plan.
It gave sunglasses...
to even more of its puni-pals!
An unexpected growth of sunglass-puni
spells trouble for Team Airune.
Loverune is captured
Coolrune is captured
With Coolrune and Loverune down,
only Airune and Enerune remain.
Airune's in trouble.
It leaves its hopes
in the hands of leader Airune.
Enerune is captured
Only Airune hasn't been captured.
And what of the captives?
They're surprisingly having a good time.
Airune is exhausted.
The captives seem to be having
more fun at this point.
Will Airune give up?
Tomorune is moved by
Airune's earnest spirit.
The two leaders battle for it all.
Will the flag be captured,
or Airune?
They muster the last of their
energy and leap for it!
Will Airune capture the flag?
Will Tomorune capture Airune?
Everyone is cheering Airune on!
Team Airune finally takes the win.
This was actually their first game of tag,
a game Yuka and Aoi often play.
And it went perfectly—everyone had a blast.
I'm glad you enjoyed your game.
Hmm?
You're playing it again?!
Punirunes Album
Punirunes Album!
The Punirunes have visited
a café created by Loverune.
Oh? Is Airune still hungry?
It's asking for more of
its favorite appuni pie.
Huh? You want more?!
Loverune wants them
to enjoy their food.
It fills its hearts with that sentiment
and sprinkles it all over!
Ka-pow!
The food has come out cute, squishy,
and full of love!
Airune is in bliss,
having the yummiest appuni pie!
And eating with all its friends
makes it all the happier!
Both its tummy and its heart
are full.
"Thank you, Loverune!"
Punirunes Album
What memories do you think
they'll make next?
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Whoa, Airune, Enerune,
what's wrong?
Enerune's in trouble?
Oh no, it is! It melted!
Next Time
Don't worry. My squishing
will bring it back in no time.
Huh? That's not enough?
Next Time
You have to be a sea animal?
Uh, explain.
Next time: "Enerune Melts♪"
Enerune Melts♪
"Puni" in next time!