Coming up on Punirunes...
The show is squishing!
Punirunes.
They're squishsterious creatures
you might find just nearby.
They all love to be squished.
When the Squishsterious Antenna glows,
a new puni-pal might come to hang out!
Angelrune Brings Us Luck♪
"Angelrune Brings Us Luck♪"
The Punirunes are having fun as always.
They lost both their gummies
and their crayon.
The Punirunes seem awful unlucky today.
It's Tomorune's puni-pal, Angelrune.
Angelrune
Angelrune's arrows make something lucky
happen to whoever it strikes!
How amazing!
They all want Angelrune to show off
the power of its arrows.
First, it will bring luck to Tomorune.
That doesn't count!
Looks like Angelrune isn't too good
at hitting its targets.
They got hit, but nothing happened.
Oh, dear. Yuka's pencil case
fell underneath her desk.
Their luck has come in!
Angelrune's arrows really are amazing!
Well, that's one way to stay on target.
What's this?
Togerune's come to play some mischief!
Angelrune's not too sure
what just happened either.
"Don't worry, I'll figure something out,"
Angelrune says.
Hitting them with another arrow might undo it.
Will Angelrune hit Togerune
with its arrow?
It missed!
It's got it this time!
Oh, dear!
It feels super depressed.
Togerune's trying to make
Angelrune feel better!
The thorn-less Togerune wants to
give Togerune something.
Togerune's luck has come in.
It was lucky enough to
experience squish contact!
They wanted to thank Angelrune
for giving them luck.
Angelrune's arrow hit its target at last!
But nothing happened.
I see.
Tomorune considers itself lucky
to make Angelrune happy.
Angelrune's going on a journey
to spread luck all over.
Keep an eye out,
Angelrune might come to visit you!
The Puni Channel!
And squish.
Today, I'll be introducing Angelrune.
Angelrune
A puni-pal of Tomorune's
it invited through Puni-Pal Link.
When you're struck by its arrow,
something lucky will happen to you.
There's one problem.
It's not good at hitting its targets.
But it doesn't give up.
Time for the question.
Who did Angelrune's arrow
strike first?
Here's the answer!
Here's the answer...
The answer is Ururune!
And it's on its way to bring
luck to you too!
That's all for today.
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Tomorune, you wanna be squished
under Komugi's paws?
Oh my, that Punirune looks like a cat!
So you're called Nyarurune!
Next Time
Good for you, Tomorune,
getting to feel some squishy paws!
Wait, what? Nyarurune
and Komugi are fighting!
Tomorune, you gotta do something!
Next Time
Next time: "Nyarurune's Squishy Paws♪"
Nyarurune's Squishy Paws♪
"Puni" in next time!