Coming up on Punirunes...
The show is squishing!
Punirunes.
They're squishsterious creatures
you might find just nearby.
They all love to be squished.
When the Squishsterious Antenna glows,
a new puni-pal might come to hang out!
for Everyone♪
Valentine's Day Gifts ❤
"Valentine's Day Gifts ❤ for Everyone♪"
Darling, would you mind helping me
with these chocolates?
I'm on it!
I've got this side.
Thank you a choco-lot!
One, two... Hup!
Yuka's family business
has had a busy day so far!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Off we go!
Oh? Of course they're busy!
It's Valentine's Day!
Oh, yeah. You don't know
what that is, do you?
Allow me to explain Valentine's Day...
It's a big event that comes
once a year!
A great day of battle, you could say!
Mom and Dad are at war with the chocolate,
fighting for their lives to make it
even more delicious!
That's how I see it, anyways.
It's super fun!
I don't suppose Yuka's description
gave Tomorune a good idea
of Valentine's Day, did it?
This is Puniland.
Both of them received chocolate gummies
from Loverune.
Valentine's Day is a great day of battle!
We're fighting for our lives!
Tomorune, don't fight with the chocolate.
"Valentine's Day is when you give
chocolates to your loved puni-pals,"
Loverune explains.
Now Tomorune challenges itself
to see how many chocolates it can give.
They head straight to the Squishy Market
to buy some chocolate gummies.
This store belongs to Cuprune,
Puniland's top pastry chef.
No way! Tomorune wants to buy out
all the chocolate gummies on the shelves!
Even less way! It doesn't just want
the ones on the shelves,
it wants to buy out the store's whole stock!
Tomorune has a heap of chocolate gummies.
Impressive. You're really going to give out
all of these by the end of the day?
Loverune gets one first!
Next up is Enerune.
Then Ururune.
It cries tears of joy.
One for Coolrune too.
Ururune's a friendly spirit
with lots of puni-pals.
As such, it's a real task
to hand out chocolates all over Puniland.
Huh? All that and there's still
a mountain left?
Tomorune and Airune
head to a popular park in Puniland.
This should allow them to give many
puni-pals chocolates in one spurt.
There's even more takers
than they expected!
Things are getting real hectic!
Oh my! The park has turned
into a chocolate gummy land!
Everyone is loving it!
The evening star twinkles in the sky.
It's gotten late, and now they must go home.
Their Valentine's Day was busy,
but they enjoyed getting to hand out
chocolates to everyone.
Airune and Tomorune
give each other chocolate gummies.
Eating their chocolates
gave them energy.
Happy Valentine's Day.
You two did great.
Oh? Hey, there's still
a chocolate gummy left!
Tomorune...
Was there another good puni-pal
you wanted to give one to?
Punirunes Album
Punirunes Album.
"P-P-P-Puni..."
A shrill cry echoed through
the haunted mansion.
The Babyrunes head in,
trembling as they walk,
when they're greeted by
many a ghost.
Then, all of a sudden, a voice goes...
"Peek-a-boo..."
"Peek-a..."
"Boo!"
Hey, that wasn't scary at all!
Have you figured it out?
Those cries were actually their laughs.
They weren't trying to scare the Babyrunes,
but make them happy.
The Punirunes put together
a very joyful haunted house.
Punirunes Album
What memories do you think
they'll make next?
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Why so grumpy, Tomorune?
Airune broke its promise?
Did you, Airune?
Next Time
I don't think it meant to.
You should forgive it, Tomorune.
Hey, please don't fight!
Next Time
Agh! Can't somebody stop them?
Next time: "Airune and Tomorune's Fight♪"
Airune and Tomorune's Fight♪
"Puni" in next time!