Coming up on Punirunes...
The show is squishing!
Punirunes.
They're squishsterious creatures
you might find just nearby.
They all love to be squished.
When the Squishsterious Antenna glows,
a new puni-pal might come to hang out!
Celebrating
an Anniversary♪
"Celebrating an Anniversary♪"
Hey, Yuka.
What's this picture?
Oh, that?
It's the first time we made bread together!
You've never seen that one before,
have you, Tomorune?
What about this?
Hm? Oh, this...
That photo's from the day Airune moved in.
Wow!
What's going on here?
Oh!
Oh right, today's the day...
Huh?
Alright.
I'm gonna go refill the gummies!
Did you guys hear that?!
Yuka looked at a photo from the day Airune moved in,
and said, "today's the day!"
You know what that means?
Today's their anniversary!
An anniversary is a way to remember
a special day!
The day Airune moved in
is a very special anniversary for them!
Huh? You want to celebrate it?
Loverune is a Punirune
full of love.
It wants to celebrate Yuka and Airune's
anniversary by surprising them.
Great idea!
They're going to be so happy!
But can we set something up
without them noticing?
Loverune has a plan!
Wow, you look like a movie director!
Amazing, Director Loverune!
What a perfect plan!
Yeah!
The anniversary surprise plan is a go!
First, they must bring
Yuka and Airune to the park.
Act natural. Don't let them find out!
Ehem!
G-Good day, Yuka!
Uh, good day.
Is something wrong?
You see, Yuka...
There's uh, something in the park...
There's a whale shark in the park!
A whale shark?!
We have to act fast, or it'll be gone!
Let's go!
¡V-V-Vamos!
Huh? What? Hey! Aah!
Coolrune and Ururune
are decorating Yuka's room.
They've gotten straight to work.
Oh? What's up, Tomorune?
Tomorune is asking Mom and Dad
to make a cake.
Ururune drew this.
A cake?
You want some, don't you?
Huh?! Did something happen to them?
That's a relief.
Oh, I see. It must want us
to make cake for Yuka and Airune.
Alright, then!
We're on topknot of this!
We'll make a delicious cake
they'll both love!
Great work from Tomorune.
It got the message
to them crystal clear.
While preparations are underway,
Enerune and Aoi buy time in the park.
Where's that whale shark?
Oh? Huh?
Isn't that...
Yuniko!
Oh? Yuka and Aoi.
I get it, this is a surprise!
A-A surprise?
You brought me to the park
to surprise me with Yuniko, didn'tcha?
No, uh, I...
What's the matter?
Nothing! Everything's fine!
The word surprise just reminded me
of when I first met Enerune, that's all.
Right, Enerune?
When you first met, huh?
Oh no!
It was sort of the same
when I met Airune.
Shoot!
Do you remember, Airune?
Umm...
Uhh, what do I...
You're awful excitable today, Enerune.
Y-Yeah!
When you first met?
Getting hungry?
Let's head back.
We have gummies at home.
N-Not yet!!
Huh?
Why not?
Ah!
G-Good question...
This is bad. They're not ready yet!
Oh my! It's a whale shark!
Wow!
It's so beautiful!
Keep it up, Enerune! You've got this!
That was beautiful!
You weren't kidding about the whale shark.
Let's go home.
What?!
Decorations are almost done.
Coolrune is taking a break by the window.
Oh no! This is bad!
Ururune may be tearful,
but it braves through for Yuka and Airune,
turning its tears into a powerful force!
Oh dear! We won't finish decorating in time!
I'm home!
Huh?!
What's all this?
Happy anniversary, Yuka and Airune!
Huh?
Did you all set this up?
Aw, guys...
This outfit was designed
by the fashion leader Coolrune.
The plan was a success!
Awesome!
Celebrating an anniversary...
Wow! Thanks so much!
So what's today?
Huh?
What?
What did you mean when you said
"today's the day" while we were looking at photos?
Oh, yeah.
I remembered that today was the day
Airune ate too many gummies and couldn't move.
Gah!
It can't be!
But I still appreciate it!
Thanks, you guys!
Maybe it was a misunderstanding,
but since everyone is celebrating,
today may as well be an anniversary.
The Puni Channel!
And squish.
Today, I'll be introducing
Coolrune and Ururune.
Coolrune and Ururune
Coolrune is a very tidy Punirune.
It's the fashion leader of the group
and loves following trends.
Ururune is a tearful Punirune.
It's an artist who's always drawing.
Time for the question.
What did Coolrune and Ururune do
to help prepare for the anniversary?
Here's the answer...
Here's the answer!
The answer is decorating Yuka's room!
They worked well together.
That's all for today!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Airune, Tomorune, why the glum looks?
So your luck's been bad today, huh?
Next Time
You know just the one to call?
Oh, hello there, Angelrune!
Huh? You bring everyone
happiness and luck?
Next Time
That's awesome!
Angelrune Brings Us Luck♪
Next time: "Angelrune Brings Us Luck♪"
"Puni" in next time!