Coming up on Punirunes...
The show is squishing!
Punirunes.
They're squishsterious creatures
you might find just nearby.
They all love to be squished.
When the Squishsterious Antenna glows,
a new puni-pal might come to hang out!
The Festival with Utarune♪
"The Festival with Utarune♪"
Hi, guys!
Airune, Tomorune!
What's the singing about?
Wow, you're holding a music event
in Puniland?
And it's called the Punirunes Festival,
or Punifest for short?
Sounds like fun!
Huh?
You want to call in a big guest?
That would make things more exciting.
Utarune
This is Utarune.
It's a Punirune who loves to sing.
Wait, the top superstar
in Puniland?
That's awesome!
Gee, Tomorune can even make
puni-pals with a superstar!
Wow! They must all be fans of Utarune!
Are you Utarune's manager?
It's a squish contact event.
It's a real fan-pleaser,
like any superstar.
Me too!
Puni-squishy!
A squishy for you too, Manager!
Airune and Tomorune ask Utarune
to perform in the festival.
It's checking the schedule.
It has a recording session
followed by a music video shoot,
and has to rehearse for its puni-dome tour.
Talk about a packed schedule!
But it sounds fun,
so you wanna do it?
Utarune is in!
Happy for you!
Hope Punifest goes well!
Good luck!
Flash forward...
to the day of Punifest.
The audience is packed!
"Our opening act is...
"Loverune!"
Loverune's idol performance
steals the crowd's hearts.
"Next up is...
"Puni-Pal 5!"
Their cool dance routine
has the audience pumped up!
Coming up after this
is Utarune's performance!
Though there's a problem.
"Huh? Utarune is falling behind?"
Squishy Market is awful crowded today.
Could it be?
Oh no! It's pleasing its fans!
Agh, it's even giving out autographs!
That concludes the Puni-Pal 5
feat. Tomorune show.
Airune is going to fetch Utarune.
In the meantime...
Tomorune has an idea!
It's Enerune's circus show!
I see. They're going to buy time
until Utarune makes it to the festival.
Next, Coolrune's magic trick!
But the audience is confused
why Utarune isn't on stage yet.
Where could Utarune be, they ask?
Try and try as they may...
the audience is getting tired of waiting.
"Hurry up, Utarune!"
The time has come!
The headliner act of the Punifest...
Utarune's performance!
My goodness, this is amazing!
The Punirunes are united
through Utarune's song.
Punirunes Album
Punirunes Album!
It's finally time for Coolrune's fashion show.
It's the other Punirunes'
first time modeling!
They're almost up...
Will they be ready in time?
Coolrune gets a head start
and struts a cool walk down the runway.
The other Punirunes have...
five seconds to get ready?!
Get a move on!
It's showtime!
Phew, just in the nick of time.
Huh? Enerune's missing a shoe.
I suppose this is fashionable
in its own way.
Their first time modeling
went perfectly!
Fantastic!
Punirunes Album
What memories do you think
they'll make next?
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Airune, Tomorune! You look giddy.
What'cha up to?
Huh? A Punirunes camping trip
in the backyard?
Next Time
Aw, you're in for a treat!
You get to eat yummy food outdoors
and have a campunifire!
And of course,
tell scary stories at dark!
Next Time
It's gonna be super-duper fun!
Next time: "Punirunes Go Camping♪"
Punirunes Go Camping♪
"Puni" in next time!