Coming up on Punirunes...
The show is squishing!
Punirunes.
They're squishsterious creatures
you might find just nearby.
They all love to be squished.
When the Squishsterious Antenna glows,
a new puni-pal might come to hang out!
Comin' Right Up! Sushirune♪
"Comin' Right Up! Sushirune♪"
I'm gonna go eat sushi with
Mom and Dad today!
I made sure to cook up
your favorites for dinner!
Here, Airune, your appuni pie!
And Tomorune, your puni burger!
I can't wait to have some sushi!
Yuka, do you have a moment?
Yeah?
Your father has a situation...
I'm a failure of a baker!
He's stumped on ideas
for a new pastry.
And you know how he gets.
Oh boy...
So I don't think we'll get to eat out today.
We'll have to save sushi for another day.
Gotta do what you gotta do
for the shop, I guess.
Sorry, Yuka!
We'll talk later, Yuka!
Okay, Mom.
So no sushi today...
Huh? You've never seen sushi before?
Here, I'll show you.
This here is sushi!
Sushirune
Tomorune has invited its puni-pals,
the Sushirunes, over.
Hi there! I'm Yuka!
Wow, you really do look like sushi!
You're like salmon sushi!
And you're like maguro!
I see! Altogether, you're Sushirunes!
So squishy! So cute!
Oh?
The Sushirunes are interested
in the foods they see.
Looks like the Sushirunes
don't like appuni pie.
The Sushirunes are eating a hamburger!
So weird.
They finished the plate in a flash!
Looks like puni burgers
are the Sushirunes' favorite food.
The Sushirunes also love
sitting on plates.
When you sit out on that plate,
you look even more like real sushi!
Oh, that gives me an idea!
Squishing you like this
makes me feel like a sushi chef!
Irasshai! Welcome in!
So funny.
Do I like sushi?
Well, of course...
I love sushi!
Oh? You want to learn what
human world sushi is like?
Well, there's many kinds.
But personally, I like the restaurants
where the sushi spins around!
Uh, you're spinning in circles?
Back in Action
So that's how you function...
Oh, and that's not exactly
what I meant by sushi spinning.
That's not what I meant either...
Oh, I know. Sushirunes,
take a look at this clip.
See, this is how the sushi spins around.
Oh, wow! It's norimaki,
temaki, and gunkanmaki sushi!
The Sushirunes are entertainers.
They love to make others happy.
Huh? What's that?
You're going to put on a quiz now?
I'm down! Sounds like fun!
So you want us to guess which one of you
is hiding that wasabi-like spot?
Alright! I'm gonna ace this!
Viewers, try taking on
the Sushirunes' quiz too!
Quiz (Easy Course)
Hmm... Which one is it...?
This one maybe?
How about you? Do you think you got it?
What's the answer?
Awesome! I got it!
Too bad for you, Airune.
You'll get it next time!
Huh? The next one will be
uber-difficult?
Quiz (Uber-Difficult)
I can't keep up!
Now that's real fast.
Talk about uber-difficult!
"Take a guess!"
...Who could possibly?
Dang it! I don't know,
it was too fast!
I'll just have to guess randomly!
This one!
So? Which one is it?
Wow! Good job, Airune,
you got it right!
That was a lot of fun!
Huh?
I give up!
Are you okay, Darling?
Good enough isn't good enough!
It has to be something special!
A pastry so unique
it blows everyone away!
Hang in there, Dad!
Yeah! Give it your all-star!
Oh?
Hey, now.
I need you to move over.
That plate's going to be washed.
And you sat right back down on it.
What a bother.
You little plate-seekers.
Oh my!
Aha! That's it!
Huh?!
It's ready! Feast your eyes!
My very own Three-Course Power Bun!
And I have you three to thank
for helping me come up with it.
Darling!
You did fin-tastic today!
Now that you're done fishing for ideas,
let's not shrimp out on
the celebrations!
I'm inking sushi for dinner!
Sound good?
Sure does! Let's go get some sushi!
Yay!
Coming right up!
Yeah!
It's revolving sushi!
Punirunes Album
Punirunes Album!
This is Squishy Park,
beloved by all.
The Punirunes are riding the ferry wheel
and roller coaster,
and look like they're having
a great time.
Wait! Airune, are you okay?
Airune looks somewhat frightened.
Its friends are worried.
Tomorune seems to have
thought of something.
Hey, Tomorune,
what do you think will
put a smile on Airune's face?
A merry-go-round!
This cheered Airune right up.
Puni-pals are a lovely thing.
Now, all the Punirunes
will continue their fun day at Squishy Park.
Punirunes Album
What memories do you think
they'll make next?
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
With Puniland as their battlefield,
the Punirunes battle
with their fates on the line.
Airune runs!
Tomorune chases!
Next Time
They'll run, hide,
and throw sunglasses-puni
off their trail?!
They have to stay on their toes!
Just who will claim victory?!
Next Time
The Intense Face-Off
in Puniland♪
Next time: "The Intense Face-Off in Puniland♪"
You'd best "puni" in!