Coming up on Punirunes...
The show is squishing!
Punirunes.
They're squishsterious creatures
you might find just nearby.
They all love to be squished.
When the Squishsterious Antenna glows,
a new puni-pal might come to hang out!
The Punirunes
Watch the Moon♪
"The Punirunes Watch the Moon♪"
So this is a supermoon?
Yeah!
It's when the full moon
appears the biggest all year—
and that's today!
Really?
That's so cool!
Did you know?
The moon and sea have
a very strange relationship.
They do?
For example...
Horseshoe crabs and corals
lay their eggs on full moons!
Also, supposedly pufferfish
all get together and spawn on beaches!
It's an amazing experience
that takes 2 hours!
I've seen videos of it,
but I want to see it for myself someday!
O-Oh, really? Interesting.
Wow...
"Let's have a sleepover
and watch the full moon!" it says.
Everyone's on board!
That's too bad.
The moon's blocked by the clouds.
You must be getting tired.
Alright now, it's time for bed.
Punirunes always fall asleep at 8 P.M.
Oh? Tomorune got up.
It just remembered a certain someone!
This is Hikarune,
a Punirune resembling a crescent moon.
Hikarune
Another one of Tomorune's puni-pals.
Puni-Pal Link
Tomorune calls on its friends
using Puni-Pal Link.
Oh, they woke up the other Punirunes.
It says that Hikarune can
take on the form of a full moon.
Seems Hikarune's very bashful.
Puniland
They looked all over,
but Hikarune's nowhere to be found.
Airune wishes it had been able
to make friends with Hikarune.
There's Hikarune!
Hikarune's bashful
and doesn't want to be seen.
Hikarune started peeking out
to see Tomorune dance.
The Punirunes are going to do their very best
to make Hikarune come out!
Starting off...
enjoy this magic show!
Next up...
you're invited to a special concert!
It's super effective!
And the last act goes to Airune!
Now that's a face full of confidence!
I think we can expect an amazing performance!
Airune's Ultra-Super Tornado Special!
It messed up.
Alas, they're back to square one.
As hard as they've tried,
Hikarune is still hidden away.
And the Punirunes
are getting too tired to go on.
"As long as we're together,
we can keep going!" it says.
The others aren't planning
on giving up either.
It worked!
Everyone's fallen asleep.
Is this it for them?
Is this as far as they go?
Hikarune was touched
seeing them work so hard!
It seems Hikarune's glow
is able to give them energy.
"It's so beautiful!" they say.
The moon showed itself here as well.
The Puni Channel!
And squish.
Today, I'll be introducing Hikarune.
Hikarune
Hikarune is a Punirune who was called
to Airune's house with Puni-Pal Link.
It resembles a beautiful moon.
But it's very shy,
and doesn't often appear to others.
Sometimes it hides behind clouds,
and when it's happy,
it takes on the shape of a full moon.
Time for the question.
What can Hikarune's glow do?
Here's the answer...
Here's the answer!
The answer is: it gives everyone energy!
What a wonderful ability.
That's all for today!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Huh? Airune, you got into
a fight with Enerune?
Yeah, you should go apologize to Enerune.
Wait, Enerune?
Next Time
Airune just went to see you.
What? Airune?!
Enerune already went home!
If you keep going back and forth,
you'll never meet up!
Next Time
Next time: "Squish! Let's Puni-Pal Link♪"
Squish!
Let's Puni-Pal Link♪
"Puni" in next time!