This Episode's Squishyyyy Points
Squishy
Punirunes. Before we knew it,
these creatures began to inhabit the human world.
They're very squishsterious creatures!
They all love to be squished.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
That was amazing!
They're putting on a performance for a Halloween party.
Bakerune on Halloween♪
Those pumpkin costumes
are so cute!
You really wowed me with that dance too!
Do you know what Halloween is?
You don't?!
Every October 31st,
People say it's a celebration of the autumn harvest!
It's also the day when the spirits of our ancestors
return to their families.
Mhm!
She actually just learned that in class today.
Why do people dress up as monsters, you ask?
Because...
I dunno!
You don't?!
The spirits of our ancestors bring back
evil demons and witches with them,
so dressing up as monsters
is to make them all feel welcomed.
Mhm!
There's one more fun thing about Halloween!
You dress up as monsters and scare grown-ups
by saying "trick-or-treat!"
And they give you treats!
All done!
Oh, pumpkin cakes!
They look so good! I'll give it a taste...
– No you don't!
– Ow!
This is for Yuka and the Punirunes.
Boo-hoo...
Trick-or-treat!
M-M-Monsters!!
Have mercy on us!
Neither of them are very great actors.
Give us treats, or we'll play a trick on you!
Darling, get some treats!
We should have some gummies...
W-Will this do?
H-Help yourself to some pumpkin cakes!
Honey, we have to get out of here!
Okay!
We scored big!
These pumpkin cakes look so good...
Let's make use of this pumpkin cake!
It's squisine time!
Squisine Time!
Give it some of the squishsterious squishence...
Stir it...
Knead it...
Give it a squishy kneading so it'll be nice and fluffy!
Plumpkin Cake
Plumpkin Cake, ready to serve!
Dig in!
Do you like it?
Who's sneaking around up here?
I'll start giving out gummies!
Here.
Your gummies disappeared?
What are Ururune's gummies doing over there?
Huh? Airune took them?
They're starting to get suspicious of Airune.
Now, hold on. Why would Airune have
a reason to take Ururune's gummies?
What's wrong, Airune?
Airune...
"It was floating around...
"became see-through...
"and passed through the door?"
It wasn't a ghost!
None of them believed Airune.
You were hungry, right?
But you can't take Enerune's gummy.
Huh?
Trick-or-treat!
Looks like the shock knocked him unconscious!
Who is he?
Oh! He's squishable!
Are you alright?
I guess we gave you too big a scare.
We're sorry.
His name is Bakerune!
Bakerune
You're a bit of a scaredy cat for a ghost, though.
Why did you take their gummies?
I see. You wanted to be friends with them,
but couldn't speak out and tried to get their attention.
Airune, sorry for doubting you.
Have some plumpkin cake!
Trick-or-treat!
So weird!
But we worked hard on these costumes...
They're not very great at costumes either.
Bakerune really is easily frightened for a ghost.
The Punirunes Guide!
Punirunes Guide
Today...
Bakerune
Bakerune loves scaring people,
but he's easily scared himself.
Squiz time!
Monsters
Dark Spaces
Komugi
Which of these is Bakerune most scared of?
1. Monsters?
2. Dark Spaces?
Or 3. Komugi?
The answer is...
All three!
Take care, Bakerune!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, touch it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Seeing them all full
Is just such a warm sight♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
When you think about it (Squish! Squish!)
Friendship is (Squish! Squish!)
A very squishsterious thing!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, touch it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Airune wants to be stylish!
You're going to help her, Kuurune?
What do you have planned?
Next time: "Kuurune Gets Stylish♪"
Next Time
Kuurune Gets Stylish♪
Squish into the next episode!