This Episode's Squishyyyy Points
Squishy
Punirunes. Before we knew it,
these creatures began to inhabit the human world.
They're very squishsterious creatures!
They all love to be squished.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Dad Watches Airune♪
Oh?
Looks like the bakery is closed today!
Here you go!
Please take good care of her, Dad!
Of course!
While you and Mom are out,
I'll man the house with Airune!
If she gets hungry, make her food with squishence!
And don't forget to bathe her if she gets dirty!
I know, don't have to wear it out!
I'm a certified L1 caretaker!
You can count on me!
Certified? You're not certified.
You got me.
I left some food in the kitchen
for you to eat for lunch.
Huh? I can just make myself lunch, you know.
You shouldn't!
You know you worked yourself too hard
for the store's anniversary yesterday!
You should kick back today and take it easy!
Darling...
See you later!
Have a fun trip!
I was hoping I could spend time with Yuka,
but if they insist...
Today, I'll kick back and...
Hello, everyone!
Oh! Interesting, I see.
Uh, sorry. I don't actually know
what you're saying.
Yuka's Dad doesn't understand the Punirunes' speech.
Oh, I know!
Do you want to play outside?
I thought I'd get to take it easy...
S-Such an innocent look in their eyes...
They want me that much...
I must respond to that!
Alright! Get ready to spend the day
playing with Daddy!
Alright!
Now run!
They're about to play Tag.
When I was in college, I was known in
the table tennis club as the Swift Noble Steed.
I can do this...
You can't run from me!
He's really getting into it.
Tag!
Huh?!
No fair!
T-Tag...
L-Let's play... something else...
5...
6...
7...
Now they're playing Hide and Seek!
8...
9...
10!
Alright!
When I was little, I completed the
Perfect Detective Collection!
I'll sniff all of you out, lickety-split!
How am I supposed to find...
...such tiny little creatures?
Uh, I mean, I'll find you!
Found one!
Uh, umm...
Oh, never mind. Didn't find one. No siree.
Gosh, I'm beat...
You still want to play?
Oh, no! A crow is after the Punirunes!
Have no fear!
I took a three-month online karate class!
Do you think you can defeat me?!
Then come at me!
They're giving him a massage.
Thanks, I feel a lot better.
Hm? What's up?
Oh, I know! "Daddy, that was so cool!" Right?
Aw, where's all the praise
for saving you from that crow, huh?
Oh, you're hungry, aren't you?
Mommy makes the best rice balls, doesn't she?
Alright! Just like Yuka taught me,
let's squish up a dish!
Squisine Time!
It's squisine time!
Give it some of the squishsterious squishence...
Stir it...
Knead it...
Give it a squishy kneading so it'll be nice and fluffy!
Rice Squish
Rice squish, ready to serve!
Thought it'd be nice to eat outside for this occasion.
Good with you?
Everyone liked Dad's rice squishes.
I'm glad.
Whew, I'm beat.
Yuka sure has gotten big...
I bet the more time passes...
she'll probably want to spend less time with me.
And th-then...
Yuka, don't leave me!!
Komugi?!
Are you trying to console me?
Thank you, but I'm fine.
Nothing will make me happier as a parent
than to see my little girl all grown up.
Um-um-um-um, w-wait, K-Komugi?!
Don't leave me!!
We're home!
Oh, you're back!
Dad!
Sorry we're late!
Welcome home, Yuka, Darling!
This is for you!
What's this?
It's from the both of us.
To say congratulations on the store's anniversary!
Though we're a day late...
Pajamas!
Now you can get some good sleep!
Yuka...
Darling...
Thank youuu!!
Thank you so much!!
Dad, you're overdoing it!
Huh?! Dad hurt his back trying to chase off a crow
and had to sleep it off on the ouch?
But Airune had a lot of fun.
Well, that's good to hear.
Never!!
Yuka spent ages picking those out for you!
Just wear them!
Never!!
I'll put it up on the wall
and keep it in good condition until I die!!
Today on the Punirunes Guide...
Punirunes Guide
Squisine
By stirring and kneading squishence into food,
you can make Punirunes food.
It's squiz time!
Squishing à la Mode
Plumpple Pie
Rice Squish
What squisine did Dad make for the Punirunes?
The answer is...
Rice squish!
It was very delicious!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, touch it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Seeing them all full
Is just such a warm sight♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
When you think about it (Squish! Squish!)
Friendship is (Squish! Squish!)
A very squishsterious thing!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, touch it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Airune and Enerune,
did you make this huge mess?!
Next Time
Ugh, what do I do?!
Huh? Kuurune, you want to clean it up?
Next Time
Next time: "Punirunes Clean Together♪"
Punirunes Clean Together♪
Squish into the next episode!