This Episode's Squishyyyy Points
Squishy
Punirunes. Before we knew it,
these creatures began to inhabit the human world.
They're very squishsterious creatures!
They all love to be squished.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Merry Squishmas with Hapirune♪
It's Christmas day!
We're going to throw a party
and have a huge feast!
You might even get presents!
I can't think of anything!!
Mom and Dad are trying to think up
a special dish for the party.
I better give them a hand.
Looks like the Punirunes are
going to get ready for the party!
Oh?
I just thought of something!
Oh, my! This is a surprise!
It's the Punirune that loves making everybody happy...
Hapirune!
Hapirune
Hapirune is a professional
who makes people around him happy
without anyone seeing him.
Airune is making a Christmas tree out of building blocks.
Raburune is trying to come up with
a special variant of her hearts.
Kuurune is studying a special outfit for the party.
Ururune is drawing a Christmas tree.
Enerune is training to make himself hungry
for the feast...
Looks like it worked too well.
Aha, found you!
Huh?
Where'd the star go?
Huh? It's gone...
What now...?
We can't have a Christmas tree without a star!
Hapirune is set on making Yuka happy
by finding the tree star!
Yuka, did you find it?
Yeah!
Coming!
Airune is going to ask Yuka
to make food for Enerune.
Airune spotted Hapirune like nothing!
Hapirune is too busy looking for the star
to be bothered by Airune.
Hapirune's rule is to make people happy
without anyone seeing him.
Shooting stars!
She's finished her special Christmas hearts!
And Kuurune found the finishing touch for her outfit!
Ururune and Enerune are also very happy now!
Oh, there's the star!
Huh?
Togerune, did you bring this to me?
Thanks a ton, Togerune!
What's up?
So soothing!
That's it!
How about a matcha warabimochi bread?
That sounds great!
Then we can add red raisins
to give it a Christmas color palette!
Absolutely perfecto!
Thanks again, Togerune.
Merry Christmas!
Those presents are from me!
Hapirune has to go soon.
What's up, Airune?
Hm? You want a squish?
Sure, no problem!
Squishy-squish!
It's very cold outside.
I'm so glad I got to have a party with you all...
It was so fun!
Huh? That felt like a completely new texture...
So pretty!
What do you think is shining up there?
Airune got to meet Hapirune
and had a very merry Christmas.
Maybe Hapirune will come to your place next!
Punirunes Guide
The Punirunes Guide!
Today...
Hapirune
Hapirune is a Punirune that loves making people happy!
It's squiz time!
Where's Hapirune?
Look for him!
The answer is...
Here!
If you found him, tomorrow will be a very happy day!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, touch it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Seeing them all full
Is just such a warm sight♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
When you think about it (Squish! Squish!)
Friendship is (Squish! Squish!)
A very squishsterious thing!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, touch it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Oh, no!
Airune changed colors!
Everyone's acting weird!
What's going on here?!
Next Time
Next time: "Punirunes Swap Colors♪"
Punirunes Swap Colors♪
Squish into the next episode!