This Episode's Squishyyyy Points
Squishy
Punirunes. Before we knew it,
these creatures began to inhabit the human world.
They're very squishsterious creatures!
They all love to be squished.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
What am I doing?
There's a chorus at school during music class!
But I'm not really a great singer...
You'll cheer me on?
Thank you! I'll do my best!
See you later!
Airune wants to know what school is like.
According to Aoi,
they study...
play...
and eat lunch, says Enerune.
Airune still wants to know more.
Pikarune
The Punirunes have called their friend Pikarune.
Airune asked him to teach them
what school is like.
Pikarune is very wise.
He writes everything in that book he's holding.
Pikarune has agreed to be their teacher
and teach them about school!
Pikarune Does Elementary School♪
Class is in session at Mr. Pikarune's
Punirunes Elementary School!
First period is Math.
Be quiet during class!
What is 3+2?
That's very wrong, Enerune.
I'm not sure how this works,
but these hearts are spreading all over!
The answer is 5.
Second period is Science.
When you mix red and yellow,
you get orange!
If you mix yellow and blue,
whose color do you get?
They think it will turn the color of Kuurune.
Where have they seen this color before?
It's the color of Togerune!
Now they're mixing Airune and Ururune's colors...
And it turned Kuurune's color!
How would they make Raburune's color?
Third period is Music!
Airune offered for Pikarune to sing with them...
But he's not very good at exercise or singing.
I'm home!
Chorus went well!
Oh, you brought a friend over to play?
Pikarune, huh?
I'm Yuka! Nice to meet you!
I heard you guys earlier, what were you up to?
A chorus?!
Let me sing with you guys!
Wanna sing too?
Don't worry!
My teacher told me this...
Just be cheerful and have fun singing!
Alright!
Start the music!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Seeing them all full
Is just such a warm sight♪
Pikarune's doing the rap part?!
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
When you think about it (Squish! Squish!)
Friendship is (Squish! Squish!)
A very squishsterious thing! (Puni!)
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy-squishy, touch it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Punirunes Elementary School
is a fun, lively school.
Would you like to go here too?
Punirunes Guide
Today on the Punirunes Guide...
Pikarune
Pikarune is very wise.
He writes everything in the book he holds.
It's squiz time!
Cooking
Dancing
Drawing
Which of these is Pikarune not good at?
The answer is...
All of them!
Good luck, Pikarune!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, touch it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Seeing them all full
Is just such a warm sight♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
When you think about it (Squish! Squish!)
Friendship is (Squish! Squish!)
A very squishsterious thing!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, touch it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Uh-oh!
That crow took your hat!
The trick to getting it back is... your jumping power?!
Next Time
Next time: "Squishy Jumping for It♪"
Squishy Jumping for It♪
Squish into the next episode!