This Episode's Squishyyyy Points
Squishy
Punirunes. Before we knew it,
these creatures began to inhabit the human world.
They're very squishsterious creatures!
They all love to be squished.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Next, I'll bring this...
Meltyrunes Panic♪
Come in!
Yuka, are you all packed for tomorrow?
Yep, just finished!
We'll be leaving early tomorrow,
so don't stay up too late, okay?
Okay!
There's a baker's convention
happening in a faraway town,
so Yuka's family will be staying there.
Hey, Airune!
I wonder what breads there'll be in that town!
Mom told me it's by the ocean too!
Man, I can't wait!
Let's explore together, okay?
We'll be leaving early, so let's get to sleep now.
But don't worry, I'll bring your house with me.
Good night, Airune!
Airune is so excited for the trip that she can't sleep.
She's swimming in the sea...
in her mind.
Taking a cool photo...
Relaxing in a hot spring...
yep, in her mind.
She ended up passing the time by imagining the trip.
We'll be leaving early, so let's get to sleep now.
But don't worry, I'll bring your house with me.
Left behind, Airune melted from sadness.
I mean, you brought this on yourself...
In order to turn her back,
they'll have to squish her in Yuka's place.
Getting squished by other Punirunes
isn't going to turn her back, it looks.
Enerune has melted!
Not being able to play with Airune made him sad.
What will you do, Punirunes?
Good work, Kuurune!
Playing it cool and assessing the situation...
She thought that showing them food
would cheer them up.
And now Raburune and Ururune have melted!
I see!
They're trying to get Komugi to come and squish them!
At her final stand, even Kuurune has melted...
Now they're not Punirunes, but Meltyrunes!
When suddenly, Togerune shows up!
Looks like he's scheming up a prank.
Airune, are you okay?
Huh? She's not here...
Huh? Where is she?
Oh, no! Airune!
All of you!
I'm sorry for leaving you behind...
I was so sure you were sleeping away in your house...
I'm sorry to you all too.
You must have felt really sad.
I was too, Airune.
Airune...
I'm so sorry!
Thank goodness.
What's going on here?
They're overfilled with energy after melting
and being stuck for a long time.
Yuka!
Is everything alright?
Yeah! Uhh...
I think so.
Sure looks like it.
After everything, Airune still loves
Yuka's squishing the best.
Punirunes Guide
The Punirunes Guide!
Today...
Meltyrunes
Punirunes melt when they're not taken good care of.
When they melt, they're not able to do anything.
Squiz time!
How far do you think Enerune can move
in three seconds while melted?
The answer is...
3 millimeters!
So slow...
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, touch it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Seeing them all full
Is just such a warm sight♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
When you think about it (Squish! Squish!)
Friendship is (Squish! Squish!)
A very squishsterious thing!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, touch it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
It's Christmas!
The Punirunes have been waiting so long for this!
Huh? Airune, who's that?
A secret? Aww, tell me!
Next Time
Next time: "Merry Squishmas with Hapirune"
Merry Squishmas with Hapirune♪
Squish into the next episode!