This Episode's Squishyyyy Points
Squishy
Punirunes. Before we knew it,
these creatures began to inhabit the human world.
They're very squishsterious creatures!
They all love to be squished.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Kuurune Gets Stylish♪
Kuurun is a cool beauty who loves being stylish.
Looks like Airune wants to try it on.
I'm home!
What happened here?
I see, Kuurune lent it to you!
Do you want to be stylish like her, Airune?
Huh? You two were just about to head out?
Kuurune really likes keeping tidy.
Have a safe trip!
This is the Punirunes' world.
Where could these two be heading?
They've arrived at the market!
This appears to be a store where they can remodel their room!
Here's a place where they can buy
clothes and other stylish accessories.
Welcome back!
How'd it go?
You seem mighty confident!
She's about to show us
what she bought at the market!
You okay?
I mean, I know you're happy getting all dressed up...
Kuurune has an idea!
Komugi's over there, Kuurune.
You're going to train her to act cool?
Kuurune seems to think that what Airune's style
is lacking is coolness.
But where does Komugi come in then?
Umm... So you want her to play with Komugi?
S-Such cool poise...
I see! You want her to master this!
Wanna give it a shot, Airune?
You've got this!
Airune...
Airune has fallen into deep despair.
Now there's nothing stylish left.
Airune!
You gave it a good try!
Being squished has cheered her up!
Not only that...
She's motivated, too!
You look ready to take this on, Airune!
Alrighty!
Your training is back on!
First off: Play it cool and walk
without breaking any plates!
Next: Play it cool and resist the urge
to dig in on your favorite Plumpple Pie!
Next: Do a cool spin without getting flustered!
And then...
You did it, Airune!
Thanks for having me!
Come to think of it,
Enerune's been acting strange lately.
He doesn't seem very cheerful...
Is he feeling down?
He was, but then...
He suddenly started trying to be stylish.
How did you know?
Well...
They've all started training because
they want to be stylish like Kuurune!
Oh, I see!
You all look wonderful!
Happy for you!
So cute!
She says arrangement is key in fashion!
Airune's finally found her own style!
This may be the beginning of her true fashion path!
Hey, don't overdo it, now.
Kuurune's already getting to work
on a cool new training plan.
Punirunes Guide
The Punirunes Guide!
Today...
Kuurune
Kuurune is a fashion leader
who loves being stylish.
She's always visiting the market to see what's trending.
She dreams of owning her own brand.
Squiz time!
Which of these did Kuurune rock today?
Wings
Life Preserver
Scarf
The answer is...
The scarf!
Seasonality is also key to fashion!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, touch it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Seeing them all full
Is just such a warm sight♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
When you think about it (Squish! Squish!)
Friendship is (Squish! Squish!)
A very squishsterious thing!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, touch it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Hello, we're Pekopa!
"Pekopa" is a comedy duo that appears in
advertisements for the Punirunes toyline.
We're Pekopuni!
Pekopa? Pekopuni?!
Huh? Wha?! Which one is it?!
Next time: "Pekopa Become Punirunes♪"
Next Time
Pekopa Become Punirunes♪
Squish into the next episode!