This Episode's Squishyyyy Highlights
Squishy
Punirunes.
Before we knew it, these creatures began
to inhabit the human world.
They're very mysterious...
No, not quite.
They're squishsterious creatures!
They all love to be squished.
Take good care of one,
and it'll grow up to be cute and squishy.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune just nearby!
Squishy Airune♪
This one's name is Airune!
Airune
It's a Punirune that's full of curiosity and energy.
Though it doesn't seem very energetic right now.
I'm home!
Airune?
Come on out!
Alright.
Squishing you is just so soothing.
You feeling hungry?
Your dish today will be apple pie!
Let's get squ-ooking!
Give it some of the squishsterious squishence...
Stir it up...
Knead it...
Give it a squishy kneading so it'll be nice and fluffy!
Appuni pie, ready to serve!
Appuni pie
Airune loves appuni pie.
Is it good?
I'm glad!
Must be full now, right?
Urk!
Airune is a big eater.
I can't!!
Was that Dad?
Oh, sorry, Komugi!
What's wrong, Dad?
I can't do it anymore!
Mom?
He's trying to think of a new pastry for the store.
But...
I can't think of anything good!!
Why?!
Gah.
He's tried everything to find inspiration,
but he's plumb out of luck.
We'll help you think of something!
Yuka!
I want to be a lovely baker just like you and Mom!
Yukaaa!!
Airune and I have got this!
We've got you squished!
I'm gonna go work up front,
so good luck, you three!
Thanks!
What would make a good pastry...?
Well, that's how it is.
Alright, time to get to work!
Hah!
I'll think of a pastry this world has never seen!
Dad, stop!
I'm sorry, Airune...
Be sure to help brainstorm too, Airune!
Even your snot bubble is squishy...
No, wake up!
Looks like Airune has invited some friends
to help brainstorm.
Punirunes greet each other by squishing
their skin against one another.
Squish contact
It's called squish contact!
Loverune is going to announce its idea first!
Loverune
Loverune loves cute things!
It's making a heart-shaped pastry.
Instead of a heart...
it looks like an onion!
Ururune loves drawing!
Ururune
It wants to make a cornet with ears!
Tearful little Ururune has broken into tears.
Coolrune
Coolrune is a cool beauty, who loves keeping tidy.
Looks like it just wants to clean the place up.
Hm, yeah...
Can't do this, can't do that...
Nothing good's coming to mind...
There has to be something...
That's it, that's perfect!
Did you come up with something?
Yeah!
It's ready!
Aww, cute!
They look just like them!
Doesn't just look like them!
They're squishy!
Nice elasticity!
Right?
The secret to this squishy bun is...
the Squishence!
Squishence
I see now!
So, how is it?
It's amazing!
How about I give it a taste-test?
Whaaat?!
I really wanted to know how it tasted...
The Punirunes love squishy things.
Punirunes Guide
Today on the Punirunes Guide...
Airune
Airune's favorite food is the one
Yuka made for it earlier: appuni pie!
It's time for the squestion!
The squestion!
1. Punigiri
2. Ice punieam
3. Puning à la mode
Here's another one of Airune's favorites.
But which one is it?
The answer is...
Puning à la mode!
3. Puning à la mode
Airune, you're still going?
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
My friend Aoi picked up a tiny Babypuni!
I started taking care of it,
but it's turned into total chaos!
Next time: "Babyrune Grows Up♪"
Next Time
Babyrune Grows Up♪
"Puni" in next time!