This Episode's Squishyyyy Points
Squishy
Punirunes. Before we knew it,
these creatures began to inhabit the human world.
They're very squishsterious creatures!
They all love to be squished.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Airune and Enerune Trade Places♪
Oh?
Enerune's looking for something.
They were playing hide and seek!
Airune wants to eat plumpple pie.
Enerune is more in a squishing à la mode mood.
I'm home!
Enerune, I'm here to pick you up!
Huh? Did you eat all of these gummies?
I'm honestly kinda impressed.
That's far too much for you!
Guess you won't have room for dinner today.
I was thinking of making squishing à la mode...
Enerune, you want squishing à la mode?
I was actually planning on making plumpple pie...
You want plumpple pie?
What do we do?
How about we have Airune stay over at your house?
Huh?
And have Enerune stay here!
Airune will stay with me...?
They'd be trading places for a bit!
Doesn't that sound fun?
Yeah, it sounds fun!
Alright, then!
Let's give it a squish!
Make yourself at home!
Oh, this?
It's a guide book on aquatic animals.
Want to read it?
This is the whale shark!
They're about 20 meters long!
How does it feel?
The Yuka treatment!
I'm always massaging Airune like this.
This is the giant siphonophore!
It says it's the longest living creature on Earth!
Mhm! That's a jellyfish!
Let's get to work on that plumpple pie!
Before we eat, let's do some squish-cercises!
Enerune does it everyday!
Supposedly, it makes food even yummier!
Alright, let's do some squish-cercise!
And now, nine more sets of that!
I messed up again!
I can't!
It's still not squishier than my last one!
It's like dad always says while baking bread:
"Always be better than you were the day before!"
Will you cheer me on, then?
Airune always cheers me on,
and it helps get my brain going.
Nope, no good...
After all that,
both of them finally got to eat.
Is it good?
I'm glad!
Oh, this?
It's a bandage. I got a bit hurt yesterday.
Huh?
You want to have one?
You're so much like Yuka, Airune.
When I was younger, I scraped my knee
and had to put a bandage on it.
When Yuka saw it, she was like,
"That's so cool! I want one!"
She put a bandage on
even though she wasn't hurt!
He's taking her temperature.
Huh? You want me to go to bed?
But I'm not tired yet.
Oh, I see. You think I might've caught a cold?
Thanks, Enerune.
But I'm alright!
Look at me, full of energy!
You were worried about me, huh?
Reminds me of Aoi,
that kindness and concern.
Right? And then, Yuka...
What's wrong, Airune?
Are you starting to miss Yuka?
I had a feeling.
What are you guys up to?
Since they overate a bit,
they're going for a jog together.
Me? I'm taking Airune...
Aoi!
Yuka!
Enerune...
Airune!
Yuka, why are you out here?
I was telling him stories,
like when you tripped during the relay race,
and when you got lost at the aquarium...
And Enerune was starting to look worried.
Said "I'm going home!"
I see.
Thanks, Enerune.
Say, Airune,
what's with the bandage?
I see! You do look cool in it!
All that jogging must've made you hungry!
You guys too?
The hungrier you are,
the yummier the food?
A-Airune, what's the matter?
"Squish-cercises?"
I'm kinda confused...
but do you wanna cook up
some squisine at my house, Aoi?
Of course!
Wherever they go, the Punirunes
will always love yummy foods.
Punirunes Guide
Today on the Punirunes Guide...
Enerune
Enerune lives with Aoi.
It's squiz time!
Which one of these is Enerune's house
you'll find in Aoi's room?
The answer is...
Number two!
Enerune loves his house!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, touch it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Seeing them all full
Is just such a warm sight♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
When you think about it (Squish! Squish!)
Friendship is (Squish! Squish!)
A very squishsterious thing!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, touch it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Ran and Run are always together!
Huh? They're fighting?
How do we get them to make up?
Next time: "The Friendly Ran & Run Fight♪"
Next Time
The Friendly Ran-Rune Fight♪
Squish into the next episode!