This Episode's Squishyyyy Highlights
Squishy
Punirunes. Before we knew it,
these creatures began to inhabit the human world.
They're very squishsterious creatures!
They all love to be squished.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Babyrune Grows Up♪
When you spray whipped cream,
instead of forcing on the cap,
you want to push it out from the bottom.
Watch, just like this.
Whoa!
Now, you try it.
Okay!
As a pâtissier, Yuka's mother teaches
cake-making classes in town.
I did it!
Thanks, Airune!
Yuka!
Meet Aoi.
She's Yuka's best friend.
What's wrong? You look flustered!
Look at this!
A Babyrune!
Babyrune
Feels nice being all clean now, right?
Aoi, where did you find this Babyrune?
Well...
A-A crow?
Oh, no!
The poor thing's going to get eaten!
I...
I have to save it!
Huh?!
That was amazing...!
Oh, no!
Are you okay...?
Come on, speak to me!
I wasn't sure what to do with it,
so I thought maybe you and Airune could help.
I see...
Alright, I'll teach you how to take care of it!
Take care of it?
Yeah!
Giving it a bath like this is a good start!
Now, it needs to eat!
What should I give it?
Punirunes only eat very squishy foods.
Like miso konjac?
Why is that the first thing
that pops into your mind...?
No, no...
Mom's homemade gummies!
You try feeding it one!
O-Okay...
Huh? What's wrong?
It must still be hungry.
So do I give it more gummies?
You could...
But we can also make one of its favorites!
Let's get squ-ooking!
Give it some of the squishsterious squishence...
Stir it up...
Knead it...
Give it a squishy kneading so it'll be nice and fluffy!
Puning à la mode, ready to serve!
Puning à la mode
So squishy!
That was fast!
Finally, the most important part
of caring for a Punirune...
Squishing it!
Sq-Squishing it?
Yup, you gotta give it a good squish!
Like this...
Give it a try!
O-Okay...
Why...?
Huh? It grew!
This is a Yellorune!
Yellorune
Punirunes grow when you take good care of them!
But it didn't like it
when I pet it...
What am I doing wrong?
I know...
The squishing power in your fingers...
they're all grip, and not enough squip!
Wh-What's "squip"?
Aoi, I will train you!
Train me how?
Fight!
Are you sure she's not just massaging them...?
And thus, Aoi's training continued.
A few days later...
Aww...
I don't get it.
I just want to get along with Yellorune...
Why don't you try taking care of it
over at your house?
Huh? At my house?
That'll get you two bonding, guaranteed!
Alright, then!
I'll give it a try!
Another few days later...
You think those two are getting along well?
Of course they are.
Yellorune...
Punirunes melt when
you don't take good care of them.
I made sure to feed it bath and give it a dinner...
I mean, I gave it a bath and fed it dinner,
and I still messed up...
Calm down, Aoi!
Airune?
I'm sorry, Yellorune.
This is all my fault...
If I give you my energy, will you go back
to being the energetic Yellorune I know?
Wh-Who are you?
So your name is Enerune!
Enerune
Enerune?
I'm happy for you, Aoi!
But everything I tried up until now has failed...
What changed?
Aoi!
How did it feel when you squished its skin?
Soothing!
And...
very warm!
That's it! That's proof you have "squip" in you!
Then what was all that finger training for...?
Yuka!
Yes, Mom?
Aoi's on the phone!
Hey, Aoi! What's up?
Yuka, there's trouble!
Did Enerune melt again?
When I came home...
A house for Enerune randomly appeared!
Must be because it loves you for
doing your best to take care of it!
That's right — Punirune houses are
a sign of a tight bond with their partner!
It definitely got its energy back.
In fact, it's exploding with energy!
Glad to hear, Aoi!
Punirunes Guide
Today on the Punirunes Guide...
Growth
How Punirunes Grow
There are three stages of Punirune growth.
1. Babypuni
They're born as Babypuni,
2. Kidpuni
grow into Kidpuni,
3. Adultpuni
then grow a bit more and become Adultpuni.
The squestion!
It's time for the squestion!
What category does Airune fit into?
1. Babypuni
2. Kidpuni
3. Adultpuni
The answer is...
Adultpuni!
Though it certainly doesn't act like one.
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
A bunch of Babypuni
keep showing up at my house lately...
But I can't figure out why.
Hm? Loverune? What's going on here?
Next time: "Loverune's Big Love♪"
Next Time
Loverune's Big Love♪
"Puni" in next time!