Coming up on Punirunes...
The show is squishing!
Punirunes.
They're squishsterious creatures
you might find just nearby.
They all love to be squished.
When the Squishsterious Antenna glows,
a new puni-pal might come to hang out!
Let's Get Some
Halloween Candy♪
"Let's Get Some Halloween Candy♪"
There!
They're ready!
Sixty specially-made pumpkin cakes!
Phew, we're finally done.
Great work, darling!
You deserve a samba, rumba,
a numba of praises!
Oh, honey.
Thanks a darter!
You too! Thanks a butterfly!
Anything for a ladybug!
Tomorune.
You want to know why
we made pumpkin cake?
Because it's Halloween!
You'll just have to wait and see!
Tomorune has never heard
of "Halloween".
It asks the rest what Halloween is.
None of them can give a good answer.
Trick or Treat
They remember the phrase "trick or treat".
If you recite that phrase,
you'll get candy.
The Punirunes make their way
to Puniland.
The Halloween Candy Collecting Squeme
is about to begin.
No candy for them.
No candy.
Still no candy for them.
They got the line down,
but something is missing.
They say the phrase
with a pumpkin,
and they get...
no candy.
Just having the pumpkin isn't enough.
But what else?
They get...
no candy.
Riding it won't do?
Show them lots of pumpkins!
And still, no candy.
Lots of them won't do?
Show them a big pumpkin!
And still, no candy...
A pumpkin mask?
They've garnered a crowd!
The crowd left to get something.
Could that something be candy?
The crowd just wanted to wear matching masks.
In the end...
they couldn't get any candy.
A parade has broken out!
The Punirunes join the parade.
Seems like they've moved on from the candy.
Hm? Is that who I think it is?
It's Happyrune!
And that's Bakerune!
They're both puni-pals with Tomorune!
Everyone's having a merry time.
They may not have gotten candy,
but the Punirunes had a lot of fun.
Trick or treat!
Give us treats...
or we'll play a trick on you!
Oh, sorry.
Was it really that scary?
You're not scared?
You sure are sociable, Tomorune.
Here, to make up for scaring you.
Airune finally figured it out.
On Halloween, you get candy
when you get scared yourself!
The Punirunes promise to one another
that they'll get very scared next year.
I think you have it a bit wrong...
Oh, whatever.
The Puni Channel!
And squish.
Puniland
Today, I'd like to introduce Puniland.
It's the habitat of Punirunes,
which they can access from their houses.
At the Squishy Market,
you can buy many things
from food to accessories and more.
It also has attractions
like Squish'n Jump.
They sometimes throw
parades too!
Time for the question.
What kind of carriage did Tomorune ride
at the parade in Puniland?
Here's the answer...
Here's the answer!
The answer is a pumpkin carriage.
Tomorune had a jolly time.
That's all for today!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
What's up, Ururune?
You just saw an amazing,
squishsterious Punirune?
Next Time
You must be very curious
what it's like!
I get the feeling I might come across
a new friend myself!
Next Time
Who knows!
Unirune and
the Squishsterious Friend♪
Next time: "Unirune and the Squishsterious Friend♪"
"Puni" in next time!