This Episode's Squishyyyy Points
Squishy
Punirunes. Before we knew it,
these creatures began to inhabit the human world.
They're very squishsterious creatures!
They all love to be squished.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Something's Cooking on Valentine's♪
Yuka is hanging out with Aoi at her house.
So cute!
These two are having plenty of fun as well!
It's over!
What d'ya wanna watch next?
How about a manta ray video?
A what?
The biggest ray in the world!
It grows to be as wide as 6 meters!
Ever heard of it?
C-Can't say that I...
How about...
...the broadfin shark?
Or the cryptic bearded goby?
So cute, right?
I-I guess...
Fine, what do you want to watch?
Umm... I usually watch cooking videos.
Like, good temporing methods
to avoid blooming.
Huh? What does that even mean?
I'm not good at cooking like you are anyways...
Fine, watch your maple ray video then.
It's a "manta" ray!
And I don't care. Watch your temper videos.
It's tempering! Don't just call it whatever you want.
Why does it matter?
You went first, didn't you?
No, I didn't.
Yeah, Airune?
You think I took it too far?
Airune and Enerune ask the group for advice.
Ururune draws without thinking...
then gets even more shocked
upon seeing it.
Kuurune says to let things be,
let the wind take its course.
February winds are very chilly.
Raburune takes a walk around,
looking for ideas.
All set!
Why, hello, Raburune!
Hello!
This is a Valentine's Day sign!
Valentine's Day is when you
give someone special a gift
and communicate your feelings!
Most people give chocolate,
so we're using that to our advantage!
We're gonna boost our sales ten-fold!
Yeah!
She's a director?!
Raburune's Valentine's operation
is underway!
Hmm? "Valentine's is a wonderful day"?
If I make chocolates for her,
I should be able to easily make up with her?
Huh? What the?
Give her something on Valentine's Day?
Huh? What do you mean?
It would be a good idea
to make up with her on Valentine's Day...
But I don't know...
I can't really get myself to cook right now...
Raburune?
Huh? What is it?
What is it?
The Valentine's operation:
Chocolate-making is already underway
in the kitchen!
Airune!
Are you okay?
That's not a chocolate!
That's chocolate fondue Airune!
You can melt it in the microwave,
but to make really good chocolate...
...there's something extra you can do!
They call this "tempering!"
By adjusting the temperature like this,
we can make the chocolate smooth
and melt in your mouth!
Take a look!
I made chocolate gummy bears!
Give them a taste!
Oh my!
This is bliss!
The theobromine in chocolate
is said to aid the brain substance serotonin,
which boosts our motivation and happiness.
That's to say, delicious foods
bring us happiness.
Why did I take things so far...?
Airune...
I...
want to apologize to Aoi.
How do I make my feelings clear?
I think that cooking is fun, and I like doing it.
If I make something that Aoi likes too...
That's it!
Aoi, I, uh...
I'm sorry!
Me too, I might've come on a bit too strong.
What's this?
Go ahead and open it!
A dolphin!
An orca too!
I thought, whatever my precious friend likes
is very precious to me too!
Yuka...
I almost don't want to eat them...
It tastes so good!
You're amazing, Yuka! Thank you!
I'm glad they made you happy!
I actually made you some Valentine's sweets too!
Huh? You did?
Here!
Thank you!
Are these chocolate daifuku?
Yeah!
Enerune and Kuurune
helped me come up with it!
I thought since you liked squishy things,
that it might make you happy!
Really?
Thank you, Aoi!
And you, Enerune, Kuurune!
Like you said, what's precious to my friend
is precious to me too!
Making sweets is fun, but really hard!
So I thought I'd give it a shot!
You must be working really hard.
Aoi...
I'm sure it won't be as good as your cooking.
Delicious!
Thank goodness!
Mmm, it's a whole new texture!
Huh?
It's a brand new squish!
The syrupy chocolate melting in my mouth,
combined with the soft, doughy texture!
I never thought of this before!
I have to study it at once!
You really do like cooking and squishy things, huh?
Yeah...
Their friendship is rekindled,
thanks to the hard work of the Punirunes!
Oh, right! Here!
Valentine's for all of you too!
Thanks for everything!
Have a squishy Valentine's Day!
Punirunes Guide
Today on the Punirunes Guide...
Raburune's Hearts
Raburune's hearts are free like the wind.
Today, they're Valentine's hearts!
Squiz time!
Which one is the chocolate heart?
And begin!
The answer is...
This one!
All of you who found it,
have a squishy Valentine's Day!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, touch it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Seeing them all full
Is just such a warm sight♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
When you think about it (Squish! Squish!)
Friendship is (Squish! Squish!)
A very squishsterious thing!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, touch it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Leave Airune to your father — I'll take care of her!
Umm... Yuka?! What's Airune saying?!
Next Time
Next time: "Dad Watches Airune♪"
Dad Watches Airune♪
Squish into the next episode!