This Episode's Squishyyyy Points
Squishy
Punirunes. Before we knew it,
these creatures began to inhabit the human world.
They're very squishsterious creatures!
They all love to be squished.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Togerune's Prickly Debut♪
Upsy-daisy!
Get it!
Hup!
Huh? Who are you?
One of Airune's friends?
No?
Toge...rune?
Togerune
Togerune loves making mischief
and pricks all sorts of things.
He's gone...
Aww...
Don't make that face!
Come on, smile for me!
Squishing you is just so wonderful!
Squishy-squish!
Airune's returned to her good spirits, however...
Kuurune!
Oh! Is that a new silk hat you've got there?
It looks great on you!
What's got Komugi so riled up?
Looks like Togerune has set everyone off.
Even so, we don't know
where Togerune's running off to.
Calm down, you all. Let's not get too upset.
I'm about to prepare something
yummy for you to eat!
Here we go!
It's squisine time!
Squisine Time!
Give it some of the squishsterious squishence...
Stir it up...
Knead it...
Give it a squishy kneading
and it'll be nice and fluffy!
Squishing à la Mode
Squishing à la Mode, ready to serve!
Mmm, it came out perfect!
Togerune?!
"They caught me!"
...as if you didn't make yourself obvious.
Togerune.
Wanna eat with us?
Huh?
What's wrong?
Huh? You guys aren't eating?
They decided to eat first
before going after him.
Yuka! Can you help me with something?
Togerune?
Are you okay, Togerune?
Uh, sorry. What are you trying to say?
You didn't get any of that?!
I get it!
You wanna be squished too!
Doesn't seem like it.
No need to hold back!
I love squishing, after all!
Here I go! Squish!
This squish is amazing!
Wait, what?
Your thorns...
T-Togerune, are you okay?
There he goes...
Where did Togerune go after that, you ask?
He stayed in Yuka's house.
Punirunes Guide
The Punirunes Guide!
Today...
Togerune
Togerune is a mischief-maker who loves pricking things!
It's squiz time!
Which vase is Togerune hiding in?
Let's begin!
The answer is this one!
Oh, Togerune. Looks like that made you a bit dizzy!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, touch it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Seeing them all full
Is just such a warm sight♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
When you think about it (Squish! Squish!)
Friendship is (Squish! Squish!)
A very squishsterious thing!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, touch it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Oh, no! Airune melted!
We all have to work together to bring her...
Huh? What happened?
Next Time
Next time: "Meltyrunes Panic♪"
Meltyrunes Panic♪
Squish into the next episode!