Everyone!
Happy new year!
We had a lot of fun with the Punirunes last year!
Here's to more squishy fun!
Punirunes. Before we knew it,
these creatures began to inhabit the human world.
They're very squishsterious creatures!
They all love to be squished.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Punirunes Swap Colors♪
Airune, I'm off
to school now!
Is she not here?
She's not still sleeping, is she...?
There you are!
Wait!
A-Airune?!
Wake up! Wake up already!
Wh-Whoa...
Oh, okay. Goodnight!
Wait, no!
What happened to your colors?!
Oh, my!
Airune's usually red,
but she looks different today!
Why did your colors change?
Airune doesn't know either!
Nothing else feels different, right?
Like, do you feel sick?
That's a relief.
Well... I really gotta get to school soon.
Will you be okay?
Alright, we'll figure this out when I get home, then!
Looks like Airune wasn't the only one
whose colors changed!
Only one Punirune left...
There he is.
Ururune was so confused
that he hid and started crying.
Normally-purple Kuurune
is telling Ururune that it fits him.
Hm? Normally, Kuurune
would give him a handkerchief...
but her attitude has changed!
Now he's looking like Kuurune!
It seems as though their personalities
changed with their colors.
What a shocker!
They swapped colors by squishing one another!
They're having a lot of fun!
Everyone has returned to their normal colors.
I'm home!
Hey, Airune!
Oh, good! You're red again!
Hmm? Yuka is convinced that
this red Togerune is Airune!
Oh, you're here too, Togerune?
Airune, I'm gonna make you a ton of Plumpple Pie
to celebrate you regaining your colors!
It's squisine time!
Togerune could get used to this.
Alright!
Off we go!
What will you do now, Airune?
She can't think of a way to turn back.
She's back again!
Or is she...?
Do the squish!
Bravo!
But you're still not back to red!
No red for you!
Help yourself!
She's more like a Poutyrune now!
Airune's all out of options.
All she can do now is wish upon a star
that she turns back to red.
Airune... Airune!
Wake up!
Airune!
Are you okay?
You were groaning in your sleep!
Airune was dreaming.
Must've been having a nightmare...
Err, your colors changed up?
And I didn't know who you were?
Are you kidding? That would never happen!
Even if your colors changed,
you would always be Airune to me!
Alright!
I'll make you some Plumpple Pie!
Airune's back to her cheery self!
You're so cool, Togeking!
Prickle-prickle!
What an interesting dream he's having!
Punirunes Guide
Today on the Punirunes Guide...
Airune
Airune loves Plumpple Pie
and Squishing à la Mode.
Squiz time!
Pinapplump
Squishbone
Stewuish
What food is this?
The answer is...
Squishbone!
Airune likes it a lot more than she thought she would!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, touch it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Seeing them all full
Is just such a warm sight♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
When you think about it (Squish! Squish!)
Friendship is (Squish! Squish!)
A very squishsterious thing!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, touch it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Airune, where are you going with Komugi?
Huh? I thought you were just going for a walk!
Are you sure about this?
Next Time
Next time: "Airune Rides a Cat♪"
Airune Rides a Cat♪
Squish into the next episode!