This Episode's Squishyyyy Points
Squishy
Punirunes. Before we knew it,
these creatures began to inhabit the human world.
They're very squishsterious creatures!
They all love to be squished.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
The Friendly Ran-Rune Fight♪
Ran-Rune
This is Ran-Rune.
This half of Ran-Rune is assertive and proactive.
This half of Ran-Rune is shy and cautious.
Are they twins, perhaps?
He can't get himself to ask
if they can play together.
Airune and Enerune decided
to play with Ran-Rune!
Seems like he wants to work on his landing.
The sand applied to their bodies
stops them from skidding,
keeping them at just the right speed.
Now they're jump-roping!
Ninety-nine, one hundred!
Airune and Enerune's friend-jump broke 100!
Uh-oh, are Ran-Rune getting out of sync?
Ran-Rune's thoughts have been scattered,
causing them to split into two!
Uhh... What does this make of them?
He's Ran-Rune,
and she's Ran-Rune...
He's also Ran-Rune,
and she's also Ran-Rune!
Okay, let's see.
We'll call the proactive one Ran,
and the cautious one Rune.
Ran is heading off on her own without Rune.
Airune and Enerune promised Rune
they would bring Ran back.
Wow, really?
Yeah! And then...
Oh, there you are, Enerune!
I was going to bake some apple pie with Aoi!
You guys want some plumpple pie?
Um, guys! What about finding Ran?
Ran's been completely drained of her spirit.
It turns out Airune and Enerune
didn't forget about Ran and Rune.
Ran and Rune are in sync again,
thus rekindling their friendship!
Ran-Rune's friend-jump has broken 300!
The plumpple pie is ready!
Oh?
Did you guys make new friends?
Dig in!
Huh? Where is everyone else?
"Squishy Warriors: Punirunes!" they cry.
Huh? You're imitating Ran-Rune?
Bravo!
They're in full sync!
That adds up...
The friendly Ran-Rune are always together,
and forever will be.
Punirunes Guide
Today on the Punirunes Guide...
Ran-Rune
Ran-Rune is a pair of Punirune friends
that always sticks together.
It's squiz time!
Which of these silhouettes is Ran-Rune?
The answer is...
...number 3!
Huh? Togerune?
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, touch it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Seeing them all full
Is just such a warm sight♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
When you think about it (Squish! Squish!)
Friendship is (Squish! Squish!)
A very squishsterious thing!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, touch it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Who are these "Punirunes"
that everyone's talking about?
What really is "squishing?"
Next time: "Close-Up! The Prosquishonals♪"
The Prosquishonals♪
Next Time
The truth is about to be uncovered.