Coming up on Punirunes...
The show is squishing!
Punirunes. Before we knew it,
these creatures began to inhabit the human world.
They're very squishsterious creatures!
They all love to be squished.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Our New Puni-Pal,
Tomorune
"Our New Puni-Pal, Tomorune"
They're sooo squishy!
I hope they come out great!
Yuka
Meet Yuka,
a girl who loves all things squishy.
This is Airune.
Airune
It's a perky Punirune
living with Yuka.
Coolrune here is very tidy,
and very cool as well.
Coolrune
Ururune
Ururune is prone to tears.
Loverune
Loverune is full of big love.
Enerune
And Enerune is full of energy!
Oh!
Hey, slow down there, Enerune!
Enerune's a real handful,
even for Aoi.
Yuka's friend Aoi is a girl
who loves sea animals.
Aoi
Enerune lives with her.
This squishy band of friends
often hangs out together in Yuka's house.
Okay, the pastries are done!
The squishy Punirune buns...
are ready to serve!
Yuka's father is a baker,
and her mother teaches
cake-making classes.
It's so squishy!
Just like an aplysia oculifera!
That's silly.
I'm glad you like it!
Here's a toast to you!
Your puns are on-point as ever, Honey!
Croiss-anks!
Whoa!
I dough appreciate it!
You're on fire!
Oh, Mom...
Komugi
That was so good.
The Punirunes have so much energy
now that they're all full.
Hm? What was that?
And you see, the barreleye...
Huh?!
What the?
Oh, no!
The house!
What just happened to it?
The inside's all different!
Wh-What was that?
Yuka, look!
Someone's inside!
What?!
This is how Punirunes greet one another:
squish contact.
Hi there!
What's your name?
Tomorune
Huh, so you're Tomorune!
So squishy!
It's very friendly!
That's so cool, Tomorune!
Wow!
Look at you go!
That was awesome, Tomorune!
What's wrong?
Say what?
Ururune's gone missing?
You were playing around so much
we didn't even notice!
Airune takes it upon itself
to look for Ururune.
They all decided to look for it together.
But will they be able to find it?
They spot it in an instant, although...
How do we get it down
from all the way up there?
I get it! You want to use that
like a seesaw to jump up there!
But who's gonna jump?
Will their plan work out?
Go for it!
Oh no!
Tomorune!
It did it!
Now they can land safel—
Watch out!
Thank goodness.
Yeah.
Hold up.
I don't remember that cushion being there.
Hey, Airune.
You asleep already?
Eventful day, wasn't it?
Huh?
Wait, what?!
Tomorune's taken a liking
to Airune's home.
Congrats on the new puni-pal, Airune.
The Puni Channel!
And squish!
Today, I'll be introducing
Airune and Yuka.
Airune and Yuka
Airune and Yuka are good friends.
Squishing you is just so soothing.
Airune loves when Yuka
squishes it.
Appuni pie
And its favorite food is
appuni pie made by Yuka.
One day, Yuka went on vacation
and accidentally left Airune behind.
Time for the question.
What happened to Airune
when it got lonely?
Here's the answer...
Here's the answer!
The answer is: it melted!
You must have felt really lonely.
I was too, Airune.
Good thing it turned back to normal.
That's all for today!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Airune, I'm happy you and Tomorune
get to live together!
But if you're going to share a room,
you should probably buy some stuff for it.
Next Time
Sounds like a plan!
Have fun in Puniland!
Wait, what happened to shopping?
Next Time
Why are you playing Squish'n Jump?!
A Day in Puniland♪
Next time: "A Day in Puniland♪"
"Puni" in next time!