Coming up on Punirunes...
The show is squishing!
Punirunes.
They're squishsterious creatures
you might find just nearby.
They all love to be squished.
When the Squishsterious Antenna glows,
a new puni-pal might come to hang out!
A Day in Puniland♪
"A Day in Puniland♪"
Double the squish...
This is the life!
Tomorune moved into Airune's home.
Wow!
Thanks for cleaning my desk up!
Alright, time for a bath!
Be careful now!
Now let's have dinner!
When I mix some apple pie and a big burger
with the squishence...
Let's get squ-ooking!
Give it some of the squishsterious squishence...
Stir it up...
Knead it...
Give it a squishy kneading
so it'll be nice and fluffy!
Here you are!
Appuni pie for Airune...
and a puni burger for Tomorune!
Puni burger
Appuni pie
Eat up!
Now I'm hungry!
They all look so happy together.
Isn't that bed a bit small for the both of you?
Airune got knocked off it last night too.
Seems like the bed's too small
for both of them to sleep on.
They've decided to go out
and buy a bigger bed.
Have fun, you two!
Hm?
Puniland
This is Puniland, the habitat of the Punirunes.
Squishy Market
They've arrived at the Squishy Market.
They're thinking over which bed to pick...
Wait, no they're not!
Hey, this is the food shop!
They bought some food.
But what about your bed?!
Now they're looking for a bed, I'm sure...
There's no beds here!
This is the accessory shop.
What are these headbands everyone is wearing?
They're star headbands.
They're all the craze in Puniland right now.
So much so, they're already sold out.
So they can't buy them here.
But apparently, Squish'n Jump
is giving it out as a reward!
Looks like they'll be going head-to-head
to see who can get the headband.
And off they go to Squish'n Jump.
Aren't you going to get a bed?!
Squish'n Jump
Squish'n Jump is a game where you have
to jump all the way to the top.
If they can get to the top,
they'll get the star headband!
Airune takes the lead!
Airune gets knocked off
by the robot and fails!
Will Tomorune make it to the end?
Darn! Tomorune fails the challenge as well.
Time for the rematch!
Will either of them make it this time?
Airune takes the lead...
Wait, this isn't going to go the same way, is it?
Airune makes it forward!
They both look out for the bat this time!
They did it!
Now they can jump straight to...
There was another bat!
The second failure has drained
the energy out of them.
Is it time to give up?
Their friends have come
to cheer them on.
Airune suggests they work together
to get to the top.
Third time's the charm!
They clear the obstacle as one!
They make it to the bats!
Oh no! Both bats fly at them together!
How will you get past them?!
It's the food you bought earlier!
What are you planning?
L-Look at this!
They're jumping in sync!
Otherwise known as...
jumpuning!
And together...
they reach the goal!
Indeed, there's only one star headband.
What will they do?
They're both letting the other have it.
Another one was dropped down to them!
Perhaps someone was so moved
by their teamwork
they decided to reward them.
I'm glad you both got star headbands,
Airune and Tomorune.
That's so adorable!
So what about your bed?
You forgot?!
These friends sleep another night
in the same bed.
And they'll be good friends tomorrow.
The Puni Channel!
And squish!
Today, I'll be introducing Tomorune.
Tomorune
Tomorune is a Punirune who unexpectedly
showed up in Airune's house
from the squishsterious light.
He's very excitable and outgoing,
and is good at making new puni-pals.
His favorite food is a big burger
made with squishence:
the puni burger.
A squishsterious Punirune
is looking after Tomorune,
but its identity is yet a mystery.
Tomorune loves Airune.
The two are always together.
Time for the question.
What did Tomorune and Airune
obtain from Squish'n Jump?
Here's the answer!
Here's the answer...
The answer is: the star headbands!
It's a symbol of their friendship.
That's all for today!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Tomorune, you don't know what
Halloween is?
Airune and its friends will teach you about it!
Wait, you don't know it that well either?
Next Time
Yeah, that's it. You say "trick-or-treat"
and get candy!
But you're not getting any candy?
Next Time
What's the deal?!
Let's Get Some
Halloween Candy♪
Next time: "Let's Get Some Halloween Candy♪"
"Puni" in next time!