This Episode's Squishyyyy Points
Squishy
Punirunes. Before we knew it,
these creatures began to inhabit the human world.
They're very squishsterious creatures!
They all love to be squished.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Where am I?
Airune?
Thank goodness, I thought I was alone.
Huh?
A forest?
Where are you going?
Airune!
Airune!!
Airune Parts Ways♪
Was I dreaming?
Airune, I'm home!
I have so much homework to do today...
What's up?
Huh? Where are you going?
The forest?
Wait, does that mean...!
Some species of fish and animals have a habit
called homing instinct,
where they return to the place they were born.
Where they were born...?
Oh, welcome back, Yuka!
Hi, Mom.
Listen to this!
That cake we served for the first time today...
Some species of fish and animals have a habit
called homing instinct,
where they return to the place they were born.
Is Airune... going home?
One day, she showed up out of the blue.
And we became good friends.
And yet...she's leaving me, out of the blue...
What is it, Mom?
Yuka, can we talk for a bit?
Here.
Th-Thank you.
We were a little worried about you.
If something's bothering you,
let's talk about it! We can help!
Thanks.
Airune is going home into the forest.
She is?
And I'm never gonna see her again...
How do I deal with this?
"Life is full of goodbyes."
"Life is full of goodbyes!"
It means that as we live,
we'll part ways with many people.
But I think if you're saying the same word,
it's better to have a happy goodbye
than a sad goodbye.
Yeah. You'll feel much better that way.
Thanks, Mom and Dad!
I've decided I'll use the time left
to make amazing memories!
It's squishy Punirune Bread!
Airune!
How does it feel?
Squishing really soothes the soul!
Wait, hold up.
What's wrong?
Well, I was thinking about making
amazing memories,
but this doesn't feel any different from usual.
Wouldn't that mean you always
had amazing times with them?
I suppose!
I've been having fun ever since the day we met!
I'm always happy!
Rather, I'm ecsquishstic!
Where am I?
Airune?
A-Airune...
Are you leaving?
You're actually leaving, aren't you?
Life is full of goodbyes.
I'll be fine.
I'll say goodbye with a smile on my face!
No, I should be the one saying that!
Thank you!
Airune!
So squishy!
See you!
Goodbye, Airune.
When I woke up,
Airune was gone.
And...
so was Enerune.
Enerune? Enerune?!
So were Raburune, Ururune, and Kuurune.
Two weeks later...
Dad, more wheat flour please!
You're sure fired up about this, Yuka!
Well, I gotta win that Youth Cooking Contest!
Yuka...
You've got this!
Thanks!
Alright, let's get squishing!
I can't get it to feel squishy like Airune...
Hey, Airune, how are things over there?
Anything fun happen?
Not like she's actually gonna answer.
Huh?!
You're home?
Huh?
Wait...
What?!
You were at a hot spring?!
Oh, wow.
You weren't feeling squishy enough,
so you all visited a hot spring?
You're even squishier than before!
Hey, Airune!
Let's stay together forever, okay?
Ecsquishstic!
Airune and Yuka's "ecsuqishstic" days
squished onwards.
Please remember this.
Even if you have to say goodbye
to a Punirune...
It's simply the beginning
of your next mysterious...
...no, squishsterious encounter.
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, touch it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Seeing them all full
Is just such a warm sight♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
When you think about it (Squish! Squish!)
Friendship is (Squish! Squish!)
A very squishsterious thing!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, touch it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!