This Episode's Squishyyyy Points
Squishy
Punirunes. Before we knew it,
these creatures began to inhabit the human world.
They're very squishsterious creatures!
They all love to be squished.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Raburune's Big Love♪
I'm home!
I'm back, Airune!
Here's Yuka!
Huh? She's not here.
Where could she be?
Punirunes do as they please.
They often go exploring when not being watched.
No wonder.
She's been getting along real well with that spunky Enerune.
Even Airune's gonna want to spend time
far away every now and then!
Oh!
You never know where you find them!
So you were all just sunbathing here, huh?
Airune, Enerune, Ururune, Kuurune, and Raburune!
A Babyrune?
For some reason, they brought home a Babyrune!
Airune, what happened to it?
Was it in danger like Enerune was?
Oh, you can't understand them?
Airune and the rest are taking a stroll
when they come across a Babyrune.
It's fallen head over heels for Raburune!
I see!
All things considered...
it sure seems like it loves Raburune a whole lot!
I can see why you'd follow her home.
She's gentle and full of love — anybody would fall for her!
I'm happy for you, Babyrune!
The next day...
Hi, Komugi!
Is Airune here?
Nope.
They're sunbathing again?
There's more of them?
Why is there more?!
Looks like they've brought home a few more Babyrunes.
So, uhh...
Where did they come from?
To put it simply, they've all grown attached to Raburune.
Raburune can't take a good walk
without making new fans, can she?
Oh, no! We have to help her take care of them!
Enerune's going to try playing with the Babyrunes.
They've gotten very dusty from the crash.
Kuurun loves keeping tidy.
So she's doing what she does best —
cleaning up the Babyrunes.
She can be a bit persistent about cleanliness, though...
Ururune is trying to make them happy
by drawing Raburune.
Ururune's tears are infectious!
What now?
Huh? Oh, right!
Let's make a meat manju!
It's squisine time!
Squisine Time!
Give it some of the squishsterious squishence...
Stir it...
Knead it...
Give it a squishy kneading so it'll be nice and fluffy!
Squeat Manju
Squeat Manju, ready to serve!
Alright, dig in, everybody!
Already?!
H-Hey, wait...
I can't make more that quickly...
Right, Airune?
Aw, not you guys too! I can't make that much!
How am I supposed to deal with this?
Raburune?
Kuurun plays it cool, even when she's ignored.
A-Amazing...
Raburune's like a pro at spreading love!
Raburune will save the world with her love!
Is this...
her Big Love?
Huh?! What the?
Aoi?
What in the world?!
They're everywhere!
Hey! What do we do about this?!
Will Raburune save the world with her love?
Punirunes Guide
The Punirunes Guide!
Today...
Raburune
Raburune is a Punirune overflowing with love.
Just one heart wink is charged with love!
Squiz time!
Can you count how many hearts
she makes in three seconds?
Good luck!
The answer is...
Five times!
Now you're one of her fans too!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, touch it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Seeing them all full
Is just such a warm sight♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
When you think about it (Squish! Squish!)
Friendship is (Squish! Squish!)
A very squishsterious thing!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, touch it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
The Punirunes are having a sleepover, I can't wait!
Huh? Ururune's about to cry, what do we do?
Someone do something!
Next Time
Next time: "Ururune Goes Adventuring♪"
Ururune Goes Adventuring♪
Squish into the next episode!