This Episode's Squishyyyy Points
Squishy
Punirunes. Before we knew it,
these creatures began to inhabit the human world.
They're very squishsterious creatures!
They all love to be squished.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Ururune Goes Adventuring♪
Is Enerune doing okay...?
He's not bothering you, is he?
Not at all!
Everyone's having fun at the sleepover.
If he ever gets sad, I can come pick him up at once.
Don't worry about it.
They should all be asleep by now anyway.
The Punirunes all get to sleep by 8 P.M.
Ururune must be hungry.
Ururune's off to find food on his own.
Woo-hoo! I won!
I lost again!
Too bad!
If I had just taken the corner...!
Let me play next!
Okay! You can take my place, then.
Alright! You're on, Yuka!
Airune's caught on to Ururune's absence!
They're all set on looking for Ururune!
Airune's party set off
on their adventure.
I won!
I can't believe I lost again!
You're terrible at this, Dad!
One more! Let me play you again!
Nope!
Yuka and I will play next!
Aww!
Then, uh, can we try 2-on-1 again?
No!
Airune found Ururune!
Be careful when you go down stairs.
They're all hungry now.
Now they're all set on finding food together!
Yuka!
Don't go eating snacks late at night!
Okayyy...
The Punirunes continue, quietly.
A cat blocks their path!
But it is resting.
Punirunes
Fight
Go Around
Cat - 1
Ururune is five seconds away from breaking into tears!
Looks like he just wanted a squish.
Just barely stopped him!
Gadzooks!
They've found gummy bears!
But how will they get up to it...?
Puni Tower, followed by...!
Puni Rocket!
Getting those gummy bears won't be an easy task.
Huh?
Isn't that...?
I see.
You just wanted to eat some gummy bears!
Did you all wake up hungry?
But they can't snack this la—
During a sleepover, eating snacks at night is A-OK!
Whaaat?
Let them have it for today, okay?
Fine, just for today. Consider it an exception.
Here, Ururune!
Would ya look at that, he's smiling!
The rest of you can have some too!
They're all giving him their gummy bears!
Getting so many gummy bears
puts a big smile on his face...
My, my.
There he goes again.
Must be very happy!
Ururune!
Whether he's happy or sad,
Ururune sheds tears.
Punirunes Guide
The Punirunes Guide!
Today...
Ururune
Ururune's very tearful and is quick to break into tears.
Squiz time!
Cleaning
Drawing
Cake-Making
What's Ururune very good at?
The answer is...
Drawing!
Ururune loves drawing!
Though when it comes out very good,
he gets too happy and cries.
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, touch it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Seeing them all full
Is just such a warm sight♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
When you think about it (Squish! Squish!)
Friendship is (Squish! Squish!)
A very squishsterious thing!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, touch it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Trick-or-treat!
The Punirunes are having a wild Halloween party!
When suddenly, we're greeted by...
Is that real?!
Next Time
Next time: "Bakerune on Halloween♪"
Bakerune on Halloween♪
Squish into the next episode!