This Episode's Squishyyyy Points
Squishy
Punirunes. Before we knew it,
these creatures began to inhabit the human world.
They're very squishsterious creatures!
They all love to be squished.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Airune Rides a Cat♪
Today is Yuka's day off.
Sorry, I'm too busy making this dessert.
I want to finish it before Aoi gets here,
so just wait until then, okay?
She's gotten bored.
Seems she napped on top of Komugi!
Cats are fickle.
Airune's taken a liking to this.
She decided to go out with Komugi on his walk.
Komugi's walk starts with a patrol
around the house.
They're keeping an eye out
for anything out of the ordinary.
Hm? What do they see?
Kuurune is practicing her runway walk.
He recollects himself
and heads to the entrance.
Now there's something shining.
Raburune is holding a concert!
Komugi doesn't need any of her hearts.
Now that he's leaving home,
where could Komugi be going?
He's not telling Airune.
Yuka told me she was making a dessert!
I can't wait!
Huh? Isn't that...
Yuka's cat?
Wait, Airune?!
Enerune, you want to join Airune on her walk?
Alright! I'm gonna head
to Yuka's house, so have fun!
Be careful, you two!
You too, Komugi!
Oh? He went back home.
Or so I thought,
but he's going to the park.
Airune wants to play with Komugi!
Togerune just came up with a prank.
Time to work together
to save Komugi!
Had a feeling you were here!
Did you have fun?
I brought you your dessert!
Huh? Where are Komugi and Airune?
This place...
is the end of their walk.
Komugi thought Airune would like this spot
and wanted to show her.
Komugi, Airune!
Time to go home!
Wow!
Really? Sounds like you had a busy day.
Y'know, I wouldn't have expected
you and Komugi to go on a walk together.
But I'm glad you two are getting along well.
The next day...
Good morning, Airune!
Good morning, Komugi!
Yuka, you're gonna be late for school!
I'm coming!
Bye, Airune, Komugi!
See you later!
Cats are quite fickle.
But their budding friendship isn't fickle!
...You could say.
Today on the Punirunes Guide...
Punirunes Guide
Komugi
Komugi is Yuka's family cat.
He loves to squish the Punirunes.
Squiz time!
One part of Komugi is squishy like the Punirunes.
Whiskers
Tail
Paw Pads
Which is it?
The answer is...
His paw pads!
Yuka loves squishing his paw pads too!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, touch it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Seeing them all full
Is just such a warm sight♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
When you think about it (Squish! Squish!)
Friendship is (Squish! Squish!)
A very squishsterious thing!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, touch it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Airune, you're gigantic!
So adorable!!
Wait, whaaat?!
What's happening?!
Next Time
Next time: "Airune Grows Big♪"
Airune Grows Big♪
Squish into the next episode!