This Episode's Squishyyyy Points
Squishy
Punirunes. Before we knew it,
these creatures began to inhabit the human world.
They're very squishsterious creatures!
They all love to be squished.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Hmm?
Something's different about today...
Greetings, Punirunes.
I plan to make the tastiest cake
out there for Aoi's birthday.
But there's something I need for that.
It is...
I love your cake, Mom!
How do you always make it so good?
I add a secret ingredient.
What is it?
That's a secret!
Can you give me a hint?
Let's see...
You can't buy it anywhere,
but I always have it on me.
You could say!
Your mission is to find Mom's secret ingredient.
Don't let any grownups notice.
You must accomplish this with your own skills.
This message will self-destruct in five seconds.
SQUISHON: IMPOSSIBLE♪
Smells wonderful!
It's almost time.
I've awaited you.
Agent Punirunes.
Mission start.
Based on my investigation,
our target always carries a notebook on her.
She uses it to jot down ideas.
The recipe for her cake has to be in there.
Thus, so will the secret ingredient!
We must obtain it!
I'll set a trap to separate the target from her notebook.
Looks like changing the amount of sugar
was the right call!
Guess I'll have this all to myse—
– Mom!
Since the shop's very calm right now,
why not take a break?
Drink some black tea in the living room!
That sounds nice!
I even have snacks!
You're going to eat those all by yourself...?
O-Of course not!
Really?
Oh, whatever. Let's get a move on!
Alright.
Hey, quiet down, you two!
Honey?
Huh?
You just got here?
Yeah. I was taking a break with Yuka.
But I just thought of a new recipe!
What should we have for dinner?
Oh, we're almost out of soy sauce...
And we're running low on meat...
What to do, what to do...
You're using it as a motorcycle...?
Guess we can just get food delivered.
Oh, Kuurune! What are you doing here?
You're wiping the dishes?
Thank you!
Then I'll trust your say and let you handle the rest!
I'm going to go clean up.
Thanks a ton.
That just gave me another idea!
Did Yuka head out?
Maybe she's at the park with the Punirunes.
That was close!
Welcome!
Thanks to your hard work,
we have finally acquired the notebook.
Mission success!
Let's see what that "secret ingredient" is!
Oh, this...
It's from Mom and Dad's anniversary!
She must like having this photo with her.
Right, that's not important right now!
Umm...
Whole egg, egg yolk, granulated sugar...
Cake flour, butter...
They're all just normal ingredients!
There's no secret ingredient in here...
Now what...?
Squish me and cheer up, you say?
Thanks, Airune.
Nothing beats this squishing, I can tell you that...
Mhm, there's no use feeling so glum.
Secret ingredient or not,
I can still make a delicious cake!
Will you all help me one more time?
Where's that notebook...?
Weird...
Where did I leave it?
Let's get to work!
Just you wait...
Aoi!
I-It's done!
Mom, can you try this?
I tried making Aoi's favorite chocolate...
How is it?
It's very good!
R-Really?
You're improving a lot, Yuka!
But...
How do you always make it so good?
I add a secret ingredient.
It doesn't have your secret ingredient.
Is that what you think?
Remember this?
Y-Yes, of course!
That cake you made was so good...
It was much spongier than usual,
and the cream was moist and sweet...
That's because...
I thought to myself,
"I want Yuka and my darling to eat a delicious cake!"
What were you thinking when you made this?
I guess...
"I want to make Aoi happy!"
That is your secret ingredient!
I get it!
We did it!
Now we can really call this mission...
...a success!
Agents. Today's Punirunes Guide is...
Punirunes Guide
Squishing
Punirunes love being squished.
It's time for the squiz.
1. Kuurune
2. Ururune
3. Airune
Please tell me which of these three
was squished by Mom during their mission.
The answer is...
Kuurune.
If you got this correct,
you must be a talented agent.
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, touch it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Seeing them all full
Is just such a warm sight♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
When you think about it (Squish! Squish!)
Friendship is (Squish! Squish!)
A very squishsterious thing!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, touch it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Whoa! Who are you?
You seem a bit different from Airune and the others...
Next time: "Togerune's Prickly Debut♪"
Next Time
Togerune's Prickly Debut♪
Squish into the next episode!