This Episode's Squishyyyy Points
Squishy
Punirunes. Before we knew it,
these creatures began to inhabit the human world.
They're very squishsterious creatures!
They all love to be squished.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Punirunes
Punirunes, creatures full of mystery.
In order to bring their ecology to light,
we're conducting our first ever
close-up coverage of them.
This footage was obtained by a news crew
that followed a day in the life of one Punirune.
What true nature of the Punirunes
will this reveal?
The Prosquishonals♪
This is Airune,
the Punirune we'll be covering.
Airune's day starts early.
They say that daily exercise is crucial
for maintaining their squishiness.
But her routine doesn't stop here.
Airune keeps her nose on the grind.
She's going running.
Like they say, squishiness wasn't built in a day.
Our news crew was able to catch a glimpse
of Airune's stoic side.
Why are you up so early?
"I have to stay squishy!"
The news team didn't quite understand yet
what she meant by that.
8:00 A.M.
After her morning routine,
Airune gets back to rest.
Airune?
Are you still sleeping?
I'll leave this here for you!
Oh, no!
I'm so late! Bye, Airune!
Airune's day has only just begun.
10:00 A.M.
At 10 A.M., Airune arrives at the market.
Are you waiting for somebody?
This is Airune's close friend Enerune.
He seems very energetic,
but he appears to have
accepted the news crew.
And today...
We will witness many Punirunes.
Stylish trends are crucial
to the world of the Punirunes.
"It's important to stay cool,"
said passionately by
the fashion-conscious Punirune, Kuurune.
What is being stylish to you?
Our next sighting is a popular figure
in the Punirunes world.
Raburune often holds fan events like this.
Pikarune is the host.
Some Punirunes are skillful enough
to do things like this.
The Punirunes' ecology is quite diverse.
12:00 P.M.
It is the early afternoon.
Airune and friends have met up,
but are still looking for someone.
What's next on the agenda?
An artist is going to hold an exhibition here.
And that artist is...
There he is.
The up-and-coming artist, Ururune.
Even though his exhibition is starting so soon,
he's still not satisfied with his latest drawing.
He's stopped drawing.
He couldn't bear the pressure
and ripped it.
Punirunes have already lined up by the venue
to see the exhibition.
How will he handle this situation?
The news crew was kicked out.
Airune is on the move.
She runs the road she trained on
for the sake of her friend.
Are you a friend of Airune's?
The exhibition went on as planned.
What do you think of
when you look at this art?
I'm sure the art is full of memories.
They've all been through hard times
and fun times together, haven't they?
2:00 P.M.
After that, they're all invited
to Airune's room for a party.
But even then, Punirunes are free creatures.
Some sit and eat, others get up and dance.
Some give advice on how to
arrange their furniture in a "feng shui" way.
Some have been hiding the whole time!
And some are shy.
3:45 P.M.
I'm home!
Oh, you...
You're still sleeping?
Punirunes are creatures full of mystery.
Through their coverage
the news crew realized something.
To be squishy...
isn't about the flabbiness of their bodies,
but perhaps the strength to repel
any adversity.
8:00 P.M.
Today on the Punirunes Guide...
Punirunes Guide
Market
The Punirunes market
sells all sorts of items.
It's squiz time!
Which shop sells this item?
Food Shop
Stylish Shop
Furniture Store
The answer is...
The stylish shop!
Kuurune checks there
for new products every day!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, touch it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Seeing them all full
Is just such a warm sight♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
When you think about it (Squish! Squish!)
Friendship is (Squish! Squish!)
A very squishsterious thing!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, touch it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Airune, where are you going?
"Goodbye?"
You're leaving for good?
Anything but that!
Next Time
Next time: "Airune Parts Ways♪"
Airune Parts Ways♪