Coming up on Punirunes...
The show is squishing!
Punirunes.
They're squishsterious creatures
you might find just nearby.
They all love to be squished.
When the Squishsterious Antenna glows,
a new puni-pal might come to hang out!
Unirune and
the Squishsterious Friend♪
"Unirune and the Squishsterious Friend♪"
The Punirunes get along very well.
They're playing the day away as always.
You fit in with them well now, Tomorune!
Must be nice to make new friends.
I gotta go meet Aoi.
See you guys later!
"I saw this pretty glittering Punirune outside,
but it vanished!"
"Did you guys see it?" asks Ururune.
It says this is Unirune,
one of its puni-pals.
Unirune...
It's a legendary Punirune
known to Punirunes only in myth.
It has squishsterious powers,
can fly freely in the sky,
and is seldom encountered.
Basically, it's a super-duper amazing Punirune—
and it's puni-pals with Tomorune.
Not long ago, they would spend
a lot of time together.
Everyone really wants to meet Unirune.
They're going to go look for it!
And the scaly-foot gastropod...
Oh?
What brings you all here?
You're asking if we've seen this... Unirune?
Kind of looks like Willan's chromodoris...
but it doesn't ring a bell.
Oh dear! Tomorune went to ask the crow!
Is it going to be okay?
Oh no!
Tomorune!
Did you save it?
Hey, thank you for the help!
What's your name?
Yuniko.
Yuniko, is it?
Do you live near...
...by?
Whuh?
What are you doing?
Huh? Um... hey...
What are you doing...?
Saying hello.
Don't you do that?
I think I've heard of cultures
where you greet others like this before.
Oh, wow. Guess there's still a lot
to learn about the world.
Anyways, thanks to you
Tomorune is safe and sound!
Must feel hungry now that you're relaxed.
Oh, right!
I brought these to share with Aoi!
Here.
Try it, Yuniko!
What's this?
Our specially-made squishy bun!
They're very good.
A bun?
So good!
Yuka's family runs a bakery!
All the pastries they make are delicious.
Pastries...
they "make?"
No more until we get home.
They're all so carefree.
Oh yeah! Yuniko, do you...
Did she have to run home?
What a strange girl.
I hope I see her again.
I'm home!
That's it! Keep it going!
Wait, what?!
Yuniko?
Yuka! Welcome homosapien!
Wait, why are you here?
I'm kneading.
She wanted to learn to make pastries!
How wonderful.
But will she be able to
get it into a circle?
And she's gotten chummy with them!
But, well...
I guess I sparked an interest
in baking for her!
Are you okay, Yuniko?
Okie-dokie-artichokie.
Mom, don't teach her your weird jokes!
Knot for me!
Even Tomorune's taking after me!
I did it.
Oh my...
That's certainly a unique shape.
Is it bad?
It's stellar! You're a superstar!
Let's get it in the oven!
Alright, you two.
Thanks for your helpaca!
You too, Yuniko!
Huh?
Knot for me.
Do you hate gummies?
Oh, sorry then.
Knot for me...!
How is my pastry?
So chewy!
Every bite I take spreads
the flavor through my mouth!
It's the best!
You think so?
Yeah!
Your pastry is delicious!
So... good...
Yeah!
When you say "so good!" out loud,
it tastes even better!
So good!
Hey, Yuniko.
I didn't get the chance to ask you earlier.
Do you wanna be friends?
Be... friends?
Yuka!
Can you help us bring these out?
Okay!
I'm so happy I made friends with Yuniko!
Also, you sure look like you're enjoying those.
Wh-What's wrong, Ururune?
Now that they've made
a new, squishsterious friend,
their lives will only get more
squishy-exciting from here on out.
The Puni Channel!
And squish.
Today, I'll be introducing
Unirune and Yuniko.
Unirune and Yuniko
Unirune is a legendary Punirune
seldom seen by anyone.
It has squishsterious powers
and is still shrouded in mystery.
Yuniko is a girl that Yuka and Aoi
met in the park.
She's a very mysterious person.
Time for the question.
What does Yuniko hate?
Here's the answer...
Here's the answer!
The answer is gummies.
Knot for me.
Unirune doesn't seem
to like them either...
Keep your eyes peeled
to learn more about it.
That's all for today!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Tomorune, how's your life
living with Airune been?
So much fun everyday, you say?
I'm glad to hear that!
Next Time
And you've made lots of puni-pals!
Huh? You still don't have enough?
What do you mean?
Next Time
What? You want to make puni-pals
with everyone all over the world?!
Tomorune's Many Puni-Pals♪
Next time: "Tomorune's Many Puni-Pals♪"
"Puni" in next time!