This Episode's Squishyyyy Points
Squishy
Punirunes. Before we knew it,
these creatures began to inhabit the human world.
They're very squishsterious creatures!
They all love to be squished.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Airune Grows Big♪
Dig in!
Yuka and Aoi have made a feast for the Punirunes.
Yuka's going to teach me her pie recipe!
We'll make that next, okay?
Alright, let's get cooking!
Squisine Time!
It's squisine time!
Give it some of the squishsterious squishence...
Stir it up...
Knead it...
Give it a squishy kneading so it'll be nice and fluffy!
Plumpple pie, ready to serve!
Plumpple Pie(?)
All done!
But the colors are all off...
That sure looks... interesting...
What went wrong...?
I followed the recipe!
You're going down on it...
Huh? It stinks, doesn't it?
"It's so good!" she says.
D'oh!
Well, okay, then.
Airune, what d'ya wanna do today?
Are you still asleep...?
Wait... Huh?!
Wh-What the...?
A-Airune?
A-Airune?!
What happened to you?
Huh? What in the world?
How do I turn you back...?
Wait... Hold on.
You're fine exactly the way you are!
You're so...
so...
so much more squishable like this!
Calm down, Yuka.
Now I can do this...
...and this...
Oh, the things I can do!
You love this too, Komugi?
But seriously, how did you get so big?
I think I might like you bigger.
Meanwhile...
Kuurune is on to something!
I know I said I like you bigger...
...but this is a bit overkill.
And if you just keep growing...
Please, anything but that!
We gotta get you outside!
Okay, then...
Airune, this way!
I have to hurry up and find a way to shrink you!
There.
What do you think of my
newly-improved Airune Bread?
Oh, wow!
They're lovely!
Holy cow!
You're even bigger than before!
Yuka, what's going on here?
Yuka!
Is that Airune...?
Yeah...
How did she get so big?
No idea!
Isn't that...
Huh?
"I'm Detective Kuurune!"?
Detective Kuurune
No way!
You figured out what caused Airune's growth?!
I'll interpret her dialogue for you
going forward.
The culprit behind Airune's growth is here among us.
Who did it...?
It's...
Them!
What?!
The squishence did it?
But how?
Airune grew because of the plumpple pie
overfilled with squishence.
Huh? But I only put two in, like usual...
Not exactly.
There were more squishence
added on top of that.
And thanks to my investigation,
I was able to pinpoint
exactly who's responsible.
Please take a look.
What is that dent?!
The real culprit behind Airune's growth
is whoever made this dent.
And that is...
Him!
Togerune?!
Case closed!
Kuurune, that was amazing!
Excellent detective work!
So, how do we turn Airune back to normal?
I don't know.
D'oh!
Airune, don't flop like that!
We have no choice...
Yuka?
Airune...
...is going to have to live like this forever!
Worry not! I'll build a new house for you!
Good idea, Yuka! I'll help you!
How are you going to build that?
Are you sure about this...?
You're still hungry?!
Please don't grow any more!
Whaaat?!
Airune!
How did you turn back?
You shrunk to normal because you were hungry...?
D'oh!
Punirunes Guide
Today on the Punirunes Guide...
Growth
Airune's body grew after eating food
with lots of squishence in it.
It's squiz time!
Of these four Airunes,
which one is her at normal size?
The answer is...
Number four!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, touch it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Seeing them all full
Is just such a warm sight♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
When you think about it (Squish! Squish!)
Friendship is (Squish! Squish!)
A very squishsterious thing!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, touch it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Who's this?
Pikarune?
"Punirunes Elementary School?"
What the heck is that?
Next time: "Pikarune Does Elementary School♪"
Next Time
Pikarune's Elementary School♪
Squish into the next episode!