Dino Girl
Gauko
The Dino Girl
Episode 10
Dummy! Dummy!
Oh, shut it!
World peace...
Matsui Meat Shop
Freshly-fried croquettes!
Naoko!
Toshio!
Matsui Meat Shop
Looks like you're feeling a lot better today.
Oh, uh, yeah.
Matsui Meat Shop
Right, I made a new type of croquette!
Give it a try!
The Love and Peace Croquette!
Matsui Meat Shop
"Love and Peace?"
It's very good!
Matsui Meat Shop
Toshio?
Yeah?
How do I bring about love and peace?
Seeing you smile definitely makes me happy.
Huh?
I don't really get all that complex stuff,
Matsui Meat Shop
but I think it's up to you to decide
how the world should look like.
Matsui Meat Shop
So good!
I'm glad you like it.
Matsui Meat Shop
Look, Naoko!
So pretty!
Yeah!
Today was such a good day.
Dino Girl
Gauko