GAU
Dino Girl
Gauko
Gauko Returns
Episode 5
Naoko, something seems different about you.
That couldn't be!
I know I'll attain true beauty this time!
Pipin' hot octopus balls!
My, an octopus ball stand
way out here?
Wanna try one?
Oh, wow! That's very generous of you!
I'll try one!
Thank you very much!
I'll stop that fire, merp!
All good, merp?
Bwop.
Mmm, your undies are even less
appealing than last time!
What's the big idea?!
No, bad Naoko!
And you were so close to attaining true beauty...
Wise words, girl!
You can't let this knock you down!
Sorry 'bout that!
I-It's... fine...
Hey, my bad...
N-No... problem...
B-Brave through it, Naoko...
Just brave through it...
That's what makes you...
a true...!
Whew, much better!
Hey, you've got a doody on your head, merp!
What's wrong, merp?
You look frustrated, merp!
Bwop.
What's your problem?!
Dino Girl
Gauko
To Be Continued
Dino Girl