Dino Girl
Gauko
My Peaceful Town
Episode 6
Freshly-fried croquettes!
Matsui Meat Shop
They're crispy on the outside,
fluffy on the inside!
Matsui Meat Shop
They're very delicious!
We also have minced... Huh?
Naoko?
Eek! He saw me!
Matsui Meat Shop
What are you doing, Naoko?
Don't look!
What's wrong?
You're blushing an awful lot!
Someone's got a crush.
Huh? A crush?
Oh, so you're crushing on someone?
N-N-N-N-No I'm not!!
It's Toshio, the guy
selling croquettes, isn't it?
I don't have a crush!!
There's nothing to be embarrassed about.
Yeah.
We really have to live with
all this war, woof...
I'm really scared...
Toshio, oh Toshio,
wherefore art thou Toshio?
Oh, Toshio...
You called?
Are you on your way home?
Huh, Naoko?
What's wrong with you, girl?!
Why would you run away?!
I hope everything will be okay...
It'll be fine, ribbit...
I'm home...
Good night...
What about dinner?
I'm not hungry...
Hmm? What's gotten into her?
I wonder...
I hope I meet Toshio in my dream!
Dino Girl
Gauko
To Be Continued
Dino Girl