Dino Girl
Gauko
Inside the Box
Episode 7
Uh-oh...
Did you see those planes
on the news yesterday?
Yeah! So freaky...
I hope everything will be okay...
Our lives won't be affected by all that, right?
Aw, come on.
You know that won't happen!
Are you sure...?
On a brighter note,
how about that show yesterday?
Oh, yeah, I watched that!
Such a good episode.
I didn't see that ending coming!
Are you sure...?
Pus-pus!
– Off home we croak-croak!
– Peep-peep!
– Let's go, peep-peep!
– Wait for me, goo-ga!
Let's go play video games
at my house!
Heck yeah!
Freshly-fried croquettes!
Oh, Naoko!
Are you on your way home?
Naoko?
I wonder what's wrong...
I'm home.
I'm so sorry, Naoko!
I ate your pudding without asking!
Whatever.
What's the matter, sweetie?
I'm fine.
Does she have a stomachache?
I don't know...
Is this actually something
that's happening somewhere else?
It looks like it's just happening
inside the box...
Someone else is suffering
underneath the same sky as me.
Naoko, dinner's ready.
All while we're living peacefully.
Naoko!
Dino Girl
Gauko
To Be Continued
Dino Girl