We ran after our adjacent shadows
I'll always be with you
Just how much light can you bring me
Like that which shines through the trees into my dark room
My soul was covered in sand, and you were a raincloud in the desert
That was when we first met
I forgot all about your mischievous smile
I just love you so much with every passing moment
Every path takes us back to our first encounter
I've always loved you, as childish as it sounds
I'll always be with you
Let's walk to the ends of the earth
After the free consultation at the park,
Leo-kun completed his training trial
and enrolled here at Proud Dog,
where he and my dog Singe train together!
Alright, that's it for today.
Eguchi-san, your walking with Leo
has improved greatly.
Continue practicing what you've learned, okay?
Okay!
Samura, Monkey, you've barely improved.
Wash your faces and come back.
His name's not "Monkey," it's Singe!
Living in Bliss
I can't take it anymore!!
Pipe down, will you.
What's the problem?
You need to start going
home straight after work.
Hey, Niwa-san.
You don't suppose maybe Singe
just can't hear me?
What?
Well, during our training earlier...
Leo-kun was able to walk just fine
with Eguchi-san, but Singe...
Don't! We're supposed to be walking!
No! No sniffing!!
I'm training him exactly the same,
yet he won't listen to any of my commands...
Hey!!
How many times do I have to tell you
not to pee on the floor?!
Well, it seems like Monkey's been
getting used to living with you.
Y'think it's about time?
Huh? Time for what?
Time to get neutered.
Now hold on! He can't!
He doesn't even have balls, see?
C-Clearly, Yuko must've already had him neutered
before making me take him in!
'Cuz like, there isn't a smudge down there!
Smooth as a baby's bottom!
So you can't tell, then.
Tell what?!
Hand him over.
Huh? There's nothing there!
Look closer.
Right here. There's a bump in his groin.
He must have an undescended testicle.
Oh god, he's right!
The other is probably in his abdomen.
W-Wait... what does that...?
A dog's testicles stay in their abdomen
during the embryonic stage.
They typically descend between
6 to 8 months after birth,
but some dogs' testicles don't.
If you ignore it, it's possible
it'll descend on its own with time...
but judging by his teeth,
he's likely around 10 months old,
so you should consider surgery.
10 months... old?
He's only a puppy?!
That broad really didn't tell you anything, did she?
I mean, look at him! He's so big!
He doesn't look anything like a puppy!
It doesn't matter how big he is.
You use the teeth to judge a dog's age,
not their size.
But I got him a checkup before I started working here,
and the vet didn't think he was a puppy...
Which vet was it?
Th-The second one past that light...
That place is full of frauds.
You've gotta be kidding me!!
That said, he's very much a puppy,
he has not been neutered,
and he has cryptorchidism.
It's fairly possible this is why Monkey
can't stay focused during training sessions.
Even moreso as an uncastrated male.
Marking is territorial behavior,
so if he's sniffing restlessly,
it's likely to pick up information on other dogs,
or he's picking up the scent of a female dog.
Uncastrated males can smell a female in heat
from up to 6km away.
If one comes into that range,
he'll be uncontrollable.
A-A dog's nose is that strong?!
That tiny black bean?!
S-So, if I get him neutered,
then he'll be more focused during training?
Well, it's no guarantee,
but it would increase the chances, yes.
I see...
E-Excuse me, Ourson-senpai...
He's clear!
What the hell are you doing to my dog?!
Surgery All Done
Leo-kun didn't have any either...
SMOOOTH
Surgery All Done
I dunno...
What are you even thinking about...?
I-It just sounds so painful!
You don't have to put
yourself in their shoes here.
Besides, why do dogs need to be neutered?
It's not so much that I pity them
or that I think it's unnatural.
I just don't know if it's necessary
to do surgery on a perfectly healthy body.
Dogs have three main instincts:
breeding, danger avoidance, and preying.
Anything and everything they do
can be linked back to one of those instincts.
Their danger aversion and preying instincts
can be substituted through training,
to prevent them from causing issues
when cohabiting with humans.
Breeding instincts are a
beast of their own, though.
Since games and sports cannot substitute it,
their instinctual desires go unfulfilled.
They can't keep harmony
with humans nor other dogs.
Hey, stop messing with my baby!
PANT
Their nerves are constantly on edge,
making it hard to sit still.
PANT
There are many cases of males
sniffing out females in heat and getting loose,
resulting in injury and even death.
Today's BenchBARK Lesson
Let's delve deeper into dog instincts.
Danger Avoidance Instincts
We'll talk about the three main instincts,
and the problems that arise from them.
Preying Instincts
Breeding Instincts
Danger Avoidance Instincts
Preying Instincts
Breeding Instincts
Danger Avoidance Instincts
Preying Instincts
Breeding Instincts
Danger Avoidance Instincts
Preying Instincts
Breeding Instincts
Danger Avoidance Instincts
Preying Instincts
Breeding Instincts
Danger Avoidance Instincts
Preying Instincts
Breeding Instincts
Danger Avoidance Instincts
Preying Instincts
Breeding Instincts
Danger Avoidance Instincts
Preying Instincts
Breeding Instincts
Danger Avoidance Instincts
Preying Instincts
Breeding Instincts
Danger Avoidance Instincts
Preying Instincts
Breeding Instincts
Danger Avoidance Instincts
Preying Instincts
Breeding Instincts
Danger Avoidance Instincts
Preying Instincts
Breeding Instincts
Danger Avoidance Instincts
Preying Instincts
Breeding Instincts
Danger Avoidance Instincts
Preying Instincts
Breeding Instincts
Danger Avoidance Instincts
Danger avoidance is a dog's instinct
to perceive and escape from danger.
Ding
Dong
Barking at certain sounds,
Ding
Dong
biting out of fear or anxiety,
or tensing up after being startled
are all from this instinct.
There are ways to substitute this
instinctual behavior through training.
For one, you can train a dog to
stop biting your hand as a nervous reaction.
Start by applying a bitter spray
to your hand that's safe for dogs.
Then let the dog bite,
teaching them through the taste.
Once they've stopped, reward them.
That'll make them happy
and stop biting you.
Danger Avoidance Instincts
Preying Instincts
Preying instincts make them
hunt and catch animals.
Biting at your heels as you walk,
chasing after fleeing people or dogs,
and running after cars and motorcycles.
Using play equipment that resembles prey,
you can train them to substitute this as well.
At home, you can do several things,
like play fetch with a ball.
Outdoors, you can exercise them,
such as with a flying disc.
Preying Instincts
Breeding Instincts
And finally, breeding instincts,
which make them mate and have children.
Males will act more aggressive
and destructive,
try to grab onto something and shake their hips,
or sniff out a female and get loose.
These instincts cannot be substituted
through training,
so we must reduce their desires
in order to keep them out of danger.
Thus, most owners choose to neuter them.
Niwa-san, you believe in humans making changes
for their dog's happiness, right?
But neutering is forcibly taking a dog's instincts
away because they're inconvenient for us...
Isn't that just being selfish?
You have a sex drive, don't you?
W-Well, yeah, of course I do!!
What kind of dumb question is that?!
If there was a naked woman
standing in front of you,
and you had to spend your whole life
getting yelled at not to touch her or get excited,
would you feel "happy?"
Do you really think that making a dog happy
means preserving their nature?
He'll be in pain for a bit afterwards,
but if it would reduce his desires
and allow him to live in peace,
I would choose to get him surgery.
Even if it's selfish.
In the end, he's your dog.
I won't force you to do anything.
He was clinging onto Ourson-senpai...
You can put a stop to it,
but that's not a part of training.
It's just taking control of his instincts.
But that's also selfish, isn't it?
Now I'm even less sure...
...what would make Singe happy.
One more thing.
There's more?!
I think my brain's hit max capacity here!!
Unlike regular testicles,
undescended testicles
have a higher probability
of developing a tumor.
Huh?!
Tu—what?! Huh?!
If you wanna know more,
I can hook you up with a competent vet.
Please do!
Nosuke Pet Clinic
I brought him over.
Please give him a look, Nosuke.
Th-Thank you!
Ritsuka told me you
had hired someone, Shinichiro,
and I was quite curious who the lucky guy was!
He's really drawn to puppy-like people, isn't he?
P-Puppy?!
This is the director of Nosuke Pet Clinic,
Kubo Suzunosuke-sensei.
Seems like he's close with Niwa-san and Izumi-san.
They're even on first-name terms...
Y-Your fluffy blond hair
had nothing to do with it, I swear!
I never said it did!
Alright, checkup time. Right this way.
You're right, there's one caught in his inguinal canal!
Cryptorchidism is usually inherited,
but if a dog is born with a narrow canal,
the descending testicle gets stuck and stops.
Normal
Normally, the other testicle
will descend to the correct spot,
Undescended
but seeing as the lower sack is empty,
then it must be in his abdomen,
just as Shinichiro estimated.
Can you prepare the ultrasound?
Okay.
Why is he stretching his forepaws out like that...?
Let's take a looksy...
So this is how they take a dog's ultrasound...
It's possible an undescended testicle
that hasn't developed into a tumor
won't get picked up by an ultrasound...
Oop, there it is. See?
Huh? Wh-Where is it?
Right here!
So, what do you wanna do?
Do you wanna take it out?
What's with the big smile?!
Do people normally smile here?!
No, that's just him. Don't overthink it.
Castration can cause joint damage,
and is also known to cause growth in some cancers.
There's also differing attitudes towards castration
in the U.S. and Europe.
Though our little descendant here
has the risk of developing cancer,
so I very much recommend
proceeding with the surgery.
I-It's an easy surgery, right?
Yep. If the testicles are in the correct position,
then it's a very simple process—
only takes about 5 minutes!
Since it's stuck in his inguinal canal,
it might need a slightly bigger wound,
but it won't take any longer.
However...
Yeah?
The ones stuck in the abdominal cavity
are a bit tricky.
If it were anywhere else,
I could just cut out a bit of skin and remove it...
But for an intraperitoneal surgery, I can't extract
the testicle without opening his abdomen,
so the wound would be larger,
and the operation may take longer.
Additionally, the longer the procedure is,
the larger the risks of anesthesia will be.
Also, because of the size of the wound,
he might need more time to rest post-op.
So... What are the risks of anesthesia?
Ah, yes. I'll give it to you straight.
He could die in his sleep
under its effect.
Huh...?
However, the technology for anesthesia
has improved drastically,
so that rarely happens nowadays.
I wouldn't entirely write off the chances, though.
Rest time depends on how long
the wound takes to heal,
but for this little guy, it'd probably be about...
Can I have some time to think it over...?
Sorry, I'm going home for now.
Must've freaked him out.
Samura.
If you're not going to listen
to the whole thing here,
look up the risks of not having surgery
when you get home.
Then you should make your decision.
Marking is territorial behavior,
so if he's sniffing restlessly,
it's likely he's picking up
the scent of a female dog.
Their instinctual desires go unfulfilled.
They can't keep harmony
with humans nor other dogs.
Their nerves are constantly on edge,
making it hard to sit still.
Ah, right! The search!
cryptorchidism no surgery risks
"Undescended testicles that are not operated on
have a high incidence of testicular cancer."
Huh?!
"In comparison with uncastrated male dogs
without undescended testicles, the incidence is..."
6-14 times larger...
"When body temperature
is high in the abdominal cavity,
mitogenic activity tends to lead to
the formation of a tumor,
which can be difficult
to spot due to its position.
Whether you choose to have surgery or not..."
He could die in his sleep under the effect.
I wouldn't entirely write off the chances.
This one decision could cost me Singe's life.
I could lose him...
Do you really think that means
preserving their nature?
Forcing him to live in a way
that suits my needs is selfish.
But in the modern day, a domesticated dog
has no other choice but to coexist with humans.
So what do I do...?
What's the right option...?
In the end, he's your dog.
I won't force you to do anything.
Singe...
I want you to be able to live in peace.
Nosuke Pet Clinic
Calling...
This is Samura. About the surgery...
I wish only happiness for you,
Nosuke Pet Clinic
but I think this is for your own good.
It's finally time, Samura-kun.
Before I begin the surgery, please read this agreement
and sign at the bottom.
Oh, okay.
I'm still worried...
Apologies, by the way.
I wasn't trying to scare you off.
It's just a regulation.
Once I sign this consent form...
then I have to accept if Singe dies.
Singe could...
Samura-kun?
Dogs will believe if their owners believe.
If you're anxious about it, he's anxious.
If you have faith in him,
he'll overcome it and come back to you.
He's not gonna die.
Mhm. I won't let him die. Have faith.
Well then!
Off I go, papa!
This is what it means to own a dog.
Even his very fate rests in my hands.
SURGERY
Hang in there, Singe...
Hang in there...!
SURGERY
All done in here! He's awake, too!
He's still a bit half-asleep,
but do you wanna see him?
Right over there!
You can pet him a bit if you'd like.
How are you, Singe?
You must've felt so helpless...
No wonder...
You're still a little puppy, after all.
You did great.
Very good boy, Singe.
For the first time,
I really felt like Singe's owner.
Thank you for coming back to me.
Since it was a laparotomy,
he stayed at the vet overnight to be safe.
When I went back the next day,
Singe was standing up and wagging his tail.
Last night, he fell asleep clinging onto
the hoodie you left him with.
Huh?
He must've really missed you.
Oh, wow!
That's not like you!
Who knew dogs were so cute?
Hey, Miyu-kun! I have something cool
to show you before you head out!
Come over here!
Behold! Singe-kun's testicles!
Aren't they just the cutest?
I've had all my babies' testicles
soaked in formalin and put on display!
He's competent, but a weirdo.
Don't amuse him.
Want his balls formalin-ed?
I'll pass!!
Nosuke Pet Clinic
I then prayed to Singe's old self...
then carefully discarded it.
I'm home.
Today, Singe begins his new life.
Back home for the first time in a day!
Last night was a lot quieter without you,
and that was the norm before I got you,
but that silence felt miserable.
Before I knew it, you became
the new normal for me.
Now, I can't imagine a life without you.
Welcome back, my little Singe.
Now you can finally live in...
What? Why?!
Weren't you supposed to stop marking
once you got neutered?!
And I just laid out that new rug, too...!
The surgery doesn't change what he's made of.
It just gave him an easier
foundation to train from.
It depends on the dog, too.
From here on out, it's up to how well
his owner can train him.
Keep working at it, Samura.
Giving a name to chance
Or giving love to fate
If I'm being honest
It's all the same either way
The things that you love
Are what make me happy
It's hilarious
Just how simple I am
Your heartbeat, stuck in my head
It brings back memories
To when we rushed home, laughing along the way
I hate being alone
It makes the night feel so slow
So come on, fall for me already
Sugarspot
You make my days even sweeter
With brown freckles just like your spots
I can get through a scratch or a rough patch
Just like that, the day's over
And in the deepest depths of my heart
Somewhere I feel lonely
Or maybe I miss you
Or a mix of both?
I don't know
Wait for me!
I heard Sin-chan got neutered.
I know it's for the best, but still...
You must've been very worried.
You totally get it, Eguchi-san!
That's just how I felt.
This is Proud Dog.
You want to book a counseling session
tomorrow evening?
What time?
A customer!
The person who called yesterday
is coming at 4 P.M., right?
Yeah.
Oh, man! It's almost time!
This is so exciting, right,
Ourson-senpai?
Oh, I should make some tea!
Can't you just sit still...?
Hey, stop, Ricochet!
E-Excuse me...
I'm Miyake, I called in yesterday.
W-Welcome!
That's a lotta energy!
What the heck?
Haha, he's so friendly.
What's his name?
I-It's Ricochet...
Hello there, Ricochet-chan!
You're such a cutie-pie!
So what are you seeking consultation for?
Now, now, save it for later, okay?
Well...
My dog...
keeps spinning.
Huh?
Spinning...?
Today's BenchBARK Advice
The way you should take care of a dog varies
depending on its breed, personality,
and the environment it's kept in.
Just be aware, not every dog should be treated
or thought about
the same as the doggos from today's episode!
Today's BenchBARK Advice
Next Time:
Spinning Dog