We ran after our adjacent shadows
I'll always be with you
Just how much light can you bring me
Like that which shines through the trees into my dark room
My soul was covered in sand, and you were a raincloud in the desert
That was when we first met
I forgot all about your mischievous smile
I just love you so much with every passing moment
Every path takes us back to our first encounter
I've always loved you, as childish as it sounds
I'll always be with you
Let's walk to the ends of the earth
But why?
Did I do something wrong?
Come back!
I just want to...
D-Don't...
W-Wait, calm down!
S-Stop!
It burns... Or not...
It's warm? Huh?
Yuck! You peed on me?!
What's wrong with you?!
N-No barking!
Shut up, you dumb dog!
We're done, Miyu.
-Yuko
Two months ago, on a typical, average morning,
my girlfriend moved out
and dumped me with a letter.
A few days ago, she suddenly showed up again.
Think of this dog as me,
so you don't have to be lonely anymore.
Take care, Miyu.
...She said.
She also stopped responding to
my calls and texts.
I didn't really want to keep him,
but I couldn't find anyone else
to look after him.
And there's no way I could just abandon him.
So I thought I'd try to take care of him
in the meantime...
Gotcha!
Samura-san!
Samura Miyu-san!
Come on, I know you're in there!
I-Is there a problem?
How many times do I have to tell you?
We may allow you to have pets,
but we can't have it causin' a disturbance!
I'm sorry...
It was goin' off all night
while you were at work!
I'm really sorry!
H-He won't be noisy tonight!
I'm off work, anyways.
He should behave if I take him on a good walk.
I just read that online.
Just so you know, if I get any more complaints,
I'll have to ask you to move!
I understand...
What a pain in the neck.
My apologies!
Homeless with You
Whoa there!
Why are you standing like that?
What are you, a monkey?
It took me an hour just to put on
his collar and leash.
Then we finally get outside,
and he acts up!
This isn't how I expected
walking a dog to be!
It should be more like...
Stop.
Sit.
Good.
That's so cool...
See? That's how you should act on a walk!
What's your problem, you idiot?!
Sorry! A-Are you okay?
Don't do that! You'll hurt yourself...
What now, a kangaroo?
Ey, what are you doing?!
Hey, get outta the way!
When did traffic build up?!
Sorry! I'll move.
His collar!
Stop!
He's gonna get hit!
Come.
There.
Good boy.
He caught him...
It's like he's made of magic!
Thank you, sir!
You saved him!
What you just did was amazing!
Are you trying to kill him?
I'm sorry?
If you don't even know how to hold a leash,
you shouldn't have a dog.
What happened to the other guy?!
Yikes!
Wait, am I holding it wrong?
I thought he could get into trouble
if he had too much free reign...
Please teach me your ways!
Today's BenchBARK Lesson
How to hold a leash,
and the basic fundamentals of walk training.
Today's BenchBARK Lesson
I will demonstrate and explain
how "heeling" works.
Today's BenchBARK Lesson
First, holding a leash.
Open your palm and put the loop around your thumb.
Then hold down on the leash.
Today's BenchBARK Lesson
If the leash is too long,
fold it up then hold down.
Today's BenchBARK Lesson
Don't tug on it, just hold it down softly.
Let the leash sag to prevent impact
in case of a sudden pull.
The human should always be in charge during a walk.
Essentially, you want to make sure
your dog doesn't walk ahead of you.
Today's BenchBARK Lesson
Don't tie the leash around your hand or wrist.
Wow, really?
Yes, really.
Today's BenchBARK Lesson
Don't just hold the loop alone, either.
You won't be able to control your dog either way.
The dog could come loose,
or the owner could get hurt.
Like what you just went through.
Tee-hee.
Today's BenchBARK Lesson
Now for heeling.
Have your dog, say, to your left,
and say "follow."
That or "heel" will work.
They're both easy words for dogs to make out.
However, once you've picked a command,
you have to stick with it.
You can also add actions like patting on your thigh
to help your dog understand.
I see!
Next is the command to walk, "go."
If your dog tries to get ahead,
you should stop to let it get back.
Back. Follow. Okay.
And repeat.
Man, he's so cool!
Simple, right? Give it a try.
O-Okay!
Simple, you say?
Uh, first, set him down to my left...
Don't go wild, don't go wild...
I knew you'd do that!
Cut it out! Stay still!
Follow, boy, follow!
Would you listen to me?!
What about "follow" don'tcha understand?!
Come.
Hold on...
Is he going to show me how?
Is it magic time again?!
Wait, what?
Eh, you'll fit.
Wait...
What?!
Kneel.
Whaaat...?
What the heck...?
That's messed up...
Now, hold on...
What are those men doing?
Look away, now.
This isn't appropriate!
Are you deaf? I said move.
Everyone thinks we're engaging in some weird kink!
Ugh, fine! All I have to do is walk, right?
My dignity's already out of the question!
Why me...?
Who said you could lead?
(This is dangerous, please do not try this at home)
What's the big idea?! I could've gotten killed!
It's the same thing you did to your dog.
What about "follow" don'tcha understand?!
What's your problem, you idiot?!
When you tug on the leash like that,
it chokes on his neck.
The pain only makes him struggle more.
Which just makes you tug harder.
It's a vicious cycle.
Of course he won't listen to you.
So...
What do I do, then?
Let's walk again.
This is so embarrassing...
Not to mention how casually he's doing it.
Listen. Leashes aren't for choking dogs
to get them to listen to you.
They're for giving them restraint,
keeping them out of danger,
and to prevent them from bothering other people.
They're important for giving quick cues to our dogs.
Cues?
Like that.
As long as the leash is loose,
a slight tug like that will get the dog's attention.
As it did yours.
A pull from behind will choke them,
but not a slight one from the side.
He's right...
You can send cues all the same
with a normal collar,
but with the one you're wearing—a half-choke collar—
when you close it, the chains close in
and make a sound to attract the dog's attention.
Sometimes they can close in too much,
so you have to be careful with them.
They're best for smaller breeds.
Do you want to try? I'll watch from the side.
Can I?
Yay, let's go!
It's time for practice!
Wait.
Running up to a dog like that
will provoke it.
Especially with an aggressive dog like yours.
Dumbass.
I had no idea...
Now, as for a more friendly dog...
He looked away...
It's a way of saying,
"I don't want to fight with you."
Wow, really? That's awesome!
You're like Dr. Dog, PhD!
Looks like there's more you need to learn
before dealing with that collar.
Today's BenchBARK Lesson
Now, I'll teach you how to approach
an unacquainted dog without making it hating you.
First, avoid eye contact.
Approach it from a curve,
and avoid facing it head-on.
Today's BenchBARK Lesson
Then crouch down beside the dog
and make a fist for it to smell you.
Today's BenchBARK Lesson
sniff
This will tell the dog,
"I mean you no harm. Please be my friend."
sniff
This is something you must take
slowly and calmly,
Today's BenchBARK Lesson
so don't get too enthusiastic.
Will that actually work...?
Will it...?
Avoid eye contact...
That look...
I've never seen him so—
I've never seen his face so clearly...
You're actually so cute!
Not even once...?
That's pathetic...
I didn't want to keep a dog.
My ex forced me to take him in
three days ago.
It's not like I hate dogs...
I just thought, maybe this is fate, or something...
If I get any more complaints,
I'll have to ask you to move!
Excuse me...
I know this is a bit forward considering we just met,
but could you please help me train him?
What is it?
You should cover today's fees first.
On-site training is ¥10,000 an hour.
1.5x the price for ad hoc training,
so it's ¥15,000.
Huh...?
About two hours have passed
since I stopped your dog,
so the total is ¥30,000.
I'm a professional dog trainer, mind you.
A professional...?
Of course! It all makes sense!
How else would he get a dog
to obey him so easily?
But there's no way...
I can't just pull ¥30,000 out of nowhere!
U-Uh, hey!
Can you wait until I get my paycheck?
No.
For ad hoc training,
I expect cash on the spot.
B-But ¥30,000 is an awful lot for me...
Alright, fine.
You can also work it off.
Huh?!
If you're broke, you can work for me
until you pay off your debt.
Me, work as a dog trainer?
You do know how to hold a leash the pro way now.
To think, I didn't know how to walk him.
Or anything, really.
I'll give you three days.
Call me if you have the money.
Representative/Dog Trainer
Dog Training
"Niwa...Shinichiro?"
Would you shut your dog up?!
I've made up my mind.
I'll work off my debt.
And in exchange...
please help me train this guy
when you're free!
What about your job?
I quit.
Wasn't a difficult decision, was it?
I-I can't blame you for thinking that.
My ex begged me to quit my sales job
and work at the bar she has a job at.
But then we broke up, and she quit.
Honestly, there wasn't much of a reason
for me to stick around there.
Plus, this guy's constantly barking at night
when I'm out at work.
If the landlady gets any more complaints,
we'll be kicked out...
I need to train him, or we're both out of a home!
Have it your way.
Really?
However...
The dog's not the one I have to train.
Huh?
People are quick to call a poorly-trained dog bad,
but the dogs aren't the ones at fault.
It's the humans who don't know
how to handle them.
So I'll be training you
to better control your dog.
That's how I do dog training.
Stop, don't pull me!
Hey!
No.
There. Good boy.
How does he do it?
At their core, dogs are friendly to humans.
As long as you know how,
you can communicate with them.
Isn't that right?
How you communicate...
Not head-on, from the side...
Avoid eye contact...
Warm up to it slowly and calmly...
Hi there! Err, what's his name?
Ourson.
Ourson...-kun.
I'm Samura Miyu.
We're going to be workmates.
Huh... he's staring at me.
It's like he's actually listening to me!
Do you want to be friends?
Did you see that?
We're connecting!
You made one mistake.
What? But he just licked me...
Ourson here's been working for me
for eight years.
So it's not Ourson-kun.
It's Ourson-senpai to you, rookie.
Rookie?!
Here's to our future working together,
Ourson-senpai!!
Why is he prostrating to a dog...?
What are you laughing at?!
I hadn't expected all of this,
but I've certainly begun to admire him.
And now I want to be able
to connect with dogs just like him.
You told me to do that!!
And that's what brings me here!
I, Samura Miyu, 23 years old,
was forced by my ex-girlfriend
to take care of this guy,
when I suddenly met this amazing dog trainer
and got a job under him!
Representative/Dog Trainer
Dog Training
But, well...
Representative/Dog Trainer
Dog Training
Is this the place?
Why are the shutters closed...?
They should be open, right?
This isn't a work holiday...
Hello?
It's pitch black in there.
Is there even a real business here?
I hope he doesn't mind me coming up...
Niwa
"Niwa..." That should be him...
It opened!
Is this a storage room...?
Excuse me!
There he is!
Hey, Niwa-san?
Who are you?
Uhh, Samura? It's my first day here?
Did you already forget?!
Ahh, I remember now.
Anyways, it's too early for this.
Pipe down, will you, rookie?
Hold on, it's past opening time!
Don't want to miss any customers!
What customers?
I'm sorry?
We haven't had any business in two months.
What?!
But you told me I had to work here!
How am I supposed to pay off my debt?!
I quit my job for this!
I did say that, yeah.
But most people wouldn't come
after what I put you through.
Kneel.
I wish I could erase all that!!
Hey, don't let go of his leash.
Sorry for the wait!
Your dog has been trimmed!
Since it's early,
I just evened out the ends of his hairs.
Ourson-senpai, look at you!
You're so fluffy!
Who's a fluffy boy?
You smell so good, too!
Oh? Never seen you before.
Are you one of Shinichiro's friends?
That couldn't be.
I-I'm Samura Miyu!
I just started working here!
It's a pleasure to meet you!
That explains the "senpai" business.
So you hired someone, hmm?
Did you get any customers?
Of course not.
Don't fall back asleep!
For Ourson's trim.
If you can afford an employee,
you can pay for this.
Put it on my tab.
Huh?! What about the three months'
rent you still owe me?
He fled into dreamland!
Show me some drive.
Maybe when customers show.
Then go find some!
S-So strong...!
Um, miss!
Can you, uhh...
My name is Izumi Ritsuka.
I'm a landlady and a dog groomer!
I run a dog salon two doors down!
Giving a name to chance
Or giving love to fate
If I'm being honest
It's all the same either way
The things that you love
Are what make me happy
It's hilarious
Just how simple I am
Your heartbeat, stuck in my head
It brings back memories
To when we rushed home, laughing along the way
I hate being alone
It makes the night feel so slow
So come on, fall for me already
Sugarspot
You make my days even sweeter
With brown freckles just like your spots
I can get through a scratch or a rough patch
Just like that, the day's over
And in the deepest depths of my heart
Somewhere I feel lonely
Or maybe I miss you
Or a mix of both?
I don't know
Today's BenchBARK Advice
A dog's behavior varies depending on
its breed, personality,
and the environment it's kept in.
Just be aware, not every dog will act or treat you
the way the doggos from today's episode do!
Today's BenchBARK Advice
Next Time:
Your New Name