This Episode's Squishyyyy Highlights
Squishy
Punirunes. Before we knew it,
these creatures began to inhabit the human world.
They're very squishsterious creatures!
They all love to be squished.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Doing Our Best
Squish'n Jump♪
You look great!
What are those for?
Wow, really? So bobble hats are in?
You all look cute in those!
You're going to Squishy Park today, right?
Have fun!
Alright.
I'm going to...
Squish'n Jump
This is Squish'n Jump in Squishy Park.
It's a game where you jump
to try and reach the goal.
Excellent going, Enerune.
Everyone made it to the goal!
Hm? Yuka's not here.
You've got this, Yuka!
Stand like a splendid garden eel!
Uh, okay...
A-Are you alright?
Y-Yeah, I'm fine.
Wait...
Airune?!
You're back?
Oh, I lost track of time...
I wanted to jump ten times...
I'm the only one in my class
who hasn't gotten a stamp for passing yet...
B-But hey, I'm not very good at the high bar.
Not even vaulting boxes!
Everyone has things they're not good at.
Just look at dolphins!
Believe it or not, they can't breathe underwater.
Wait, really?
Dolphins are mammals like us humans,
so they have pulmonary respiration!
I didn't know that!
Airune wanted to wear Ururune's hat.
Ururune's hat has been stolen!
G-Get back here!
Wh-What now?
We have to go after it!
Huh?!
You want to get it yourself?
Looks like it feels responsible for this.
If you insist.
Airune promised it would get it back.
Y-Yuka?
If Airune's going for its goal,
then so will I!
Let's go! Ten basic bounces in a row!
That was close...
Are you sure you can do this alone?
It's worrying me a bit...
Alright!
Yuka!
Huh?
I searched online, and apparently
there's tutorial videos for jump-roping!
Aoi...
I want to help you too!
Thank you...
W-Wow, that's a high jump.
If you could do that too,
you could get that hat back!
Enerune, that comes from me too!
Please teach Airune!
Thank you, Enerune!
First, they strengthen their leg muscles
on the jungle gym.
That crow is utterly toying with them.
But Airune doesn't back down!
Relax your muscles!
Imagine you're a spotted jelly!
The rope spins around the shark's pectoral fins!
Where's that supposed to be?!
Again...!
"Now you're ready to take back that hat," it says.
The time has come.
One!
The wind forces it back!
It rides the wind like leaves from a tree...
and does an XXL Jump!
Nice catch!
Marvelous!
Eight!
Nine!
Ten!
I...
– I did it!!
– You did it!!
Now you can get that passing stamp!
Yeah! Thanks a lot, Aoi!
Good job, Airune!
I succeeded too!
The two share their joys among each other.
Airune is still no match for Enerune.
Punirunes Guide
Today on the Punirunes Guide...
Squish'n Jump
It's a popular game in Squishy Park.
The squestion!
It's time for the squestion!
Which of these do you find at the goal?
1. Snowman
2. Palm tree
3. Crab
The answer is...
2. Palm tree
The palm tree!
It's also a good spot to take a photo
to commemorate your goal!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
What do I do...?
I got into a fight with Aoi...
Huh? I can make up with her on Valentine's Day?
Next time: "Something's Cooking
on Valentine's Day♪"
Next Time
Something's Cooking
on Valentine's Day♪
"Puni" in next time!