This Episode's Squishyyyy Highlights
Squishy
A cat blocks their path!
This Episode's Squishyyyy Highlights
Squishy
Punirunes. Before we knew it,
these creatures began to inhabit the human world.
They're very squishsterious creatures!
They all love to be squished.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Ururune's Adventure♪
Is Enerune doing okay...?
It's not bothering you, is it?
Not at all!
Everyone's having fun at the sleepover.
If it ever gets sad, I can come pick it up at once.
Don't worry about it.
They should all be asleep by now anyway.
The Punirunes all get to sleep by 8 P.M.
Ururune must be hungry.
Ururune's off to find food on its own.
Woo-hoo! I won!
I lost again!
Too bad!
If I had just taken the corner...!
Let me play next!
Okay! You can take my place, then.
Alright! You're on, Yuka!
Airune's caught on to Ururune's absence!
They're all set on looking for Ururune!
Airune's party set off
on their adventure.
I won!
I can't believe I lost again!
You're terrible at this, Dad!
One more! Let me play you again!
Nope!
Yuka and I will play next!
Aww!
Then, uh, can we try 2-on-1 again?
No!
Airune found Ururune!
Be careful going down stairs.
They're all hungry now.
Now they're all set on finding food together!
Yuka!
Don't go eating snacks late at night!
Okayyy...
The Punirunes continue, quietly.
A cat blocks their path!
But it is resting.
Punirunes
Fight
Go Around
Cat - 1
Ururune is five seconds away from breaking into tears!
Looks like he just wanted a squish.
Just in the knick of time!
Gadzooks!
They've found gummies!
But how will they get up to it...?
Puni Tower, followed by...!
Puni Rocket!
Getting those gummies won't be an easy task.
Huh?
Isn't that...?
I see.
You just wanted to eat some gummies!
Did you all wake up hungry?
But they can't snack this la—
During a sleepover,
snacking at night is okie-dokie artichokie!
Whaaat?
Let them have it for today, okay?
Fine, just for today. Consider it an exception.
Here, Ururune!
Would ya look at that, it's smiling!
The rest of you can have some too!
They're all giving it their gummies!
Getting so many gummies
puts a big smile on its face...
My, my.
There it goes again.
Must be very happy!
Ururune!
Whether it's happy or sad,
Ururune sheds tears.
Punirunes Guide
Today on the Punirunes Guide...
Ururune
Ururune's very tearful and is quick to break into tears.
The squestion!
It's time for the squestion!
1. Cleaning
2. Drawing
3. Cake-Baking
What's Ururune very good at?
The answer is...
2. Drawing
Drawing!
Ururune loves drawing!
Though when it comes out very good,
it gets too happy and cries.
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Trick-or-treat!
The Punirunes are having a wild Halloween party!
When suddenly, we're greeted by...
Is that real?!
Next Time
Next time: "Bakerune's Halloween Scare♪"
Bakerune's Halloween Scare♪
"Puni" in next time!