This Episode's Squishyyyy Highlights
Squishy
Punirunes. Before we knew it,
these creatures began to inhabit the human world.
They're very squishsterious creatures!
They all love to be squished.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
The Punirunes
Clean Together♪
Wh-What happened here?!
Alright, you two! That's enough playing chase!
Look at the mess you've made!
They're quite sorry about the mess.
I-It's good to see you two having so much fun...
But you have to clean up after yourselves.
I'll help you guys out, okay?
Oh, yeah! Coolrune, as the cool beauty,
you're great at cleaning, right?
That's promising!
Well, good luck!
Let's get cleaning!
That's it!
My handkerchief...
What's it doing over here?
Remember this?
You alright, Airune?
There's no way I'd forget.
This handkerchief will always remind me
of the day we met!
It really brings me back...
So much has happened since then.
Then we met the other Punirunes,
and things have gotten squishier and squishier and...
S-Sorry, Coolrune.
Back to cleaning!
It happens—sometimes you get stuck cleaning
because you start reminiscing.
The work of a master—good work, Coolrune!
The window looks clean and sparkly!
However...
It's only gotten messier.
This is the hat I wore on Halloween.
I should keep it up as decoration.
I wish I could practice with the jump-rope more
so I can get better at it...
Wait, this isn't helping me clean up at all!
Huh? Wh-What are you doing?
Amazing!
You're amazing, Coolrune!
You all wanna try?
Let's get cleaning again!
Looking real clean!
Hm? A building block?
I should take this to Airune's house.
Whaaat?!
Everything was piled up in here.
Now we're back to square one...
Aah... So soothing...
But that soothing won't help this mess...
Guess we'll just have to clean up again.
What do you need the Babyrunes for?
Coolrune seems to have something up its sleeve.
What's going on?
Squishfusion
The Punirunes have fused into one!
Whaaat?!
Amazing!
Whoa...
So convenient!
Alright! I'd better help out too!
This goes here...
And this goes here!
Now they're really done cleaning!
Cleaning up feels so good!
My room feels so much more
spacious than before!
Coolrune's cleaning spirit
is on fire!
I-I think my room is clean enough now...
Coolrune is going past its limit!
It's so clean up here!
Wait, what?!
What in the world happened here...?
You even got rid of the couch and the table...
That's going too far!
Uh, it looks nice up here! Very wide and open...?
Meanwhile, up in the attic...
Clean in moderation.
Punirunes Guide
Today on the Punirunes Guide...
Cleaning
Among the Punirunes,
Coolrune is the greatest at cleaning.
The squestion!
It's time for the squestion!
1. Dad's weird mask
2. Broom
3. Christmas tree
Which tool did Coolrune use to clean today?
The answer is...
2. Broom
...the broom!
Coolrune's cleaning job is never over!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Huh? Airune, you're going to Aoi's house?
Enerune, you're going to Yuka's house?
Sounds fun!
Next time: "Airune and Enerune Trade Places♪"
Airune and Enerune
Trade Places♪
Next Time
"Puni" in next time!