This Episode's Squishyyyy Highlights
Squishy
Punirunes. Before we knew it,
these creatures began to inhabit the human world.
They're very squishsterious creatures!
They all love to be squished.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Punirunes
Punirunes, creatures full of mystery.
In order to bring their ecology to light,
we're conducting our first ever
close-up coverage of them.
This footage was obtained by a news crew
that followed a day in the life of one Punirune.
What true nature of the Punirunes
will this reveal?
The Punifessionals♪
This is Airune,
the Punirune we'll be covering.
Airune's day starts early.
They say that daily exercise is crucial
for maintaining their squishiness.
But its routine doesn't stop here.
Airune keeps its nose on the grind.
It's going running.
Like they say, squishiness wasn't built in a day.
Our news crew was able to catch a glimpse
of Airune's stoic side.
Why are you up so early?
"I have to stay squishy!"
The news team didn't quite understand yet
what it meant by that.
8:00 A.M.
After its morning routine,
Airune gets back to rest.
Airune?
Are you still sleeping?
I'll leave this here for you!
Oh, no!
I'm so late! Bye, Airune!
Airune's day has only just begun.
10:00 A.M.
At 10 A.M., Airune arrives at the market.
Are you waiting for somebody?
This is Airune's close friend Enerune.
It seems very energetic,
but it appears to have
accepted the news crew.
And today...
we will witness many Punirunes.
Stylish trends are crucial
to the world of the Punirunes.
"It's important to stay cool,"
said passionately by
the fashion-conscious Punirune, Coolrune.
What is being stylish to you?
Our next sighting is a popular figure
in the Punirunes world.
Loverune often holds fan events like this.
Pikarune is the host.
Some Punirunes are skillful enough
to do things like this.
The Punirunes' ecology is quite diverse.
12:00 P.M.
It is the early afternoon.
Airune and friends are gathered together,
but are still looking for someone.
What's next on the agenda?
An artist is going to hold an exhibition here.
And that artist is...
There it is.
The up-and-coming artist, Ururune.
Even though its exhibition is starting so soon,
it's still not satisfied with its latest drawing.
It's stopped drawing.
It couldn't bear the pressure
and ripped it.
Punirunes have already lined up by the venue
to see the exhibition.
How will it handle this situation?
The news crew was kicked out.
Airune is on the move.
It runs the road it trained on
to help its friend.
Are you a friend of Airune's?
The exhibition went on as planned.
What do you think of
when you look at this art?
I'm sure the art is full of memories.
They've all been through hard times
and fun times together, haven't they?
2:00 P.M.
After that, they're all invited
to Airune's room for a party.
But even then, Punirunes are free creatures.
Some sit and eat, others get up and dance.
Some give advice on how to
arrange their furniture to be more feng shui.
Some have been hiding the whole time!
And some are shy.
3:45 P.M.
I'm home!
Oh, you...
You fell back asleep?
Punirunes are creatures full of mystery.
Through their coverage
the news crew realized something.
To be squishy...
isn't about the flabbiness of their bodies,
but perhaps the strength to repel
any adversity.
8:00 P.M.
Today on the Punirunes Guide...
Punirunes Guide
Market
The Punirunes market
sells all sorts of items.
The squestion!
It's time for the squestion!
Which store sells this item?
1. Food store
2. Fashion store
3. Furniture store
The answer is...
The fashion store!
Coolrune checks there
for new products every day!
2. Fashion store
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
Airune, where are you going?
"Goodbye?"
You're leaving for good?
Anything but that!
Next Time
Next time: "Airune Says Goodbye♪"
Airune Says Goodbye♪