This Episode's Squishyyyy Highlights
Squishy
Punirunes. Before we knew it,
these creatures began to inhabit the human world.
They're very squishsterious creatures!
They all love to be squished.
Who knows, there could be
a Punirune right next to you!
Loverune's Big Love♪
I'm home!
I'm back, Airune!
Here's Yuka!
Huh? It's not here.
Where could it be?
Punirunes do as they please.
They often go exploring when not being watched.
No wonder.
It's been getting along real well
with that spunky Enerune.
Even Airune's gonna want to spend time
far away every now and then!
Oh!
It wasn't far after all!
So you were all just sunbathing here, huh?
Airune, Enerune, Ururune,
Coolrune, and even Loverune!
A Babyrune?
For some reason, they brought home a Babyrune!
Airune, what happened to it?
Was it in danger like Enerune was?
What's happening here, you ask?
The Punirunes are taking a stroll
when they come across a Babyrune.
It's fallen head over heels for Loverune!
I see!
All things considered...
it sure seems like it's taking a liking to Loverune!
I can see why you'd follow it home.
It's gentle and full of love —
anybody would fall for it!
I'm happy for you, Babyrune!
The next day...
Hi, Komugi!
Is Airune here?
Nope.
They're sunbathing again?
There's more of them?
Why are there more?!
Looks like they've brought home
a few more Babyrunes.
So, uhh...
Where did they come from?
To put it simply,
they've all grown attached to Loverune.
Loverune can't take a good walk
without making new fans, can it?
Oh, no! We have to help it take care of them!
Enerune's going to try playing with the Babyrunes.
They've gotten very dusty from the crash.
Coolrune loves keeping tidy.
So it's doing what it does best —
cleaning up the Babyrunes.
It can be a bit persistent about cleanliness, though...
Ururune is trying to make them happy
by drawing Loverune.
Ururune's tears are infectious!
What now?
Huh? Oh, right!
Let's make a meat dumpling!
Let's get squ-ooking!
Give it some of the squishsterious squishence...
Stir it...
Knead it...
Give it a squishy kneading so it'll be nice and fluffy!
Meat dumpuning
Meat dumpuning, ready to serve!
Alright, dig in, everybody!
Already?!
H-Hey, wait...
I can't make more that quickly...
Right, Airune?
Aw, not you guys too! I can't make that much!
How am I supposed to deal with this?
Loverune?
Coolrune plays it cool, even when it's ignored.
A-Amazing...
Loverune's like a pro at spreading love!
Loverune will save the world with its love!
Could this be...
its Big Love?
Huh?! What the?
Aoi?
What in the world?!
They're everywhere!
Hey! What do we do about this?!
Will Loverune save the world with its love?
Punirunes Guide
Today on the Punirunes Guide...
Loverune
Loverune is a Punirune filled with love.
Just one of its heart-shaped winks
is charged with love!
The squestion!
It's time for the squestion!
Can you count how many hearts
it makes in three seconds?
Good luck!
The answer is...
Five times!
5 times!
Now you're one of its fans too!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Give the squishence a good stir
And make a nice yummy dish
Once they're all full
They look so happy♪
The more that we're together
The more we understand each other
And just like that (Squish! Squish!)
We're best friends (Squish! Squish!)
It's so squishsterious!
Puni!
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Squishy squishy, pet it, take care of it
Squishy squishy, puni puni
Punirunes! (Rune-rune!)
Let's play, Punirunes!
Next Time
The Punirunes are having a sleepover!
I can't wait!
Oh no! Ururune's about to cry, what do we do?
Someone do something!
Next Time
Next time: "Ururune's Adventure♪"
Ururune's Adventure♪
"Puni" in next time!