Noble
FARMER
Oh no! I'm gonna be late!
I'm supposed to play mahjong
all night with my friends,
but I lost track of time milking the cows!
I'm gonna be so late!
But when I sped around a bend
on the farm roads...
I came face-to-face with a combine
wheat harvester taking up both lanes.
Now I'll really be late!
Head 37
Left Behind by Farmers
August is when wheat harvesting kicks in,
and when it gets late, you tend to see
these giant, impassable combine harvesters.
I see. They travel at night
to avoid causing traffic!
Which brings me to today's topic:
road blockage left behind by farmers!
Oh yeah! There's always reports
about vegetables falling out on the road.
Do you get 10% of it if you turn it in?
In tonnes, yes.
In... tonnes?
Now I'll talk about a few different things
farmers leave behind.
Starting with...
Oop, that's a lotta radishes.
That's a real stinker.
Baskets often come loose
from the back of delivery trucks.
In Kushiro...
In the Kushiro area, there were reports
of a large amount of loose cod.
In Kushiro...
Here is a farm road with rice planted in it,
(Meant for paddy fields)
likely due to a rice transplanter
being left in planting mode.
When a freight train got derailed,
scattering potatoes all over the place...
It costs money to get it all collected,
so you all can just take it.
Hooray! Woohoo!
The year after, the potatoes that weren't taken
grew in abundance along the tracks.
Potatoes sure are persevering.
But not every loose item
is a people-pleaser.
When this manure spreader (a.k.a. the poop-scatterer)
went off the side of the road...
I don't wanna pick this all up,
so you all can just take it.
Forget it!
The year after, the grass
along the road overgrew.
DANGER
Plenty of nutrients for them...
I don't wanna pick
this all up,
so you can just
take it!
I don't wanna pick
this all up,
so you can just
take it!
Forget it.
The year after,
the grass along
the road
overgrew.
The year after,
the grass along
the road
overgrew.
It IS nutritious...
Noble
FARMER
Did you destroy that Noble Farmer?!
Noble
FARMER
While the examples so far
have had their dangers,
others are more dangerous dangerous.
Like, super big and super heavy?
Precisely. And round bales fit that bill quite well.
Regardless of the type of pasture grass
or the moisture,
Compact excavator: ~500 kg
Round bale: 300 to 500 kg each (depending on moisture content)
round bales typically weigh
from 300 to 500 kilograms each.
Compact excavator: ~500 kg
Round bale: 300 to 500 kg each (depending on moisture content)
So seeing them left out on the road
is a horrifying sight.
Yikes, so they could just start
tumbling towards you?!
But I have a frightening tale
about something even bigger... even heavier!
Yeesh, I can hardly see anythin'.
He crashed into a loose draft horse in the fog!
Someone left behind a horse?!
Thank goodness I was going slow...
The horse suffered a minor injury,
but the car was done for good.
Giant horses are terrifying...
Lots of stories about horses
breaking down cars by trampling them.
Unbelievable...
But that has nothing to do
with road blockage.
I'd like to close out with a story
about another time I was late.
Oh no! I'm gonna be late!
I was fooling around in town
and I'm gonna miss the cows' evening milking!
But when I sped around a bend
on the farm roads...
a huge herd of crows
filled up the whole road.
All the cows from the ranch nearby got loose...
I ended up guiding them back
to their owner by car,
making me late for the milking at home.
Farmers and non-farmers alike,
please watch out for road blockage.
There's cow poop all over the road!
Storming through a wheat field, just like anybody else
One big slip, and my life flashes before my eyes
But even through my wounds my body still shines!
So on nights so painful I can't help but have a cow
I'll shake off the vines entangling me and look forward
Just pushing yourself forward makes every task a breeze
Not that I can prove it!