Noble
FARMER
October, during the fall harvest.
Pumpkins take over the world
as Halloween decorations begin.
Look, the rest stop decorated
for Halloween!
They put all these pumpkins
across their grass, isn't it adorable?
I'm so sick of looking at pumpkins.
But for farmers, Halloween is a time
where we sit down and polish pumpkins 24/7.
Head 32
Pumpkins
If we get any trick-or-treating brats,
I'm gonna drag 'em away
to help with the harvest.
They'll get their treats
only as compensation for their labor.
These pumpkins are driving them mad...
Darn, a mouse got into this one.
In addition to vegetables that are
malformed, too big or too small,
Non-Standard Vegetables
pumpkins chewed up by mice
are non-standard, rendering them unshippable.
Unshippable
Since mice are particular about taste,
they take one bite out of each pumpkin,
Unshippable
Bland
Yucky
then eat through the first one they find tasty.
Yummy!
Since it only took one bite...
Whoa, check this out!
It ate a whole chunk of this one!
Which means this pumpkin...
must taste super good!
Super Yummy!
Wild animals have reliable tongues.
So we can cut a bunch of this out
and have the rest for dinner!
But it would be at our own liability,
given we know it's full of bacteria.
The Pumpkin of Self-Liability
Some mice get cocky and carve
themselves a home in those pumpkins.
The Pumpkin of Self-Liability
Welcome
To the trash with you
and your food house!
On that note, pumpkins will form scabs
to cover any damages,
Scraped by rocks
Scratched by their own vines
and as a result of its rough appearance
it will be non-standard.
Chewed up by wildlife
However, there are decent uses
for these scabs.
We can use a chisel to carve drawings or words
into these pumpkins before they're ripened to make...
Scab art pumpkins
Bear
scab art pumpkins!
We've also held events where children
can make scab art pumpkins,
which they've certainly enjoyed.
I've also taken requests for scab art pumpkins.
I have a fun memory of doing scab art
on a giant pumpkin weighing over 100 kilograms.
Bring it on, autumn festival
Though the yellow pumpkins you see
on Halloween are usually for livestock,
and so we'd use them as feed
right after the holiday ended.
However, the cows on Arakawa Farms were fed
non-standard pumpkins grown for humans,
and grew to not like the less sweet pumpkins
made for them as much.
Here's another thing that happened
because of us feeding them human pumpkins.
Y'see, the cows would go poop
on the field after eating the pumpkins.
Undigested
seeds
And their feces would have undigested seeds in them!
Undigested
seeds
Their feces get piled up in the corners
of the field and used as compost,
then pumpkins start growing in them.
Then the cows eat the pumpkins,
poop on the field,
they grow again, they eat again,
and so on.
The cows grow the pumpkins,
forming Field-Confined Eco-Agriculture!
Field-Confined Eco-Agriculture
I heard they're super tasty
since they're grown with lots of compost.
Alright. Give it a try, then.
I heard they're tasty!
No one was brave enough to eat it.
Apparently Halloween started as a Celtic harvest festival.
They used to use turnips instead of pumpkins!
It didn't get replaced with pumpkins
until it reached the U.S.
Lookie, lookie! I made a jack-o'-lantern
out of a non-standard pumpkin!
Well, it's kinda rough, and... green,
but eh, let's use it. Why not.
That crude jack-o'-lantern finally got us
into the Halloween spirit. But then...
The next day, it was savaged by mice.
JACK!
Storming through a wheat field, just like anybody else
One big slip, and my life flashes before my eyes
But even through my wounds my body still shines!
So on nights so painful I can't help but have a cow
I'll shake off the vines entangling me and look forward
Just pushing yourself forward makes every task a breeze
Not that I can prove it!