This anime centers around manga artist Arakawa Hiromu's
experiences as a farmer in Hokkaido,
taking her most rib-tickling
and off-the-wall stories
and really squeezing 'em out
for your entertainment!
It's a masterpiece of a series
you can learn from and laugh to...
indeed!
Noble
FARMER
I'm Arakawa Hiromu.
Manga artist
I'm a manga artist who spent 7 years
on my family's farm in Hokkaido.
This is Ishii from Shinshokan.
Editor for Shinshokan
She's the editor on Noble Farmer.
Nothing screams Noble Farmer
like cows, am I right?
Do you have any more cow stories
left in the vault?
Oh, plenty more.
But I worry about getting too niche.
If not cows, maybe your pets?
People really loved hearing
about your dogs and cats!
Ah, pet talk. I see.
Oh! How's this for pet talk?
Head 29
Pet Cow
Uh, you can keep a cow as a pet?
Not really, but just picture it:
what would happen if you, Ishii,
kept a cow as a pet?
Wait, I'm the one with the cow?
Oh, hold on. Pigs have miniatures, right?
Maybe cows do too!
Here's your miniature cow!
My room!
You call this small?!
Holstein cows largely weigh from 600 to 700 kg,
Holstein
Weight: 600-700 kg
making this 500 kg wagyu
on the smaller side!
Wagyu
(Female Japanese Black)
Weight: approx. 500 kg
That's still over half a ton!
(Female Japanese Black)
Weight: approx. 500 kg
Wagyu
(Female Japanese Black)
Weight: approx. 500 kg
Wagyu
(Female Japanese Black)
Weight: approx. 500 kg
And so began the life
of Ishii and the cow under one roof.
So cold...
This is Arakawa.
I'll be giving you the play-by-play.
With me, I have two guests.
Arakawa Hiromu's father
I'm Arakawa's father.
Arakawa Hiromu's mother
I'm Arakawa's mother.
Maybe it'll be warmer
if I rest with the cow...
Looks like she's seeking heat from the cow!
Cows do have a nice, toasty
body temperature of 39°.
The average body temperature of a cow is 38-39°C.
Aww, so warm!
This could be such a cozy way
to fall aslee...p...
Ow-ow-ow-ow!
If that cow turns in her sleep,
she'll flatten a human like a pancake.
Do not sleep with a cow,
as it will crush you if it turns in its sleep.
Sleeping near a cow is a great way
to get crushed, that's for sure.
I thought I was a goner last night...
After making it out alive somehow,
Ishii takes the cow for a walk.
Y'know, walking a cow isn't too bad.
It's nice and sunny out.
Just so relaxi...
Wagyu cows poop 20 kg a day, I believe.
Wagyu will defecate 20 kg and urinate 7 l on average in one day.
And they urinate 7 liters.
Geez, who knew a walk
required so much labor.
Oh, is the cow about to sneeze?
Ah, yes. Sneezing while defecating
makes 'em shoot their poop out.
Sneezing during defecation will make it shoot out poop.
She's lucky it didn't hit her.
Ishii began to feel—and I mean feel—
the difficulties of keeping a cow.
But there were still more challenges ahead.
Cows are sensitive to heat,
so the AC must stay on all the time.
Due to heat sensitivity, cows need protection
in form of ventilation, forced draft and cooling.
My electricity bill!
Without a soft bed,
she'll hurt her legs,
For comfort, cows need a soft bed and regular cleaning.
so you'd best keep her
on the tatami mat.
My tatami bill!
Cows drink from 20 to 50 liters of water a day.
Wagyu drink 20-50 L of water on average.
My water bill!
Ishii continued caring for the cow
at her expense.
Many days passed, and at last
the time came for her to say goodbye.
Th-Thank you for everything,
Hanako the wagyu cow.
She passed in peace.
Allow me to begin her cremation.
My life with Hanako was nothing but trouble,
but we made so many amazing memories toge...
Why does it smell so good...?
Here is her urn.
That's humongous!
That's how it'd go.
Wanna give it a shot?
As if!
In conclusion:
Keeping a cow as a pet
in a regular household...
ain't it!
Storming through a wheat field, just like anybody else
One big slip, and my life flashes before my eyes
But even through my wounds my body still shines!
So on nights so painful I can't help but have a cow
I'll shake off the vines entangling me and look forward
Just pushing yourself forward makes every task a breeze
Not that I can prove it!