Dino Girl
Gauko
A Cry for Peace
Episode 9
World Peace
World peace!
World peace?
What's all this about, Naoko?
While we're lazing about
learning in class,
there are innocent people
suffering in our world!
You tell 'em, woof!
And we're just supposed
to sit and watch?
We should be taking action!
Throw away those textbooks
and arm yourself, woof!
That isn't any of our business.
It is our business!
Pew-pew-pew-pew-pew!
Every time you blink,
another precious life is taken from us!
What she said, woof!
Oh, yeah, what about that terrorist
plane crash the other day...?
That was freaky...
We have to go fight!
Fight how?
Well...
You're not expecting us
to go out to war with guns, right?
That wouldn't make us different
from those scary people.
B-But we have to do something!
You keep saying that, but...
What can we do anyways?
W-Well...
Arm ourselves and fight?
We can't do that.
But they're out there
killing harmless civilians as we speak!
What do you want us to do, then?
W-Well, we...
Oh, music class is up next!
Let's go.
Wait, you guys!
Naoko, I get what you're trying to tell us,
but there's only so much we can do!
I know, but...
It's not like we can just turn into big monsters
and take out the bad guys ourselves.
We're still just children.
Ain't it better to have fun
and take care of yourself?
Have fun and take care, you say?
Come on, we better get to class!
Pus-pus!
If I could turn into a big monster...
Dino Girl
Gauko
To Be Continued
Dino Girl