Dino Girl
Gauko
This Beautiful World
Episode 8
I wake up
and open the window.
It's sunny outside.
If my hair looks good,
it'll be a good day.
If not, then things might not go as planned.
I eat breakfast with Mom and Dad.
Miso soup, rolled omelette,
and freshly-boiled rice.
Let us eat!
Let us eat, ribbit!
It's as delicious as always.
Hey!
Hi!
I meet my friends at school.
Did you see that show yesterday?
Oh, yeah, I did!
Such a good episode!
They're very excited to talk about
the show they watched yesterday.
Probably my favorite so far!
Same!
Class is kind of boring.
My town is very peaceful.
Like a typical day playing on loop.
And it's very beautiful.
Every day is the same as the last,
never changing.
But in truth,
I'm just blissfully unaware.
The sunset is so pretty...
Dino Girl
Gauko
To Be Continued
Dino Girl