This is Snack World, the hallowed ground of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam and people have handy smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
And my name's Chup!
My village was burnt down by the evil land-destroying merchant Vinegar Khan,
so I've embarked on a journey to get my revenge 1000-fold!
The tickets to King Oyster City, where Vinegar is, cost 20 million gillan.
So I'm on an adventure searching for big treasure to make loads of cash!
Crystal Sword!
Goooleeem!
You're goin' down!
Hyaaah!
Hah... Oh, yeah... It's settled.
It's like my grandmother once said...
The decision makes a man... A man who can't decide is inconclusive!
A decision makes a man.
A man who can't decide
is inconclusive!
A decision makes a man.
A man who can't decide
is inconclusive!
Ooh, sounds right!
Back at it with his grandmother's wisdom...
- Oh?
- It's a treasure chest!
Aha, what luck!
- How about we take a look inside?
- Treasure time, treasure time! Open it, open it!
Wait!
Something smells off...
What if there's a Mimic in that chest?
- What's a Mimic?
- Sniff sniff...
Mimics are these Monsters that take the form of treasure chests...
...with a powerful Monster inside waiting to tear apart whoever dares open it!
- Sooo, do we just go, then?
- Huh?
Wait just a second. I'm the lone Monster here, and I know another when I smell one.
This smells like...
I know! There's canned mackerel in this chest!
- Ooh!
- Hot dog, that's a relief!
- Let's go!
- Hold on, now!
Why would you even smell canned mackerel in a place like this?
Well, they call it canned mackerel because you get it served in a tin.
On the internet,
there's a person that run things called the "server admin..."
That's not what I'm asking!
Why would there be a smell of canned mackerel in this dungeon?!
How should I know? Does it hurt to just go along with things? Jeez.
They look tasty!
Aaah! I just saw something glow in there!
What? Like a gemstone?
Really?! Sweet, let's open it!
I wonder if they left the skin on the mackerel!
Come on, now! Open up, open up!
Open up and lemme eat you guys...!!
Wait, Chup!
What's wrong, Mayone?
You should approach everything with care!
- Make perfectly sure it's safe!
- How so?
What are you talkin' about?! Who cares if it's safe?!
Any day now, Mayone!
We should approach things with haste, too!
Will you read the room?! What are you doing?!
Yeah, what's the point of speaking up if you don't have any ideas?
Open the box already, pleeeease!!
Think of something, Pepperon!
You idiots...!
Huh?
If you're all taking your time, I may as well fill my stomach.
He's eating...
This guy is eating... Looks so tasty...!
Aww, eating sounds nice...
Aaaah! Something came out of the treasure chest!!
I can't stand that guy!!
I've got it! I can use my fire spell to expose whoever's in there!
If anyone's there, show yourself!!
Wow, Mayone, you're like a real wizard!!
Hehe, of course I am!
That scorches!!
Ey, what do you think you're doing?!
Aaah, no, my sweet baby!
Hot!! Hot!!
Hey, you better not be trying to eat off the floor, old man!
Please, please!!
- I'll just brush off the dirt!
- Would you stop getting distracted?!
End this, please!! End it already!!
You heard her, Gob-san!
Put an end to the pain already!!
Huh?
Ugh...this is getting painful to watch.
This is a complete waste of my MP anyways.
Y'know, come to think of it, you look pretty cool when you're doing magic!
Wow, you think so? You want a little more then?
Aaaagh! That burns! Hot! Hot!!
You're amazing!
H-Hey g-guys, s-s-stop p-p-playing with f-f-fire...
Dangit dangit dangit dangit dangit!!
Put it out, put it out pleeeease!!
I can't go on!!
Nothing happened...
Maybe I was just imagining things?
You're always very cautious, Mayone.
I guess so... Sorry, Chup.
I'm so-so-so-so-so stupid!
What kind of item d'ya think we'll get?
Ohh, yeah, yeah!!
I can't wait to find out!
It's unboxing time!
Opening it now!
Huh...aha!!
Huh?
Well? What's in the chest, Chup?
We got some well-done meat! Heheh.
konbini de kuda wo maku ukiyo wo samayou wakoudo yo
コンビニでクダを巻く 浮世を彷徨う若人よ
ま
うきよ
さまよ
わこうど
コンビニでクダを巻く 浮世を彷徨う若人よ
All you youngsters loitering about your lives,
shrouding the convenience stores
omaera wa genjitsu ni torinokosaresugi andeddo
オマエらは現実に 取り残されすぎアンデッ奴
げんじつ
と
のこ
ド
オマエらは現実に 取り残されすぎアンデッ奴
You're like undead who have left behind reality
itsumade sonna koto
いつまでそんなコト
How long are you going to keep doing this?