This is Snack World, the hallowed ground
of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam
and people have handy smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
And my name's Chup!
After a long battle,
I've finally defeated the evil merchant Vinegar Khan,
and now I'm moving towards a new goal!
Whatever perils await me,
I'll fully, flawlessly overcome them!
Alright, let's go on another big adventure today!
Princess Melora! Princess Melora!
Episode 48: The Birth of a Sorta-Overlord!
We have news!
Oh, Chup! What's the matter?
Huh? Right, guess what?
I think we defeated Scardon!
Wow, did you?
Here we go, Glace!
Yup! Fully, flawlessly, I think!
100%, without a doubt, I think!
There's no need to worry, I think.
You seem very jolly.
Yeah, very jolly, I think!
By the way, who are you?
Oh, lemme guess.
Relatives of the king?
What?
Of course not!
I haven't a clue of their identities either.
Alright, you two.
Show some respect for his majesty.
Now, introduce yourselves.
What was that?!
What did you just do?
Wait, are you illusionists?
Can you make anything disappear?
Yeah, that's right!
You're magicians!
Oh, is that all?
Y'know, I did once hear rumors
about a young pair of brothers
doing magic tricks together
a long way back!
We're so close up, and I can't
tell how it's done. Impressive.
Awesome!
Good show!
I have a question!
Can you also bend spoons?
What?
Anyone got any spoons?
Spoons?
I got one!
Why do you have that...?
You never know when you'll
come across a free sample!
Yeah, you do. Not often.
Here, bend this spoon!
No!
I didn't mean with your hands!
What's his problem?
I wonder.
Chup, remember that they're illusionists.
They're not going to do small tricks.
I get it! So can you make Gob-san disappear?
Just so you know,
I didn't plan this out.
You'd better applaud
if I actually disappear.
Huh?!
What the heck, dude?
What was that for?
Don't tell me.
They're faking it, aren't they?
I get it, man,
but you don't gotta hit him!
Who are you two?
This guy sucks.
He's no fun at all.
I asked you a question!
What's wrong, Vinsant?
You're sharper than I thought.
You will soon meet your end.
And with you, the world as well!
Where have I heard that before?
What was that?
That's what Scardon said.
Hate to break it to you,
but that was us, not Scardon.
Say what?!
We were sleeping away
in Demi-Glace Castle...
when Scardon arrived.
Ugh, what is it...?
Can't you keep it down?
Crap!
Isn't that Scardon?
We beat him on accident.
So we took his place
and messed around with you guys.
You took down Scardon?!
Wait, really?
I'm not sure I believe you.
You wanna see for yourselves?
Come on, play with us.
Let's take this outside.
Dang, that's cool!
Are you strong?
You might be some fun after all.
You guys think they actually
took down Scardon?
I kinda doubt it.
How could some pipsqueaks
take down an overlord dragon?
I'd have to disagree.
I've been sensing something off about them.
Huh?!
How long have you been with us?
What do you mean?
From my ranking,
I had a strange feeling from the start
Scardon may already be dead.
Seeing things in a whole new light yet?
What's with the lame catchphrase?
Also, you should've said so sooner!
Aren't you supposed...
Dragon Warp!
He got away!
That little brat...
What the?!
My word!
They're super-fast!
Dang it...
You're so weak. Lame.
All done.
Got a nice new weapon!
H-Hold on...
What, uhh... happens...
to the people you... "disappear?"
What do you mean by
"all done?"
What happens happens.
It's simple: they disappear from our world.
So you kill them?!
Yup, basically.
No way...
They got Vinsant...
They're too powerful.
Now I know for certain
they took down Scardon for real.
How could you...
Chup?
How could you take Vinsant?!
I won't let you have your way!
Chup!
The Super Great Dragon Knight!
I knew you were special.
Sure did.
He's super powerful!
He could defeat them!
Come face me!
Ugh, laaame.
So you're just as weak as him.
Say that again.
Chup!!
No...
He didn't even get to go all-out...
You're already giving up?
Well, alright. Time to go!
Chup!!
You brats!
Oh, relax. You'll have your turn
once we're done with him.
And we'll lead the world to ruin
while we're at it.
Wait!
I surrender.
On behalf of my kingdom and its people.
I will meet whatever demands
you give me.
Your majesty!
I don't like how high and mighty you sound.
Should we mess with them a bit, Demi?
Why not. I'll take...
this one!
D-Don't you dare!
Alright, Grandpa.
Enjoy the show!
What's up, Demi?
A strong guy has finally
come to see us!
Wait, what?
Are you hearing things?
I swear, I sensed someone strong just now...
I won't let you hurt Princess Melora!
You're getting on my nerves.
Take this.
Ah, Butako!
Chup!
It can't be...
Wait, where's Butako?
So it's true after all.
Ugh, you're back?
One can possess power
beyond their limits.
Also known as the Limit Break:
Dragon Knight Legend!
Once a Dragon Knight maximizes
their internal energy to the ultimate level,
they can fuse with a dragon!
Dragon Knight Legend
Chup
My word!
That name sounds powerful too!
Dragon Warp!
He got away again!
H-Huh?!
What happened?
He turned back to normal!
Warp-pa, get over here
and explain!
He's never there
when we need him!
I suppose that was just
a fleeting miracle.
Looks like they've both run out of stamina...
C'mon, you done already?
Laaame.
Demi, let's just erase him already.
Damn it!!
Nah, Glace.
Let's bring out the big guns.
Aw, I don't wanna.
Let's just get him over with.
I know, but a great deal of force
will really instill fear into 'em.
I get it!
Uh, what are they talking about?
Who are you?!
Overlord Demi-Glace.
Demi-Glace
This is, uh, how do you put it...
not looking really good for us, huh?
What's wrong?
Stand up and fight.
Dang it...
So you're an overlord, so what!
We're gonna throw you overboard!
Is this really the time for puns?
Chup!
This is bad.
We gotta...
We gotta save Chup!
Huh?!
Drat, went too far.
You're no different than Vinegar.
I won't let anyone who hurts the innocent...
ever, ever get away with it!
Oh?
So you've still got some drive in you, I see.
Very well.
I will give you 24 hours.
Until then, you can resort to any means
to try and defeat me.
If you can't, I'll destroy the world.
What?!
Now, let the game begin!
Ehem!
To all citizens, we are now
in a state of emergency.
The fate of our world
rests in the hands of an evil overlord.
Everything may be reduced to rubble
in 24 hours from now.
I request the assistance of anyone
with wisdom and strength.
Wisdom and strength?
Sages of this kingdom,
please grant me your wisdom!
Well, if you insist.
Miss Snow White,
I deeply appreciate your support.
Are you hanging in there?
Master Panpan!
I had a feeling
you'd be hopeless without me.
Our hope has arrived.
You're kidding.
I see.
I don't think we'll win
in a normal battle.
Master Panpan,
give us a strategy!
What is this?!
Hey!
I'm seeing cutlets, but no dipping sauce!
What is the meaning of this?!
That doesn't matter!
You, over there!
Go buy me some sauce.
Or borrow some from a neighbor.
Why am I the sauce guy?
All you're doing is
taking up space anyways! Now, go!
Warp-pa, we're begging you!
Man...
Dragon Warp...
If strength won't win the battle,
we'll need a more sophisticated plan.
But don't you worry—
I've got superhuman strength.
Hey, get up! This is no time to take a nap!
I'm awake.
Don't lie! You were totally asleep, I saw it!
I'm totally awake.
Hear you loud and clear.
Then tell me what I just said!
You got pissed off about
not having dipping sauce.
Cut the snark! Dipping sauce is a grave issue!
You have it.
It's under your side.
What?
You're right!
And you're calling me the sleepyhead.
Here, I got your sauce.
Shut up! Leave me be!
Huh?!
Snow White, tell me
you have an idea.
If you can't beat him in battle,
you'll have to confuse him.
Confuse him?
I know!
Sauce-pa, we have a job for you!
Who are you calling Sauce-pa?
I'm Warp-pa!
I finally got used to that name!
Sauce-pa, to the Spirit Garden, please!
Dragon Sauce!
He actually teleported us
by shouting "Dragon Sauce!"
I am Si.
And I am Ren.
Together, we're...
The Siren Sisters.
Their singing should confuse him
and throw him off balance!
Then we attack!
Huh?!
Such a strong voice!
What a beautiful baritone.
Your singing, it is pleasing to the ears
What?!
Drat, he confused them
before they could confuse him!
It was a failure?
I had a feeling
you'd be hopeless without me.
Master Panpan, what are our orders?
I'll talk to him face-to-face.
They call me the super negotiator of the forest.
So I'll negotiate with the overlord.
The super negotiator of the forest?!
How are you doin'?
Don't get me wrong.
I'm not here to fight you.
I'm here to talk.
Though it's pretty hot out.
Days like these make me
wanna go right home and shower.
You get me?
You wanna take a shower, right?
I suppose.
A great way to come out on top
in a negotation
is to get the other party
to say "yes" as much as you can.
I get it!
And he already got one!
Keep it up!
I know! How about we do
a personality test?
Close your eyes for me.
A personality test?
Listen.
You're going to visualize
a home in your mind.
Now close your eyes,
and imagine a home you would like.
Just keep your eyes closed.
Yes, take your time. Think carefully.
Think of the size of your home.
Think of the home you want to build...!
Just pretend!
Are you okay, Master Panpan?
Of course. I'm A-OK.
More importantly, Mayone,
do you have any spare underwear?
Underwear?
Master!!
Don't wet yourself!!
You baby!
B-Break up!
Dragon Warp!
Are we out of options already?
Guys!
Why didn't any of you come to me?
Goemon!
No one's coming. This is lame.
I miss when she was still around.
Don't talk about Sonia.
But it was so much fun back then!
Are we ever gonna hear her
laugh like that again?
Of course not.
She's dead.
This world's so lame.
We just have to destroy it.
Obviously.
Ram into him with the Sky Barracuda?!
The Sky Barracuda is the most powerful
weapon in the world.
It can break through the magic barrier,
and it has fuel for the Neo-Beam.
You want us to crash the airship
into an overlord?
Yes. I think that's our best bet.
Yeah! Let's do it!
Oh, yeah. Where's Griffon?
Huh?
I haven't seen him lately.
Chup, can you summon him
on the Fairypon?
Okay!
One thing...
If we do this,
won't the person piloting
the Sky Barracuda ram into him too?
G-Good point...
That is correct.
D-Does that mean the person
piloting the ship also...?
Yes.
What the?
Griffon's giving a
summoning error.
An error?
You don't suppose
he's already dead?
What? Why?!
Don't tell me they got him too!
So you don't have a pilot?
That's not good.
Dang it! If only I could pilot a ship!
Don't worry. Whoever takes the wheel,
I'll give you precise instructions.
Huh?
I have a scar on my elbow!
Damn it!
I'll steer the ship!
Chup, weren't you listening?
If you pilot, you'll crash
into the overlord.
I'll be fine! Butako, come with me!
Right before we crash,
you'll fly me out!
I see!
That makes sense!
You can come back safe and sound!
It's like my grandmother said!
Don't put your life
on the line.
Put some sauce
on it.
Don't put your life
on the line.
Put some sauce
on it.
Don't put your life on the line!
Put some sauce on it!
-Tome
Good thinking, Chup!
Chup, you're still making a risky bet.
I have to do it!
Butako and I
will fully, flawlessly save the world!
Preparing for takeoff.
All clear.
Just hit the launch switch
and you'll be in the air.
Are you ready?
Ready as ever!
Let's go, Butako!
Then hit it!
Alright! Launch switch...
on!
Launching in 5 seconds.
Butako, hang on to something.
Sky Barracuda, takeoff!
Good, Chup! Keep it going!
Alright! Let's go, Butako!
I hope this works...
It's our only option.
We gotta help how we can!
By distracting the overlord!
What is this?
A gift!
We think you'll like it.
Please accept it!
Please turn to stone!
No good.
What's that?
Take this!
Fire Sky Barracuda Crash Attaack!!
Alright! Let's get out of here, Butako!
Huh?! Butako?
She's gone!
I'll erase the whole ship.
nee kimi doko kara kita no?
Where are you from?
ima boku hima shiten dakedo
I've got time to spare
ochashite morae masenka?
Can I pour you some tea?
dame? dame? doushite desuka
No, you say? What's wrong?
jinsei wa rooringu sutoon
Life is like a rolling stone
tamaru konbini bukuro
Shopping bags piling up
seishun wa kumori zora
Youth is like a dark cloudy sky
sumafo izonshou sa
They're all glued to their phones
donzoko demo iijan
So what if we've hit rock bottom
ki ni shinakute iijan
Don't get so hung up on it
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
tabetara kateru kamojan
Maybe it'll help us get this katsu-done
dame dame demo iijan
But if it won't? Oh well
doutte koto neejan
Don't worry 'bout it
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
megezu ni ikouze
And keep moving forward
charanporan de iijan
Maybe we're kinda sloppy
muchakucha de iijan
And sure we're kinda reckless
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
tabetara kateru kamojan
Maybe it'll help us get this katsu-done
masshigura de iijan
So let's go full speed
tsuki susumeba iijan
And keep pushing onwards
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
tokoton yarouze
And see our goals all the way through
nee kimi doko kara kita no?
Where are you from?
ima boku hima shiten dakedo
I've got time to spare
Why don't we eat KATSUDON?
He hit the target...
Chup survived, right?
What happened, Butako?!
Did you fail to bring
Chup to safety?
Does that mean Chup
went down with the ship?!
Chup...
Thanks, Warp-pa!
Chup!
Oh, I see! You used Dragon Warp
to teleport out of danger!
Yeah!
How d'ya like that?
I don't just warp,
I think quick too!
Have you recognized my greatness again yet?
Warp-pa, you finally played a part!
What do you mean "finally?!"
Just today, I went
and bought sauce...
My word!
That's enough.
Time to erase all of you.
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone!
What are you teaching us about today?
Today's lesson is on the
Dragon Knight Legend.
Dragon Knight Legend
It's the form a Dragon Knight takes
after maximizing their powers
and fusing with a dragon.
Chup was able to fuse with Butako
because of their strong bond.
Butako and I were so cool!
Unfortunately, they transform back
when they run out of stamina...
but they're super powerful otherwise!
Next Time
Our final chance to save the world!
If we want to figure out the overlord's secret,
we'll have to warp through spacetime
to the past!
Unraveling the Secret of Overlord Demi-Glace
Next time: "Unraveling the Secret
of Overlord Demi-Glace!"
Alright, it's time for a big adventure!