This is Snack World, the hallowed ground
of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam
and people have handy smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
And my name's Chup!
After a long battle,
I've finally defeated the evil merchant Vinegar Khan,
and now I'm moving towards a new goal!
Whatever perils await me,
I'll fully, flawlessly overcome them!
Alright, let's go on another big adventure today!
Episode 47: Scardon Vanishes
Scardon is one mighty foe,
that's for sure.
We have to think outside of the box.
Vinsant, don't you have any ideas?
We're up against a dragon
so powerful he's called an overlord.
There's no shortcuts to beating him.
I just got a good idea!
What if we shot him with
some big projectile from super far away,
making him go "ka-boom?"
We could also send him a poisoned dumpling
from super far away,
so when he eats it, he goes "ka-blooey!"
Stop suggesting we take down
a final boss from a distance!
But it's the safest way to go!
Yeah.
No way! This is an overlord,
striking him with a sword is the way to go!
Right, Mayone?
Honestly, does it even matter
if we defeat Scardon?
Are you kidding, Mayone?
Of course it does!
Look, I thought about it,
but he's not really doing anything evil.
Has he even done any damage?
Now that you mention it...
Hmm...
I already told you about this.
Scardon brought ruin to our world twice.
Did you see it happen?
Uh, no, I read about it in books...
Maybe they're just slandering him?
You know how fast rumors spread!
This was bothering me for a bit.
RPGs and such always paint
overlords as the face of evil,
but maybe they're not so bad after all.
Mayone, that's a sensitive topic.
I get it.
Scardon is evil!
Monsters have been going savage
since he returned!
You sure? 'Cause they seem
fairly sociable to me.
Oh, that's true! Gob-san's a monster,
but he hasn't changed at all!
Don't call me a monster!
Oh, gosh.
Now I feel bad for attacking Scardon...
Oh, yeah!!
Sorry for attacking you!
Scardon, bro!!
Don't apologize!
Or act chummy with him!
The worst has yet to come. I know it.
And we can't just wait until it does.
He may even be turning a town
to rubble as we speak.
Hold on.
What's wrong?
Scardon's gone.
Huh?!
Wait, by gone, you mean...?
The Dragon GPS isn't picking him up.
Why not?
He's not in our world anymore.
Was he defeated?
That can't be right...
I haven't turned on the Dragon GPS
in a few days.
Maybe it's just broken.
Where the hell did he go?!
Are you sure someone
didn't already beat him?
Of course not!
A final boss doesn't just
get beaten in the background.
That's certainly unheard of by RPG rules.
I get it then! So that someone
who beat him was me!
Huh?
Explain.
When we were fighting him
with Robin Hood,
I managed to land a hit
on Scardon!
Maybe I hit his weak spot,
then it started to kick in
later at night,
and then wham, he died!
It wouldn't be that easy!
I nailed it!
My "It'll Kick In Later,
Then It'll Be Too Late When You Notice" Attack!
It's a little late to name your attack.
I think I may be the one
who defeated Scardon.
The heck do you mean?
Remember the mushroom Pepperon gave
Robin Hood that was stuck to my loincloth?
Oh no, there's no more mushrooms!
Oh, I have one more!
Robin, have this mushroom!
Wait, what?
You mean the one
he barfed out after?
Indeed!
I propose there was a bit of that
mushroom left behind in Demi-Glace Castle.
Scardon got hungry and ate it,
making him sick to his stomach,
and eventually die from it.
Perhaps he's strong on the outside,
but didn't think to train his stomach.
So you defeated him
with food poisoning?
That's the power of
my loincloth mushroom!
Oh, I know!
Scardon had really
sharp talons, right?
Yup, he sure did!
Maybe those did him in!
A mosquito bit his neck
in the dead of the night,
so he tried to scratch that awful itch...
...and sliced his neck right open!!
Doing himself in?
Come on, he can't be that clumsy.
Strength has its downsides!
Would you guys knock that off?!
There's no chance Scardon
went down like it was nothing!
He has to still be alive.
Please live, Scardon...
Uhh... aren't we supposed
to be defeating him?
Demi...
I'm tired of playing as Scardon.
Come on, Glace.
Demi
It was your idea to make it look like
Scardon's still going
to keep the magic alive.
I know, I know.
Glace
But I don't feel like getting in
and moving Scardon around.
We're only in this to begin with
because you defeated him.
All I did was whack him
and he died!
He's a bunch of phony-baloney.
Now, Glace.
If Scardon hadn't been resurrected,
we wouldn't have awakened
from our long slumber.
No kidding! His voice
is the perfect alarm clock.
Let's keep going a bit longer.
Didn't that one guy who showed before
look like beating Scardon was his life's purpose?
Oh, right.
The one with the long hair
and the smug look?
Yeah, him!
Saying things like,
"Fight me, Scardon!"
He was sooo desperate!
Yeah, he was!
Even though Scardon's already dead.
Even though it was just us inside!
He caught on to the fact
that Scardon doesn't speak,
then started frantically researching him.
If that dude gets word
that Scardon's gone,
he'd lose all reason to live!
What's his reason to live matter
if we die, though?
Let's just destroy the world
and get some sleep already.
No way. I wanna play with them
a bit more while we're still awake!
You remember the other guy with him,
with the spiky hair?
Yeah, I do!
The one who looked like a total doofus?
'Cuz of that and his hair,
I've been calling him "Spike Doof"
on the inside!
Spike Doof?
That fits him.
Wasn't he fun?
Yeah, he kinda was!
Wouldn't it be fun
to play with him?
Oh yeah!
Then let's stay awake a bit longer
to play with Spike Doof!
A toast to Scardon being
maybe-hopefully-defeated!
Cheers!
Come on, celebrate with us, Vinsant!
I'm not in the mood.
Also, isn't it a bit early to celebrate?
We don't know for certain
that Scardon's been defeated.
But he's clearly not around anymore, no?
I sent my Dragon GPS out for repairs.
Until it comes back,
there's no saying either way.
Well, yeah! We don't know,
and that's why we're doing this!
Once we know he's actually defeated,
we'll throw a much bigger party!
I'm thinking a feast 100 times bigger than this!
Agreed!
And 100 sexy ladies for me!
I'll report it to Princess Melora,
and she'll praise me a bunch,
and maybe even give me a reward...
I'll ask for her to do so many things...
Show some tact!
You didn't defeat him anyways!
And Vinsant, it wouldn't kill you
to drop the serious look and eat with us.
We won't know where to find Scardon
until the Dragon GPS is fixed.
I suppose.
You gotta learn to kick back
every once in a while!
It's like my grandmother said!
Stuff and nonsense.
Stuff your bags
and go on a trip.
Oh yeah.
Stuff and nonsense.
Stuff your bags
and go on a trip.
Oh yeah.
Stuff and nonsense.
Stuff your bags
and go on a trip.
Oh yeah.
Stuff and nonsense!
Stuff your bags and go on a trip! Oh yeah!
-Tome
Spike Doof's in this town, right?
Yeah.
I'm pretty sure they ran off towards this place.
Cheers!
Let's ask around.
What is this place?
A weapons shop?
Whoa! Demi, look!
Ain't this cool?
Wow. Weapons really have evolved some
since we were last awake.
Welcome in.
Hm? Who's this guy?
What's he doing?
This is a new feature.
I'm performing a finance scan.
Budget: 0 gillan.
No cards.
Unprofitable children.
Reception Level G.
Now activating reception
where I try to turn kids away.
What was all that?
Kiddos! Did you come in here by mistake?
This is a weapons shop!
It hurts a whole lot when you touch them!
Owie-owie!
Peek-a-boo... I see you!
What the heck?
It's funny. I've never seen a weird guy like this!
My! You better go home soon,
or your mommy will be worried sick!
Na-na-na boo-boo!
What's goin' on, Pinocchio?
We have customers?
Nah, they don't have any cash,
so I'm trying to turn them away.
Hold on now.
Look closely. Their outfits
look top-class!
They might have rich parents.
Lots of kids are getting weapons
out of their parents by begging for 'em.
No harm in showing them respect.
You've really thought this through.
I'm impressed.
Kids like those will fawn
over any old Jara.
Ey, kiddos!
I'll let you play with some Jaras!
I wanna play with one of the bigger ones!
I see. How's this shield, then?
Isn't it cool?
This is the Paccarat Titan Shield
from Paccarat Lapa.
It'll protect you from just about
any monster attack!
Wanna buy one for when
you get older?
But swords are so much cooler.
Hey. What's that weapon?
Oh, that's the Dark Knife.
It's a Phantom-brand.
A treasure hunter friend of mine
gave it to me after I yielded to him.
It's very rare!
Can I play with it?
No way.
That knife packs a terrifying punch.
I don't think I should let a little kid
like you handle it.
Terrifying, you say?
Now I wanna play with it more!
Sorry, kiddo. I mean it,
it's very dangerous.
Man, laaame.
I'm sorry?
Buh-bye!
Wait, what?! Uh, Mas...
Uh. What did you just do?
I erased him.
He wouldn't listen to me,
so I got bored of him.
You...erased him?
What happens to him after that?
No clue.
But he's definitely not coming back.
I-Is that true?
Hurry, let us play with it!
Aah, I-I apologize for the wait!
P-P-Please help yourselves...
Awesome!
Why are you a scaredy-cat now?
You were just treating us like little kids.
N-No, that's not what I...
I'm bored of him.
No, don't! Please don't erase me!
I'll do whatever you want!
I just ask to live!
You're going out begging for your life?
That's just sad.
Oh, yeah. You know this guy?
Huh? Chup?
Oh, so Spike Doof is named Chup!
Where can we find him?
I don't know where he is right now...
Okay, you're useless.
Huh?
Y'think it's okay
I take the knife?
Knock yourself out.
What's happening here?
You boys!
You have to line up
like everyone else.
Line up?
Akami, a former member of AKZ48,
is doing a handshake event.
If you want to shake her hand,
you have to line up here.
FORMER AKZ48 MEMBER
AKAMI HANDSHAKE EVENT
Listen, boys. This is a big deal.
After she graduated from AKZ48,
Akami became full of herself.
In order to put her fans first again,
she's set up her own handshake event
to show them her gratitude!
I don't get it, but maybe it's fun.
Let's give it a look.
Do you have handshake tickets?
Nope.
Pft, amateurs.
You can't get your hand shook
without a ticket.
It's like running out onto a battlefield
starch naked!
Leave at once!
He's getting on my nerves.
Or so I'd say,
but it's promising kids so young
can find the appeal in Akami.
Take these.
What's that?
Handshake tickets.
They were bonuses with her CD.
I have around 20 for myself.
I've already shook her hand five times today.
Interesting.
No need to thank me.
But I'd like it if you called me
Master Panpan.
Master Panpan?
More honor!
"Good morning, Master Panpan." Go.
Good morning, Master Panpan.
"Master Panpan, your face is so beautiful." Go.
Master Panpan, your face is so beautiful.
"Master Panpan, you are my sun." Go.
Master Panpan, you are my sun.
Good! Well done.
Now, line up behind me.
Don't stand behind me!!
You just told us to line up behind you.
Just a little joke from the Master.
Funny, right?
Huh?
"It was very funny, Master Panpan." Go.
It was very funny, Master Panpan.
Great.
I don't think I can take this, Glace.
You sure? He looks funny.
We should stick around him a bit more!
How long will this take?
I'd garner around 15 minutes.
What, really? That's, like, forever!
You fool! Don't be in a rush!
You should spend the time waiting in line
thinking about what to ask Akami.
FORMER AKZ48 MEMBER
AKAMI HANDSHAKE EVENT
You'll only have about 7 seconds
during your handshake.
FORMER AKZ48 MEMBER
AKAMI HANDSHAKE EVENT
So you have to ask a question that's short,
FORMER AKZ48 MEMBER
AKAMI HANDSHAKE EVENT
easy to answer,
and that no one else will ask.
Think about the ways she'll respond,
and the things you'll say back.
Your conversation could go
hundreds of different ways.
I think it's only fair to say
that the time spent waiting
is the true thrill of handshake events!
Wait, what?
We're up. Let's go.
That was oddly quick.
Shoot, I haven't even
thought of a question yet.
You boys go on up ahead.
Oh, no...
Should I ask about the cooking
she posted to her blog?
No, I just asked her about
the café she recommended.
She'll think all I care about is food!
Oh, no...
I'll ask what her favorite
animal behavior is!
Are you the last ones in line?
Yeah.
Are you here for my handshake event?
Yeah, sorta.
Thank you so much!
Do you have any questions for me?
Not really.
Oh.
I'm going back to my roots,
so I'll do my very best!
Okay, and?
Uh, you know...
Please keep cheering me on, okay?
Are all handshake events like this?
Yeah... You can come again if you like!
It was just a handshake...
That was boring.
Uh... huh?
Buh-bye!
Glace, look! It's Chup!
It is him!
Let's go, Glace!
Alright, I know what to ask!
"Do you sleep in pajamas or a nightgown?"
"By the way, I sleep naked!"
It's a plan!
Huh? Akami?
Where'd you go?
Don't stand behind me!!
She's not there...
Where is she?
I've finally made it to French Toaster.
I'm here to get my fresh start.
I've had a long journey, looking back.
I caught the attention
of arms dealer Vinegar Khan,
and was set to make my debut
with him producing...
His debut single should feel dark!
Its theme: devilish love!
"I love you so, I want you dead!
Yes, vine-vine!"
I was gifted the opportunity
to sing on a big stage.
I was so close to making my big break that day...
...then Vinegar died.
With my debut out of reach,
I lost sight of myself.
Hey, punk!
Watch where you're going!
Milkshake it, baby!
M-My apologies.
But the god of music
never stranded me.
Hold on. Where have I seen you before?
Oh yeah!
Aren't you the guy who sang
atop Vinegar Palace recently?
Yeah, that's me.
We've been lookin' for you!
Yeah! We fell in love with your voice!
We want you as our band's vocalist!
And now...
I have the best bandmates I could ever ask for.
Hold on there, Bowie.
Are we just supposed to walk
straight into town?
You might pass for a human,
but we're pretty clear-cut monsters.
Won't we scare the townspeople?
Only at first!
What?!
Believe in the power of music!
With your performance
and my singing,
they'll fall in love with us in no time!
It won't matter if we're people or monsters!
We'll be admired through our charm.
Hah, you got that right!
Yeah! Ain't no one our music
don't work on!
Milkshake it, baby!
Off we go! Our legend is about to begin!
Outta the way!
Huh?!
Where did Chup go?
Ugh, we lost him. Thanks to you.
Milkshake!
B-But our legend!
Buh-bye!
Demi, isn't this a castle?
Maybe this is where Chup is!
There's no way.
A doofus like him hanging out
with a royal leader? That's crazy.
Good point.
Wanna erase the leader here?
It could be fun,
plunging the kingdom into chaos!
I like where your mind's at!
Hold it right there, you two.
No one enters without permission.
What do we do?
I wonder!
That works.
What did you just do?
You just made them vanish!
Sure did. You catch it?
How'd you do that?
Like this.
Watch it!
You're no ordinary people, I take it!
Wow, this guy's fast!
He seems fun. Let's toy with him.
Oh, you raving to go? I'm in!
I sure like me some strong foes!
I'm back!
Dragon GPS repairs are finished!
Are they?
Go ahead and check it!
Now we'll know if Scardon
really got defeated or not!
He's definitely still alive,
I'll tell you that now.
No readings?
It can't be.
Where the hell is he?!
Give it up, Vinsant.
He was clearly taken down
while we weren't looking!
That's right!
And now that we know,
we can take this party to another level!
Come on!
Let's go report this
to Princess Melora!
Is that the leader?
Who knows.
Her skin looks smooth,
and she smells nice.
Let's observe her a bit.
Okay.
Good timing!
Do you mind helping me
put on my moisturizing cream?
Huh?
Sure, why not.
Be gentle, okay?
Melora, who could these boys be?
No idea!
How did you get in here?
There should be soldiers guarding
the gates and inside the castle.
Oh, yeah, we erased them.
You what?
And we got attacked by
some guy dressed like a bird.
He seemed awful strong,
so we erased him quick.
Could you explain what you mean by "erased?"
Explaining it could take a while,
so I'll just show you.
nee kimi doko kara kita no?
Where are you from?
ima boku hima shiten dakedo
I've got time to spare
ochashite morae masenka?
Can I pour you some tea?
dame? dame? doushite desuka
No, you say? What's wrong?
jinsei wa rooringu sutoon
Life is like a rolling stone
tamaru konbini bukuro
Shopping bags piling up
seishun wa kumori zora
Youth is like a dark cloudy sky
sumafo izonshou sa
They're all glued to their phones
donzoko demo iijan
So what if we've hit rock bottom
ki ni shinakute iijan
Don't get so hung up on it
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
tabetara kateru kamojan
Maybe it'll help us get this katsu-done
dame dame demo iijan
But if it won't? Oh well
doutte koto neejan
Don't worry 'bout it
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
megezu ni ikouze
And keep moving forward
charanporan de iijan
Maybe we're kinda sloppy
muchakucha de iijan
And sure we're kinda reckless
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
tabetara kateru kamojan
Maybe it'll help us get this katsu-done
masshigura de iijan
So let's go full speed
tsuki susumeba iijan
And keep pushing onwards
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
tokoton yarouze
And see our goals all the way through
nee kimi doko kara kita no?
Where are you from?
ima boku hima shiten dakedo
I've got time to spare
Why don't we eat KATSUDON?
Could you explain what you mean by "erased"?
Explaining it could take a while,
so I'll just show you.
Princess Melora! Princess Melora!
Oh, Chup! What's the matter?
We have news!
Here we go, Glace!
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone!
What are you teaching us about today?
Today's lesson is on the Dragon GPS.
Dragon GPS
The Dragon GPS is a radar
that detects for dragons.
Vinsant's radar is customized
to help us find Scardon.
Can it find us a dragon
who grants wishes?
You know there's no dragon like that!
Whatever. Let's keep it moving.
Next Time
Trouble's afoot in the castle!
No one gets away with hurting
the princess!
But man, I wasn't expecting
to face such strong enemies!
Next time: "The Birth of a Kinda-Overlord!"
The Birth of a Kinda-Overlord!
Alright, it's time for a big adventure!