This is Snack World, the hallowed ground
of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam
and people have handy smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
And my name's Chup!
My village was burnt down by
the evil land-destroying merchant Vinegar Khan,
so I've embarked on a journey
to get my revenge 1000-fold!
At last, my journey has brought me
close to Vinegar.
In order to defeat him, I will overcome
any impossible mission that comes my way!
Alright, let's go on another big adventure today!
I've traced their destination.
They appear to have fled to Dragon Shaolin Temple.
Hmm, Dragon Shaolin Temple, you say?
That'll be tricky...
Should we destroy the temple
and seize them?
No, don't bother.
I happen to be an alumnus of that temple.
How about we send one of our best men instead?
You know the one...
Who?
Ninjaman Asura.
Episode 29: A Formidable Foe?! Here's Ninjaman Asura
All that traveling wore me out...
My feet are in terrible pain!
Pushing on these secret pressure points
passed down in this temple
will make all that traveling pain go away!
Why is this giving me so much déjà vu?
Push harder, Sir Laozi! Harder!
Come on, do it!
How unbecoming of me...
This last one's gonna sting!
Push!
Ugh! Can we get training already?
I didn't spend my money for nothing!
Ooh, how terrifying.
Y'know, no one likes a girl with a temper.
You tell her, Sir Laozi!
That's very true!
Forget it. Just let us start training!
Alright, alright. Upsy-daisy.
Huh?! When did you get there?
That was so fast!
It is time for training, everyone.
Our first exercise will be Ti Dang Zhong—
Hit the Bell!
What's the point of making it sound Chinese?!
You will slide down this ramp
on a log then jump at the end.
You'll then use your force
to strike the bell at the end.
I have a real bad fear of heights...
We're dangling over a cliff, too...
If we don't hit the bell,
we'll fall down to our dooms!
Yikes!
A reward awaits those who can hit the bell.
Now, let us hear the ringing
of that lovely bell.
My log is all decayed
because of termites!
Nice, it really suits you!
How rude!!
Let us begin!
Princess Melora looks amazing on that log...
Crap!
Go!
What the?!
Wonderful work, Princess.
Hey, that's not fair!
That has to be cheating, right?
Just music to my ears.
Wait, wait, wait!!
What the heck?!
I'll beat this!
Go!!
Sure, good enough.
That was a wonderful ring,
Princess Melora.
The three of you get...
...dragon-yaki!
Dragon-yaki is known to give you strength!
It's called "dorayaki" for short!
Man, I want some...
Aww. I'll have to pass,
I'm on a diet.
What?! That's such a waste!
Our next exercise will be Dang Li Wuiwui—
The Slippery Gold.
Okay, you're so making that up!
You must run as fast as you can,
across that golden fruit.
Uhh... a banana peel?
If we run across that, we'll just slip...
I'll go first.
Grade 3.
For what?!
I almost slipped there.
Yeah, because you did it on purpose!
Grade 7.
Huh?!
Grade Tofu.
Grade Cockroach.
I'm sorry?!
Sounds boring. I'll pass.
Why does she get so muck slack?!
Watch this! I'll show you
how a real banana peel slip is done!
He's stuck in an eternal loop...
What's his goal here...?
Grade 1! You pass!
Wow! Good going, Chup!
Ugh, I don't even get
what we're being graded on!
How d'ya like that?
Cool, right?
Was there some sort of point to that exercise?
It's Sir Laozi. There has to be a point.
I just know it.
It's like my grandmother said!
Nothing entered, nothing drained!
Nothing ventured,
nothing drained.
-Tome
There's so much wrong with that one...
Onto the next course.
Next up is Jieken Chen—
The Iron Man Fist.
Are you kidding me?
That's literally just a kung-fu star!
No, it's Jieken Chen!
Not helping your point!
Huh, a bunch of Pinocchios.
And they're all 1.0 models, too!
Those things are ancient.
Don't judge a book by its cover.
He bought a bunch of used Pinocchios
for cheap from a chain called ROBOTOFF,
and modified them into iron men
for training purposes.
Wake up, my iron men!
Can you make it to the other side?
If you lose to them, you won't get anywhere.
I'll go first.
Whoa, super cool!
Me next!
The heck?
You won't get anywhere
if you let yourself fall for their cheap tickles!
Keep going!
E-Easier said than done!
No can do!
Cut it out!
Th-Those iron men were real trouble...
You better not do anything nasty
to the princess!
Thank you so much!
What am I looking at?!
Do all VIP get to cheat like this?
I made it!
Good work making it through!
You all pass!
I'm kinda...
Old news, buddy.
Next up, Attraper à l'élastique—
The Bungee Catch.
That's not even Chinese,
that's French!
We're doing bungee jumping?
More than just jumping.
You're going to bungee down
and catch fish from the river.
What? We can't do that.
Whatever you catch will be our dinner.
And if you can't catch anything,
no lunch for you!
What?!
I don't wanna miss lunch!
Ho-ho, good work.
Heck yeah!
This is amazing!
Oh, no! My lunch!!
Should we be concerned?
Is he dead?
Ah, Gob-san!
Are you alright?
He's not answering...
I can't believe we lost Gob-san!!
You're talking to a rock.
I'm over here...
I'm a bit soaked, but I'm alive and well!
Well now I feel stupid for worrying.
That's just rude!
She gets an elevator?!
Here is your fish, Madam Melora.
Oh, my! It looks very delicious!
Hey, she didn't have to bungee down!
That concludes your training session.
Time for lunch.
Pepperon and I don't get to eat...
I could never!
I'm left with no other choice...
Your souls still have much to be developed.
Next up is Xiao Xiao Jinzhi—
No Laughing.
No can do, I'm totes busy!
You sure don't look busy!
Good luck, Chup!
Thanks! I'll do my best!
Try to hold back your laughter,
lest you disrupt your soul.
This'll be a piece of cake.
Who could've seen that coming?!
Hello.
It's Werewolf as a human.
Oh, good to see you.
Thank you.
Oh, no~!
Nooo!!
This is nothing!
Oh hey, it's Master Panpan!
Stop!
So dancing!
Non-stop...
Dancing!
This is non-stop dancing!
Dancing!!
Non-stop, non-stop, dancing!
Oh, no~!
They're all wearing
flower-patterned underwear!
It's over.
You still need more training.
Everyone aside from Vinsant
will go through a harsher course as punishment.
Aww, what?
And it's called...
Ta Shi Min Min Chi Pei Pai—
The Burning Road.
That's ridiculous,
it's only two letters!
I'll repeat.
Ta Shi Min Min Chi Pei Pai!
Why is it so long?!
You will walk across the burnt stones
holding pails of boiling water in both hands.
Sounds terrifying...
Oh, Sir Laozi?
I just got a sudden craving for something sweet!
I had a feeling you would,
so I made sure to set you up
an afternoon tea.
That's no fair!
I can't even have lunch!
Me neither!
Let me know when you're all finished.
If he's not watching,
we could probably...
Don't get any bright ideas!
I'm watching you!
He read us like a book...
Now, begin!
Ouch!
Why do we have to put up with this?!
I think we should see
how a veteran does it first!
No! I refuse!
You've got this, Gob-san!
Show us what a real man can do!
Shut up! Why do I have to be
the veteran now of all times?!
Ow ow ow! Hot! Hot!
Let's run while the stones are still wet!
Ow! So hot!
Huh? Doesn't seem that bad to me.
How thick is the skin on your feet?!
The ground feels so good...
What was the point of all this?!
Where's Gob-san?!
I thought I was a goner...
That's ridiculous.
Who's there?!
I am known as Asura.
I hold the ultimate title of Ninjaman.
I have no resentment
against the likes of you,
Asura
but I have been ordered to eliminate you!
A Ninjaman?!
Vinegar must have sent him after us.
He's sniffed us out!
You stinky poo-poo-head Vinegar sent!
I'mma take you down!
Where'd he go?!
I am a ninja living in the shadows of society.
I seek to remain invisible!
Says the guy dressed like that?
Thus, I shall eliminate anyone
who lays their eyes on me.
He's too fast!
Time for my ultimate spell!
Dang it...
Seek cover!
Exodus Blade!
Exodus Blade.
Interesting. Thou appear to be
much different from the others.
Who is this guy...?
He isn't even in a fighting stance,
but there's no openings...
So this is a real Ninjaman...
So strong... What even is a Ninjaman?
It's one of the ultimate titles
someone can receive, like Dragon Knight.
Whoa, dang...
I am a Ninja... I doth not do photographs!
Then why the pose?!
Don't underestimate him, Chup.
Ninjas are professional assassins.
They sneak up on their opponents
and kill them in an instant.
The title is only bestowed up on those
who have gone down in history
and been inducted into a hall of fame.
That's what makes a Ninjaman.
You know your stuff.
I'm sure thou are very honored
to be in my presence.
This dude is so cool!
I told you, I doth not do photographs!
And yet you love the spotlight, clearly.
Chup, you cannot win against him.
I'm not even sure if I'll make it.
But I'll try!
Vinsant!
Clone art.
Vinsant!!
I guess you're no better than the rest.
If only I had the power of the Dragon Knight...
I could have stood a chance!
It's like my grandmother said!
You're asking for the moon,
I'm asking for you!
I'm asking for you.
You're asking for the moon,
-Tome
The heck does that mean?!
Ninjaman? Who cares!
This Chupman is gonna take you down!!
There's no title like that!
Dettonic Sword!
Dettonic Sword.
Dettonic Shield!
Dettonic Shield.
I can see through your moves!
Huh?
Chup!!
Stay back!
I'll...
...take care of him!
Chup, don't push yourself.
We'll do it together!
Asura art.
What the?!
Vinsant!!
This is no time to care for others.
H-How is he so much stronger...?
I'll take thou two down first.
Do it, then! I dare you!
Farewell.
Fireball!
Who goes there?!
Wh-What's your name?
What a beauty...
Me? Oh, you flatterer...
Don't tell me...
He's fallen in love with Mayone?
Please accept my gift.
Aww, so cute!
My word.
They were destined to be!
That was so good!
Aah, Princess Melora!
Don't come any closer!
P-Princess Melora!
N-No way! What is she doing here of all places?!
She's here to lose weight.
Is it really you...?
What's the problem?
Huh?
I didn't think I'd live to meet her in person...
I'm the happiest person in the world!
Hold on, are you a fellow Melorer?
Yeah.
I'm the biggest Melorer in all of
King Oyster City!
For real? That's awesome!
D-Did thou say you were a Melorer too?
Behold!
My stars!
Heck yeah!
So, what do you like about Melora the most?
Her big, round eyes!
Mine's her bubble butt!
So cool!
What are you up to?
Aah, so close! She's so beautiful, it's blinding!
He really toyed with Mayone, huh...
It just gets worse the more you think about it.
I'm all sleepy after that dessert...
I think I should take a nap, Sir Laozi.
Understood. I'll lead the way.
Princess Melora...
Oh, right!
Princess Melora!!
Please accept my gift.
Oh?
I'll pass.
Melorer, you say?
Big, round eyes? Bubble butt?
Who cares about all that?!
Don't toy with other people's feelings!
Oh, no, I just...
I was into you for a bit,
but I didn't think I'd see Melora here...
The gemstone kinda suits her better...
Excuse me?!
Don't give me your dumb excuses!
You big blockhead!!
My goodness...
Has Mayone always been so powerful?
Who'd'a thunk you'd own
such a rare Melora card?
Oh, please.
It's nothing in comparison
to the likes of your collection!
Let's trade again someday!
We shall!
Let's take a Melorer selfie together!
I'll be sure to get you a photo of
Melora in her uniform later!
Splendid! Thank you, my friend.
Ugh, I'm so sick of you.
Would you get out of my sight?!
Alright.
I guess no Melorer could possibly be a bad guy!
She should be waking up from her nap soon.
I wonder what she's wearing right now...
Pajamas? A nightgown?
Knock it off, boy.
shobokure gao no mobukyara domo ga
On and on these tired old NPCs
iiwake shinagara aruiteru
Keep walking around excusing themselves
itsumo miteiru michisugara
As I took the same old path again
mita koto mo nai wakuwaku wo mita
I found the thrill I've sought for my whole life
itsumade shibonda mama nano
Just how long will I keep drooping around like this?
minikui ahiru no mama nano
How long will I stay an ugly duckling?
ima no reberu wa ichi dakedo
I'm still only level one
ima ni mitero yo sono uchi JUMP UP
But watch me, soon I'll jump up
saikin no wakai mon wa tte
"Why, kids these days..."
toshiyori domo ga boyai teru kedo
...Our old boomers grumble and complain
soro soro omei henjou da
But it's not too late to clear my name
iya ga ou ni mo mattanashi daze
I might not like it, but I can't wait any longer
ketsu no ana kara jetto funsha daaa
I gotta blast free from my cowardly shell!!
ore wa itsuka hana ni naru
Give me time and I'll bloom like a flower
sora ni nobiru hana ni naru
A flower spread out to the sky
kimi ni todoku hana ni naru
The flower that reaches you
Vinegar.
Asura's power is weakening.
This doesn't please me.
He better put his back into it.
I'm going to show you real hell!
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone!
What are you teaching us about today?
Today's lesson is on ultimate titles!
Ultimate Titles
Ultimate titles, such as
Dragon Knight and Ninjaman,
are given to people who have made their mark
on legends or history books,
or who have outstanding abilities.
There may be people with ultimate titles
in even more fields than just those two!
I'd love to meet them!
Next Time
We're up against a savage Asura,
and the Dragon Brothers?!
We don't stand a chance!
Then the Dragon Heart starts glowing!
Next time: "A Sighting of the Legendary Darefalcon!"
A Sighting of the Legendary Darefalcon!
Alright, time for a big adventure!