This is Snack World, the hallowed
ground of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam and
people have handy smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
...And my name's Chup.
My village was burnt down by the evil
land-destroying merchant, Vinegar Khan,
and I've embarked on a journey
to get my revenge 1000-fold!
The tickets to King Oyster City, where
Vinegar is, cost 20 million gillan.
So I'm on an adventure searching for
big treasure to make loads of cash!
[Chup humming theme song]
Alright, let's go on another big adventure today!
I see you couldn't beat the Phoenix...?
I'm sorry.
More importantly...how is Melora doing with her illness?
Ep. 13: I'll Buy Butako!
We have our top doctors looking after her and keeping her safe.
We also have an esthetician keeping her skin smooth.
[Melora moans]
Princess Melora...
There are estheticians for this?
[Melora squeals]
- [Gasp]
I feel like I'm in heaven...
That’s so misleading…
[Melora coughing]
Agh, Princess Melora!
I think that shark fin I ate earlier got stuck in my throat...
What kind of "sick patient" with a fatal illness eats like that?
At any rate, she's still yet in a very dangerous condition with no sign of change.
You need to get the Phoenix's Eternal Life power ASAP!
Yes, of course! Though he is a very formidable foe...
That's why I entrusted you guys with that high-class brand Clanarine's lance and shield!
And we're very grateful you did!
But if I could just ask one more thing...?
One more thing?
You don't suppose we can have more strong weapons, no?
First a spear and shield, and now a knife?!
The king's really serious about this, huh?
Princess Melora's life is hanging in the balance!
So who wants to handle the knife?
Since I already have the clan metal lance and shield.
I'm not very good with small weapons...
You can have it, Mayone.
Hmm...it doesn't really match my outfit, does it? That's what matters...
If you won't take it, I will!
Hehe...how do I look?
I feel like you're about to mug me...
You look like a straight-out burglar.
Wait, what if we let Butako have the knife?
Oink?
Butako?
How would she even wield it?
I guess she'd put it in her nostril and charge at the enemy?
Oink-oink-oinky!
That sounds like it'd be epic!
Wouldn't that put strain on her nostrils?
Can't she just turn into a big dragon and fight the Phoenix?
That won't do! Turning into a big dragon in a critical moment uses a lot of her stamina.
Oink...
Then when will she be able to handle it?
Butako's completely useless.
Oink...oink...oiiiiink!!
No, Butako!
She's crying again...
She's always such a crybaby.
You called her useless! It's like my grandmother said...
Everything comes in handy when you make a yummy pork stew!
Everything comes in
handy when you
make a yummy
pork stew!
Everything comes in
handy when you
make a yummy
pork stew!
-Tome
That's all wrong - a pig's only good for ginger-fried pork!
And you can't change my mind.
Where did this conversation go...?
Thing is, no matter how strong of a weapon we get, we're still no match for the Phoenix's Fantasy trick.
I can agree with you on that.
I don’t like it, but we should ask the combat professional.
You need to know how to beat the Phoenix?
That's correct, Sergeant Cinderella, I thought you might know.
Hmm... I've heard of that fantasy trick the Phoenix uses.
Indeed... we had to face it, too.
Memories of my past appeared before my very eyes.
Memories of your past, you say?
And it was a cursed part of my past I really wish I could forget...
I see... Well, in that case, I've got just the thing!
Listen up! From now on, you're starting all the way over.
Over?
You'll empty your mind and body.
That way, there'll be no cursed memories in you to be dug out!
You'll be invincible to the Phoenix's Fantasy trick!
But, just how will we get rid of them, sergeant?
Maggot!!
Oink...
You'll clear your body's energy and wipe away your memories and emotions.
Drop down and act like a slug!!
Yessir! Blehhh....
You maggots! You're acting like tired store clerks!!
You need to forget about your bones and muscles too.
Yessir! Byegh...
Should I be following along...?
- Another way of going about it...
YOU!
- Huh?!
You've already got the feeling of a slug from the get-go.
No, I don't really at all...
Sluggy...sluggy...
Good!
You've all become good slugs.
I'm telling you, I'm really not!
You're fine the way you are. Good slug!
What the hell does "good slug" mean?!
Alright, next step!
Make sure you've emptied your head!
Bloop...
What is your name?
Name's Chup!
[Cinderella gasps and shouts]
[Chup squeals] What the?!
You maggot!! If your head is empty, you shouldn't be able to tell me your name!!
One more time!!
- [Chup groans]
What is your name?
How old are you?
[Shouts]
But don't just ignore me, that's infuriating.
R-r-right...
- Oink...
So do we do this or that?
[Shouts]
Aagh, why me?!
Your face is starting to piss me off.
You're just making rules up now!
Alright, you're next! What's your name?!
I forgot...
Hm-hm, very good answer.
As a reward, I'll prepare you some steak!
Aah, swee-
- [Cinderella shouts]
Such a careless move! If you start all over, you'll be forgettin' that appetite too!
Darn it...
[Shouts]
Guh...what was that for?!
Just like I thought, your face pisses me off.
I can't do anything about my face!!
Pepperon, slug-out!
OH! Bloooop...
Great reaction time!
What's with this so suddenly?
Hehe...Chup, slug-out!
Ah- bloooop...
Oho, you're a good slug!
Haha, I'm already a full, flawless master at it!
Isn't there some other way we can do this? 'Cuz I'm not doing it in public...
- Mayone, slug-out!
Huh?! Wiggle wiggle...
Oh man, you're a natural!
You've got the most slug talent of all of us!
That doesn't make me feel better!
Can't we at least not do this randomly while we're talking?!
Life is fun!
Life is a bore.
It's a paradise when you look!
And hell when you turn it around.
Two sides of the same coin!
That's right, Kesaran Pasaran!
Kesaran
Pasaran
Kesaran Pasaran?
It appears a comedy duo stands in our path.
Excellent! Let's show off the results of our training!
Everyone, slug-out!
Huh--?
Bloooooop...
- Wait, so, how exactly does turning into slugs help?
[Screaming]
The slug plan was supposed to defend us from the Phoenix's Fantasy!!
Kaahahaha...
You guys see an enemy and you get wrigglin'?
That's sooo stupiiid!!
What a loud-mouth.
But I think you guys are way strong and each unique in your own ways!
Your party is very well-balanced!
Ahaha.
The white side sure is saying nicer things.
So, what do we do, Chup?
Oh, yeah! Should we try the knife the king gave us?
That's right! It'd be wise to practice using it before we go up against the Phoenix.
Got it!
Clan Metal Knife!
Clan Metal Knife.
Come at me, black-and-white monsters!
You're sooo cute...I don't think I've ever met a better human before!
You...you mean it?!
Of course! With beauty like this, you should consider becoming an idol!
No way! I should think about it...
No, no, no. You're really takin' this guy for real?
Just look at you, with your ugly, half-
baked face. You must live the worst life ever.
What are you trying to say?!
Imagine, you're tryin' to become an idol lookin' like that!
You’ll have the whole town dying of laughter!
You're...so mean...
Let it sink in. Not a single soul'll line up for ya in a handshake event!
[Sobbing]
That's right! Kesaran Pasaran!
M-Mayone... everything alright?
Leave me alone...how could a half-baked loser like me possibly...
She took some critical damage there...
If I must, I'll take the lead here!
Wooden Axe!
Your choice for adventure, Qloris!
Wooden Axe.
You're so big and strong, I just adore your muscles!
Oh? You really think so?
Of course! A man's charm is more than just good looks and kindness!
It's really just the muscles, right?
Haha, you're making me blush...
Nuh-uh. Most guys who brag about their muscles have nothin' where their brains should be.
[Groans]
Don't ya think this kind of power just makes you a lame warrior who's only useful in crucial situations?
[Stumbles]
Admit it! Up until now, you've only ever been useful in battle, right?
[Stumbling]
You're done for. Just a good-for-nothing wimp putting on a show of your strength.
[Groaning]
That's right! Kesaran Pasaran!
P-Pepperon?
I really am just a good-for-nothing wimp...
Forget about me...
Grr... the white one lifts you up for a moment while the black one badmouths you and makes you feel bad.
That's how they pack a ton of damage to your soul.
Leave this to me, I've got a good plan.
A good plan?
I'll flip things around!
Let the black one badmouth you first, then let the white one praise you!
Take that route, and you'll be feeling twice as good and up to fight!
I see! Gob-san, you really do say good things 1% of the time!
Oink!
You're exaggerating that a whole lot! ...Whatever. Mayone, I'm borrowing your knife!
Hmph. Kesaran Pasaran! Come get me!
Hey, hey!
Not yet!
Urgh, revolting! You're like a ball of filth!
Like, take all the gross things in the world, clump 'em together, and sit for 30 years,
ripen it and you get premium filth, dont'cha?
I've certainly taken damage...
You must be used to people lookin' at you like that.
If I looked like you, I'd die 40,000 times!
Hang in there, Gob-san! Time for the white one to praise you!
Enough with you!
Get praising!
W-well, gramps, you seem like a...nice person?
That's it?!
He couldn't find ways to praise him...
- Oink...
Kahahaha, this is just great! Of course even Kesaran ain't got nothin' nice to say about you!
Um... I'm sorry I can't praise you.
What?
He's apologizing...he really can't find anything to praise.
Oink...
Just like I thought, a Monster is a Monster at heart.
You're nothin' but an ugly, smelly, revolting Monster.
[Stumbles]
That's right! Kesaran Pasaran!
I'm a completely worthless man...
No, you're not, Gob-san!
- Huh?
You're not a man, you're a Monster!
That's not helpful!!
Looks like it's my turn!
Clan Metal Lance!
Clan Metal Lance.
Let's do this!
You're totally...
- Ey!
[Kesaran screeching]
Oi, listen up--
- Take this!
I did it!
Oink!
I see.
We weren't supposed to listen to them at all.
That's right.
It's sweltering up here...
We're not even fighting yet and I'm already sweating.
Show yourself, Phoenix! This'll be your end!
[All gasp]
[Phoenix screeching]
It's time! Everyone, slug-out!
Bloooop...
[All screaming]
Hold on! I thought the slug stuff was supposed to stop its attacks!
No it wasn't! The slug plan makes us vulnerable to other attacks besides Fantasy!
One more time! Everyone, slug-out!
Nyooop...
[All screaming]
Why's it only performing normal attacks?!
How are we supposed to know?! Just give up with the slug plan!!
[Warbling]
Look at the way it's moving!
That's the way it moved before it used Fantasy last time!
It's gonna use the Fantasy trick this time! Everyone, slug-out!
[Screeching]
Where are we? Did the Phoenix put us in Fantasy again?
But whose Fantasy is it?
Oh, Chup's been taken down!
Chup, get back up!!
I am not Chup. I am a slug.
Forget about it already!
Oiiiiink!
- Hm?
Oiiink...
Butako?
- Oink?
Could the Fantasy we're watching be...?
Oink?
Of all things, it targeted Butako because she didn't practice being a slug.
Oiiiiink!
- [Men shouting & grunting]
Oiiiink!
I'll catch it!
- Oink!
This is...
Oink...
Hehehe... this is the dragon you captured, I take it?
Ah, Vinegar! Grr...
You little...! Take this! And this!
Chup, don't bother. This Vinegar's just part of the Fantasy.
Aww... guess this pile of fruits is just part of the Fantasy too.
Heh.
Oink...oink!
Ah...what are you doing to Butako?!
I throw my money away for you to capture a dragon and you come back with this puny thing?
I couldn't possibly admire such an ugly face.
Shut up! Take this! And this!
Chup, calm down!
Give this puny thing to some stallholder, would you?
Oink?! Oink...
Butako, you idiot!!
- Oink?!
Idiot, idiot, idiot!!
Chup, why are you insulting her like that?!
Because Butako's an idiot!
Why would you hold on to such bad memories?!
Haven't we done tons of fun things together for a long time?
You have to remember those, Butako!
Oink...!
Oink...
You sure ain't a popular sell, are ya, pig-nose?
[Stallholder sighs]
Oink...oi--oink?!
Hm?
Huh, does that kid look familiar to you?
It's you, dummy.
Huh?! I look cooler than that, right?
No, not at all.
- Uh.
This girl's been collectin' dust for ages, since her face is stranger than that of other dragons.
Hmmm?
But, being different from the rest isn't a bad thing, right?
She has a lot of unique features of her own.
Oink!
You interested?
I just got my base salary and I'm not sure what to spend it on.
Oink, oink! Oink!
Ahaha, how adorable.
Oiiink!
This squirrel!
Yeah, the squirrel next to her is definitely 100 times more adorable.
Oink...
Oink! Oink, oink, oink!!
Huh, if I take you with me, you'll do my cleaning and laundry and stuff?
Oink, oink!
Does this mean you can understand what Butako says...?
You're telling me none of you understand Butako?
We can sorta read her gestures, but you're the only one who clearly understands her, no?
Really...
Haha. I don't particularly need any help with chores.
[Squirrel munching down]
Aw...the way it eats is so cute...
Oink! Oink! Oink, oink, oink!
What's that? You're powerful?
Oink, oink! Oiiink!
Wah! What was that for?! It burns!!
Bad girl! What are you doing to the customer?!
There's a reason no one wants to buy you.
Oink, oink...
Aight, I'm settled! Sir, I'd like this, please!
Sounds good, enjoy your squirrel.
No, I'd like to buy this.
Oi...oink!
Haha, your nose is really weird.
Aight! From now on, your new name is Butako! Kapeesh?
That out of the way. Later, Butako!
Oink?!
You must've been cramped in that cage forever.
After all, dragons are made to soar the skies!
Oink-oink-oink!
Plus, they don't allow pets at the inn.
Oi...oi...
Well, up, up, and away! You're free now!
You're free now!
Oh, we're back where we started. Butako got rid of the Fantasy!
That's my Butako!
Oink!
It's like my grandmother said!
Pork buns are still tasty without sauce!
Pork buns
are still
tasty
without sauce!
Pork buns
are still
tasty
without sauce!
-Tome
Oink, oink!
I'd put a teeny bit of mustard soy sauce on it.
Does any of that really matter right now...?
Chup! Now's your chance, while the Phoenix is confused!
It's not sure how it would eat pork buns...
No it isn't!
Our attacks can't reach it up there!
Oink!!
- Huh?
Oink-oink-oink!
Right, got it!
Mayone, the Clanarine knife!
O-on it!
Clan Metal Knife!
Go! Butako, Freedom Attack!
Oiiiiink... oiiiiink!!
[All gasp]
[Screeching]
She did it! The Phoenix is down!
Good work out there, Butako!
We couldn't have done it without you! I'm sorry for calling you useless.
Did it hurt your nostrils at all?
Oink...oink...
Alright, let's think quick and get the Eternal Life!
Gob-san, how do we do it?
Don't rush me, I'm looking.
Your old flip-phone is super annoyingly slow after all...
Hm...the firebird Phoenix is...does anyone else find it hot in here?
[Screeching]
Agh-of course! It's a Phoenix!!
Beat it as many times as you want, and it'll come back up again!
Oh dear...
It looks very angry...
Butako, can you do the same attack you did just before?
Oi!
You can't, the knife's all the way over there!
Oh?
Oink, oink!
- What is it, Butako?
What's wrong?
Oink-oink-oink!
She wants us to leave it to her!
What?!
Oink! Oink-oink, oink!
Ooh! We haven't seen your dragon form in a while!
But doesn't this wear out your stamina?
Oink, oink-oink-oink!
She says, "If I don't try my hardest now, when will I?"
Oohoo! How sharp!
You're on a roll today, Butako!
Go, Butako! Burn this Phoenix to a crisp!!
konbini de kuda wo maku ukiyo wo samayou wakoudo yo
All you youngsters loitering about your lives,
shrouding the convenience stores
omaera wa genjitsu ni torinokosaresugi andeddo
You’re like undead who have left behind reality
itsumade son na koto kurikaesu no o-tsu-ka-re
How long are you going to keep doing this?
Don't you get tired of this same old routine?
hashiridase yo ENDLESS ROAD
Run forth through the endless road
koetemiroyo BORDERLINE
Go on past that borderline
sekai wa mugen ni hirogaru kouya
The world is an endless, limitless wilderness
omae no dokyou wo tameshiteiru
Where you can put your courage to the test
sumafo nankaja kensaku dekinai
It’s not something you can search for on your smartphone
sekai wa mugen ni hirogaru PARADISE
The world is an endless, limitless paradise
omaera wa giragira no
Soon you'll come to life taking in the blazing sun
taiyou kuratte ikiteiru
Raws
Translation/Typesetting/Timing
ED Karaoke
QC/Review
Raws
Translation/Typesetting/Timing
ED Karaoke
QC/Review
AnimeLand (BSJ)
Lumpstud
Noroino Hanako
NeSubs
(Specter Subs)
AnimeLand (BSJ)
Lumpstud
Noroino Hanako
NeSubs
(Specter Subs)
Oiii.....oink!
Huh?
Oink!
Oink-- oiiink! Oink...
What was...that?
She must've used all her stamina when she became big.
So all that motivation was for nothing.
Oi...oink?
Butako really is useless!!
[Screeching]
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone!
What are you teaching us about today?
"Butako"
Today's about Butako!
Butako is a pig-nosed dragon girl.
Normally she's at a portable size, but as a big dragon,
others can take a ride as she soars the skies.
Speaking of, Chup's the only one
who can clearly understand what Butako says.
Strange, right?
Butako's a great companion to us!
Next Time
Pepperon's acting weirdly strange, and he's acting self-conscious around enemies!
It seems to have to do something
with Pepperon's shocking past!
Next time: What Remains of Pepperon!
What Remains of Pepperon
Alright, it's time for a big adventure!