This is Snack World, the hallowed ground
of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam
and people have handy smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
And my name's Chup!
My village was burnt down by
the evil land-destroying merchant Vinegar Khan,
so I've embarked on a journey
to get my revenge 1000-fold!
At last, my journey has brought me
close to Vinegar.
In order to defeat him, I will overcome
any impossible mission that comes my way!
Alright, let's go on another big adventure today!
Episode 26: Farewell, Chilipepper—The Final Mystery
You still don't have enough mana?
M-My apologies, sir...
You see, mana is energy
that boils up from inside people.
Fear, regret, and anger
can all spawn it.
Here comes mana!
Are you afraid of me?
Or perhaps...
are you mad at me?
I-I wouldn't dream of it!
We've deployed agents all over
to collect more,
but we didn't collect
as much as we hoped.
Oh, whatever.
Vinegar Khan.
Oh! Do I smell an update
on our big new talent project?
Yes. We've finished the poster at last.
Looks just as I envisioned!
What are you thinking
for his first song?
Oh, it's coming!
I can see it clearly!
His debut single
should feel dark!
Its theme: devilish love!
"I love you so, I want you dead!
Yes, vine-vine!"
Extravagant, Vinegar Khan.
When the people hear this,
they'll be so frightened,
their mana will overflow!
Um, sir, what is all this...?
Since a certain dunce is
taking his sweet time collecting mana,
I'm taking matters into my own hands.
This monster's song will brainwash the humans,
flooding them with dark energy,
so we can swoop in and take their mana!
Th-That's a good idea!
So, going forward, I have a new job for you.
And that is...?
You'll be Devil Bowie's manager.
Huh?
You've got a lot of work ahead of you!
I'll even give you a new body
that can endure all this work.
You'll be born again!
Don't tell me...
Please!! Don't strip me of my humanity!!
The breakfast at this place sucks...
What do they put in that stuff...?
I don't even know what this skeleton is for.
Yuck, what is that?!
Hm? Pepperon, why didn't you
join us for breakfast?
I don't really have an appetite...
Huh, really?
By the way, Chup,
what have you got there?
Oh, this? It's a letter for us
from Inspector Chilipepper!
"Emergency Summons!"
EMERGENCY SUMMONS!
Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's
mansion at
11am!
Chilipepper
"Gather at Mr. Fishburger's mansion
at 11:00 A.M.!"
"Chilipepper."
What does he need us for so suddenly?
Maybe a crime of some sort?
Maybe some evil monster showed up?
But it's almost 11:00 already!
We gotta get going!
You got that right!
Um, guys!
I need some time to get ready,
so you guys go on without me!
I made it in time...
Sorry, I'm here now!
Is that all of you?
Good. Now, let's listen
to Mr. Fishburger's opening speech.
Huh?
Greetings, everyone.
I'm opening up! Open sesame!
Just messin'.
Bad joke aside, what's this for?
I wanted to thank you for your assistance
with the Eternal Rose incident the other day.
So I thought I'd put together
a little party for you all!
Yay, a party!
Aw, you flatter us!
Wanted to make it a surprise!
Buiyong and Bunnilla?
What are you two doing here?
They ordered catering from our hotel!
And since you're extremely wealthy,
I can't wait for the bill!
Oui, oui!
Thanks!
Maybe later...
I could get a bit of time
with Bunnilla on the dance floor!
Cheers, everyone!
Cheers!
What is this?
Hm?
Oh, no...
What's the matter?
"I've set a bomb in this room."
I've set a bomb in this room.
It will go off at noon!
"It will go off at noon!"
A threat left from a bomber!
Oh, stop it.
This is another one of your fancy surprises, isn't it?
No! We didn't plan this!
Er, excuse me.
The door is locked.
Wait, really?
Huh?
My word...
The lock is sealed using dark magic!
We've been locked in here using magic!
It looks like we have a real threat!
But why are they after us?
Quite perplexing...
Chup, we'll have to find the bomb
before noon.
If we don't, the whole mansion
will go up in smoke!
We have one hour!
It's like my grandmother said!
Time flies before you know it!
Oranges rot before you think it!
Time flies before
you know it.
Oranges rot before
you think it.
Time flies before
you know it.
Oranges rot before
you think it.
-Tome
I can take 'em just a bit rotten.
Inspector, if we solve this,
you'll take us to Vinegar Palace, correct?
You can rest easy! I always...
...keep my promises!
Split up and search!
If you see anything suspicious,
let me know immediately!
Inspector, I found a ball!
Don't just touch it!
Huh?
Pass!!
Huh?!
Um, pass to Gob-san!
What are you doing?!
Take it!
Huh? Whuh??
Here!
Take it!
Gob-san, think fast!
You've got this!
I'm good!
Go for it!
Goodbye, cruel world!
What's your plan?
I'll use my strong stomach
to minimize the damage of the blast!
But if you do that...
You would sacrifice yourself to save us...
We'll never forget about you, buddy...
Doesn't look very explode-y to me.
Weird...
Actually, I don't wanna die!!
Someone take the ball back!!
Hey, stay back!
Pass!
No, get away!
This is just...
a normal ball!
All that...
What a huge waste of our time...
Oh, right!
If we all stay quiet,
maybe we can hear the bomb timer ticking...
Good call.
Come on!
I'm sorry, it happens when I'm nervous...
Oh, right!
Maybe Butako's nose
can sniff out the gunpowder!
Go for it, girl!
Good thinking!
Instead of a police dog,
we have a police pig!
You mean a dragon.
Have you found any gunpowder?
Huh? In the food?
It's not in there, is it?
It's a good thing we haven't eaten!
Someone go get it!
Don't get up close to it, that's dangerous!
Please, this isn't gunpowder.
Just fish powder rice!
We keep wasting time
on pointless distractions!
The bomber left a second message!
What does it say?
Let's see here.
I won't let those who
betrayed me get their way!
"I won't let those who
betrayed me get their way!"
I don't get it. What does that mean?
I won't let those who
betrayed me get their way!
I do. Someone in this room
backstabbed the forces of evil!
So they retaliated by setting a bomb!
Is all the flexing really necessary?
By the forces of evil...
do you mean Vinegar?!
Say what?
No way!
Is anyone in here familiar with Vinegar?
Please, no one we know is that suspi...
Don't tell me... Was it you, Mr. Yong?!
What's this?
You know, he was able to get weird stuff
for Gob-san from who-knows-where.
And he had scary
debt collecters on his case.
Oui, oui, I can see why you don't trust me...
...but if you're wrong,
I'll charge you for damages.
Now hold on!
The worst thing Buiyong is capable of
is mixing in yesterday's leftovers
into that fish powder rice.
Guilty as charged!
That's just despicable!
So, if Buiyong is clear...
Tell me you guys aren't
doubting my Bunnilla!
She's not "yours," you know that?
Come to think of it,
we don't know much about Bunnilla, do we?
You're right. She doesn't talk much,
and I can't help but feel like there's a reason.
Wait, if being a hotel employee
is just a guise to hide from the world...
could you be part of the evil forces?
That bomb is gonna go off!
If it's true, then just tell us!
I'm...
...not.
It took you five minutes
just to say that?!
Then who's the traitor?
Chup, I know you want
to have faith in your friends,
but have any of them been up to
anything suspicious as of late?
Wasn't Pepperon acting a bit off this morning?
You think I did this?
She's right. You skipped out on breakfast
and said you didn't have an appetite,
and then you rummaged around
by yourself in the room.
W-Well, I was j-just...
Say it isn't so.
Pepperon!
You traitor!
I'll tell you, I'll tell you!
So...
So good!
The breakfast at this place sucks...
What do they put in that stuff...?
I hid the last of those melonpan cookies
you were saving
so I could have it to myself later.
That's so petty.
If Chup found it, he'd go...
"Yippee, mine!"
and gobble it up...
I'll take half then!
I knew it...
Was anyone else acting strange?
Oh yeah! Mayone!
You got here late after us!
He's right!
Pepperon, is this payback
for what I said before?
Have you been working with Vinegar?
Answer honestly!
Mayone!
Whoa, calm down!
Then tell us, why were you late?
Um, I was just...
Suspicious...
Fine, fine!
I secretly bought a new spell online,
so I was waiting for it to come in.
Wanted to surprise you guys with it in battle.
Really? What kind of spell?
It's called Cloudy; it covers its opponent in fog,
rendering them unable to fight.
But I haven't tried it yet,
so I'll give it a whirl now!
Cloudy!
My word, I feel so young and cloudy!
Oh my...
I need to kiss somebody, anybody! Mwah!
Come on, Mayone!
What do you take me for?!
Ugh, me too!
Stay back!
I think I feel a rebellious phase coming on!
Now Pepperon's acting up?!
Why don't my parents get me?!
I hate grown-ups!
I get you, I feel you!
I remember my childhood all too well!
Wait, is Cloudy supposed to
give you cloudy adolescent thoughts?
It's like my grandmother said!
If it makes you pouty, get out!
If you feel cloudy, let it out!
If it makes you pouty,
get out!
If you feel cloudy,
let it out!
If it makes you pouty,
get out!
If you feel cloudy,
let it out!
-Tome
Rebelling against your parents,
but adhering to your grandmother's words...
You really are a growing boy!
Let's run into the sunset!
Where's the sunset?!
Thanks, Mayone. We wasted time
and our stamina.
Oh, you're blaming me now?
Never mind that.
Only 30 minutes until the bomb goes off!
Hold up!
It's open!
The spell on the lock broke!
Life is fun!
Life is a bore.
Up front, it's heaven!
On the flip side, it's hell.
Two sides of the same coin!
That's right...
Kesaran Pasaran!
I remember these monsters!
They're those annoying brats
that lift people up then badmouth them!
This is the police!
I'd like to speak with you.
Hey, wait up!
You're a key suspect!
Get back here!
Freeze!
My, you're so fast!
You're too much!
So fast your brain can't keep up!
Why, you!!
Man, you're already at the mercy
of their rise-and-fall game.
What business do you have here?
My, you have wonderful muscles!
Oh, really? Please, they're not all that.
You could'a used some
of that discipline up here!
Excuse me?! Look, I'm disciplining it!
Not like that!
That doesn't matter!
Tell us why you're here!
My, you look like a strong warrior!
I'm not, really!
But your humongous body is holding ya back!
Ouch, right where it hurts...
I feel awful...
Man, you guys have terrible comprehension!
Did you two set the bomb
and lock us in that room?
We won't let you off easy for it!
A bomb?
Lock you in?
We're only here in King Oyster City
for tourism!
You're tourists?
Yeah. And by the way,
where's that 10,000 gillan?
10,000 gillan?
For what?
Look!
"The first person on the Fishburger estate
at 11:30 wins 10K gillan!!"
The first person
on the Fishburger
estate at 11:30
wins 10K gillan!!
What is this, Mr. Fishburger?
That flyer is fake!
Who would pull a prank like that?
When we were walking down the street
after we got here,
that flyer blew by us! Lucky!
But now we're not getting anything...
Unlucky...
So you guys didn't set the bomb?
You're so sensible!
I bet you'll be very successful.
Aw, shucks!
You're just a plain idiot.
What was that, stinkface?!
Stop letting them get to you!
But seriously, who's doing this and why...?
The bomb, the traitor,
the fake 10,000 gillan...
So much mystery... I'm stumped.
Stumped, now, are you? As am I.
Oh, I know! Let me see those fliers.
Good idea! If we compare it
with the other messages,
we might be able to connect it
to the bomber!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
I've set a bomb in this room.
It will go off at noon!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
I've set a bomb in this room.
It will go off at noon!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
I've set a bomb in this room.
It will go off at noon!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
I've set a bomb in this room.
It will go off at noon!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
I've set a bomb in this room.
It will go off at noon!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
I've set a bomb in this room.
It will go off at noon!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
I've set a bomb in this room.
It will go off at noon!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
I've set a bomb in this room.
It will go off at noon!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
I've set a bomb in this room.
It will go off at noon!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
I've set a bomb in this room.
It will go off at noon!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
I've set a bomb in this room.
It will go off at noon!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
I've set a bomb in this room.
It will go off at noon!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
I've set a bomb in this room.
It will go off at noon!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
I've set a bomb in this room.
It will go off at noon!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
I've set a bomb in this room.
It will go off at noon!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
I've set a bomb in this room.
It will go off at noon!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
I've set a bomb in this room.
It will go off at noon!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
I've set a bomb in this room.
It will go off at noon!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
I've set a bomb in this room.
It will go off at noon!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
I've set a bomb in this room.
It will go off at noon!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
I've set a bomb in this room.
It will go off at noon!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
I've set a bomb in this room.
It will go off at noon!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
I've set a bomb in this room.
It will go off at noon!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
I've set a bomb in this room.
It will go off at noon!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
I've set a bomb in this room.
It will go off at noon!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
I've set a bomb in this room.
It will go off at noon!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
I've set a bomb in this room.
It will go off at noon!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
I've set a bomb in this room.
It will go off at noon!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
I've set a bomb in this room.
It will go off at noon!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
I've set a bomb in this room.
It will go off at noon!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
I've set a bomb in this room.
It will go off at noon!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
I've set a bomb in this room.
It will go off at noon!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
EMERGENCY SUMMONS! Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's mansion at 11am!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
EMERGENCY SUMMONS! Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's mansion at 11am!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
EMERGENCY SUMMONS! Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's mansion at 11am!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
EMERGENCY SUMMONS! Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's mansion at 11am!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
EMERGENCY SUMMONS! Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's mansion at 11am!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
EMERGENCY SUMMONS! Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's mansion at 11am!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
EMERGENCY SUMMONS! Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's mansion at 11am!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
EMERGENCY SUMMONS! Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's mansion at 11am!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
EMERGENCY SUMMONS! Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's mansion at 11am!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
EMERGENCY SUMMONS! Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's mansion at 11am!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
EMERGENCY SUMMONS! Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's mansion at 11am!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
EMERGENCY SUMMONS! Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's mansion at 11am!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
EMERGENCY SUMMONS! Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's mansion at 11am!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
EMERGENCY SUMMONS! Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's mansion at 11am!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
EMERGENCY SUMMONS! Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's mansion at 11am!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
EMERGENCY SUMMONS! Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's mansion at 11am!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
EMERGENCY SUMMONS! Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's mansion at 11am!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
EMERGENCY SUMMONS! Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's mansion at 11am!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
EMERGENCY SUMMONS! Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's mansion at 11am!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
EMERGENCY SUMMONS! Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's mansion at 11am!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
EMERGENCY SUMMONS! Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's mansion at 11am!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
EMERGENCY SUMMONS! Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's mansion at 11am!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
EMERGENCY SUMMONS! Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's mansion at 11am!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
EMERGENCY SUMMONS! Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's mansion at 11am!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
EMERGENCY SUMMONS! Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's mansion at 11am!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
EMERGENCY SUMMONS! Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's mansion at 11am!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
EMERGENCY SUMMONS! Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's mansion at 11am!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
EMERGENCY SUMMONS! Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's mansion at 11am!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
EMERGENCY SUMMONS! Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's mansion at 11am!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
EMERGENCY SUMMONS! Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's mansion at 11am!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
EMERGENCY SUMMONS! Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's mansion at 11am!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
EMERGENCY SUMMONS! Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's mansion at 11am!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
EMERGENCY SUMMONS! Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's mansion at 11am!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
EMERGENCY SUMMONS! Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's mansion at 11am!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
EMERGENCY SUMMONS! Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's mansion at 11am!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
EMERGENCY SUMMONS! Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's mansion at 11am!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
EMERGENCY SUMMONS! Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's mansion at 11am!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
EMERGENCY SUMMONS! Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's mansion at 11am!
I won't in let those who
betrayed me get their way!
The first person on the
Fishburger estate wins 10K gillan!
EMERGENCY SUMMONS! Gather at
Mr. Fishburger's mansion at 11am!
Hey, why did you take out the invitation too?
Ah, my bad. It looks so similar,
I mixed them up.
Hm? Oh, Chup!
What is it?
I figured it out!
Oh, please. This one's
way too complicated for you.
I can already see it!
See what?
That!
Huh? What?
The flier for the gillan,
the two bomb threats...
and the invitation for the party...
They're all the same piece of paper?
So the same person wrote both
the bomb threats and the invitation...
Right on the nose.
That means...
Yup!
Inspector Chilipepper did the crime!
Inspector Chilipepper, not you...
There has to be a mistake!
Oh, I get it! This is all a part of the surprise party!
I'm afraid there's no surprise!
Gob-san!
What's the meaning of this?
Thanks to you,
I've gotten all the mana I need.
Say what?!
Wh-What is that?
I was seeking out your distrust,
your anger amongst each other...
For your confusion and anxiety...
From those negative feelings...
the dark power, mana, is created!
We need it to revive Scardon,
the evil dragon overlord who will lead our world to ruin!
So you were trying to get us
at each other's throats!
You used...
us too?!
Now that you know my secret,
I can't let you leave this place alive!
Is he turning into a monster?
Fairy Crystal Sword!
Sarria Staff!
Wooden Axe!
You're going down!
He's not even transformed yet,
but his aura looks so strong...
It's a boss-class aura!
We can't let him take form!
Evil is most beautiful
in its complete form.
Devil
Bowie
Good work losing at the end...
You dunce!
Vinegar Khaaan!
Who are you?
The up-and-coming performer,
Devil Bowie!
We hope you'll egg him on
in his endeavors!
Mister
Tamagohead
A performer?
So cool!
He's currently scrambled
to keep up with demand!
We better hurry to your next gig!
See you at my next concert!
Coming soon!
I'll have to stay diligent
until then as shell!
After all, a human's gotta keep growing!
Oop, though I'm not a human anymore!
shobokure gao no mobukyara domo ga
On and on these tired old NPCs
iiwake shinagara aruiteru
Keep walking around excusing themselves
itsumo miteiru michisugara
As I took the same old path again
mita koto mo nai wakuwaku wo mita
I found the thrill I've sought for my whole life
itsumade shibonda mama nano
Just how long will I keep drooping around like this?
minikui ahiru no mama nano
How long will I stay an ugly duckling?
ima no reberu wa ichi dakedo
I'm still only level one
ima ni mitero yo sono uchi JUMP UP
But watch me, soon I'll jump up
saikin no wakai mon wa tte
"Why, kids these days..."
toshiyori domo ga boyai teru kedo
...Our old boomers grumble and complain
soro soro omei henjou da
But it's not too late to clear my name
iya ga ou ni mo mattanashi daze
I might not like it, but I can't wait any longer
ketsu no ana kara jetto funsha daaa
I gotta blast free from my cowardly shell!!
ore wa itsuka hana ni naru
Give me time and I'll bloom like a flower
sora ni nobiru hana ni naru
A flower spread out to the sky
kimi ni todoku hana ni naru
The flower that reaches you
We solved the case...
But...
Inspector Chilipepper
ended up being the bad guy...
Now all of our previous cases
were for nothing.
Wait, does that mean we can't
get into Vinegar Palace?
Oh, Vinsant!
Where were you?
We had a situation!
There was all this stuff with a bomb threat!
A bomb? Did you get rid of it?
Get rid of it how?
It's supposed to go off at noon...
Wait, it's already noon!!
That's Mr. Fishburger's home!
We completely forgot about the bomb!
Don't "tehe" us!
My collection!!
Vinsant, we're at a loss here.
How are we supposed to get
into Vinegar Palace now?
Don't worry. I found a way.
For real?
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone!
What are you teaching us today?
Today's lesson is on Vinegar Enterprises!
Vinegar Enterprises
Vinegar Enterprises is Vinegar's company
located in King Oyster City.
They turn monsters
all over the continent violent
so that they can sell weapons and armor,
and they've been polluting the air and sea
because of all the factories they've built.
I won't let him get his way!
I'm going to take him down!
Next Time
Go, Butako! Infiltrate Vinegar Palace!
Take the Dragon Heart
so they can't revive Scardon!
Plan Butako! A Close Encounter with Scardon!!
Next time:
"Plan Butako! A Close Encounter with Scardon!!"
It's time for a big adventure!