This is Snack World, the hallowed ground
of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam
and people have handy smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
And my name's Chup!
After a long battle,
I've finally defeated the evil merchant Vinegar Khan,
and now I'm moving towards a new goal!
Whatever perils await me,
I'll fully, flawlessly overcome them!
Alright, let's go on another big adventure today!
Off we go to Demi-Glace Castle!
Episode 39: The Search for Goemon, the Legendary Blacksmith
Scardon's going down!
So where is Demi-Glace Castle?
It can be found on an island
far southwest of the continent,
standing tall over its surroundings.
Be brave, young ones.
Safe travels...
Explain yourselves.
Huh? You know!
Aren't you gonna use
your Dragon Warp?
What?
Take us to Demi-Glace Castle!
You brats!
Have I become no more
than a tool to you all?
Huh?
Your respect for me
appears to be fading away.
That's not true! Right, Chup?
Yeah! It was always around this level.
We'd have to get across the sea
to reach the castle.
But the railways and boats have been
out of service because of the vin-ancial crisis.
Our dragons won't take us
past the barriers, either.
So warp us on over to the castle, pretty-please!
I'm afraid I cannot.
Why not?
I cannot visualize a locale
I have never been before.
Therefore, I cannot warp there.
Aw, come on.
You can't just zip wherever you want?
Nope.
Why, you!
At least try to pretend I haven't lost
all worth to you!
What do we do now?
Ah! How about we ask Mr. Carbonara?
Good idea!
Darefalcon! You've been to
the weapons shop in town, right?
I-I have...
Then can ya Dragon Warp us there?
Now hold on!
The weapons shop is only
a brief walk away!
Agh! You're all waiting for me to warp you!
If you will!
Dragon Warp!
Let's go in!
We'll only be a minute,
so please wait out here.
What am I, a taxi?!
Demi-Glace Castle, eh?
That'll be tricky.
You'll have to wait for transportation...
This can't wait!
The fate of the panties...
I mean, the world is at stake!
Sir! We should help save
the panties...
Um, I mean, the world!
The magic barrier is a problem,
as is the lack of transportation services...
Wait, I thought of something.
Where was it...
Aha, here!
The Great Airship should be able
to make that trip!
The Great Airship?
It's said to be able to
pass through the magic barrier!
Here are the blueprints.
Whoa! It looks awesome!
It's a world-class airship
packed with a special engine!
Though now you'll only find it
in Davy Jones' locker...
But if we have the blueprints...
we can rebuild it!
And its production was directed
by a legendary creator!
If only I could remember his name...
He's gotta be real old,
but I've been told he's still breathing.
So if we find him...
we'll be able to reach
Demi-Glace Castle!
Let's go through all the airship creators!
Right! Pinocchio, search for
creators in our area!
Did you figure something out?
Take us to these locations.
You're kidding me!
We're in a bit of a hurry!
One moment...
Okay, even I cannot warp
to all these random places!
Aw, what?
Not to mention,
all these places I've never been...
Oh, shut up!
Why are you so stubborn?
There she goes...
If you can't, then figure something else out!
That's how a job gets done!
A-A job?
Something wrong with that?
I think that's good, Mayone.
You're crossing a line.
Dragon Summon?
Yes. I can summon people to me
if I recognize their faces.
It'll reduce waste of my Dragon Power
compared to warping around.
Please do it, then!
Pinocchio, please show him
one creator's face at a time.
You've got it!
Here is the first creator.
Okay! Dragon Summon!
Whoa!
I'm gettin' real creator vibes
from this guy!
Excuse me, Mr. creator?
Yes?
Can you build an airship?
Of course not. I create art!
Behold!
Mt. Everest painted with lemon juice!
It's so faded...
I have other pieces!
A cat, painted with apple juice!
Sumo citrus painted with
citrus iyo juice!
I'm the fruit juice creator!
I paint with juices!
Art is all about vitamins!
What is he talking about?
He's out of his mind.
What led you down this path?
Why do I use fruit juice, you ask?
It all goes back 35 years ago!
I was still a wee lad...
You can send him home now.
Dragon Disperse!
Around then, I...
Aah! I gotta keep painting!
Huh? He ran home?
What a bizarre trick.
Dragon Summon!
Now that looks like a creator!
Excuse me?
Are you capable of crafting an airship?
I create balloon art.
Behold! My red toy poodle!
And my green toy poodle!
And how could I forget...
the ripped toy poodle!
I've been makin' 'em toy poodles
on their own for 40 years.
Art is about them toy poodles!
Dragon Disperse!
Oh, no! The children are calling for me!
Welcome! I'm a creator of wagashi!
Dragon Disperse!
Whaaat?! That's all the screentime I get?
We'll now read the next letter.
This one's from The Epic Jokester.
Yes, it's mine!!
Dragon Disperse!
They read my letter!!
A postcard creator, huh?
Is there even a legendary creator out there?
This is the last one.
Okay!
Dragon Summon!
What's that sound?
Hey!
I remembered the name of the creator! It's Goemon!
He's known as the legendary blacksmith.
Blacksmith?!
What's that?
They manufacture and repair
items such as swords and armor.
Huh? Could it be?
It is! It's a blacksmith!
Excuse me, sir!
Sir?
Hm? Where am I?
Who are you?
Uhh...
Would you happen to be Goemon?
I am Goemon IV's elder brother,
6oemon III.
6oemon
So complex, for what?
Why do you seek Goemon?
Don't tell me Griffon sent you after me?!
Who's Griffon?
You're planning to hold us hostage
and take our food, aren't you?
Not on my watch!
I won't allow it!
No, of course not!
You've got it all wrong!
Give up!
We have a job for Mr. Goemon!
Do you?
Aah, you got me! You hit me!
And it burns...
What kind of job?
That was close.
Don't use me as your shield!
We'd like him to build the Great Airship!
The Great Airship?
Been too long since I've heard that name.
So Goemon really is a master blacksmith!
Yeah. He could make anything
from swords to artillery.
So where is he now?
Please take us to him!
We need this job done!
Don't hold your breath.
Goemon doesn't take jobs anymore.
At least try!
Forget it.
I have work to do.
I'm going home.
You mentioned a "Griffon" earlier.
Who is that?
He's a food thief from our home village.
He's strong for a little brat.
No one can stand against him.
But you don't have to worry about him.
We'll take care of him!
What was that?
And if we do, you take us to Goemon!
We'll beat him, fully, flawlessly!
Sure. It's a deal.
Where is he?
He's taken up residence in the Roast Beef Mines,
not too far from our village.
Roast Beef Mines...
Let's head on over!
Darefalcon!
Hey! Why do I have to wait outside?
Please take us to Roast Beef Mines.
Hey! I told you to stop talking to me
like I'm a taxi!
Cut it out!
Roast Beef Mines
So these are the Roast Beef Mines...
Let's go search for Griffon!
Yeah.
Dragon Warp!
He ran away!
Hehehe.
Where is he?
Griffon, are you there?
Birds?
Yo!
You called me?
Are you Griffon?
You're being eaten by a bird, dude!
I'm pretty sure that's a costume.
Wow, you rock!
Griffon
Where'd you get such a cool outfit?
Wanna trade with my
horned owl suit?
Don't approach him!
Ain't it sweet?
You should know,
I'm the strongest guy out there.
And I can fly across the sky!
How about you guys? Are you strong?
Oh yeah, super strong!
You bet.
You're talking to two Dragon Knights!
Chup, Vinsant!
Show them what Dragon Knights can do!
Alright! Watch us!
Wait, what?
How do I turn into a Dragon Knight again?
Don't you just flash into it or something?
Darn it, I forgot!
Vinsant, how do I...
Whaaat?!
Whoa-ho, you look awesome!
Huh? How did you do it?
It took a while, but I figured it out.
T-Tell me! How?
Uh, can we have a timeout?
Why would he do that?
Silly me.
I'm not sure I can explain it well, but...
You have to tuck in your abdomen.
Tuck in my abdomen! Got it!
Hmph!
Don't laugh at me!
Farting is good for you!
One more go!
Hmph!
Stop laughing!
You're no Dragon Knight,
you're a Dung Knight!
I am not a Dung Knight!
Dung Knight!
No, not a Dung Knight!
He seems pretty easily humored.
Alright! You, the one strong guy!
Let's fight!
Very well.
Chup, stand down.
Aw, man...
Don't let your guard down, Vinsant!
He has flight on his side!
So quick!
Wow, that was quick.
That had to leave a mark.
Whoa, you're real strong!
My word!
He took that like it was nothing!
Now it's my turn!
The Dragon Knight comes out on top!
He's not getting up from that one!
So cool...
This is so awesome!
I can't get enough of it!
You're so powerful, man!
To say nothing of your endurance...
How is he taking all that?
Man, I wanna fight too! Hmph!
Alright! I'll show you what I'm all about!
So will I!
Exodus Blade!
Exodus Blade.
My word! His surge caused an explosion!
It must've blown him to bits!
I'm sorry.
Whoa, I wanna do that too!
Yeah, that was cool!
Huh?!
I can't get enough of this!
Did you dodge that attack?!
I'll do it again!
Wait, what?!
Why'd you turn back?
He must not have become
a full Dragon Knight yet!
I'm out of stamina...
Here I come!
Huh?
Aw, man. Where'd all that strength go?
Dang it!
I'm bored... I've had enough of this.
This is bad! The battle's turned in his favor!
We'll have to back him up!
We'll fight another time!
Huh?
What do you mean?
We'll fight again in the sky
once you're strong again!
Good luck to you, half-baked!
Later!
Wait up!
Huh?
You don't seem like a bad guy, do you?
Don't let your guard down, Mayone!
That there is a thief!
I mean, he seems to only be fighting us
for the fun of it.
Why do you steal from others?
How else am I supposed to live?
It's the only way to get food!
Besides buying it?
Huh? Buying it?
What does that mean exactly?
Uh. You're serious?
Okay, look: you get money by working.
Then you can use that money
to buy food.
The exchange of money
is how things work!
Oh, I see. I didn't know that.
He didn't?
He's just foreign to the ways of society.
So you can't go stealing food!
Go get a job and use it
to buy food, okay?
That sounds boring.
Well, that's how things work!!
A rice ball you work for
tastes ten times better
than one you steal!
Is that true?
Hmm... Alright, then!
I'll stop stealing.
There you go!
You changed his mind pretty easily!
Later!
Wait up!
I just put together this pledge.
Sign this to swear you won't steal anymore.
Sounds good to me!
I pledge not to
steal again.
-Griffon
I pledge not to
steal again.
-Griffon
I pledge not to
steal again.
-Griffon
I pledge not to
steal again.
-Griffon
I pledge not to
steal again.
-Griffon
I pledge not to
steal again.
-Griffon
I pledge not to
steal again.
-Griffon
I pledge not to
steal again.
-Griffon
I pledge not to
steal again.
-Griffon
I pledge not to
steal again.
-Griffon
I pledge not to
steal again.
-Griffon
I pledge not to
steal again.
-Griffon
I pledge not to
steal again.
-Griffon
I pledge not to
steal again.
-Griffon
I pledge not to
steal again.
-Griffon
I pledge not to
steal again.
-Griffon
I pledge not to
steal again.
-Griffon
I pledge not to
steal again.
-Griffon
I pledge not to
steal again.
-Griffon
I pledge not to
steal again.
-Griffon
I pledge not to
steal again.
-Griffon
I pledge not to
steal again.
-Griffon
Mission complete!
Let's fight again!
W-Wait, he's leaving on foot?
I bet he can't actually fly.
Dang it, I thought I got away from you!
I have your Snack,
so I can summon you at any time!
Next time you run, you'll pay.
When did I become your workhorse?
Did you find Griffon?
Ta-dah!
We got him to swear
he wouldn't steal again!
You have?!
Rest easy.
Your village is now safe and sound.
What an accomplishment!
Naw, please.
All you did was fart.
Please take us to Mr. Goemon!
A deal's a deal.
He should be on his way home.
Let's go to the village.
Okay.
Dragon Warp!
I'll be here.
I'm home.
Hey, welcome back, Goemon.
Huh?!
We have guests?
Goemon
They have business with you, Goemon.
You're Goemon?
And who are you?
You're perfect! Just my type!
Creep.
This can't be.
Mr. Carbonara said Goemon was very old.
Yeah, Goemon IV.
That's her successor,
Goemon V.
Don't look down on her
just because she's a girl!
Her smithing outdoes that
of her predecessors.
She's quite promising!
Ugh, don't talk about me like that!
I don't wanna be a blacksmith.
I'm taking classes to become
a hair stylist!
Don't spout that nonsense!
You told the teachers to support me
during the meeting!
I'm going to work.
Get back here!
Goemon, wait!
Leave me alone!
We have a job for you.
We want you to rebuild
the Great Airship.
What's that?
These are the blueprints.
Yeesh, what is this? It's ancient.
Some nerve!
Hey now!
It's important, we need your help!
Wh-What's going on?
It's an earthquake!
Huh?! What is that?
My word!
This is a real troublemaker!
I'm getting some weird déjà vu.
I-I remember now! This is Dullahan!
A.k.a. the Death Sentence!
The Death Sentence?!
A powerful monster said to take the lives
of those soon to pass!
Dullahan
Wh-Who's sentenced to death here?
It's Gob-san, right? Tell me I'm right!
Considering his age,
he really oughta just give in!
Don't throw me under the bus!
Chup!!
It's like my grandmother said!
Only cowards and fried chickens
pick on girls!
Only cowards
and fried chickens
pick on girls.
I'm going to
dunk you in
barbecue sauce.
Only cowards
and fried chickens
pick on girls.
I'm going to
dunk you in
barbecue sauce.
I'm gonna dunk you
in barbecue sauce!
-Tome
That's enough, get out of there!
Chup!
My word!
Chup just died!
Wait!
Chup, you scared us!
Here I come!
Counterattack!
Take this!
Say-Your-Prayers-Mr.-Scaryface-Slas—
Dang it!
Take this!
Look at him go!
What an extreme battle!
He's open!
It's over!
Wait, what?
H-He turned back!
Used up his stamina, just like that...
Wait, what?!
nee kimi doko kara kita no?
Where are you from?
ima boku hima shiten dakedo
I've got time to spare
ochashite morae masenka?
Can I pour you some tea?
dame? dame? doushite desuka
No, you say? What's wrong?
jinsei wa rooringu sutoon
Life is like a rolling stone
tamaru konbini bukuro
Shopping bags piling up
seishun wa kumori zora
Youth is like a dark cloudy sky
sumafo izonshou sa
They're all glued to their phones
donzoko demo iijan
So what if we've hit rock bottom
ki ni shinakute iijan
Don't get so hung up on it
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
tabetara kateru kamojan
Maybe it'll help us get this katsu-done
dame dame demo iijan
But if it won't? Oh well
doutte koto neejan
Don't worry 'bout it
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
megezu ni ikouze
And keep moving forward
charanporan de iijan
Maybe we're kinda sloppy
muchakucha de iijan
And sure we're kinda reckless
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
tabetara kateru kamojan
Maybe it'll help us get this katsu-done
masshigura de iijan
So let's go full speed
tsuki susumeba iijan
And keep pushing onwards
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
tokoton yarouze
And see our goals all the way through
nee kimi doko kara kita no?
Where are you from?
ima boku hima shiten dakedo
I've got time to spare
Why don't we eat KATSUDON?
Dragon Warp!
I think I've regained a bit of my dignity...
I thought we were goners.
Thanks, Darefalcon!
Are you alright, Goemon?
I'm so done!
I'm sorry? We saved your butt!
But it's fine.
I'll repay the favor.
Wait, really?
So you'll build us the Great Airship?
No way.
Aw, man. You can't do it?
Not that lame husk of a ship.
Huh?
If I'm gonna make a ship,
I'm gonna make it my way.
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone!
What are you teaching us about today?
Today's lesson is on the
Roast Beef Mines.
Roast Beef Mines
The Roast Beef Mines
are a dungeon in the Salami Desert.
It's characterized by its
bedrock resembling tree rings
and its difficult-to-navigate tunnels.
Oh! That big boulder looks like
a slab of meat!
Leave those kind of lines
to Pepperon!
Stay on alert if you go in deep,
because it's easy to get lost!
Next Time
We head to the headquarters of Detton
to build our airship.
We need their technology to craft it,
but the engineer is in a funk!
Let's Get to Work on the Great Airship!!
Next time: "Let's Get to Work
on the Great Airship!!"
Alright, time for a big adventure!