This is Snack World, the hallowed ground
of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam
and people have handy smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
And my name's Chup.
At last, our adventure has come to a climax.
Failing to put up a fight
against the invincible overlord,
we've put our final hope
on the legendary sacred sword.
Come at me, Demi-Glace!!
Hey, untransformed overlords!
We're gonna take you guys down!
The sacred sword Muramascalibur
will end you!
I shall end you!
Chup, are you sure about this?
Yeah! If you brag about it now,
it'll be embarrassing if we lose again!
At least say something like,
"We might just defeat you for real!"
We'll fully, flawlessly take you down!
Uh, probably!
Drop the "fully, flawlessly!"
Oh, great. You're back.
You never learn, do you?
They combined!
My, he certainly has a thirst for blood.
Episode 50: Big Adventures are Endless!
Chup, I've been thinking it over,
and now that we know their backstory,
is defeating them really the right choice?
Surely, there's a way we can reason with them?
I hope so too.
I feel bad for them after
seeing what they went through.
Wh-What is this?
Sonia, what's wrong?
Wake up! Look at me!
Father, explain!
The alliance is off.
I tried to rescue her,
but she was casualty to a skirmish...
I'm sorry, boys.
No way!
Why...?
Say it isn't so!!
I really think we should try
to talk things out!
It's probably better that way, yeah.
Talk things out?
That's comical.
Are you giving out excuses
since you know you can't win?
Ah, did you overhear us?
Look, we know why
you're doing all this.
So we might be able to forgive you.
I don't remember asking for forgiveness.
The only options are I destroy the world,
or you destroy me!
Had a feeling we wouldn't get through to him.
That adds up.
Come face me!
The midnight train bound for your graves
will de departing momentarily.
Are we going anywhere?!
Oh, there was a feature
on classic songs the other day.
Fine! If I gotta beat you,
I will!
Then do it.
I'll beat you!
You twerp!
Don't quiver now!
Here I go!
You're a handful, y'know that?
I'm coming at you!
Calibur!!
Final Battle Time Slash!
You still haven't even drawn him out!
Fighting with an unsheathed sword?
How weak do you think I am?
Please, I don't have to draw my sword
to take you down! Ain't that right, Calibur?
Yes!
Don't agree with him!
You can't even draw yourself!
What an irritating foe!
I don't want to hear that
from the talking sword!
I won't deny that!
Or will I?
Is it actually working?!
I'm getting bored now.
Let's finish this.
I won't let you kill Chup!
We won't lose!
You already are!
Chup is our friend!
And friends don't let friends
get killed!
Look who's all cool now.
This is the end for you!
Prepare to face my ultimate sp—
You guys...
You're right! I can't lose!
Not here, not now!
Butako!
Here, girl!
So you can do that!
Let's go!
You think you stand
a chance against me?
I won't give up.
I will win this battle!
S-So will we!
But this seems like a bit much for us.
Chup!
Stay back!
I swore...
I would overcome any challenge!
I can do it! I will do it!
I'll do it fully, flawlessly!
Maybe!
Muramascalibur!!
The Muramascalibur did it!
He drew himself!
Go, Chup! Slash at him!
No way!
Is it over?
Wow! He split the overlord right in half!
Whoa there!
That was close.
What?!
So no matter how powerful
the sword is,
they can just split apart and dodge it?
That's messed up!
That's playing dirty!
But I admit, that was a pretty good slash.
You flatter me.
Don't get smug, you didn't help us!
But a slash won't get us.
If even the sacred sword can't beat him,
then all hope really is lost!
Now we're all out of options!
Time to throw in the towel.
It's like my grandmother said!
The only way
to rival
a strong foe
is to do
what they cannot.
The only way
to rival
a strong foe
is to do
what they cannot.
The only way to rival a strong foe
is to do what they cannot!
-Tome
What's your plan this time?
Scopeion!
Nature!
Ayo, it's me, Scopeion!
Where do you need me to peep?
Wait, what?!
What's goin' on?
No clue.
Buttery!
Huff-puff-puff!
Yeti!
So cold...
Mermaid!
I'm here!
How many of them
are you gonna summon?!
I guess summoning with Snacks
is something the overlord can't do?
Are you hoping they'll work with you
to defeat him?
That's really not a good idea.
If you're not careful,
he'll kill all of them!
Don't worry about it!
Great, that's all of them!
Hey everyone!
I think you used too many Snacks.
And it's not just monsters,
you called lots of humans, too.
Is Bunnilla here?
I'm glad you summoned me
for my assistance,
but with such a large turnout,
I'm wondering if I'll get to do anything.
Am I important here or not?
Tell me you're not gonna leave first!
Of course not!
Perfect! This is just the team we need!
Hey, overlord!
I've been waiting to see
what you were cooking up.
Were you hoping to band together
all your friends to beat me?
No matter the numbers,
I'll erase them in a flash.
You're wrong! They're not here to help us battle!
Then what are they here for?
They're here...
to sing!
What's this?
Warp-pa's holding a baton.
The Darefalcon Chorus Group
will now present its top-class singing talent.
Thanks, Warp-pa!
Let's do it as we planned!
Hold on! When did you find the time
to plan this with him?
Now, let us begin!
You can find us all down in town
So don't feel so glum, you're not alone
You'll hit it off with someone
So come on down and be our friend! (Be our friend!)
No time to waste, let's be friends! (Let's be friends!)
How are y'all doing?
Anyone can make friends—so can you!
So join hands with us and sing along
What are you doing?
Why do you have to destroy the world?
Because you don't have friends?
Because you don't have Sonia?
How do you know that?!
Keep her name out of your mouth!!
Demi, Glace, watch this!
Demi, Glace, are you watching this?
What's that?
Oh yeah, Chup asked Darefalcon
to Memory Warp him alone.
Wait, does that mean
he met Sonia?!
My word!
What are we looking at?!
Chup told me he met you guys
far in the future.
I often wondered what you were up to
after we separated,
or if you ever got sad about anything...
Demi, Glace, my kind-hearted brothers,
please don't harm anyone
for my sake.
No matter how far apart we are,
or how much time passes,
don't stop being my kind-hearted brothers.
Sonia...
You're not alone.
I may not be with you,
but you can still make
great new friends,
lifelong companions,
and lovely families!
Chup, you knew Sonia
and got us a message from her?
You were doing things all wrong!
The person you love so dearly
doesn't want you to do this!
Demi... Have we been doing things all wrong?
Would Sonia be sad if she saw us now?
Probably. I feel Sonia wouldn't
accept what we've been doing.
But it let us see her again.
Yeah. I forgot.
It's just what she would've said.
Sonia never asked for this.
Right.
Actually, we might've known that already.
From the very start,
that we were making a bad choice.
But we were sad about losing Sonia.
Hey, Chup!
Work together and take us down,
that's fine with us!
Do it!
Come on, Chup! Take us on!
I know you didn't get all your friends
together just for a musical!
Come on, Chup! Take us on!
I know you didn't get all your friends
together just for a musical!
You're wrong!
I didn't bring everyone here
just to beat you!
Then why did you?!
I did it...
so we can...
throw a party!
What?!
Chup, what the heck?!
I'm following my grandmother's words!
The only way to rival a strong foe
is to do what they cannot!
Huh?
Once those two destroy the world
and everyone in it,
they can't throw a party on their own!
So that's what you meant.
A party sounds like so much fun!
Oh, yeah!
Life is full of pain and sorrow
Sometimes everything just sucks
Makes you wanna cry, makes you wanna quit
Makes you wanna throw it all away, makes you wanna run away
'Til you're all depressed again
But we keep going in spite of it
You can find us all down in town
So don't be glum, you're not alone
You'll hit it off with someone
So come on down and be our friend! (Be our friend!)
No time to waste, let's be friends! (Let's be friends!)
Anyone can make friends—so can you!
So join hands with us and sing along
I am the world, and you're traveling me
We're always together, no matter where we go
You'll hit it off with someone
So come on down and be our friend! (Be our friend!)
No time to waste, let's be friends! (Let's be friends!)
Anyone can make friends—so can you!
So join hands with us and sing along
Uh, Glace...
What is all this?
What's wrong, guys?
Come have fun with us!
It might hurt to lose someone you love,
but you gotta cheer up!
I lost my mom, my dad,
and my grandma,
but I'm fully, flawlessly,
happier than ever!
Chup...
Demi, I...
I know.
Come on, join us!
I've made so many friends
So let's have some fun, all together now
You'll hit it off with someone
All of you are my friends! (We're all friends!)
You beast!
You here, you there, you're my friends! (You're my friends!)
Everyone here is my friend!
So join hands with us and dance!
Sexy!
Arena!
The whole world is my friend
So join hands with us and walk on!
This is friendship?
Demi, my eyes won't stop
making water...
Mine too...
It's like my grandmother said!
Don't cry when you're sad,
cry when you're happy!
Don't cry when
you're sad,
cry when
you're happy.
Don't cry when
you're sad,
cry when
you're happy.
-Tome
Chup...
Thank you...
What happened to me?
Vinsant!
You got erased like nothing!
I see.
What about those kids?
The final battle is all over!
Everyone's back!
All's well that ends well!
Really?
Yes, really!
Come on, dance with us, Vinsant!
Okay.
Chup!
Well done, Chup!
You have my gratitude.
Your majesty! Princess Melora!
Thank you!
Amazing as ever, Chup!
Would you like a reward from me?
D-Do you mean it?
I-I'd absolutely love it!
What would you like?
C-Can I ask for anything?
Of course!
I-I wanna see you na—
ked...
You know you can't ask for that!
I-It was just a joke!
Jeez, you're such a worrywart.
Oh, I'm sure it was.
What?!
Chup, why do only you get a kiss?
Where's mine? I want one!
I'm in a wonderland of love!
Choochoo!
Alright, guys!
Let's go nuts tonight!
Yeah!
nee kimi doko kara kita no?
Where are you from?
ima boku hima shiten dakedo
I've got time to spare
ochashite morae masenka?
Can I pour you some tea?
dame? dame? doushite desuka
No, you say? What's wrong?
jinsei wa rooringu sutoon
Life is like a rolling stone
tamaru konbini bukuro
Shopping bags piling up
seishun wa kumori zora
Youth is like a dark cloudy sky
sumafo izonshou sa
They're all glued to their phones
donzoko demo iijan
So what if we've hit rock bottom
ki ni shinakute iijan
Don't get so hung up on it
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
tabetara kateru kamojan
Maybe it'll help us get this katsu-done
dame dame demo iijan
But if it won't? Oh well
doutte koto neejan
Don't worry 'bout it
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
megezu ni ikouze
And keep moving forward
charanporan de iijan
Maybe we're kinda sloppy
muchakucha de iijan
And sure we're kinda reckless
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
tabetara kateru kamojan
Maybe it'll help us get this katsu-done
masshigura de iijan
So let's go full speed
tsuki susumeba iijan
And keep pushing onwards
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
tokoton yarouze
And see our goals all the way through
nee kimi doko kara kita no?
Where are you from?
ima boku hima shiten dakedo
I've got time to spare
Why don't we eat KATSUDON?
Are you really leaving?
It'll be pretty lonely here
without you around.
You're gonna look into that treasure map
your father sent you, right?
Want a lift from Warpman?
Must be shocking to find out
your dad's alive after all this time.
Yeah. I was so sure he died way back then.
But he happened to be doing laundry
down by the river,
and made it out alive.
Who does laundry by the river these days?
Then he sends me this weird map on SnaLine.
The map too!
How old-fashioned is he?
Sounds like a good spot
to take Warpman to.
He's out there looking for that treasure, right?
Yeah, I think if I follow this map,
I might come across him.
Sorry, Chup. Wish I could tag along,
but I gotta help my mom with her job.
And I have to pass since I'm
taking sword training classes.
My schedule's free, by the way!
I'm good! I'll do this alone.
I wanna see how far I can make it
on my own!
Though you will have me.
Sure will!
What about me?
But y'know, it's just like you
to leave one adventure behind
with the energy to tackle
a brand new one right away!
Got that right.
Are you sure you'll be okay, Chup?
I really don't mind coming with you...
You never know when you'll need
the power of Warpman!
I'll be off! Take care, you guys!
Okay!
This is Snack World, the hallowed ground
of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam
and people have handy smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
And my name's Chup.
In order to become a super great adventurer
that overcomes any challenge,
I'm gonna keep walking down the path ahead,
one step at a time!
Alright, it's time for a big adventure!
It's like my grandmother said!
Big adventures are endless!!
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone!
What are you teaching us about today?
Today's lesson is on Snack World!
Snack World
Snack World is the world
where we live!
People call it the "hallowed ground
of dreams and adventures."
It's more than just the continent
of our adventure—
there's other continents
out there too!
Some kingdoms out there
are advancing their magic tech.
So sweet! I wanna see what's
out there in the world!
Oh, Chup. Take care!