This is Snack World, the hallowed ground
of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam
and people have handy smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
And my name's Chup!
After a long battle,
I've finally defeated the evil merchant Vinegar Khan,
and now I'm moving towards a new goal!
Whatever perils await me,
I'll fully, flawlessly overcome them!
Alright, let's go on another big adventure today!
Episode 40: Let's Get to Work on the Great Airship!!
So you'll build us the Great Airship?
No way.
Aw, man. You can't do it?
After all we did for you?
Not that lame husk of a ship.
If I'm gonna make a ship,
I'm gonna make it my way.
Alright, get to it!
But building the Great Airship requires
mobilizing several different brands' technologies.
What does that mean?
Well, to begin with,
we need Detton's shipbuilding tech.
Oh, Detton!
I have one of their weapons!
Ah, the Detton brand did get its start
in the ship industry.
No wonder you'll need them.
Yeah. We'll use their technologies
to build the ship's hull.
Without them, it'll burst into smithereens
the moment it hits the magic barrier.
Smithereens, huh?
We really will need their help.
What else is needed for the ship?
We'll need instruments
that measure to a nanolevel,
and only Peffany makes those.
I see.
Peffany is an accessory brand,
so you'll be utilizing their embossing technology.
Another thing we'll need
is high-level maneuvering equipment,
something we can only go to
Paccarat Lapa for.
Ah, yes. You'll make maneuvering equipment
with their gimmick technology.
And lastly, a black magic engine.
If we want to break through
the magic barrier,
we'll need Fairy Electronics' technology.
I see. They're an electronics manufacturer
with top-of-the-line technology,
so you want them
to perfect the Great Airship.
Yep. There you have it.
Once we have all the technologies,
it'll take about three days.
Awesome!
You must have a full blueprint
already laid out inside your mind!
You really are a master blacksmith!
Did you catch that, Chup?
Yeah.
Detton's ship tech,
Peffany's embossing tech,
Paccarat Lapa's gimmick te—
Te-te-te-te-tehh!
Great, he short-circuited.
Point being, she'll make the Great Airship
once we get her some stuff!
We'll have to start by
visiting the brands in person.
Detton's headquarters are in Durian,
a trading port city in the southwest.
Let's get over there!
Darefalcon!
We'd like a warp to Durian.
You want another warp?
Surely, I'm not just the woman
doing all your chores to you, am I?
Of course not! I just call on you
whenever I need to be warped, is all.
That's exactly my point!
I'm just a housewife, aren't I?
We don't think that even in the slightest!
We just wish to be helped
by your mighty power, O Darefalcon!
We beg of you!
Fine.
That praise should buy us
at least three more warps.
Dragon Warp!
Durian, Trading Port City
Whoo! We're here!
Adrian!
It's Durian.
Don't mix it up
with Mr. Carbonara's chicken.
Should I go with
shrimp or crab?
Why do you only want to eat?
We don't have time for that!
We can't stop at a port city
and not eat seafood!
It's like stopping at a chicken restaurant
and not getting chicken!
I don't care!
We already decided
we would go straight to Detton.
What a hottie!
Look over here!
Aw, shucks.
They're not looking at you.
He doesn't pay their squeals any mind!
It only makes the ladies fall harder for him.
We've made it to Detton.
Detton HQ
No dumb jokes. We're going in.
Hey, good to see you again!
The desert is so hot,
I get all sweaty and my foundation comes right off,
so here I am!
And when I'm not performing on stage,
I'm here as a receptionist, oh yeah!
Oh hey, it's Mermaid!
We met her in the desert!
Let's get this show on the road!
Are y'all ready?
Yeah!
Forgot he loved this so much.
Arena seats!
Yeah!
There's no arena, doofus,
it's just the floor!
What brings you here today?
Yeah!
That's not an answer!
We're here to build the Great Airship!
Wow! That's one big dream
you've got there!
Y'all agree? Second-level seats!
There are no seats!
But if you believe,
then your dreams will come true!
So go bring your big Durian dreams
to life here!
I believe in you.
Aw!
C'mon.
Do you want to hear my next song?
Yeah!
This is a single from my second album,
Green Coelacanth!
It's called Desert or Sea? Don't Matter to Me!
That's a wrap!
We're not here to listen to music!
We need to get to the engineers already!
I was just dancing
because Pepperon was.
No, Chup started it.
It really doesn't matter to me!
Doesn't matter to you?
I already told you
we don't have time for this!!
You can hear the rest of the song at my concert
next week in the Durian Town Plaza!
We'll be there!
Mr. Chup, please head
to Room C on the 6th floor.
You will see Rice,
our senior technology officer.
What was the hold-up for?!
Wait, where's Vinsant?
He said he had business to attend to elsewhere.
He always goes off by himself!
He's probably just going to see
the girls who were screaming at him earlier.
Don't project on him.
I say that, but who would scream at you?
Many would!
In fact, it happened when
I stepped foot in French Toaster!
Sounds like they were screaming in fear
at the yucky Goblin.
Hello! Are you by any chance Mr. Rice?
Aah, I can't think of anything!
We're here about building
the Great Airship.
I can't help!
Do I look like I can help with that?
Rice
Why would you ask me
something like that now of all times?
Right when I lost the ability
to come up with a layout for a ship...
But we kinda sorta really need it.
What's wrong?
Hush.
What? Why?
Ugh, something finally came to me,
and you had to open your mouth
and make me forget!
What is your problem?
I don't like this guy.
He's like the nerdy classmate.
Dang it!
He's avoiding messing up his hair.
Are you really that annoyed?
Hey, Rice.
How do you come up with
a ship's design?
Ships have long been named womanlike things
such as "Queen" and "Princess."
So I design them with the beautiful figures
of women in mind.
If only I had such a figure
to work with...
The beautiful figure of a woman?
No way. I-I couldn't!
No one asked you anything.
Mr. Rice! Does anything come to mind
when you look at Mayone?
Aha! The ship! It's...
It's... not coming to me.
Oh, come on!
How about Goemon then?
Aha! The ship! It's...
It's... not coming to me.
Hey!
Maybe he needs someone
more seductive and alluring.
Alluring?
Oh, I know!
Mr. Rice, this should get your juices flowing!
Here we go! 3, 2, 1...
Open!
Look at you!
Who's ready to get pampered tonight?
Aha!
From libido comes inspiration!
Whoa!
It's finished!
What, really?
It looks old and rotten.
How rude!
Alright, let's try again!
Mr. Rice, this'll fully, flawlessly
get your brain going!
Here we go! 3, 2, 1...
Open!
What brings you here?
She's talking in her sleep again...
She's certainly alluring...
In more of a gross way
than a beautiful way.
What are you mumbling about?
Gosh, I'm tired.
How do you get tired in your sleep?
What in the world?!
She's sucking us in!
Aha!
This will be the one! I'm sure of it!
Whoa!
It's finished!
Oh, no!
That's not even a ship,
that's a wharf roach!
A wharf roach? That's uncalled for.
When I think seductive,
I think Princess Melora!
She should give him a good idea!
She has a smooth figure
from her waist to her butt.
Just one glance at it...
Mr. Rice!
Let's go see Princess Melora!
Right now?
I'm afraid I cannot,
I have an appointment at the beauty parlor.
You can miss that! Let's go!
N-Now hold on!
What's Dullahan doing here?!
I don't blame you for being
frightened by a monster this big!
I've seen many personally,
and I still wet myself half the time.
Is he still after me?
Stand back, Goemon!
Dang you! We really gotta
get to Melora, you know?
So I can get a good look
at her figure...
That was close!
Don't lose your train of thought!
One hit from that sword
and it's all over!
You won't beat me!
Dettonic Sword! Dettonic Shield!
Detton ton-ton (You like that)
Detton ton-ton ton-ton
Dettonic Sword.
Dettonic Shield.
You have Detton products!
Thank you for your patronage.
Save it!
Our Dettonic Shield is quite durable!
A 4:3 combination of
basil seed alloy and saffron iron
makes it even stronger than steel!
This isn't the time!
Our Dettonic Sword is quite strong!
A 4:3 combination of
basil seed alloy and saffron iron
makes it even stronger—
You don't have to tell us!
It's not even different!
Your sword just shattered!
Your basil whatsit and saffamacallit
were nothing special!
No, it only broke because the bad guy's sword
put pressure on a specific spot...
Though that could be a problem for us.
Perhaps I should take it
to the next board meeting...
Forget holding a meeting,
just do something!
Mr. Chup! Take a Dettonic Sword from the rack!
Wow! You've got quite the collection!
It's like my grandmother said!
Better than before.
Bees in your ear.
Better than before!
Bees in your ear!
-Tome
Agh, I hate it when bees buzz past my ear!
Is that relevant?!
He's making use of all these high-end Dettons!
I didn't say you could use all of them!
Every last one is quite expensive...
I'm out of swords!
The last one!
Chup!
Use your Dragon Knight powers!
Get angry and transform!
I've got this!
Chup! What the heck are you doing?
Didn't Princess Melora say
she hates little wimps?
Neh, neh, wimpy little Chump! What a wimp!
Womp-womp!
What was that?!
I'm no wimp!
How d'ya like that, Dullahan?
This sword will take you down!
I know your weak point!
It's your leg!
He ran out of time.
Maybe don't act so tough
and swing your sword around!
Watch out, Chup!
I'll stop you with this sword!
Wait, that isn't...!
What in the world?!
That's the Dettonic Twin Gear,
a transforming weapon we've been developing.
It's only a prototype.
We're still working out the kinks.
Are you kidding?
Vinsant, help us!
Exodus Blade!
Phantom.
Exodus Blade.
Not you too!
You don't need to pose,
just get rid of him!
This guy's bad news!
Oh gosh!
We need backup!
Dragon Warp!
Thank you, Darefalcon!
I can't believe we got out of that alive.
But if we leave Dullahan there,
he'll ruin my company for good!
Worry not!
Dullahan's only after Goemon.
He should have left Detton by now! ...Hopefully.
"Hopefully?"
So, what about you, Vinsant?
What were you up to?
I went to go see doors being developed
using shipbuilding technology.
Huh? That's what you left us for?
You know, we almost died just there!
I'm sorry. I had to...
Today was the day they unveiled it!
Doesn't make a difference!
Your majesty!
Good day, Chup!
What could be the matter?
Do you know where Melora is?
She's having a premium platinum
professional beauty treatment done.
What kind of treatment is that?
Can we go see?
No!
Aw.
Melora is currently starch naked.
No one is allowed entry into the salon room.
He's not going to get a better chance
to witness her figure.
I know what to do.
Scopeion!
Nature!
Ey! It's me, Scopeion!
Scopeion, please peek into the salon room!
Easy breezy, whoo!
I didn't say you could peek.
Mr. Rice, if you see Melora's figure,
I know you'll come up with a design!
Understood.
Whoo! It's her waist!
Oh my!
Never mind, it's a vase.
Darn.
One moment! That don't normally happen to me.
Second time's the charm!
It's her legs!
Here we go!
Oh my!
Hey!
Oh, I'm sorry.
I was trying to get a closer look.
That's too far, you pervert.
Sure, I'll take it.
So you admit it!
Gonna get it right this time!
Oh m—
It's Melora's butt!!
Holy cow!
A peach?!
Come on!
Don't roll on the floor!
This isn't working.
How are we supposed
to see her figure now?
It's like my grandmother said!
Don't think, just feel!
Don't think,
just feel.
Dachshund,
jackrabbit.
Don't think,
just feel.
Dachshund,
jackrabbit.
Dachshund, jackrabbit!
-Tome
What the heck does that mean?
It means not to use your head to think!
What?
Just show us something,
doesn't matter what!
You got it, brother!
Oh my!
Hurrah! We finally won!
Why are you getting so emotional?
How is it, Mr. Rice?
This is exactly what I needed!
I can see it! I can see it!
If I get a closer look,
I can perfect it!
Oh, hi, Chup! How are you?
Melora! Guess wha—
What?!
A-A crocodile?!
That's her new pet, Wanilla!
First it was earthworms,
now it's a crocodile?!
That's terrifying.
What a wonderful figure!
Your beauty is even more remarkable up close!
I can see it! I can see the design!
Huh?! You were focused on the crocodile?
Really?!
I see it!!
Why did the crocodile inspire you?
I suppose it's female,
and it's alluring...
What was all that fuss for?!
It's finished!
That looks awesome!
I'll get back to Detton and begin
work on the airship's hull!
Hooray!
Oh, one thing.
The bow will be stronger
if you build it with glinius alloy.
And narrow its angle so it can pass
the magic barrier's resistance.
Also...
She gives very detailed instructions!
Goemon's the real deal!
I'll be sure to take that into account!
Pleasure doing business!
All mine!
Now we're one step closer
to building the Great Airship.
Can you show me Melora's waist again?
I thought you'd ask,
so I recorded it!
Princess Melora's waist!
What are you looking at?
H-Her waist...
nee kimi doko kara kita no?
Where are you from?
ima boku hima shiten dakedo
I've got time to spare
ochashite morae masenka?
Can I pour you some tea?
dame? dame? doushite desuka
No, you say? What's wrong?
jinsei wa rooringu sutoon
Life is like a rolling stone
tamaru konbini bukuro
Shopping bags piling up
seishun wa kumori zora
Youth is like a dark cloudy sky
sumafo izonshou sa
They're all glued to their phones
donzoko demo iijan
So what if we've hit rock bottom
ki ni shinakute iijan
Don't get so hung up on it
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
tabetara kateru kamojan
Maybe it'll help us get this katsu-done
dame dame demo iijan
But if it won't? Oh well
doutte koto neejan
Don't worry 'bout it
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
megezu ni ikouze
And keep moving forward
charanporan de iijan
Maybe we're kinda sloppy
muchakucha de iijan
And sure we're kinda reckless
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
tabetara kateru kamojan
Maybe it'll help us get this katsu-done
masshigura de iijan
So let's go full speed
tsuki susumeba iijan
And keep pushing onwards
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
tokoton yarouze
And see our goals all the way through
nee kimi doko kara kita no?
Where are you from?
ima boku hima shiten dakedo
I've got time to spare
Why don't we eat KATSUDON?
I see it!!
While Detton's working on the airship's hull,
we should head to the next brand.
Agreed.
We'll need Peffany's meticulous embossing
to make high-dimensional instruments
that measure to a nano-level.
I wanna go to Peffany!
Peffany's headquarters are in
the port city Durian, just like Detton's.
Then let's go back to Durian!
Which means it's time for...
No need.
Darefalcon! Perfect timing!
I came because I was expecting your call.
You've developed some self-awareness
as our Warpman!
Show me some respect!
That's Lord Warpman to you!
That's what upset you?
Next stop: the port city of Durian!
Please gather beside me.
You've really taken a liking
to warping us around!
We're now departing.
Dragon Warp!
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone!
What are you teaching us about today?
Today's lesson is on Transjara!
Transjara
Transjara are weapon or other equipment
that can transform.
One moment it's a shield,
the next it's a bow!
All sorts of brands have been
getting in on this new gimmick!
Whoa! Transjara are so sweet!
Calm down, Chup!
Don't maximize it and
swing it around like that!
Next Time
Now we're off to see Peffany,
the #1 brand among girls!
Awaiting us inside are amazing technologies
that even Mayone's crazy about!
Peffany, the Beautiful Lady
Next time: "Peffany, the Beautiful Lady."
Alright, time for a big adventure!