This is Snack World, the hallowed ground
of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam
and people have handy smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
And my name's Chup!
My village was burnt down by
the evil land-destroying merchant Vinegar Khan,
so I've embarked on a journey
to get my revenge 1000-fold!
At last, my journey has brought me
close to Vinegar.
In order to defeat him, I will overcome
any impossible mission that comes my way!
Alright, let's go on another big adventure today!
Now I can finally resurrect Scardon.
Every last one of you is dead meat.
Vinegar, you scoundrel!
Get back here!
Take care, everybody!
Damn it!
We were this close to becoming Dragon Knights!
Even so...
I feel so much stronger!
Your inner Dragon Knight
may have awakened amidst the battle.
It's quite possible,
seeing how far you've come.
Whoa!
We won't defeat Vinegar like this.
But now that the Dragon Heart has been stolen,
we have no choice but to raid Vinegar Palace.
We'll risk our lives to destroy the Dragon Heart.
Do you think we might die there?
Not might—we almost certainly will.
Huh?
N-Now, hold on,
let me look up another way...
There is none!
If we don't do anything,
the world will end.
I'm in.
I'll do the impossible if I have to!
I'll defeat Vinegar,
and as for Melora...
...and as for Melora...
I'll take a bath with her!!
His fighting spirit is powerful...
Erm...
We'll pass.
A-Agreed.
Sorry about this.
If Vinegar is defeated,
you'll get a very big reward.
Huh?
Here's your reward: a complete Peffany set!
Feel free to take as much as you like.
Wow!
I'll do it! I'm in!
A gift to you: a free lifetime
all-you-can-eat special VIP card.
Whoa!
You can rely on me!
Gobby, you're the one who saved the world, right?
You're just so handsome! Mwah!
Whoo!
I'm gonna save the world!
Chup, it's almost finally time.
Saying Farewell to Melora
Episode 35: The Final Battle Approaches—
I didn't expect our battle with Vinegar
to come so soon...
I'll fight as best as I can!
Now, be on your way.
Darefalcon.
Hm? Yes?
Would you mind transporting us
to French Toaster before our battle?
Transport us?
For what?
We'll break into Vinegar Palace
tomorrow morning.
This'll give you all time
to fulfill any regrets.
Go home, say goodbye to your loved ones,
do whatever needs to be done.
Whatever needs to be done, huh?
Oh, right. We might just die out there.
Mm-hmm...
Got it.
Very well.
Then allow me to escort you
to French Toaster.
Thank you.
Huh?
We didn't move an inch.
All finished.
Wait, what?
I booked you seats on the
Transcontinental Railroad online.
Huh? What about your Dragon Warp?
I'm afraid there will be no dragon booking
while I'm a ghost.
Dragon booking?
You shall return on the final train of the day.
Now, off with you.
What was that light about?
Just a courtesy.
Man, so my life's about to end, huh?
You say that like it's nothing.
So what are you guys planning to do?
I'm gonna eat a great, big feast!
Getting a head start, I see.
Gob-san?
There's a luxury nightclub
I've wanted to visit before I kick the bucket!
Alright, have fun.
What about you, Chup?
Like I even have to ask...
If I tell Princess Melora this is goodbye,
do you think she'll take me on a date?
In your dreams.
What are you going to do, Mayone?
Planning to see your mom and brother?
Uh? Well, I guess.
Oh, hey! What about you, Vinsant?
I'm going to prepare for the battle
with some mental simulations.
Well then, we'll meet here again
at the end of the day.
Alright.
That's all, then.
Princess Melora!
Princess Melora! Guess who's back!
Huh? Where is she?
She's off at a flower arrangement
class for the day.
Aw, what? When will she be back?
Not until she's made a piece
she's satisfied with!
She doesn't even pick up my calls.
Last week, she didn't return
until after midnight.
N-No!!
I can't believe I won't get
to say goodbye to the princess...
What do I do with the rest of my day?
Hm? What is it, girl?
Oh? You're very close
to obtaining your flight license?
You just need to do your test?
Alright! Let's go get it!
Of course, Butako!
You're about to be a grown-up dragon!
Ey, could I get eight more servings of this?
If it isn't Pepperon!
We heard you were in King Oyster City!
Weren't you scared in
a dangerous city like that?
Wh-What is it?
Thank you for everything.
Tomorrow, I will go down in honor
like a real man!
This will be my final dinner.
Pepperon, look at me!
We're gonna battle!
I've been hoping to settle the score
between us!
I'd be delighted! But my meal comes first.
Okay.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Ribbon, our top recommendation,
will be out shortly.
Your top?!
Nice to meet you, I'm Ribbon!
Scooch over.
Maybe I'll have a drink too!
I'd like someone else.
The nerve!
Sis!
Sis, you're back!
Yeah, for the day.
Sorry to call you out of work.
Mom's a little swamped to get out right now.
We can go home if you...
No, it's fine. How is she?
What do you mean it's fine?
You really should go see her.
I don't know if I can stand to.
I was too hard on her when I left,
and I still couldn't accomplish anything...
That doesn't matter right now!
Mom's company is about to be
taken over by evil forces.
Huh?!
It's about to get bought out
by Vinegar Enterprises...
She's just about to hold
a press conference!
No...
Just come with me to see her!
Hey, w-wait!
Relax, Butako!
There's no need to worry.
I will now conduct your Dragon Flight School
official flying test.
Commander Cinderella!
That's instructor to you!
Instructor!
You work in this field too?
Yes. I have 2,043 different
licenses and certifications.
Let's go!
STUDENT
It's okay, girl!
You've got this—fully, flawlessly!
Off we go!
Not might—we most certainly will.
Take this!
So quick!
I'm not the same guy
you fought before!
I've slipped on banana peels
and gotten loads of training!
Oh, look! Meat on the ground!
Really? Where?
Ow!
Back at it!
You look like you're frozen still!
Oh, look! Meat on the ground!
Really? Where?
Ow!
Why does he keep falling for that?
Sorry for keeping you waiting.
Here is our number one, Rose,
and our number two,
Katyusha.
Number one, you say?
Hello there!
We oughta open up a new bottle!
Get me someone else!!
The nerve.
Oh, sir...
Tell me where you keep
the girls in these photos!
Those are simply for decoration.
Forget it! Just give me the check!
Will that be all? Then your fee will be...
3,020,000 gillan.
Jeez, that's steep!
You could import a car with that money!
You had a lot of food and drink.
Alright, so what drove my bill up so high?
Read 'em all out, one by one.
Okay. Then first...
Peanuts: 100,000 gillan,
multiplied by 12 grains...
That's ridiculous! You're ripping me off!
Isn't this a real stinker, good sir...
Wh-What are you doing?
Hello?
Ms. Mallory, the enterprise has
given us new conditions.
Have our lawyers look at them.
Yes?
Mom, Mayone is here!
Mom?
Oh, you're back.
She's just here for the day!
There's something she wanted to tell you.
Yes?
Um, Mom?
Sorry, Mom's a bit tied up at the moment.
Can you tell me another time?
Huh?
Mom, why are you being mean to her?
She came all this way!
It's okay. I'm sorry to disrupt your work.
Mayone.
Huh?
I'll hear everything out afterwards.
Your journey isn't over yet, is it?
I'd like to see you smiling
when you come back.
It's hard to say hello again
when you're down in the dumps.
And I'll make you your favorite
strawberry jam pancakes then!
Mom!
Ms. Mallory, it's time to prepare
for the conference.
I understand.
Cornet, let's go.
Okay!
Good work! Your steering
on those twists was perfect.
Good job, Butako!
You're all grown up now!
Vinegar Enterprises and
M&C Technologies
will be holding a joint press conference.
We are pleased to announce
that Vinegar Enterprises'
acquisition of our company...
has been rejected!
I won't be intimidated by your threats.
Mark my words, Vinegar.
The Mallory family doesn't back down—
no matter what!
Say that again, you twat!
Let's get out of here, Cornet!
Wait! Go after her!
Wow, Mom...
They're almost evenly-matched.
Yeah.
You've improved, Pepperon.
I can't lose if I want to face tomorrow!
What's goin' on tomorrow?
You said you were having your final dinner.
I'm going into battle with my comrades.
I must protect them,
even if it means putting my life on the line!
That checks out.
I'd best not waste your stamina any further.
Pepperon, take good care, okay?
Come back once you've won.
Don't count on it.
I'm completely prepared
to die out there.
I won't be coming back!
Shed your dignity, Pepperon!
You know you want to come back alive.
Say what you're really thinking!
I'm leaving.
Have you heard, Pepperon?
Fretaya's introducing a new item next week:
a demi-glace salisbury beef bowl!
D-Demi... what on earth is that?
I've never heard of it!
They just announced it
online this morning.
The demi-glace salisbury beef bowl...
It's Fretaya's most boundary-breaking
menu item yet.
Salisbury and beef bowl,
adding beef to beef...
No, it's multiplying it!
It's the ultimate dish, bringing out
the infinite possibilities of beef!
You want to eat it, don'tcha?
'Cuz you won't if you die!
You can top it with cheese
for 50 gillan extra!
I...
Come back alive, and then we'll settle our fight!
I...!
I'm just really hungry now!
F-Fair enough...
Do whatever you want with me!
I'm a worthless man anyways.
I haven't even tried to be useful once.
I'm just a big ol' burden!
M-My word...
Golem
Stop right there!
Huh? Butako, easy!
Hey!
You're going off the course!
They just don't give up!
Ugh, what the heck was that?
Move aside, kid!
I get it! You were trying to help Mayone's family!
You asked for it!
You lame scoundrels
picking on the weak! Fight me!
Dettonic Sword!
Dettonic Shield!
Dettonic Sword.
Dettonic Shield.
Not so fast.
Mom!
Dang it!
That's cowardly!
Put your hands up!
Okay!
That's not what I meant!
I said hands, plural!
Okay!
That's not exactly...
What do you want from me then?
Drop your weapons, kid!
Alright... Wait, you too!
Shoot!
Come on...
I don't even have a single gillan on me!
You're broke?
We have no use for him, Golem.
Just dump him wherever.
H-Hey... What are you gonna do?
Man...
Thanks for causing us trouble.
How about we show some gratitude...
Good going, Gob-san!
You saved the day!
Uh-oh...
Whut?
Ouch...
That was awful.
Wait, did Chup just say that
I saved the day?
Did I just do something good?
Thank you very much.
We're safe, thanks to you.
All the credit goes to Butako here...
Huh?
Don't cry, Butako!
So what if you don't get your license?
Maybe you can't fly carrying humans,
but you're still an amazing, heroic dragon!
It's like my grandmother said!
A flightless pig is
A flightless pig is...
Oh, one second.
Wait, can you finish that?
Oh, it's the king!
Chup my boy, Melora has
returned to the castle.
See ya again!
Sure!
Today
The King
Chup my boy, Melora has
returned to the castle.
See ya again!
Sure!
Today
The King
Chup my boy, Melora has
returned to the castle.
See ya again!
Sure!
Today
The King
Chup my boy, Melora has
returned to the castle.
See ya again!
Sure!
Today
The King
Chup my boy, Melora has
returned to the castle.
See ya again!
Sure!
Today
The King
Chup my boy, Melora has
returned to the castle.
See ya again!
Sure!
Today
The King
Chup my boy, Melora has
returned to the castle.
See ya again!
Sure!
Today
The King
Chup my boy, Melora has
returned to the castle.
See ya again!
Sure!
Today
The King
Chup my boy, Melora has
returned to the castle.
See ya again!
Sure!
Today
The King
Chup my boy, Melora has
returned to the castle.
See ya again!
Sure!
Today
The King
Chup my boy, Melora has
returned to the castle.
See ya again!
Sure!
Today
The King
Chup my boy, Melora has
returned to the castle.
See ya again!
Sure!
Today
The King
Chup my boy, Melora has
returned to the castle.
See ya again!
Sure!
Today
The King
Chup my boy, Melora has
returned to the castle.
See ya again!
Sure!
Today
The King
Chup my boy, Melora has
returned to the castle.
See ya again!
Sure!
Today
The King
Chup my boy, Melora has
returned to the castle.
See ya again!
Sure!
Today
The King
Chup my boy, Melora has
returned to the castle.
See ya again!
Sure!
Today
The King
Chup my boy, Melora has
returned to the castle.
See ya again!
Sure!
Today
The King
Chup my boy, Melora has
returned to the castle.
See ya again!
Sure!
Today
The King
Chup my boy, Melora has
returned to the castle.
See ya again!
Sure!
Today
The King
Chup my boy, Melora has
returned to the castle.
See ya again!
Sure!
Today
The King
Chup my boy, Melora has
returned to the castle.
See ya again!
Sure!
Today
The King
Chup my boy, Melora has
returned to the castle.
See ya again!
Sure!
Today
The King
Chup my boy, Melora has
returned to the castle.
See ya again!
Sure!
Today
The King
Chup my boy, Melora has
returned to the castle.
See ya again!
Sure!
Today
The King
Chup my boy, Melora has
returned to the castle.
See ya again!
Sure!
Today
The King
Chup my boy, Melora has
returned to the castle.
See ya again!
Sure!
Today
The King
Chup my boy, Melora has
returned to the castle.
See ya again!
Sure!
Today
The King
Chup my boy, Melora has
returned to the castle.
See ya again!
Sure!
Today
The King
Chup my boy, Melora has
returned to the castle.
See ya again!
Sure!
Today
The King
Chup my boy, Melora has
returned to the castle.
See ya again!
Sure!
Today
The King
Chup my boy, Melora has
returned to the castle.
See ya again!
Sure!
Today
The King
Chup my boy, Melora has
returned to the castle.
See ya again!
Sure!
Today
The King
Chup my boy, Melora has
returned to the castle.
See ya again!
Sure!
Today
The King
Chup my boy, Melora has
returned to the castle.
See ya again!
Sure!
Today
The King
Chup my boy, Melora has
returned to the castle.
See ya again!
Sure!
Today
The King
Yay, sweet!
Sorry, Butako! You handle things here!
Wait! What's a flightless pig?!
You made me curious!!
Alright!
Am I early?
Wait, I'm not the only one
who decided to show up, right?
Sorry I'm late!
Pepperon!
It's fine, you're just on time!
Think they're still selling train lunches?
I'm starving. I need all the food I can get!
You already have plenty, no?
Gob-san? You look like you got hit by a bus!
Where were you?
A man's gotta fight manly battles.
You sound strangely cool.
You guys can't do anything without me.
Yeah, that's not true.
Ow...
Princess Melora!
Crap, it's so dark!
Melora?
Chup!
Do you like my flower arrangement?
It's supposed to represent hope!
Isn't it just full of it?
Y-Yeah, it is!
Right?
It's like my grandmother said!
There's no roses without thorns!
There's no roses
without thorns.
The drag queens after dark
have bearded scorns.
There's no roses
without thorns.
The drag queens after dark
have bearded scorns.
have bearded scorns!
-Tome
Huh? Sorry, I didn't catch that.
It's nothing.
Is something the matter, Chup?
You don't usually visit so late.
Princess, you see, the thing is...
Follow me, Chup!
Huh?
Over here, Chup!
Isn't this place so beautiful?
I didn't know you had a room like this!
Are you dying?
Huh?
I heard it from Daddy.
I have to do it to save the world!
Hmm... That's kinda lame.
Do you really have to die
to save the world?
What? Huh?
Y-Yeah, of course! I have to protect everyone!
Why do you want to protect the world?
Is it for someone? Or for something specific?
Princess Melora...
There's nothing more important than living.
As long as you're alive,
you can put a spin on any situation.
But you can't if you die.
Simple, right?
But if I don't, then you might...
I'll be fine!
Honestly, a world where nothing
happens at all sounds way more boring.
Think, if some sort of overlord showed up,
and everyone had to stand up and fight against it!
Just the idea of putting a spin on that
sounds so fun and exciting to me!
Melora...
I really like you, Melora!
I love you!
So I'll go defeat Vinegar,
and keep you safe forever,
and become one of your bodyguard knights!
Sorry, I only let studs be my knights!
Huh?
It's Mayone...
Shoot! I don't have any time!
See you again, Princess!
Huh?
He's late.
Ugh, what is he doing?
The final train's about to show up!
He couldn't have gotten cold feet, right?
He would do no such thing!
But what else?
Guys!
You got here on Butako?!
You'd get arrested if they caught you!
This girl just got her license!
The dragon flight license is given to those
who can put both technique and bravery to the test.
Her flight technique puts her on thin ice,
but for her bravery, she passes!
Alright! Now we're all together at last!
You can't say that!
We were waiting for you!!
shobokure gao no mobukyara domo ga
On and on these tired old NPCs
iiwake shinagara aruiteru
Keep walking around excusing themselves
itsumo miteiru michisugara
As I took the same old path again
mita koto mo nai wakuwaku wo mita
I found the thrill I've sought for my whole life
itsumade shibonda mama nano
Just how long will I keep drooping around like this?
minikui ahiru no mama nano
How long will I stay an ugly duckling?
ima no reberu wa ichi dakedo
I'm still only level one
ima ni mitero yo sono uchi JUMP UP
But watch me, soon I'll jump up
saikin no wakai mon wa tte
"Why, kids these days..."
toshiyori domo ga boyai teru kedo
...Our old boomers grumble and complain
soro soro omei henjou da
But it's not too late to clear my name
iya ga ou ni mo mattanashi daze
I might not like it, but I can't wait any longer
ketsu no ana kara jetto funsha daaa
I gotta blast free from my cowardly shell!!
ore wa itsuka hana ni naru
Give me time and I'll bloom like a flower
sora ni nobiru hana ni naru
A flower spread out to the sky
kimi ni todoku hana ni naru
The flower that reaches you
Are you all ready?
Vinsant, I'm not going to die.
I'm going to defeat Vinegar
and return to this town!
Same here!
I won't die either!
I haven't had my fill of sexy ladies yet!
You guys never change.
Off we go, then!
Have a safe trip.
Good luck, Butako!
It's like my grandmother said!
A flightless pig is no more than...
The doors are now closing.
W-Wait!
No more than what?!
You made me curious!!
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone!
What are you teaching us about today?
Today's lesson is on Vinegar Palace!
Vinegar Palace
Vinegar Palace is the headquarters
of Vinegar Enterprises,
Vinegar's company,
located in King Oyster City.
It's very heavily-guarded,
and it's said that breaking in
is no easy task!
I'm gonna prove them wrong!
I'll defeat Vinegar,
and take a bath with Melora...
Is that all you care about?!
Next Time
At last, we're storming Vinegar Palace!
And we have one plan:
a frontal assault!
Just you wait, Vinegar!
You're going down!
The Battle at Vinegar Palace!
Will We Serve Justice 1000-Fold?!
Next time: "The Battle at Vinegar Palace!
Will We Serve Justice 1000-Fold?!"
Alright, it's time for a big adventure!