This is Snack World, the hallowed
ground of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam and
people have handy smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
...And my name's Chup.
My village was burnt down by the evil
land-destroying merchant, Vinegar Khan,
and I've embarked on a journey
to get my revenge 1000-fold!
The tickets to King Oyster City, where
Vinegar is, cost 20 million gillan.
So I'm on an adventure searching for
big treasure to make loads of cash!
[Chup humming theme song]
Alright, let's go on another big adventure today!
[Grunts]
I'll fully, flawlessly pour my whole heart and soul into this blow!
Ep. 7: Then, We Knew it All
Grandma, feed me your power!
Number One Fortune Attack!
Just draw your pull already, you're so dramatic.
Special prize, special prize...
"Special Time-Limited Prize!! The Ultimate Moisturizing Cream. Only One Left!"
So Hero Mart's lottery has the Ultimate
Moisturizing Cream as a prize?
Yup, and there's only one left.
Ultimate Moisturizing Cream...
Cream...cream...t-this is it!!
"... Prize"
"5th Prize"
[Shrieks]
I've...been deceived...
Congrats, 5th prize! Fruit knife!
No, no, no, no, no!! I hate fruit knives!!
I don't think we'll be eating this much fruit...
At least our lunches won't be too costly.
Won't you just relax already?
- No, no, no! I don't want it, I don't want it!!
- Congratulations! Special prize: The
Ultimate Moisturizing Cream!
Aaha!
I can't believe I won!
Miss, can I have that? Can I? Can I, please?
No way! This is gonna make me look pretty!
Then maybe my husband will come home soon...
Ohohoho!
Uhh, that's a big waste!
You really don't need it!
Don't say that to her!
She could've at least shared a little!!
My skin's so soft!
It makes your skin soft! The Vinegar-printed
Ultimate Moisturizing Cream!
Almost sold out!
Daddy, are Chup and the others done yet?
Hello, this is the king. So...
Princess Melora, we're here!
Chup, are you working hard with that job of yours?
Uh, yes! That job of mine...
That cream is almost sold out!
Is there at least a way to make it from scratch?
[Gasp] Err...no, I don't think so...
We tried amputating the Kraken, but that didn't really...
Ah, but princess, you don't need
cream to keep your skin smooth!
You're still just a child.
A lady at my age has to keep a hormone balance...
See, it's even starting to look dry and rough here lately...
W-w-w-wh-where exactly?
- Don't you see, it's here!
- Uh, where?
Gyah!
Chup, however you must, please fetch
the raw ingredients from the Kraken.
Before my smooth beauty becomes rough and dry...
I'm on it!
So how exactly are we gonna get the raw ingredients?
The axe failed, magic failed...I doubt
brute force is still in the question.
It sure looked like Melora was starting to get tired of waiting.
T-tired of waiting?!
If we keep them waiting any longer, we
may well be on the chopping block.
The chopping block... no, no, no, no, no...!!
You may never get to visit the princess again.
That can't happen!! [Sobs]
My grandmother once said.
If you can't push, try pulling.
If you can't pull, make a sweet escape!
If you can't push,
try pulling.
If you can't pull,
make a sweet escape.
If you can't push,
try pulling.
If you can't pull,
make a sweet escape.
If you can't push,
try pulling.
If you can't pull,
make a sweet escape.
-Tome
I get it! We can just use going back to bed as our strategy!
We can't just run away.
If we can't use brute force...
We can just go up to the Kraken
and ask for the ingredients!
But the Kraken doesn't speak our language...
W-well...
There's no way you can speak squid to it.
I can sorta speak squid, watch!
We need ink-gredients. We're in deep crud-stacean.
[All stammering]
- This is ridiculous...
- Oink...
Oh, but what if there's another
Monster from the same ocean that can understand it?
Ocean Monster? Wait, that's it!
Mermaid!
Marine! Marine, marine! Marine, marine!
Aah, what the heck? Why so out of the blue?
I was just in the middle of changing!
Huh, you want me to be an interpreter?
Aha, well, you're in luck!
What do you mean?
I've been studying conversational squid a lot lately.
I'm looking to expand my base in the squid country!
Squid country?
I'm going to rise up on the stage in Squiduka, the theater capital of the squid country!
It's a natural dream for an entertainer like me!
B-back to business! Mermaid, we asked if
you could interpret us for the Kraken.
Okay! I'll show you the true, free nature of this idol!
[Chup panting]
Why do these sea Monsters live in the desert anyway...?
I know, right...?
I hear you, man...
Wha- who? Where are you?
- Right here, man.
- Aah!
- Down here, down here!
- Huh?
[Gasping for breath]
Who's this fella?
This here is called the Merman.
But what's it doing here...?
I'm all dry and can't move, man...
Okay, let me help!
Thank you, man!
Merman
I'll be headin' back to my big bro's place, man. Lates!
[Panting]
Tell your bro I said "hi!"
You'd think it'd be easier to walk.
Huh?
When did it get so dark?
- Oink, oink!
- Hm?
What is all that?
A flock of Monsters?
If my memory serves me right, that's a
quite troublesome type of Monster.
Huh?
It's wandering off from the rest!
It must have bumped into one of its comrades.
- [Monster squeals]
- Aah!
Are you alright? Hang in there!
That poor thing. He's separated from the flock now...
Huh? Where did Gob-san go?
Hm?
- Hm?
- Uh...
Whaaat?!
Do I have something stuck on my face?
That's not your face, that's mine!
Wow, Mayone, you're a twin?
What about this situation led you to that conclusion?!
Thanks for thaaaat!
I'm not sure what caused it, but
somehow you turned into me, Gob-san!
- Well, what a predicament!
- Aah, no, no, stop that!!
- Look!
- Gaah, don't point it at me!
Agh, I gotta rip a big one!
Aah, you've gotta resist the urge, please!!
What's this?
Don't worry, Mayone! I'll show you my willpower!
[Gasp]
- Why'd you do that?!
- It had to come out!
Get back here!
Well, which one is which?
I remember now!
That Monster is called Clone!
It has the ability to change people's appearances!
Clone
FLASH!
Oh, I get it.
P-Pepperon?
Hm? What's wrong, guys?
Pepperon's Gob-san now?!
Hm? I was wondering why my body smelled weird.
Oh, I smell like a dad!
Sorry, that's my old man smell.
[Clone laughing]
Come on, turn him back to normal!
Hmm? Hee...
[Both gasp]
FLASH!
[Clone laughing]
My shoulder feels stiff...
My knees are killin' me...
Aw, come on, my butt hurts...this is the worst!
Ha, I'm back to normral!
How do you live with all this, Gob-san?!
It's bringin' me to tears!
- I-it hurts...
- [Clone laughing]
But what's going to happen if we don't turn back?
Simple: You can tune in at this time
next week for The Gob-sans!
- Oink...
-Not the time for that!
Hey, turn us back, you...
[Grunts] My shoulders won't move any higher...
My knees are...ow-ow-ow...
This Monster is surprisingly tough...
This part of the butt might just feel the worst...
- Guys!
- Huh?
Let's attack it on both sides!
We gotcha!
[Quivering]
W-what now?
- Aha!
- Guh...
Sweet, I'm back to normal! You're a good guy, huh!
No, he isn't! He's just making fun of you!
What's that?! Are you...messin' with me?
[Mumbling]
[Grunts]
[Quivering]
Eh, who cares!
Chup, what are you gonna do about our situation?
My stiff shoulders, hip pain, joint pain, bad breath,
old man smell, and mysterious fatigue...
I'm finally free of all of it! Hahaha!
This isn't a good thing!!
For it to only turn Chup back...what a dastardly move...
Let's get it!
Get back here!
Slow down, won't you?!
Oh, of course.
Now I don't know which one's the real Clone.
Hmm...if it's come to this...
- Is it you?!
- That hurt...
- What about you?!
- Ow, that hurts!
Then it must be you!!
Don't you respect your elders?!
[Clone laughing]
Dang it, there's one more! Get back here!
I bet it's you!
No, then what about you?!
It's gotta be you!!
Darn it, I can't be right even once! My lottery luck is awful today.
- You're doing this on purpose, aren't you?
- He is...
- Enough already!
- Ow...
Oh...that's it! It's like my grandmother says!
Misbelief is best blocked! Miss Bella is best blonde!
Misbelief is
best blocked.
Miss Bella is
best blonde.
Misbelief is
best blocked.
Miss Bella is
best blonde.
-Tome
Oink!
Butako! Let's use that combo move we've been training for for this day!
Let's go! Change! Sky Pig Hurricane! Hyah!
Oiiiiink!
W-why...
Hot-hot-hot...so reckless...
But hey, we've been transformed back!
First off...
I got Clone!
It's a treasure chest!
- Nice!
- Oink!
Sweet, I'll take that!
- Nuh-uh!
- What, why?
'Cuz you're just not in luck today!
Huh?
I'm taking this one!
Something good, something good, something good!! Hah!
- Ooh!
- So cool!
Word on the streets in French Toaster is that this
is of the number one brand young girls long for: Peffany!
I'll take this! Hehehe, yay! I've always wanted this!
She really took it for herself without running it by us.
How stingy.
Heeey, Kraaakeeen!
Ohh, here it comes!
W-wait, hold off! We're not here to battle this time!
[Roaring]
[Quivers] Please spare us, please spare us...!!
Kraken, listen to what I have to say.
D'ya think he's still mad about before?
Well then, Mermaid! I'm counting on you!
Marine! Marine, marine! Marine, marine!
Good mooorning! Is it time to get to work?
Mermaid, what are you gonna say to the Kraken?
[Kraken groaning]
"Hey, babies!"
"What'cha got for this Kraken? Yo!" it said.
He's bolder than I expected.
[Groaning]
"Do you have something to say to this Kraken?"
"I'll listen to you, sweeties. Yo!"
He seems very riled up...
We're just wasting time. Well, guess it's my turn, then.
[Mayone shrieks]
"Well, aren't you ugly, yo!"
Grr, what's that?
This doesn't look good.
The Kraken's only really into looks.
The Kraken's a flashy guy, so...
...a stylish, shiny, wild, twisty girl squid would
be the perfect way to get results from him.
It doesn't even have an hourglass figure...
But we don't have a girl squid around here.
That really messes up our plans.
- Oh!
- What's up?
Nah, n-never mind.
How suspicious. You wouldn't
happen to have a good idea, no?
- Yeah.
- Oink.
Huh? Umm...haha...
Hmmmm?
O-okay, fine.
I think the ability from that monster before might work.
But I don't wanna do it.
Oh, you want to use that snack
we recorded back then, of Clone,
and take its power to make you the girl squid, right?
Wait a minute, I was gonna be the one to say that!
So, how about it, Mayone? Wanna be our squid?
I told you I didn't wanna!
I don't wanna be all slimy and smelly
like a squid. Count me out!
You know, we did let her take that Peffany pendant even though we wanted it...
It looked very good on her.
I think that pendant would've looked better on me.
Okay, okay, I get it already!
- Chup, come over here with me.
- Aah!
Hm?
I'll keep him busy!
[Both talking in squid language]
What's Mermaid saying to him?
I wonder.
Alright!
Clone!
A soul, a ghost, a spirit!
[Clone laughing]
Hey, can you turn me into a good-looking girl squid?
[Cheery sounds]
"So, those men before were just paparazzi trying to
get pictures of me... Lying low is tough."
[Laughing]
Sorry to interrupt, but...
We brought a girl who wanted to talk to you today!
[Giggles]
[Screaming]
Did we make it mad?!
Huh?! If we have to do this...
No, hold off a minute.
It said "I'll listen to anything you say!"
I suppose he's pleased, then. It's hard to tell with him.
Mayone, you think you'll be more
popular if you're left a squid?
Aah!
[Laugh]
"It's nice to meet squids of my kind here in the desert!"
"Did you stop living in the sea too?"
Hm, what do you mean?
[Both talking in squid language]
Huh, really?
"I used to live far away..."
...peacefully with my friends and
family in my ocean home.
But because of a factory on a nearby island, the ocean
was polluted, and one-by-one, my friends were, too...
What was once a peaceful ocean became a lethal sea.
"And that's why I'm dwelling in the desert to this day."
"All because of Vinegar Enterprises..."
[Gasps] Vinegar!
"Resort Coming Soon"
You, over there! You, around the back!
[Sobbing]
Mom! Dad!
[Vinegar cackling]
Look, there's still some left!
Live garbage!
Where is everyone?
Oh, the rest of the garbage? It's been taken out.
It's all fresh and clean now.
[Cackling]
[Gasps]
[Sobs] Mom!! Dad!!
[Sobbing]
So he ruined the sea just to make more cash!
I will never forgive him!!
I will surely, definitely, absolutely take him down!!
Chup...
[Groaning]
He says "What is it you want from me, yo?"
We seek moisturizing cream!
[Groaning]
"You want my moisturizing cream?"
"That's one of my super favorite things, yo!"
[Groaning]
Oh, you're that guy from before!
You helped me on my commute, man.
Thanks to you, my big bro didn't get angry, man.
Do you seriously commute to work through the desert every day?
Don't be rude, man.
How majestic...it's like they're starting a sacred ceremony...
Ohh!
What's that? Some sort of portable shrine?
Down and out, o down and out. A bundle of his pleasure
kudareya kudare yorokobi no katamari
Down and out, o down and out. Filling up without mistake
kudareya kudare tsumaru kotonaku
Strooongly, strooongly, strooongly, strongly
mo-ri mo-ri mo-ri mori
- What are they singing?
- Ooh...
Come and bring it forth, on this day today
kyou no hi mo iza ideyo
The time for all his pleasure has come
yorokobi no toki wa kita
[Groaning]
D-don't tell me this is...
[Chanting]
kudareya kudare yorokobi no katamari
Down and out, o down and out. A bundle of his pleasure
Oh, this song must be meant to drown out all other sound.
[Groaning]
kudareya kudare tsumaru kotonaku
Down and out, o down and out. Filling up without mistake
Is this how the Ultimate Moisturizing Cream is made...?
mo-ri mo-ri mo-ri mori
Strooongly, strooongly, strooongly, strongly
For our hearts' sake, please stop this madness!
mo-ri mo-ri mo-ri mori
Come and bring it forth, on this day today
kyou no hi mo iza ideyo
The time for all his pleasure....
yorokobi no toki wa
has come!!
kita
A-a-a-a-a-anyway...
We got the Ultimate Moisturizing Cream!!
Quest
Get the Ultimate Moisturizing Cream
konbini de kuda wo maku ukiyo wo samayou wakoudo yo
All you youngsters loitering about your lives,
shrouding the convenience stores
omaera wa genjitsu ni torinokosaresugi andeddo
You’re like undead who have left behind reality
itsumade son na koto kurikaesu no o-tsu-ka-re
How long are you going to keep doing this?
Don't you get tired of this same old routine?
hashiridase yo ENDLESS ROAD
Run forth through the endless road
koetemiroyo BORDERLINE
Go on past that borderline
sekai wa mugen ni hirogaru kouya
The world is an endless, limitless wilderness
omae no dokyou wo tameshiteiru
Where you can put your courage to the test
sumafo nankaja kensaku dekinai
It’s not something you can search for on your smartphone
sekai wa mugen ni hirogaru PARADISE
The world is an endless, limitless paradise
omaera wa giragira no
Soon you'll come to life taking in the blazing sun
taiyou kuratte ikiteiru
Raws
Translation/Typesetting/Timing
ED Karaoke
QC/Review
Raws
Translation/Typesetting/Timing
ED Karaoke
QC/Review
AnimeLand (BSJ)
Lumpstud
Noroino Hanako
Manjiknights
AnimeLand (BSJ)
Lumpstud
Noroino Hanako
Manjiknights
You did it, Chup, good job!
Huh? Uhh...
What's the matter, Chup? Hurry and give it to the princess.
P-poo...
Thank you, Chup! With this, I'll look beautiful in an instant!
About that, Princess Melora...
I...I'm not so sure you want to use that...
Don't you want to see my bare face became all smooth?
You get to be the first to watch as a reward!
[Groaning]
mo-ri mo-ri mo-ri mori
Strooongly, strooongly, strooongly, strongly
[Screaming]
kyou no hi mo iza ideyo
Come and it bring it forth, on this day today
No need to be so shy!
Wow, so moist! It really sinks into my skin quickly!
yorokobi no toki wa
The time for all his pleasure...
I'm gonna put it on my lips too!
kita
...has come!!
[Screaming]
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone!
What are you teaching us about today?
We're talking about Hero Mart and One-Shot Lotteries today!
"Hero Mart, One-Shot Lotteries"
Hero Mart is the #1 convenience store across the continent.
In their One-Shot Lottery, you can win rare weapons and armor.
You can reach instant fame!
Chup won his Crystal Sword and Mirror Shield in the One-Shot Lottery.
It was difficult.
Well, that's how lotteries can be.
Next Time
We have new orders from Princess Melora!
The man who's the key to us getting
the love potion is Peter Pan!
...Or rather, Peter Panpan?
Next time: Peter Panpan the Super Explorer!
Peter Panpan the Super Explorer
Alright, it's time for a big adventure!