This is Snack World, the hallowed
ground of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam and
people have handy smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
...And my name's Chup.
My village was burnt down by the evil
land-destroying merchant, Vinegar Khan,
and I've embarked on a journey
to get my revenge 1000-fold!
The tickets to King Oyster City, where
Vinegar is, cost 20 million gillan.
So I'm on an adventure searching for
big treasure to make loads of cash!
[Chup humming theme song]
Alright, let's go on another big adventure today!
Ep. 10: New Gen Idols AKZ48
This is the yummiest thing in the world!
You don't seem to mind we just got
clobbered by the Siren Sisters.
Aha, I won a hammer!
"You won: hammer"
Ooh!
Hammers are weapons worth
bragging about, so I should get it!
Okay! I like swords better anyways.
Sweet!
That's not fair.
- Here!
- Huh?
A Blip-Blop Hammer!
[Gob-san and Chup laughing]
- Sucks to be you!
I can't battle with this.
Gahahah, hilarious.
- Calm down a notch!
Ow-ow-how-home...where's home...?
This way, that way, over there...?
- Uh, what's wrong with him?
You think this hammer's effect is
causing confusion on the enemy?
Seems like that!
Mayone, do the thing!
Wake up, would you?!
Ow-ow...
[Groaning] Ugh. What was I doing?
Aha, this is gold! Let me try!
O-oi, stay back!
Here we go~!
[Gob-san squealing]
- Oink!
I'm a bush warbler, chirp-chirp--guh!
Quit acting stupid!
Nice, my turn now!
Hey, I'm not your plaything!
[Groans]
Melora is currently concentrating her mind.
[Grunts]
[Grunting]
"Dear Chup"
Oho, I knew it! She wants the love potion for me!
That's way out of line!
Just look at what she's writing, it's gotta be!
Calligraphy can express one's true thoughts after all.
Princess Melora, even without a love potion,
I wouldn't mind if you told me on the spot.
[Melora grunting]
- You might wanna see that.
"Dear Chup, why are you so useless? -Melora"
Gah...this is bad, Princess Melora's mad at me...
I have to hurry up and get that love potion
so I won't be useless in her eyes,
so she can look at me and think I'm a super-useful guy!
King, tell me how we can get the Siren Sisters to open up!
Hm...Minister, do you know anything?
Uhhuh?? The Siren Sisters were former idols who
went inactive at the height of their popularity.
Huh? Wow, you know quite a lot.
T-that said, if you can get another idol to share
their own plight, they might be sympathetic.
But we don't know any idols...
Oh, would it be alright if I told them about my plight? Haha.
[Gob-san groaning]
- Huh?
Word on the street is that the town girl
idol group AKZ48 is a big deal lately!
I've heard rumors about them!
Let's see, forty-eight is...uh-huh...
A little under 50!
50?! If we surround them with that many idols...
Ohh, this is nerve-racking...one sec, gotta pee!
Oh, uh, me too!
Hey, what's with you two?
[Sighs] This is pointless.
"AKZ48 14th Single - CD Release Concert! 'Little Red Festival vol. 17'"
"Front of the Line" "End of the Line - No Cutting!!"
What's all this?
Looks like they're lined up to buy AKZ48 concert tickets.
This is big! I'm gonna go buy ramen
cups at the convenience store.
And I'll supply us with sleeping bags!
You're preparing to be in line all
night? We're not waiting for this!
I know, but...
[All gasping]
Master Panpan!
Don't stand behind me!! Oh, it's just you guys.
What are you doing here, Peter Panpan?
Aren't you a forest shut-in?
Basically, but I make exceptions for AKZ48.
Whether in a city or across the sea,
I'll go after them wherever!
Huh? So Panpan's a little red riding geek?
Rude, I'm no geek! I'm a serious super-geek!
This is creeping me out.
Master Panpan, I want to talk to AKZ48!
You're quite self-important for a newbie.
You're a newbie too!
The Siren Sisters were former idols that
went inactive at the height of their popularity.
[Groans]
Really? Bye.
Not even pretending to care?
Thing is, we need an idol to speak of their plight
to get the Sisters to open their hearts!
I see!
Good idea. Bye.
So cooperate with us, Panpan!
Then just call me "Master Panpan"!!
Mayone, you'll have to endure this.
Grr...
Please, oh please, help us, Master Panpan.
Hmph. Good with me. Y'see this?
Oink?
What's that?
I can only bring 5 people in as fans.
I have the Gold VIP Platinum membership card!
Well, is it gold or platinum then?!
With this baby, I can go in without taking the line.
Sweet, that's our Master Panpan!
Guh...you wouldn't believe how much this cost me...
Cool, thanks. Let's head on in.
Alright!
Hey, hey! What are you doing?
G-give it back! Give me back my life's purpoooose!!
♪ You best lock up your windows and your doors ♪
"AKZ48's 14th Single - CD Release Concert!
'Dreams and Courage and Little Red Riding Hood'"
AKZ
(Little Red
Riding Hood)
♪ That's what I told my grandmother before ♪
♪ Little Red Riding Hood, she's quite careless (careless!) ♪
This is awesome!
I've never seen a performer up so close before!
I see them all mixing together...
It's 'cuz you're old...but then again,
I can't tell the difference either.
You must have some incredible VIP card
if we can watch the show rehearsal!
So, how long will rehearsal last?
Right now, they're doing their last review on the live version
of their 13th single, "Careless Little Red Riding Hood."
They're only doing a check on their main points,
so it shouldn't be more than 2 minutes.
Gee, Master Panpan, you really know everything, huh?
Of course, 'cuz I'm a serious super-geek!
So you went from knowing nothing about the
forest to knowing everything about idols...
Oh, they're finished.
[AKZ48 laughing]
Oh, Master Panpan!
Good to see you here today, Master!
It's only natural I never miss a day.
Hehe, thank you very mu-choochoo!
And to you too, choochoo!
What kind of exchange is this...?
It's like some sort of routine.
Hey, girls, do you think you can help
us out by sharing your idol plights?
- Huh?
- They're ignoring us?
Why the hell would you ask like that?!
Listen to me: go "choochoo!"
Wait, we have to do that?!
What are you so ashamed about?
Get rid of your puny pride!
No, it seems normal to be embarrassed.
U-understood, Master Panpan! AKZ48, all of you!
Please share your idol plights with us, choochoo!
[All clamoring] - I can help! - I can help!
W-wait a minute, one at a time!
I can't hear any of you. Chup, one more time.
Y-you want me to do that again?!
We'd like it if you could please share
your idol plights with us...choochoo!
I became an idol when I was just a little girl...
Not all at once, stop it!
All 48 of them have the same highlights...
Ugh, this isn't going anywhere. Panpan,
just a pick a girl that looks good.
If you must, then leave it to the master.
Well then, my favorite - number 11, Miss Hinano!
You had the best solo part in last month's
Little Red Festival ... choochoo!
Okay! Thank you, Master Panpan!
Your part was godlike, as if you were
an angel descending to the ground!
Thanks for your words. Hurry, Chup!
Miss Hinano! Do you have any stories
of struggles as an idol, choochoo?
Hmm... Well, since my friends all applied,
I took an audition to get recruited myself.
I guess when I came to, I was singing in the dome?
Nice.
A quick success story indeed.
But there was no struggle! Panpan,
are there any other good ones?
Hmph, fine. Number 24 - Miss Nozomi.
Okay! I was scouted on the way home from school,
and I started to become a member.
When I came to, I was singing in the dome!
Super-amazing!
What's with the "singing in the dome" nonsense?
Hasn't anyone here struggled? Come on, next!
Tch...they must need whoever had the
hardest time getting on their feet...
Our initial member, number 1 - Miss Emily!
Okay! I entered through a magazine advertisement I saw.
When I came to, I was singing...
That's enough! No more of this!
All of these stories are the same!
I wanna hear about your hardships in the world!!
Everyone listen!
Haven't any of you struggled as an idol?
[Murmuring]
Of course, there has to be at least ONE person with plights...
So, haven't any of you struggled as an idol?!
Brrt!!
Not like that! Use your words!!
So, uh, we have a concert to get to after this.
Can you please direct your inquiries to our manager then?
Grr, what's with this attitude?
Their CDs will be flying off the shelves in a moment.
See you later, Master Panpan! Choochoo!
Choochoo!
Hey, I think someone dropped their shoe!
Huh? Aah!
Oh, that's mine!
Aaah!
Huh, you seem a bit clumsy, don't you? Huh?
[Gasping]
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
She's so precious...
She must be the "clumsy girl" of
the group they can't get rid of.
They always appeal to the men's hearts.
Goodness, those boys...
Ow-ow-ow...I did it again...
Who are you?
Um, uh, number 48 - Akami.
Akami
Master Panpan, do you know her?
Of course!
There was a mix-up and we had a vacant spot open,
so Akami joined as our last member.
There's the struggle! She's not just a good girl.
So, what was the mix-up?
On my way to the audition, I
tripped on the stairs and fainted.
And when I came to, I was losing time,
so I rushed to the audition hall, and ended up
in an interview hall for a security guard job.
A tragedy gone down in the history of idols...
To end up in the wrong place, it's such a sad, sad pity...
Aren't you guys being a little mean now?
They're way too caught up with the "clumsy girl."
But anyway, why did you become an idol?
I was given the job, and ended up
being a security guard for a concert.
So you still took the job interview?
Whatever it took, I wanted to be close to AKZ48,
even if I had to keep the job for a long time.
A spot opened up just before their major debut,
so they took me on as a member.
Makes me cry every time.
That much? I mean, it's a pretty good story, but...
Don't you have something more hard-hitting?
Like, you couldn't sing and the others made fun of you,
or you spent three days overtime
without food practicing choreography?
[Groans]
Huh?! That's just cruel!!
She hasn't said anything yet...
Not that much, really. While I managed to get in,
I can't sing or dance, and I'm always holding everyone back.
Sometimes I wonder if I'm really an idol.
I've tried to quit countless times...
I can't give up...wah-wah-wah...
Hey, what's with that? That's really awful fake crying!
[Boys sobbing]
- Miss Akami!!
- You can't give up!!
They completely give in.
So, if you've got the natural talent of being unable to be let go,
then we might just be able to get the Siren Sisters' attention.
Miss Akami, do you mind?
Could you please tell the Siren Sisters your story?
Huh, the Siren Sisters? Will that really be okay for me?
I can't help but be clumsy when I'm nervous...
It'll be alright! You just need to
get them to chase their dreams.
Right, that courage is the definition of an idol.
I'll tell you one thing, kid.
What is it, Master Panpan?
Miss Akami is my new favorite!
Aha, I'm glad! Choochoo~
Choochoo!
That really ruins the mood of the confession.
Alright, with Miss Akami on our side,
the Siren Sisters are going down!
Huh? Where's Panpan?
He stayed behind to watch the concert.
What? Even though he said he was Akami's fan,
he still wiggled out of going to
see the scary Siren Sisters again.
No, Master Panpan's not like that!
How is it you still look up to this guy?
[Akami shrieking]
- Huh?
Aah! Bug, bug, bug!!
Miss Akami, calm down!
Don't you think she's overreacting just a bit?
What an idol she is.
[Mayone shrieking]
- Huh?
Aah, spider, spider, sticky, aagh!
What are you staring for? Someone help me out!
Guess I better...uh.
Huh, when was there a puddle here?
You're stepping on me...you should be more careful...
Slime
Oh...sorry.
Huh, what's that? A Monster?
It's Slime.
He's good battle practice for inexperienced adventures.
One famous Monster, that one.
Has Slime always looked like that?
Are you really Slime?
Yes, I'm Slime.
But your head isn't pointy.
No, but it is! [Grunting]
- Oh...
- Oink...
[Grunting]
Maybe he's like...a novice Slime who
yearns to be the famous one?
Seems like that.
He's like me...how sad...
Stop feeling bad for me, that hurts me the most.
I'm already a grown-up Slime!
[Grunts, withers]
That's not gonna work out...Chup, do something!
If I gotta...
- Oink...
[Grunts]
A little more...mhm, mhm...uhh, a bit much...
Ahaha, now you just look like a stick.
Pepperon, can you shape his sides?
Got it!
[Grunts]
That's it, I can see it!
[Grunting]
Okay, we're gonna let go!
He did it!
Aha!
[Withers]
Oh no...
There's a long way to go for him.
But Slime is the weakest Monster of all.
It's a bit sad he can't even become that.
But we'll be supporting you all the way!
Don't give up! You'll become a full-grown Slime eventually!
Your sympathy is weak.
It's humiliating to be a Monster with the enemy rooting for you.
Then what if give you a fight?
But he's so precious!
I want you to fight and defeat me! Defeat me or else!
What kind of Monster asks to be defeated...?
In the Slime Industry, if you're defeated 2000 times,
you'll apparently be metalized.
If that happens to me, I'll carry tens of times more EXP!
Really?
If I can gain a lot of EXP,
no one will be able to look away!
So do your worst, I'm ready!
As you wish!
Crystal Sword!
Crystal Sword.
[Grunts]
Hey, just a minute. I'm going to pretend to kill you.
Can you play along?
Hm? Okay!
What are they murmuring about?
I wonder?
Take this, Slime!
[Grunt]
Slime, You're Done For Slash!
Aah...I'm done for!
What's this charade?
Were they arranging that before?
- Aah, don't do that!
That poor, poor Slime!
Agh!
[Slime shrieks]
- Uh...
He was just playing dead, but now he's real dead.
W-what? Oh dear, I'm sorry...
What an awfully sad ending...
It's like my grandmother said!
Fall seven times, get up eight.
Fall seven times,
get up eight.
Fall eight times,
get up nine...
Fall seven times,
get up eight.
Fall eight times,
get up nine...
Fall eight times, get up nine...
-Tome
How long does that go on?!
Slime, keep on growing!
[Groaning]
A treasure chest!
Heave-ho!
A brooch pin from Qloris!
Neat! The item we got outta that
Slime is a bang for our buck!
Don't say it like that!
You can have this, Miss Akami!
I could never!
With this brooch pin, you'll have 100x courage!
Hm? Does Qloris' brooch pin really have that ability?
Of course! You can boost your courage
many times over if you believe!
Now you can talk to the Siren
Sisters without getting nervous!
Thank you! I'll do my best!
[Singing]
I am Si.
And I am Ren.
Together, we're...
♪ Siren Sisters~ ♪
Tch... so you're the Siren Sisters!!
This is the THIRD time already!
Today, we brought a friend!
A friend?
What are you talking about?
Miss Akami!
Uh...
This young girl is your friend?
Make this quick, won't you?
I...I'm...the...
Miss Akami, you can do it!
I'm the 48th member of AKZ48, Akami!
Who are they?
Aren't they those idols we've seen about lately?
I've heard that you Siren Sisters used to be idols in the past.
I too dreamed of being an idol.
I'm small, not very cute, and very clumsy.
But despite that, I yearned to be an idol!
Okay.
And?
Of course, the others didn't like
me and I had to practice alone.
I auditioned without telling anyone.
I was rejected, left in worry and shock.
Days went by where I didn't eat.
But that's just what I said.
Don't bring it up now.
I wanted to be alongside the idols!
I worked as a security guard for their concerts!
I always listened to their songs behind me
while watching over the customers.
My, that's not easy to pull off.
The Siren Sisters are listening to her!
They must be starting to open to forgiveness!
Then a vacant spot suddenly opened
up and I became a member.
I'm still not good at singing or dancing.
I keep inconveniencing others.
But I'm working my darndest towards my dream!
You're doing it, Miss Akami!
Now, when I think about how I fell going
to my audition, I'm really thankful.
I think I'm working hard now thanks to that setback.
You struggled, but you're chasing your dreams?
You're young, yet remarkable.
Good work, Miss Akami!
What a touching story!
They're resonating with her!
Oh, the fog's clearing up!
Siren Sisters, what made you give up your dreams so easily?
Try to remember how you felt when you were young!
[Gasping]
When we were young?
Are you saying we're not young?
Oh dear, what did that girl just blurt out?
Although you're surely getting old,
wouldn't you say there's an appeal for your withering?
Like when meat is most delicious when it's half-rotten!
Tch...half-rotten?
T-this is bad...
Huh? Why are you getting angry?
Won't you get wrinkly if you're angry?
What?!
Don't you value your life in the slightest?
We were so close...
Wait!
Huh? You brought all of them with you?
Let's do this!
- Okay!
Siren Sisters, let's work hard together!
I'm sure you still can!
That's right, you can't give up, even if you're old ladies!
[Gasp]
- Old ladies?
Uhh...what are they doing?
This won't end well.
Don't give up just cuz you're old!
Chase your dreams, even though you're old!
There's always tomorrow, even though you're old!
"Though we're old..."
"Though we're old...?"
♪ "Though we're o-o-old?!"
[Panpan shrieking]
[AKZ48 shrieking]
[Screaming]
konbini de kuda wo maku ukiyo wo samayou wakoudo yo
All you youngsters loitering about your lives,
shrouding the convenience stores
omaera wa genjitsu ni torinokosaresugi andeddo
You’re like undead who have left behind reality
itsumade son na koto kurikaesu no o-tsu-ka-re
How long are you going to keep doing this?
Don't you get tired of this same old routine?
hashiridase yo ENDLESS ROAD
Run forth through the endless road
koetemiroyo BORDERLINE
Go on past that borderline
sekai wa mugen ni hirogaru kouya
The world is an endless, limitless wilderness
omae no dokyou wo tameshiteiru
Where you can put your courage to the test
sumafo nankaja kensaku dekinai
It’s not something you can search for on your smartphone
sekai wa mugen ni hirogaru PARADISE
The world is an endless, limitless paradise
omaera wa giragira no
Soon you'll come to life taking in the blazing sun
taiyou kuratte ikiteiru
Raws
Translation/Typesetting/Timing
ED Karaoke
QC/Review
Raws
Translation/Typesetting/Timing
ED Karaoke
QC/Review
AnimeLand (BSJ)
Lumpstud
Noroino Hanako
NeSubs
(Specter Subs)
AnimeLand (BSJ)
Lumpstud
Noroino Hanako
NeSubs
(Specter Subs)
A few weeks later...
"AKZ48's 14th Single: 'Dreams and Courage and Little Red Riding Hood'"
AKZ48's new song is out!
And Akami's up-front too!
Unlike before, she looks so full of self-confidence now!
Qloris' brooch pin...
Yeah!
You can boost your courage 100x if you believe!
Don't give up, and your dreams will come true!
It's just like you said!
Hm?
- What the?
Master Panpan?
Guh, you guys...
What are you doing, unashamedly stealing that?
I'm not stealing!
I'm going to exhibit it at the Magnificent Panpan Museum!
I'm showing them my honor!
Gah, hey, wait!
All you're doing is committing a crime, get back here!
Do you really need it that much?!
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone.
What are you teaching us about today?
Today, we're talking about No Brand.
"No Brand"
Equipment not brand-made is called No Brand.
The kids like to call it "no bra."
They're not always very high-quality,
but for most equipment, looks can be deceiving.
Ooh, that's interesting!
The paper-fan sword and blip-blop hammer
are both No Brand weapons.
Next Time
We're finally coming to a conclusion!
Even the scary Siren Sisters were
too weak for loved ones?
And huh, that guy used to be their boyfriend?!
Next time, "The Sirens' Life-Risking Love!"
The Sirens' Life-Risking Love
Alright, it's time for a big adventure!