This is Snack World, the hallowed ground
of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam
and people have handy smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
And my name's Chup!
After a long battle,
I've finally defeated the evil merchant Vinegar Khan,
and now I'm moving towards a new goal!
Whatever perils await me,
I'll fully, flawlessly overcome them!
Alright, let's go on another big adventure today!
Episode 46: Hang in There, Brave Robin Hood!
I'm home, Daddy!
Welcome back, my Melora!
Where were you?
I was worried sick!
Your majesty, we've retrieved
Melora's panties from Scardon!
Well done! That's marvelous, Chup!
QUEST: TAKE BACK THE PRINCESS'S PANTIES
I've already got them on!
Wh-When'd you do that, Princess?
What are you getting aroused for?
Even so, it's quite contumelious
for someone to steal my Melora's panties.
Yeah! I wish that were...
I mean, that scoundrel!
Chup, I hereby order you
to vanquish Scardon!
Aye! I will fully, flawlessly
defeat Scardon!
He didn't even want to get rid
of Scardon at first.
Now he's all energized!
Although...
did you manage to land
any blows on Scardon?
Well, he's a lot stronger than us,
that's for sure.
Daddy, can't you do something?
Hmm, perhaps...
Oh, Minister!
Could this be a new weapon
we can use to defeat Scardon?
Awesome!
Can I open it up?
You may.
Wait, what?
What's this paper, your majesty?
A permit to the royal archives.
The royal archives?
The royal archives are like a library
with every single book
that has been written
since this kingdom was establlished.
There should be some clues in there
on how to defeat Scardon.
Way to go, Daddy!
That's a good king.
Look at this place!
I've heard about these archives.
I'm coming for you!
Come back here, Butako!
Chup, this is a library!
You have to keep your voice down!
Come on, look at the size of this place!
What's the matter, Chup?
Seeing so many books...
makes me need to pee!
Agh, I know the feeling!
Getting the urge
when I'm surrounded by books...
Come on, you're just imagining things!
You can hold it in.
I can't, I'll wet myself!
What's all the buzzing?
Is it the "Chup wet himself" alarm?
Disturbance Level A.
Distrubance Level A.
Eliminating disturbance.
Aah, I can't take it! I'm gonna...
What's that?
Some sort of defense robot
against loud noises?
Sounds annoying.
That was close.
There's too many books in here.
We'll have to split up and search.
Alright!
The Right-Hander's Guide
to Cleaning Your Left Ear?
Oh yeah, doing that alone
is pretty tricky.
Is this book really in demand?
Look! Snow White's Fortunes!
Let's read it!
What's this say?
"First-run edition..."
"With a kiss mark from the author?"
Blegh...
Dang it!
Disturbance Level A.
Eliminating disturbance.
Freeze.
Hey, be nice to the elderly!
No more distractions.
We have to search!
Hm? Oh, my word!
The Hot Actresses of Yesteryear Photobook!
D-Don't tell me...
Disturbance Level A.
Eliminating disturbance.
I get it, you can stop chasing me!
Oh my goodness!
Doors All Over the World!
Oh wow! That door is so beautiful!
Shoot.
Disturbance Level A.
Eliminating disturbance.
I could've sworn Sir Laozi
said that was his weak spot...
Huh? What's that book?!
Did you finally find
a clue on beating Scardon?
Melora Photobook!
Take this seriously!
I thought I had all
the photos of Melora out there,
but I was wrong!
Maybe there's some ultra-rare
gemstones in here!
Every single page is just
the king playing with Shibuchin!
Perhaps it's not photos
of Princess Melora,
but photos that she took.
Man...
How to Warp?
C-Could it be? It's a book by Darefalcon
on how to warp!
Whoa, what's that about?
Do you suppose this book
can make us warp too?
So cool! I wanna warp!
I'll give it a read.
Let's see here.
"Today, I warped to the beach."
"Nothing beats fish in season."
"Today, I warped to the foot
of Gratinia Volcano."
"I knew there'd be a hot spring there,
and it was heavenly."
What the heck?
There's no guide in here...
It's just him bragging about
all the places he's warped!
Of course old Warp-pa
would try to make easy money with a scam!
Lame.
If all the books in here are like this,
I can't imagine there's any books
with how to defeat Scardon.
Now, Mayone.
Don't you think that would be too conven—
I-I found one!
It's even called How to Defeat Scardon!
Whaaat?!
Seems this book was written
by the very man who took down Scardon.
He must've been a real mighty warrior!
There's finally a glimmer of hope.
So? What's it say?
How do we beat Scardon?
I'll read it out loud,
so listen very carefully!
Wh-What in the world?!
The pages have been ripped clean out!
What?!
You're kidding...
I have an idea! Why don't we meet
the author face-to-face and ask him?
Well, we do still have the cover.
Hmm, the author is Robin Hood
from Sherwood Forest.
Robin Hood?
But this book was written 150 years ago.
The author probably left
our world long ago.
Aw, man!
But maybe he has a descendant
who knows something!
Good point! We got to work
with the fifth Goemon, too!
We'll figure something out
once we get to Sherwood Forest!
Hopefully!
Oh, we'll figure it out!
Yet we've been walking
for hours now!
Why do you keep jumping the gun?
Sorry, sorry.
But don't we gotta keep things trucking
in times like these?
Hey!!
Where is Sherwood Forest,
home to Robin Hood?!
Robin Hood?!
Huh? That sounds familiar...
We meet again.
"We meet again?"
You're just gonna ignore all that?
Master, are you alright?
I'll save you!
Don't do it!
This is part of a roleplay
between me and Candoll.
You're even cool when you're tied up!
I'm pretty sure he told me
he was of the fifth generation.
Robin Hood is both my arch-rival
and a close chum of mine.
An arch-rival and a chum...?
Ah, like the kind of friendship
that bloomed after a good battle?
Nah, we're just fellow idol geeks.
I'm into AKZ48,
he's into Mermaid.
What does he see in her?
We're always debating over them.
You're arch-rivals over idols?
That sounds pointless.
Here's the entrance
to Sherwood Forest.
I know this! It's Mermaid's song,
Desert or Sea? Don't Matter to Me!,
a single from her second album,
Green Coelacanth!
That sound quality sucks.
What a disservice to such a great song.
Robin Hood
Panpan, by what odds
are you playing a Mermaid song?
It's the only way to get you
to show yourself.
I remain unwavering
as an AKZ48 fan!
I don't know what you see in those
lip-syncing, money-hungry idols.
It just makes no sense.
Say that again.
The way those young, blossoming girls
shine in the center of the stage!
You just don't get it!
Alright! That's enough of your
unproductive idol debate!
I don't know what came over me.
That's the descendant
of the man who defeated Scardon?
He just seems like another idol geek.
Hey, do you know Scardon?
Scardon?
I've never heard of an idol group
by that name.
He's a ferocious monster
leading our world to ruin!
We were hoping you could
help us defeat him.
Forget it. Let's give up.
Hm? You guys are looking down on me
because you think I'm weak, aren't you?
Uh, to be frank, yeah.
Okay then. I'll show you
what I'm really capable of.
Robin Hood! Don't tell me
you're going to show them that?
Show us what?
Shing!
The mushroom made him grow!
Am I crazy, or have I seen this before?
Does the sky call to me?
Does the ground spring to me?
I'm the envoy of the forest,
Robin Hood!
Hi-yah!
Whoa, what's going on?
Dang, he's strong!
Justice always prevails!
He's like a totally different person.
Chup! You gotta test his ability.
Yeah! I'll give him some monsters to fight.
We'll start small.
Yeti!
A soul, a ghost, a Spirit!
So cold!
Who goes there?
Yeti! Make Robin Hood shiver
with your blizzard!
You can't just put me on the spot like this!
I'm so scawed!!
So cold...
Why's he making us shiver?
I'll give you...
my Robin Arch Hurricane!
Great! Next one's gonna be tougher!
Andead!
Undead-dead-dead-deaddy-dead!
Undead-deaddy-dead! Undead!
Hey, here I am!
Andead, give Robin Hood the runs
with some of your poison ohagi!
I'll do it in a jiffy!
I made some new ohagi
for just this occasion!
Nice, that's promising!
Have a taste of my
Black Mold Ohagi Attack!
Huh? It looks like anko,
but it's mold?!
Blegh...
That should give him diarrhea for sure!
Robin Stomach!
He took it like a champ!
I've had my fair share
of poison mushrooms.
It's given me an immunity to poisons!
Whaaat?!
Andead couldn't get him either?
Alright, next one!
Werewolf!
Fightin', fight, fightin', fight
Fightin', fight, fight Fighter
It's been a while since we've last spoke.
This is just some man!
Don't poke fun at me, now!
He may look like an ordinary man,
but when he transforms under a full moon,
he's super strong!
Chup, search up something round!
Huh? Things round like the moon...
I can't think of anything...
so here's an image of the moon!
Here we go!
That's all it takes?!
We should've been doing that
this whole time!
Here I come!
You're unharmed by my attacks?
Your feeble blows...
have no effect on my Robin Body!
Awesome!
I shall go next.
Prepare to face my special attack!
A bow under his armpit?
How's he going to use it?
Is he sucking up his bodily aura?
Why out of his armpit?!
Take this! Robin Pit Arrow!
Hm? What was I doing?
You even took down Werewolf!
You're the real deal!
No wonder, you're the descendant
of the man who defeated Scardon!
He might even be able to defeat Scardon
with that special attack.
Gob-san, what'cha up to?
You think I'll get stronger
by eating a mushroom too?
Blegh... tastes awful.
That's gross, y'know that?
I tried that too once.
But Robin Hood's the only one
who can react to it.
Yep!
Robin Hood! We need you
to help us take out Scardon!
Scardon? I never thought
I'd hear that name again.
Has the one that I defeated
come back to life?
The one you defeated?
It seems like when he transforms
from mushrooms,
he turns into his ancestor
that defeated Scardon.
Hm? My mushroom power
is wearing off.
Until we meet again!
My ancestor defeated Scardon
and saved the world?
You had no idea?
Nope.
And whenever you eat mushrooms,
you become that ancestor!
Wait, I do?
I knew I got stronger
when I ate mushrooms,
but I never remembered it.
Seems like your ancestor
was a really strong hero!
Come to think of it,
a treasure chest has been passed down in my family
as a memento of the original Robin Hood.
I'll go get it.
Here it is.
What's inside?
Treasure, perhaps?
My word! These must be
the rarest of rare items—
legendary weapons used by
ancient adventurers,
said to have the power
to change one's destiny:
Legacy!
The sword every warrior strives to have,
the Grand Seal,
and the Lunar Shield.
And lastly, a bow:
the Bound Arch!
Wowzers!
Please help yourselves
to the sword and shield.
Wait, really?!
I'll use the bow.
After all, if I don't help you all
save the world,
I won't get to hear Mermaid's next song.
Sweet! We got a mighty weapon!
I see you've made yourselves
a powerful ally.
Warp-pa!
I'm ready to bring you to
Scardon anytime.
Huh? I thought you couldn't
warp places you've never been.
Truth be told, when you all
broke into Demi-Glace Castle...
I was hiding aboard the airship.
You really lock in
when working on your warps!
Wow, amazing.
You're basically a full-on
warpineer now!
It hit me that warping
is what I was born to do!
All of our begging made you
reach enlightenment?
So we can get to Scardon
in an instant!
It's like my grandmother said!
Warps last a moment,
but a wife lasts forever!
but a wife lasts forever.
Warps last a moment,
-Tome
So you're saying when I get married,
I should cherish her for life?
How romantic!
...Wait, what does that have
to do with anything?
Now, off we go!
Dragon Warp!
Thanks for the warp,
but maybe not so close up!
Grand Seal!
Lunar Shield!
Legacy.
Grand Seal.
Lunar Shield.
Did my ancestor really defeat
such a beast?
Mr. Robin Hood!
Have a mushroom
Gob-san picked!
Does the sky call to me?
Does the ground spring to me?
I'm the envoy of the forest, Robin Hood!
Look at that, he took the hit
like it was nothing!
Robin Hood might just
be able to beat him!
Alright, Vinsant!
Yeah.
Foolish humans.
Finally showing me a real fight.
He's talking to us
telepathically again!
All three of you, come get me!
Chup and I will attack him
from both sides.
Robin Hood, you strike him head-on.
Alright!
Understood.
Now, Robin Hood!
Wait, what?!
Why'd he turn back to normal now?!
Don't worry!
I may have failed miserably before...
but prepare yourself, Scardon!
You're a funny one.
Do you really think a bow like that
will work on me?
Here comes his special attack!
Not just that, but with the Bound Arch
his ancestor passed down!
Take this! Robin Pit Arrow!
He did it!
Sweet!
You insolent...
It's working!
Is it just me, or are your powers
wearing off much quicker?
Here's another!
Do the skies call for me?
Does the ground spring for me?
I'm the envo—
You don't need to introduce yourself!!
His mushroom power is cutting off
even quicker than before!
It wore off instantly that time!
This is getting us nowhere!
Robin, go run towards Scardon!
Pepperon, throw all of the mushrooms at him!
I'm on it!
Understood!
Come at me, foolish human!
Take this!
Robin Punch!
Huh?
Oh no, there's no more mushrooms!
Oh, I have one more!
Robin, have this mushroom!
Wait, what? Huh?!
No-no-no!
Dang it.
Is it over already? That's just sad.
nee kimi doko kara kita no?
Where are you from?
ima boku hima shiten dakedo
I've got time to spare
ochashite morae masenka?
Can I pour you some tea?
dame? dame? doushite desuka
No, you say? What's wrong?
jinsei wa rooringu sutoon
Life is like a rolling stone
tamaru konbini bukuro
Shopping bags piling up
seishun wa kumori zora
Youth is like a dark cloudy sky
sumafo izonshou sa
They're all glued to their phones
donzoko demo iijan
So what if we've hit rock bottom
ki ni shinakute iijan
Don't get so hung up on it
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
tabetara kateru kamojan
Maybe it'll help us get this katsu-done
dame dame demo iijan
But if it won't? Oh well
doutte koto neejan
Don't worry 'bout it
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
megezu ni ikouze
And keep moving forward
charanporan de iijan
Maybe we're kinda sloppy
muchakucha de iijan
And sure we're kinda reckless
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
tabetara kateru kamojan
Maybe it'll help us get this katsu-done
masshigura de iijan
So let's go full speed
tsuki susumeba iijan
And keep pushing onwards
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
tokoton yarouze
And see our goals all the way through
nee kimi doko kara kita no?
Where are you from?
ima boku hima shiten dakedo
I've got time to spare
Why don't we eat KATSUDON?
That was a close call.
Warp-pa!
Thank you.
I wasn't expecting the mushrooms
to get less and less helpful.
Eating that last one
didn't even give him that power boost.
It actually tasted pretty weird.
Oh, that was stuck to my loincloth.
Huh?
Apologies for the interruption. Snack World will be back momentarily.
Be right back
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone!
What are you teaching us about today?
Today's lesson is on Legacy!
Legacy
Legacy are extremely rare equipment
made by ancient people
in an advanced civilization.
They're rarely sold in stores,
so you can usually find them
deep in dungeons.
Dang, you make them sound super rare!
Yeah, because they are rare!
Extremely so!
So you better take good care of it.
Next Time
Why aren't we getting
any readings on Scardon?
Where could our enemy have gone?
Suddenly, we're greeted by two shady...kids?!
Next time: "Scardon Vanishes."
Scardon Vanishes
Alright, it's time for a big adventure!