This is Snack World, the hallowed ground
of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam
and people have handy smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
And my name's Chup!
After a long battle,
I've finally defeated the evil merchant Vinegar Khan,
and now I'm moving towards a new goal!
Whatever perils await me,
I'll fully, flawlessly overcome them!
Alright, let's go on another big adventure today!
Episode 38: Vinsant Puts Up a Brave Fight
You all fought very well.
Thank you, Darefalcon!
We wouldn't have made it
without your assistance.
Oh, yeah!
I better go home
and tell Melora all about it!
Princess Melora!
Chup sure seems happy!
Wait for me, I'm on my way!
No wonder! He finally took down Vinegar!
He must feel as free as a bird!
So.
It looks like you're not a ghost
anymore, no, Darefalcon?
Hm? Well, you see...
The Dragon Heart?
Huh? I thought the one Vinegar had
was a fake!
Indeed it was...
Well, here's the thing. I tried it on,
and it fit my size pretty well,
and, well, it allowed me to
materialize, or something.
Really?
My word!
That's nice! Good for you!
However, since it's a fake,
my abilities aren't up to snuff.
For example, I'm able to materialize,
levitate,
and Dragon Warp,
but I can't perform
intense combat,
nor become a dragon.
Can you still make
hot spring eggs with exquisite texture
and plump omelettes?
The answer to that...
Gulp...
...is yes!
What a relief.
I'd hate to cause you all trouble...
It's no biggie! You can still Dragon Warp,
and that's good enough!
Yeah, since he can use it
to take us back to French Toaster!
I'm sorry?
Oh, bless you!
Now, we'll be known as the heroes
of French Toaster!
Despite it all, we managed
to put Vinegar in his place!
Do you think they're putting up
a parade in our honor?
My Dragon Warp is "good enough?"
Alright, Darefalcon! Zip us away!
Zip to it!
"Zip" you?
Sweet, it's the castle!
I gotta go see Melora!
You wait here, Darefalcon!
I'm sorry?
I'll need you to warp me home too!
And I could use a trip to Fretaya!
I'm gonna stuff down their new
demi-glace salisbury beef bowl until it kills me!
I'd appreciate you taking me
to the spicy club!
I call dibs on first!
Darefalcon's warping away!
Goodbye! Dragon Warp!
Hey!
He got away.
Man. There goes my ride.
Dat-da-da-da!
Aha! You registered his Snack!
Good going, Chup!
Now we can call on him
whenever we need him!
Now, castle time!
We apologize, Sir Chup,
but his majesty is busy at the moment.
Please come back later.
Whaaat?!
What is the meaning of this?!
What do you mean
you don't have weapons?!
I'm terribly sorry.
It's just how it is!
They've stopped supplying them.
Forget it! I'll take my business elsewhere.
Thank you for shopping with us!
Mr. Carbonara!
It's you, Chup!
Man, that was one angry customer.
It's that darn Vinehman Crisis.
Vinehman what?
Haven't you seen the news?
We've been pretty tied up as of late.
Vinegar Khan suddenly passed away,
and Vinegar Enterprises stopped all business.
Now the global economy is in turmoil.
Distribution dropped too!
Distribution... dropped?
It's the process of goods becoming
available to buy in stores.
Huh?
Since your intellect is level F,
I'll explain it in a way you'll understand.
You won't get your letters
if there's no mailman.
I see!
That explains why they don't
have any products.
That's rough!
"Rough" doesn't even begin to cover it.
I might have to throw in the towel.
How could things have possibly
gotten this bad?
Um, well...
It's the king!
You've returned at last, Chup!
I heard you visited earlier.
I apologize. Things have been awful busy as of late.
I-I see.
What's with the glum faces?
Did something happen?
Princess Melora...
Did... Did we do the right thing?
After all it took to defeat Vinegar,
it seems the world's suffering from it.
Without me, the world's economy
will collapse.
Soon you will recognize
the grave crime you have committed.
I'm scared.
Did we mess up big-time?
Say you knew this would happen,
would you have backed down?
Would you have given up?
I think you would have gone after him,
even if the world despised you for it.
Am I wrong?
Don't worry about the past.
Focus on the future, okay?
So you can see for yourself
what happens because of your choice!
I get it.
Thank you, Princess Melora!
M'kay, Daddy will fill you in on the rest!
Huh?
On what?
Well, you see...
The king predicted that the world economy
would collapse following Vinegar's passing.
Whoa, nice!
Indeed! And so...
He held meeting after meeting
with the rulers of other regions
in order to establish new global economic laws
that would allow the economy
to run smoothly without Vinegar Enterprises!
New global economic laws?
I don't follow, but it sounds big!
Indeed it is!
But the one who suggested
we make these laws...
Oh, Daddy! You know when to get things done!
You were really prepared for this!
You're finally looking like a real king!
We will soon announce these new laws
to the world,
and with time, the economy
and the people will return to normal.
Th...That's great!
You are all free to go out
and follow your hearts!
Yes, your majesty!
Sweet! Alright, guys!
Let's split!
Yeah!
No reaction on the Dragon GPS...
It can't be...
Are you fretting over Scardon's resurrection?
Sir Darefalcon!
One touch of Scardon's breath
will turn a warrior old.
One flap of Scardon's wings
will crumble an iron fortress like sand.
No one utters such tall tales anymore.
He isn't a tall tale!
It's a historical fact that Scardon alone
has brought ruin to our world three times.
And each time, the survivors
joined forces and became one
to rebuild the world anew.
However...
Indeed. I sense an ominous power
from the new Scardon,
much stronger than ever before.
So if the Dragon Overlord Scardon
has been brought back...
then the world will fall entirely this time.
I'm heading off now, Vinsant!
Sis, when will you be back?
Hmm... There's still a lot of baddies out there.
I can't tell for sure!
Why do you have to fight against bad guys?
Just because you're a Dragon Knight?
Not at all. I do it to protect the people I love.
Like who?
Like you, Vinsant.
And all the people in the world.
I want to protect this peaceful world
and everyone who lives in it.
I... I want to be just like you!
I must protect this world...
and everyone in it!
I'll do what my sister couldn't.
I'm getting a reading southwest.
Scardon's back, isn't he?
You've improved, Pepperon.
All thanks to you guys
for helping me train!
And now I'm back in the royal army!
Pepperon.
Hey, Vinsant!
It appears the Overlord Scardon is back.
We must leave to save the world.
What are you blabbering about?
Oh, Scardon!
You mean the legendary monster
that destroyed the world long ago?
Are you try'na play pretend hero?
Pepperon, come with me.
I decided that I would join the royal army
so that I could protect French Toaster's future.
I only take orders from his majesty the king!
You're right. I'm in no position
to take you away from your life.
But I'll wait for you.
Once you're up to defeat Scardon,
meet me at Yamajeni-Inn.
GOB'S CLUB
and Sexy Funtimes F
Welcome!
Is this your first time?
Yes, it is.
So pure!
Aren't you just adorable?
I have a question.
Well, my bust size is...
He hasn't even said his question yet!
Is your manager, Gob-san here?
I knew this was your club!
Vinsant! Why are you so popular with them?
Huh?
Scram! Get out of my establishment at once!
How rude, Boss!
You're just jealous he gets all the ladies!
You're just jealous he's handsome!
What a loser!
Now you're just being mean!
Gob-san!
Swooon!
I'm here to win you over!
It appears the Overlord Scardon is back.
We must leave to save the world.
Do you think I care?!
Get out of my sight already!
I'm begging you, just go!
Okay, okay, I'll go!
But I'll wait for you.
Once you're up to defeat Scardon,
meet me at Yamajeni-Inn.
Huh? Does Mom have a guest over?
Whaaat?!
Vinsant? Why are you here?
Welcome home, Mayone!
Sorry this is sudden.
I heard everything!
You two were out traveling together?
You must have done a lot of fun things!
Right, Vinsant?
When did you get so close to her?
He's one amazing guy!
I think he's a winner.
If I had a son like him,
I'd be set for the rest of my life!
Yay, I've always wanted a big brother!
Say what?
I was just asking him to take good care of you.
Forever, ever-after!
What did I miss?!
I'm not sure what she's talking about,
but allow me to speak.
It appears the Overlord Scardon is back.
We must leave to save the world.
Really?
Oh, is this "Scardon"
the Cupid who brought you two together?
What? No!
Was he sick?
And now he's "back" and better than ever?
That's good to hear.
Use your ears, Mom!
You should really go visit him, Mayone.
Yes. We must be quick.
You're rolling with her confusion!
Anyways, Scardon's resurrection
is none of my business!
We're through, okay?
We're all living our own lives.
Go find your own desire to fulfill!
The only desire I have
is to save the world!
Then do it yourself!
Mayone, I'll wait for you at Yamajeni-Inn.
Only one person left.
I know I can get through to him...
Let's hear some words from Captain Chup,
representative of Melora's bodyguard knights!
Listen to him with all of your soul!
Yes, Melora!
We were all born in the beauty
of Princess Melora.
We met one another through her charm.
And together, we're bound by her gorgeousness.
Once again, we shall work together
to ensure the princess' happiness and safety!
Yes, Melora!
Scopeion, where is Princess Melora now?
Uno momento!
I'm on it, aye!
I found her!
She's south-southwest from here!
Walkin' down the hallway, oh yeah!
Okay!
Are you ready?
Yes, Melora!
Face south-southwest...
and send her your love!
Love!
Keep going! Pray for her happiness!
Chup.
Oh, Vinsant!
It appears the Overlord Scardon is back.
We must leave to save the world.
Huh? How?
Love!
Scardon wasn't there
at Vinegar Palace!
Plus the Dragon Heart was a bogus.
Love!
I got a faint reading on my Dragon GPS.
Aw, but I'm busy representing
the Melora bodyguard knights!
Someone's gotta look after these guys.
Love!
You're such a worrywart.
Everything will be fine.
Does the fate of the world
not matter to you?!
We have to go, now.
Love!
Come on!
I'm getting tired of hearing this!
I'm not going! No matter what anyone says!
Chup...
Love!
Scardon!
Huh?
Why'd you punch me?!
That's Scardon?
Yes. He really is back...
This is bad.
The clock is ticking to the end of the world!
Eek!
Love?
Was that Melora shrieking?
Did Scardon get her?!
Princess Melora! Are you alright?
Not at all!
What happened?
My favorite pair of panties
went missing after I hung it up to dry!
Huh?
A p-p-p-panty thief?!
Whoo!!
Who would dare steal your panties?!
I wish I knew.
I do! I got it all on video, wow!
Really? Can you show us?
Uno momento!
I just brought these camera-equipped binoculars,
so I can show it all, sí!
So Scardon's the one who took your panties!
Eeyup!
Oh, my...
Why were you recording
just then anyways, Scopeion?
Stroke of luck, y'know?
I was taking a video of the beautiful sky,
and just happened to get her panties in frame, yeah!
This is ridiculous.
Chup, go get my panties back!
At once, Princess Melora!
Huh?
I won't let Scardon have his way!
I can't believe he'd steal
Melora's p-p-p-panties!
That's it?
What are you slacking off for, Vinsant?
Let's move!
Move where?
To Scardon, duh?
Yeah, but what happened
to "I'm not going!"?
"No matter what anyone says"?
It's like my grandmother said!
I see London, I see France!
I see London,
I see France,
I see the princess's
underpants.
I see London,
I see France,
I see the princess's
underpants.
I see the princess's underpants!
-Tome
I'm gonna fully, flawlessly
retrieve Melora's panties!
Thank you, Chup!
QUEST: TAKE BACK THE PRINCESS'S PANTIES
Panties matter more than world destruction?
I'm glad they had your favorite shampoo, Candle!
It always runs out
when you use it without thinking!
Think about that, you hairy geek!
Why'd you drop it?
Panpan?
Huh?!
Panties matter more to you
than the fate of the world?
Mayone, Pepperon!
We saw it.
It really is back, huh?
That's real bad.
I decided I had to do something.
Have you finally recognized
the gravity of the situation?
I never would've guessed those were
our company's panties.
You can't go without panties!
Panties?!
Those panties of Melora's
that Scardon had,
they're a new product
from my mom's company.
Oh, wow!
They just found out they were defective,
so Mom told me to collect them
before it gets out there...
and I got an order straight from the king
to recover those panties!
Hold on!
So all of you are taking on Scardon
over some panties?
Yeah, why?
Oh, where's Gob-san?
He's probably busy
with that new business.
He's in the middle of chasing his own dreams.
We probably won't cross paths with him again.
I see. I guess he was just some old dude
who followed us around, anyway.
I'll cheer him on!
Me too.
Let's go in and start planning!
Vinsant?
Why are you spacing out?
Clock's ticking!
G-Got it...
nee kimi doko kara kita no?
Where are you from?
ima boku hima shiten dakedo
I've got time to spare
ochashite morae masenka?
Can I pour you some tea?
dame? dame? doushite desuka
No, you say? What's wrong?
jinsei wa rooringu sutoon
Life is like a rolling stone
tamaru konbini bukuro
Shopping bags piling up
seishun wa kumori zora
Youth is like a dark cloudy sky
sumafo izonshou sa
They're all glued to their phones
donzoko demo iijan
So what if we've hit rock bottom
ki ni shinakute iijan
Don't get so hung up on it
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
tabetara kateru kamojan
Maybe it'll help us get this katsu-done
dame dame demo iijan
But if it won't? Oh well
doutte koto neejan
Don't worry 'bout it
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
megezu ni ikouze
And keep moving forward
charanporan de iijan
Maybe we're kinda sloppy
muchakucha de iijan
And sure we're kinda reckless
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
tabetara kateru kamojan
Maybe it'll help us get this katsu-done
masshigura de iijan
So let's go full speed
tsuki susumeba iijan
And keep pushing onwards
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
tokoton yarouze
And see our goals all the way through
nee kimi doko kara kita no?
Where are you from?
ima boku hima shiten dakedo
I've got time to spare
Why don't we eat KATSUDON?
Hey!
Gob-san!
Why are you guys slacking off?
We have to be quick,
or things'll get real bad!
Gob-san, you're not here
about the panties, are you?
Panties? No, why?
It's not about panties! Okay!
Phew...
Goblin...
Huh?!
Where are you, Goblin?!
Pay your debts, Goblin!
Goblin!
You got a loan from that Golem, didn't you?
My business was a failure.
So you only wanted us to hurry up
so you could get away.
Over a loan!
Whatever. We're all together now!
So where's Scardon, Vinsant?
My GPS is saying southwest.
Then let's ask him a favor!
Darefalcon!
Wh-What in the world?!
Nooo!!
Darefalcon!
Where's Scardon right now?
Scardon?
We're going to go defeat him.
Fully, flawlessly!
I see. One moment.
He appears to have made
Demi-Glace Castle his territory.
Demi-Glace Castle?
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone!
What are you teaching us about today?
Today's lesson is on
M&C Technologies.
M&C Technologies
M&C Technologies is my mom's company!
It's a successful company that specializes
in online business and apparel!
My brother Cornet acts as
her right-hand man!
My outfit was also made
by M&C Technologies!
I had no idea!
Hehe! Here's to the future
of M&C Technologies.
Next Time
If we wanna defeat the Dragon Overlord Scardon,
we need a world-class airship!
And only one person can help us with that.
Who could he be?
The Search for Goemon, the Legendary Blacksmith
Next time: "The Search for Goemon,
the Legendary Blacksmith!"
Alright, time for a big adventure!