This is Snack World, the hallowed ground
of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam
and people have handy smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
And my name's Chup!
After a long battle,
I've finally defeated the evil merchant Vinegar Khan,
and now I'm moving towards a new goal!
Whatever perils await me,
I'll fully, flawlessly overcome them!
Alright, let's go on another big adventure today!
Episode 42: Paccarat Lapa's Foal-icious Mission!!
We got Detton and Peffany on board!
The Great Airship is making good progress!
If that's the case,
how about we do some sightseeing?
I like that idea!
I've been hankering for some seafood!
I wanna go shopping!
And I wanna buy some
local melonpan cookies!
"Local" melonpan cookies?
There's an exclusive flavor
they only sell here!
Since this is a port town,
they're supposed to be salty flavored!
You're already way off track.
How about we split up for two hours
then meet back up here?
Hate to break it to you,
but we can't take things easy.
Huh?
Several days have passed
since Scardon returned.
The world has already begun
to see the effects.
What kind of effects?
Monsters have been acting
more aggressive than before.
Victims of monster attacks
have nearly doubled.
That's right!
Did you recall something bad?
The ladies at the club I visited last night
were acting so coldhearted to me!
No wonder. Scardon must be behind it!
Give me some space!
No way.
Those were human ladies!
Maybe humans are affected by him too!
The other day, I stopped by
an all-you-can-eat buffet,
and the waiters got more and more aggressive
every time I asked for more.
You're still not finished?
Yeah, 'cause you were asking for
an unusual amount of food!
That reminds me.
Princess Melora was in my dream last night,
and her sexy poses were even more
aggressive than usual!
Chup~!
Roar!
What a creepy dream!
My point is, we don't have much time!
Goemon, what's the next brand?
The third one here in Durian:
Paccarat Lapa.
Oh, Paccarat Lapa!
That's the brand Mr. Fishburger
gave me at his mansion!
The owner used to own horses,
so he designed his works
with the feeling of an elegant horse.
They're quite fashionable
and popular!
We're looking at their gimmick technologies.
It'll be crucial for our steering mechanisms.
And the man behind that tech
is the owner and engineer himself,
Mr. Marshew Mallow.
I actually met him a few times
when I was little.
You have?
Yep. He was drinking buddies
with Goemon IV.
Oh, your grandfather!
What's Mr. Marshew Mallow like?
He's just a sweet, horse-loving old man.
Though I don't like him too much.
How come?
Paccarat Lapa HQ
Ho-Horse-Horse!
Welcome to Paccarat Lapa!
Marshew
Mallow
I'm Marshew Mallow, the owner!
You weren't kidding about
him loving horses. He even laughs it!
Good to see you again, Mr. Mallow.
Oh, I remember you.
You're Goemon's granddaughter, no?
Yes. I am his successor,
Goemon V.
Wow! How long has it been, ten years?
What a memory!
Such a good little girl.
I'm glad you remember me.
I wouldn't forget a face!
A human's nor a horse's!
That's my motto.
As the owner of a weapons brand,
it is of course upon me
to refine the weapons we manufacutre,
but I also must refine my connections
with the humans and horses I meet.
Such is how I've raised
the brand of Paccarat Lapa.
It all started around 120 years ago,
back when the first owner
was still in high school!
There he goes...
What do you mean?
When he starts telling old stories,
he never stops.
That's why I don't like him.
That adds up.
Back then, he was helping feed
the cows at the stable.
He feels the need to go over the whole history
of the brand with every new person he meets.
Brace yourselves,
this will take a while.
Aww.
Oh, Mr. Mallow!
Before you tell us about the history...
Horse?
We'd like to ask you something!
No!
I'm talking here!!
That first owner fell in love
with those majestic horses.
What the heck?
He hates nothing more
than people interrupting his stories.
Then, he made up his mind!
He looks like such a vile,
disgusting creature.
...was his goal!
That's how Paccarat Lapa began.
Oh, is that all?
Now for Chapter 2:
The Rival!
There's two chapters...?
Eight in total, and by the way...
Wake up. I'm talking here.
S-Sorry, sir.
He won't let you doze off either.
And so, through the efforts
of three generations of owners,
Paccarat Lapa finally put itself on the map,
having become one of the top brands.
It's finally over.
That took forever.
We had to stand here
for two and a half hours...
So what business do you have with me?
Mr. Mallow.
We must construct
the Great Airship.
Will you lend us your company's technology?
I cannot.
Aw, what? After you made us
listen to you for ages?
I hate to say it, but I have something I must do.
What is it?
I have to obtain Mangolas Si.
Mangolas Si?
A legendary horse
that lives in the woods to the east.
All horse owners wish they could have
his coat, his muscles, and his overwhelming speed.
So until I obtain him,
I'm afraid I can't take on anything else.
Hey, we'll capture that
Mambo Bungee for you!
It's "Mangolas Si."
And when we're done,
will you help us with the airship?
I'd be delighted to,
but I'm afraid Mangolas Si
will be no easy catch.
Don't try to stop us!
It's like my grandmother said!
Don't look a gift horse in the mouth!
Don't look a gift horse
in the mouth.
My joints get sore
in the cold.
Don't look a gift horse
in the mouth.
My joints get sore
in the cold.
My joints get sore in the cold!
-Tome
Her elderly pains are showing.
Bring us to the woods!
This is where Mangolas Si dwells.
I see.
Would you like these?
Huh?
Use them. There might be
monsters nearby.
Are you sure?
I'll do anything to make sure
I get my hands on Mangolas Si!
Yay, thanks!
I've always wanted to try out
some Paccarat Lapa weapons!
Is it really gonna be that hard
to capture it?
There must be over 100 failed attempts
to capture Mangolas Si.
Allow me to tell the history of this battle
from the beginning before we go on the hunt.
Huh?!
From the beginning?
I first fell in love with horses myself
sixty years ago!
You're going that far back?
It was when my father brought me
to a race track!
He was so caught up
in watching his horses...
Look!
What a beautiful horse!
Could it be?
Mangolas Si?
Mr. Mallow, turn around!
Look behind you!
Horse?!
I'm talking here!
The beautiful sight of those galloping horses
made me deaf to the sounds around me.
It's running away!
What's the plan, Chup?
We can't pass up this opportunity!
Let's catch it!
Get back here!
So fast!
Horse!!
I'm talking here!!
This is hopeless.
This is awful. We couldn't even
capture Mangolas Si.
Next time we go,
we'll separate from Mr. Mallow.
Since he talks too much
and gets mad if we interrupt.
Mangolas Si is sensitive to noise
and quick on its feet.
It'll be a lot more tricky than I thought.
How about we have Butako
chase it as a dragon?
You won't have much space
to fly around.
We'll just have to place a trap.
What kind?
We'll lay out its favorite food,
then catch it with a net
when it takes the bait.
What could its favorite food be?
Should we ask Mr. Mallow??
Don't! That's just asking for
hours of storytelling!
Oh! Guys, check this out.
I found a blog studying
everything about Mangolas Si.
Now that's a good find!
It even has info on Mangolas Si's favorite food!
It does?
"I've planted many a food
in the attempt to lure in Mangolas Si,
"but it has paid little heed."
"The only thing it would eat is a dish
from a three-star Durian restaurant:
"shrimp mousse with caviar."
Huh? Why would you give a horse
such a classy dish?
"However, it never showed any interest in it
the next few times I planted that dish."
"Perhaps there is no effective bait
for luring in Mangolas Si after all."
Oh, come on! Are you kidding me?
Got it!
A legendary horse
needs a legendary dish!
I'll summon Warpman!
A legendary dish, eh?
Yeah. Couldn't find anything online.
Got anything for me?
Did you come all the way back from Durian
just to ask us that?
It wasn't a big trip.
We have Warpman!
Warpman?
I told you to stop calling me that.
At least call me Lord Warpman!
"Lord Warpman" doesn't sound as fun.
Oh! How about Warp Geezer?
Show some respect!
You've been treating me awfully lately.
Yeah!
Darefalcon's way, way older than us, you know!
Call him Warp Grandpa!
How about just "Warp-pa?"
Now you're just insulting me!
I'll look up legendary dishes
on myself.
With my searching capabilities,
it shouldn't take too long to...
I got a hit.
There's only one dish
that can be called legendary.
And that legendary dish is...
the Jiggly Omelette!
The Jiggly Omelette?!
According to the description,
it uses 37% half-cooked eggs.
This simple yet enriching flavor
can leave anybody speechless.
It's truly a legendary dish.
What are the ingredients?
Legendary rock salt picked near
the peak of the Macaro Mountains,
legendary purple martin eggs
nested in the Roast Beef Mines...
I had a feeling the ingredients
would be hard to get.
And finally, cooking oil,
which they sell at Hero Mart.
Of course the oil is just nearby.
It might take us a long time
to procure all of these.
Forget about it!
That's what we have Warp-pa for!
Don't settle on that nickname!
Here's the list!
What do you mean "here's the list?"
Are you not coming?
It's just a quick grocery trip.
You can handle it alone.
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Roast Beef Mines
Macaron Mountains
Hero Mart
Here's the money.
If you do a good job,
I'll let you keep some.
Really?
They're still taking advantage of him.
I've procured everything.
That was fast!
It wasn't without its toils!
I've only been around three quarters
of the way up Macaro Mountain.
In order to get the rock salt
from the top,
I had to trek the rest on foot.
Purple martins only nest
on the cliffs of the Roast Beef Mines,
so I had to risk my life
climbing to the top.
And the cooking oil at Hero Mart
was on the verge of selling out,
and someone else almost beat me
to the last one...
but I managed to get ahold of it.
That was easy!
Listen to me when I'm speaking!
Now we can make
that Jiggly Omelette!
Chup, did you read
the instructions on this?
It only gets more complicated.
Huh?
"How to Make the Jiggly Omelette: Leg 1."
"Head to a cliff with
the purple martin egg in hand."
Why a cliff?
"Tie a long piece of rubber around your foot."
"Then jump."
"Then, once you've nearly bungee jumped
down to the bottom,
"hit the egg on the ground."
His face hit the ground first!
"Then use that crack
to pour the egg into the bowl."
It hurts...
I think he might have cracked his skull too.
What was even the point
of jumping down like that?
"This makes the dish
feel even more legendary."
That's just ridiculous.
"Leg 2."
"Once you've made a good crack
and poured the egg into the bowl,"
"add the rock salt."
How much?
"However much you want."
Oh, so now they're letting us call the shots?
"Then do 100 squats in place."
Like the leg exercise?
How does that help us cook?
I don't know, but that's what it says.
It's for the dish!
1, 2, 3, 4...
98, 99, 100...
I'm beat.
"This should wear out your leg muscles
and make them start jiggling."
"Batter the eggs in the bowl
to that vibration."
I can't mix it at all like this!
"Repeat the squats as many times
as you have to
"until the yolk and white are completely mixed."
This will make the omelette
even more jiggly.
For the legend!
I did it!
My muscles are giving out...
I'll take over.
What's next?
"Leg 3: Once the yolk
and white have been mixed,
"pour cooking oil in a frying pan."
"Then pour the mixed egg in..."
We're finally getting to the cooking!
"...then scrape the pan
against the nearest rock."
Huh?
Scrape it? Like this?
"The heat generated from the friction
will cook the eggs."
What?
Is that even possible?
"This will make it profoundly legendary
and jiggly."
This recipe is fishy!
The friction! That makes sense.
Here I go!
M-My arm's giving out!
Well, certainly looks hot.
Good job!
We've finished the legendary dish,
the Jiggly Omelette!
It doesn't look all that good...
Wanna taste test, Gob-san?
Why do I have to?
You look like you could take any food.
What's that supposed to...
Ah, forget it.
It's great! This is fantastic!
Wow, really?
I gotta try.
He's right! This jiggly-ness is perfect!
Really? I want some!
Me too!
Mmm, this is so good!
Much better than you'd expect!
Nothing wrong with taste-testing,
but make sure to save some
for Mangolas Si.
No way!!
We got ahead of ourselves.
Do we have to make it over?
Warp-pa!
We're still good on cooking oil,
so we just need the rock salt
and the purple martin egg.
Here, a special tip for you.
Our trap is perfect!
Once Mangolas Si
goes in for the omelette,
we'll drop a net down from above
to keep it from moving!
Nice one, Gob-san.
Very underhanded.
I have my doubts it'd be drawn
to such a bad-looking omelette, though.
Don't worry! Believe in the legend!
Listen!
Everyone stay quiet! Hide!
It's close. Almost there...
Huh?! Dullahan?
What?!
Man, he ruined our trap!
Is he still after me?!
Actually, it seems like he had his eyes
on that Jiggly Omelette.
How's he supposed to eat
without a face?
Let's get it back!
I'm not making this omelette
over again!
Vinsant!
Right!
Over here, Dullahan!
You've been a real thorn in our sides!
You're going down here and now!
Paccarat Titan Sword!
Paccarat Titan Shield!
Pa-Pa-Palapa, Paccarat Lapa!
Paccarat Titan Sword.
B-Type.
Paccarat Titan Shield.
My legs won't work
because of all those squats!
Huh?!
You're not alone.
My arms don't work
from scraping that frying pan...
What?! Now we're in a crisis
all because of that Jiggly Omelette!
I got the omelette!
Let's retreat for now!
Shoot! Pass!
I got it! Yeah!
D-Don't come near me!
P-Pass!
Aah, no! Too scary! Pass!
Whaaat?! I gotta pass it!
Anyone?
No!!
Come on!
Help me, Chup!
I told you, I can't move my legs!
Chup, look!
Where? Aah!
It's Mangolas Si!
Yeah! It must've followed the scent
of the legendary dish!
Forget that, save me!!
I know! Pepperon, throw me at Mangolas Si!
What do you mean by that?
Doesn't matter, just do it!
You got it!
Now I can fight!
Look at you go, Chup!
Riding a legendary horse!
Does that matter?!
It's over!
Dullahan! Come and face me!
Let's go!
"I'm a Knight on a Steed,
and I'm Gonna Make You Plead" Slash!
Huh?!
Where are you going?!
Mangolas Si's running for it!
Hey, listen to me!
He wasn't taming it at all!
I know!
Chup! Summon Darefalcon
with your Fairypon!
What?!
We'll warp with Mangolas Si
to Mr. Mallow!
That'll mean we've captured it!
Got it!
Darefalcon!
Wh-What is the matter?
Dragon Warp us!
Make it quick!
Take all of us to Mr. Mallow's office!
What am I to you people?
Dragon Warp!
Wh-What in the world?!
Mr. Mallow,
we've captured Mangolas Si!
Horse! That really is Mangolas Si!
So will you help us build
the Great Airship?
Absolutely!
Hooray!
How wonderful.
Not only have you brought me Mangolas Si,
but a second horse as well!
A second one?
Wait, what?
nee kimi doko kara kita no?
Where are you from?
ima boku hima shiten dakedo
I've got time to spare
ochashite morae masenka?
Can I pour you some tea?
dame? dame? doushite desuka
No, you say? What's wrong?
jinsei wa rooringu sutoon
Life is like a rolling stone
tamaru konbini bukuro
Shopping bags piling up
seishun wa kumori zora
Youth is like a dark cloudy sky
sumafo izonshou sa
They're all glued to their phones
donzoko demo iijan
So what if we've hit rock bottom
ki ni shinakute iijan
Don't get so hung up on it
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
tabetara kateru kamojan
Maybe it'll help us get this katsu-done
dame dame demo iijan
But if it won't? Oh well
doutte koto neejan
Don't worry 'bout it
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
megezu ni ikouze
And keep moving forward
charanporan de iijan
Maybe we're kinda sloppy
muchakucha de iijan
And sure we're kinda reckless
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
tabetara kateru kamojan
Maybe it'll help us get this katsu-done
masshigura de iijan
So let's go full speed
tsuki susumeba iijan
And keep pushing onwards
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
tokoton yarouze
And see our goals all the way through
nee kimi doko kara kita no?
Where are you from?
ima boku hima shiten dakedo
I've got time to spare
Why don't we eat KATSUDON?
Why is Dullahan here?!
You told me to bring all of you here.
You're so useless, Warp-pa!
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone!
What are you teaching us about today?
Today's lesson is on Dragon Warp.
Dragon Warp
Dragon Warp is a power used by
Darefalcon... I mean, Warp-pa.
It can take us from place to place
in an instant! It's real handy!
If it's called "Dragon Warp,"
what's Dragon-y about it?
Huh? I don't know,
I guess just 'cuz he's a Holy Dragon?
We've only seen him as a dragon
once, though...
Next Time
We head to Fairy Electronics,
hidden deep in the woods!
What awaits us when we step in?
Hot dang! I've never seen
this weapon before!
I want it so bad!
Next time:
"A New Item from Fairy Electronics!"
A New Item from Fairy Electronics
Alright, time for a big adventure!