This is Snack World, the hallowed ground
of dreams and adventures.
A world where dragons roam
and people have handy smartphones!
It's a pretty cool place, ain't it?
And my name's Chup!
After a long battle,
I've finally defeated the evil merchant Vinegar Khan,
and now I'm moving towards a new goal!
Whatever perils await me,
I'll fully, flawlessly overcome them!
Alright, let's go on another big adventure today!
Hmm...
In order to perfect this airship,
Episode 41: Peffany, the Beautiful Lady
we'll need finely-made instruments
that can measure to a nano-level.
So our next stop will be Peffany
to borrow their embossing tech.
Awesome! Let's go hitch a ride
to their headquarters!
Also, what's embossing?
It's a way of crafting
very precise devices and molds.
They started out as an accessory manufacturer
known for their high-quality embossing.
They're the best!
As much as I love their equipment,
they'll always be an accessory brand to me!
I hope they give us product samples
when we show up at their HQ!
We better go!
They look excited.
Peffany is a girl's biggest weakness.
I'm constantly giving their stuff
to ladies at the bar.
Why do you think I'm broke?
Peffany has a reputation for being the brand
that a gentleman gifts to his lady.
If only someone would buy me
their latest products!
Mayone, don't you already have
enough Peffany goods?
There's no such thing as "enough" Peffany!
Sarria Staff!
Shining forever, Peffany.
Sarria Staff.
Peffany's Sarria Staff
is just the cutest thing ever!
So well-crafted!
Fireball!
Ow-ow-ow! And its firepower is excellent!
Let me try it!
N-No way, José!
Come on, you cheapskate!
Stop it, that scorches!
The age of gentlemen buying
our products for their ladies is no more.
Karen
Peffany
Peffany is refocusing its brand
on hyper-ladies
who buy our products
for their own benefit!
Are we clear?
Objection!
Ladies aren't "hyper"
or bullcrap like that.
Raidou
Yonekawa
Don't you recognize why
Peffany combines beauty and strength?
Yonekawa, do you think that
you can lecture me, the president?
Peffany is a brand of love,
offered by men to women they wish to protect.
That has remained,
and should continue to remain.
It's the spirit of Peffany itself!
Yonekawa...
You know that you're my favorite designer here.
But if you don't wish to follow my plan,
you have no place in my company!
You know the rest of your designers
are going to follow me out the door.
Peffany HQ
This is the place!
Between this and Detton,
there sure are a lot of big brands around here.
Really brings me back.
Gob-san, did you use to live here?
Believe it or not, I used to shake hands
here in the business district back in the day!
During the Yuppie era.
You never told us
you were a businessman!
So cool!
Used to be a prince, used to do business,
used to have hair...
His stories just don't add up.
I'm telling the truth.
I used to work at a big company!
Whoa!
That's awesome!
...Right behind its building!
I was fighting crows and stray cats
for scraps of food!
You call that
being a businessman?
Oh! I smell more tasty scraps!
Smells like pork chops!
Good afternoon!
H-Huh? What's going on here?
Are we interrupting?
You got any good designers?
There is me.
Wanna help us build a great airship
to break through the magic barrier?
And who are you?
I have the blueprint laid out.
This is amazing.
It's fascinating to my
inner designer.
Unfortunately, this ain't
a really good time.
Yeah, I had a feeling about that.
Huh? Are you having an argument?
We're not arguing.
We just have conflicting pla—
I understand.
A feud between management
and workers
is not in Peffany's best interest.
Finally figured it out, eh?
Both of us will develop and present
our own individual Peffany products,
and through that, we'll determine
who gets to direct the brand going forward.
Present them? You're giving them away?
Not that kind of "present."
A "presentation" is used by companies
to discuss their new projects and plans.
Sounds fun. I'm in.
Let us begin.
I'll recruit those two.
Me?
And Yonekawa, you can have the inadequate boy
and the scary-looking girl.
Inadequate? You flatter me.
That's not a compliment.
Wait a minute!
Does this mean I get to touch
new products with my own hands?
I'm so lucky!
Mayone's on cloud nine!
Peffany's power is incredible.
Not sure I follow,
but if we help you out,
you'll build the ship with us, right?
Mm-hm. Once this is all wrapped up,
I'll take it on.
Hey, what do Pepperon and I do?
I'm not sure the burly dimwit
will serve me any use.
B-Burly dimwit?!
I'll take him, then.
Wh-What about me?
That warped, triangular form of yours.
It brings manure to mind.
It's quite avant-garde!
Huh?!
What's with the Gob-san recognition?
The aesthetics of a top brand's president
are not for the likes of us to understand.
I don't really get it,
but she's taken a liking to me.
Wow! So this is where
the designers do their work!
Mr. Yonekawa, did you design
Peffany's accessories?
I did.
That's so cool!
Did you give them to girls too?
You've been raking them in!
P-Perhaps.
You're one lucky beast, you know that?
So what were you arguing
with the president about?
I'm sure you know we got our starts
as an accessory manufacturer.
It was founded by Karen's father,
the chairman of the company.
He lost his wife Sarria
after she was attacked by a monster.
What?!
It was that incident that turned
Peffany towards crafting weapons.
I had no idea.
Oh, but that explains the Sarria line,
it was named after his wife, right?
His daughter and the current president, Karen,
is ignoring her father's wishes,
abandoning Peffany's traditions
in order to mold it into her image.
And you're opposed to it, I take it.
What will you do if
your presentation loses?
I'll follow her orders,
and we'll go on to make
unglamorous products.
What?!
So I'm going to lose the Peffany
I know and love?
Unfortunately, yes.
No way! Under my dead body!
Chup, our presentation's gotta win!
Yeah!
By the way, what's the thing you made?
Come on, show us!
Here it is.
Whoa!
Aww, it's so cute!
Can I hold it?
It's so beautiful!
Whoa!
Just look at this masterpiece.
There's no way it can lose!
Don't let your guard down.
Why not?
Karen is a talented designer as well.
Finely embossed in every last detail...
It's perfect. Beautiful work, Peffany.
It's the Karen Axe—a hatchet for ladies.
Quite the novel concept, no?
Ladies no longer exist
purely for men to protect.
An era approaches of
engaging and fashionable women...
the era of hyper-ladies!
This item will show everyone
what the new Peffany is about.
What is our job, then?
I sensed something
the moment I saw you two.
You will make perfect models!
Huh?
You shall model
for my presnetation!
Huh?!
I get to model for Peffany?
I'd love to!
Then I'd best train you
on your runway walk.
I used to be a supermodel,
so no one better to instruct you!
My guess is...
aghjaerth
A Master Designer and a Supermodel!
The Rise of Karen
aghjaerth
A Master Designer and a Supermodel!
The Rise of Karen
aghjaerth
A Master Designer and a Supermodel!
The Rise of Karen
aghjaerth
A Master Designer and a Supermodel!
The Rise of Karen
aghjaerth
A Master Designer and a Supermodel!
The Rise of Karen
aghjaerth
A Master Designer and a Supermodel!
The Rise of Karen
aghjaerth
A Master Designer and a Supermodel!
The Rise of Karen
aghjaerth
A Master Designer and a Supermodel!
The Rise of Karen
aghjaerth
A Master Designer and a Supermodel!
The Rise of Karen
aghjaerth
A Master Designer and a Supermodel!
The Rise of Karen
aghjaerth
A Master Designer and a Supermodel!
The Rise of Karen
aghjaerth
A Master Designer and a Supermodel!
The Rise of Karen
aghjaerth
A Master Designer and a Supermodel!
The Rise of Karen
aghjaerth
A Master Designer and a Supermodel!
The Rise of Karen
Karen will host a fashion show
with those two as her models.
They've got two beautiful stars, and we...
We what?
F-Forget I said anything.
I'm not all that good at presentations.
I'm stumped...
Peffany is a girl's brand,
so I clearly should be the star.
I know! What about a commercial
starring and directed by me?
Maybe it could even go on TV
if it works well!
I could be in a commercial
for Peffany!
It's like a dream come true!
She's acting like we've already won.
It's all coming together!
Time to give you the story
and the casting!
I'm the beautiful swordswoman
wielding the strongest sword!
Beautiful?
Don't stop me on that!
Pepperon, you'll play the clumsy hero
who forgot his sword!
Lucky, you get to be a hero!
A clumsy one, anyway...
What's my role?
You'll be the weakling monster
who attacks the clumsy hero!
Aww, a monster?
And why am I weak?
You can't just hog the good role to yourself!
What he said!
No complaints,
you just have to make me look good!
Ugh, fine.
Ready to learn the plot?
The weak monster attacks
the clumsy swordless hero.
That's when I come in out of the blue
to save the day!
Then I wield my sword
and say a cool one-liner...
"The Sarria Sword shines for eternity!"
It's everything!
Sound good, guys?
Yeah!
I-I'll do my best!
Let's get straight to work!
Mr. Yonekawa,
you can be the cameraman!
On it!
All set!
Let's begin!
Ready, start!
You evil monster,
face the wrath of my...
Oh no, my sword!
Perfect! Just as always!
Here comes the weak monster!
Chuppy-Chuppy-Chup-Chup...
Cut!
What's with the "Chuppy-Chup-Chup" stuff?
I wanted the monster to have a creepy laugh
that felt like me!
Hmm, not what I was picturing...
I know! Chup, how about you try dying!
You want me to die?!
The clumsy hero defeats and kills
the weak monster.
He approaches with his guard down,
then gets suddenly attacked!
Chuppy-Chuppy-Chup!
The hero decides to attack,
but he has no sword!
Then the beautiful swordswoman shows up!
Got it? Ready, action!
I'm playing dead.
Looks like I've defeated him!
Aah, he's still moving!
Cut!
Why are you moving, Chup?
Sorry, my butt was itchy.
You're breaking the immersion.
Oh, Chup!
How about you hold your breath?
Hold my breath?!
You keep moving if you breathe!
So if you hold it,
you'll look more dead!
Like a weak monster!
Really?
I believe in you, Chup!
If this commercial sucks,
our presentation will lose!
I won't let that happen!
Alright! I'll give it a shot!
Ready, start!
Looks like I've defetteh...
Don't mess up your lines! Again!
Looks like I've defeated...
Huh?
Hurry up, Pepperon.
I'm gonna die for real!
Looks like I've defeated him!
Awesome, I did it!
Cut!
I'm glad you made it through the line,
but don't get giddy after!
Sorry.
Huh? Chup's not moving.
Bye!
Chup!!
Chup, Chup!
Dang, I almost died!
It's over for us if you actually die...
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight, nine!
Good! Strike a face!
And turn!
No one is more beautiful than you!
The world belongs to you!
Pour that into your performance!
No one is more beautiful than me!
This is authentic modeling!
One, two, three, and stop!
That wasn't bad for beginners,
but your walk wasn't very innovative.
Innovative?
It's important for the new Peffany
to be bold and innovative.
Do you understand?
How are we supposed to
"innovate" walking?
One moment.
I have an idea.
Hyper-ladies are still fresh and new.
If they were birds, they'd be baby chicks.
Try peeping like chicks!
You first, Vinsant.
Where's the peeps?
P-Peep peep peep peep...
Hang in there, Vinsant!
It's for our airship!
Excellent.
Now spread your wings out to the world!
Fwoosh!
Except you're actually a penguin chick!
Wha—
My, so novel!
Dang it...
That's one way to put it.
You try it now, Goemon.
Go from chick to penguin!
Huh? Uh, okay.
One, two, three!
Very good!
Keep it up!
Now, Vinsant!
Bring the world to my new Peffany!
Hold her up to the skies,
like the goddess Victoria!
Victory is ours!
You lived up to my expectations!
I can't let the others see me like this...
It feels like it's missing a punch.
I think it has plenty already.
Oh! I thought of something.
Hm? You want me to model with them too?
Not quite, but you will
certainly bring eyes to our presentation...
in a way they'll never expect.
I-I'm doomed!
I forgot my sword!
Here's where I enter stage!
The Sarria Sword shines for eternity!
And cut! That was brilliant!
Right, Mr. Yonekawa?
Hmm... It wasn't exciting enough.
Needs some fiery explosion.
Fire?
Would be a bit awkward from me
since I'm holding a sword.
Oh, Butako's got you covered!
What's wrong, Butako?
Her tank is empty!
So she's hungry.
How else do we get fire?
Oh, I got an idea!
Witch!
Born from the dark, that's me-mon
Lookin' stylish and dastardly? Probably a Demon
Hello, it's been a while!
Hey, that's Witch!
She tried to take my spot!
She has the magic
to make fire!
Huh?
That makes sense!
Plus, she and Mayone
might actually make good co-stars!
I'm sorry?!
I think that would make it
a lot more glamorous.
Aww, but my starring role!
Learn to keep your trap shut, Chup!
Mayone, remember,
this is for the win!
Let's make this a good shoot!
Fine, but I'm still the star, got it?
Let's just say you're
the weak monster's mage friend.
The clumsy hero approaches
the monster, thinking it's dead,
when the mage ambushes him with flames!
That's when I come in to save the day!
I part the flames with my sword,
and say my line...
"The Sarria Sword shines for eternity!"
It's perfect! Got it?
I do!
Ready, start!
Alright, I defeated it!
Don't you dare!
Calm down!
The Sarria Sword...
shines for eternity!
That was great!
We nailed it!
You guys don't get to decide that!
I'm the star here!!
Yonekawa and I will now
present our own works,
and determine which of us
is more fit to lead Peffany into the future.
The chairman will be our judge.
Indeed!
I will go first.
Wow, you two look awesome!
We can't afford to lose!
Hm? Come to think of it,
where's Gob-san?
Now, Gob-san!
Show them what you trained for!
Training? For what?
Yo, yo!
It's ya MC Gob-san, yo!
Let's party!
This is the Gob-Rap,
from me, Gob-san, yo!
The "Gob-Rap"?!
Gob-san is rapping?
Whoa, wicked cool!
The element of surprise
from the unexpected...
That is my image of the new Peffany!
Yo, yo!
This is the story of Karen
A talented designer
and a supermodel, yo!
Her presentation will rock the world
In ways that old man
could never dream of
He's throwing mad shade at
Mr. Yonekawa...
The customs that you hold
forever near and dear
We're tossing 'em away,
kick 'em in the rear
Oh wow, nice rhymes.
The Karen Axe is awesome, yo!
As you can see,
the Karen Axe perfectly represents
the strong ladies of this age: the hyper-ladies!
Such is the course of the brand new Peffany!
This isn't looking good for us.
We did what we could.
May as well go out with a bang.
It's like my grandmother said!
It doesn't hurt to try!
Unless you try to play f3!
It doesn't hurt
to try,
unless you try
to play f3.
It doesn't hurt
to try,
unless you try
to play f3.
-Tome
Opening with f3 in chess
can weaken your knight!
Wow, I never knew...
Wait, why does that matter?!
Let's get our presentation
on the road.
We wanted to visualize
the beauty of the Sarria Sword.
Please take a look.
Not you!
Man, you never give up, do you?
Hey, that's cheating!
You can't use real monsters
in your presentation.
We didn't summon him!
Don't come near me!!
Nooo!!
Good save!
Now it's our turn.
Vinsant!
Y-You made him mad!
Dang it!
Why you little—!
Shoot!
Oh no!
Chup!
It's me, the super ultra great Dragon Knight, Chup!
Whoa! Just as things were looking bad,
he awakened!
Still feels the need to
give himself a title.
Anyways, Chup, take this!
Thanks!
Take this! "The Sarria Sword
Shines for Eternity" Slash!
Wait, what? He ran for it!
He must've fled
so you couldn't finish him off.
That means he put up a good fight!
I used up all my power...
Uhh... that concludes
our presentation of the Sarria Sword!
Chairman, sir!
Which one of us is the winner?
Yonekawa!
Yay, we did it!
Chup, we won!
Father, how could you...
nee kimi doko kara kita no?
Where are you from?
ima boku hima shiten dakedo
I've got time to spare
ochashite morae masenka?
Can I pour you some tea?
dame? dame? doushite desuka
No, you say? What's wrong?
jinsei wa rooringu sutoon
Life is like a rolling stone
tamaru konbini bukuro
Shopping bags piling up
seishun wa kumori zora
Youth is like a dark cloudy sky
sumafo izonshou sa
They're all glued to their phones
donzoko demo iijan
So what if we've hit rock bottom
ki ni shinakute iijan
Don't get so hung up on it
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
tabetara kateru kamojan
Maybe it'll help us get this katsu-done
dame dame demo iijan
But if it won't? Oh well
doutte koto neejan
Don't worry 'bout it
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
megezu ni ikouze
And keep moving forward
charanporan de iijan
Maybe we're kinda sloppy
muchakucha de iijan
And sure we're kinda reckless
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
tabetara kateru kamojan
Maybe it'll help us get this katsu-done
masshigura de iijan
So let's go full speed
tsuki susumeba iijan
And keep pushing onwards
katsudon tabe yoojan
C'mon, let's eat some katsudon
tokoton yarouze
And see our goals all the way through
nee kimi doko kara kita no?
Where are you from?
ima boku hima shiten dakedo
I've got time to spare
Why don't we eat KATSUDON?
Alright, Mr. Yonekawa.
Glad to have you on board!
I'll do what I can.
And I got to keep this
for helping out!
The Karen Axe that Ms. Karen showed off
was a pretty fine piece of work too, though.
It's too bad they're not gonna sell it.
Yeah, that's a shame.
Actually, it will be hitting the shelves!
We're just renaming it to the Sarria Axe.
Wow! I gotta hand it to you,
you're one strong-willed businessman.
Oh yeah, Mr. Yonekawa?
Did you patch things up
with Ms. Karen?
Nope, not quite.
Why does she seem to
hate you so much anyways?
I used to get by with her well,
as my wife.
Your what?!
So you're married?!
Used to be. I had an affair,
and we got divorced.
Now hold on! You went to bat for the brand
being a thing gentlemen gift to their ladies,
and you would cheat?!
What the heck, man?
What a dirty man. And here I saw him
as an earnest designer.
Better get to that blueprint!
Don't try to get out of this!
Hey, Yonekawa!!
Mayone's Snack World Course
Hey, Mayone!
What are you teaching us about today?
Today's lesson is on Durian!
Durian
Durian is a port city in the southeast
of the continent filled with businesses.
On the main street, you'll find the HQs
for Detton, Paccarat Lapa,
and my beloved Peffany!
It's so beautiful!
Pepperon says...
they have the best seafood,
hands down.
Don't talk with your mouth full!
Also, leave some for me!
Next Time
Construction continues!
The next brand is Paccarat Lapa!
Its owner loves horses, and gives us a mission...
What could it be?
Next time:
"Paccarat Lapa's Foal-icious Mission!!"
Paccarat Lapa's Foal-icious Mission!!
Alright, it's time for a big adventure!